<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<librarycollection>
  <items>
    <item id="10142" name="Grand Canyon (a)" code="WOM 049 tk008" libraryid="6" albumid="210" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_049_USA/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Bill Connor" comment="Un thème énergique et puissant." styleid="17" lengthseconds="64" time="1:04" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_049_USA/WOM049_trk008_GRAND_CANYON_(A)_Bill_Connor_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="8" tracktotal="" search="Un thème énergique et puissant. BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, FORT, PUISSANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, PATRIOTIQUE, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA,, AMERIQUE DU NORD, ETATS-UNIS, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ENERGIQUE, EPIQUE, ELEMENTS Vor Energie und Kraft sprühend. FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, KLASSISCH &amp; SEMIKLASSISCH, SINFONIEORCHESTER, NORDAMERIKA, USA, HAUPTVERSION, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMA, KRÄFTIG, ENERGIEGELADEN, KRÄFTIG, KRAFTVOLL, BEFLÜGELND, PATRIOTISCH, FILME, EPISCH, FILME, FANTASY ABENTEUER, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LANDSCHAFTEN, PANORAMA, BEFLUGELND, KRAFTIG wom 049 tk008 bill connor grand canyon (a) wom 049 usa west one music world film score orchestral trailer classical and semi classical symphony orchestra north america usa main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) film score orchestral panoramic strong energetic strong powerful uplifting patriotic movies epic movies fantasy adventure nature wildlife energetic and powerful theme. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="17310" name="Girls Can Too (b)" code="WOM 210 tk014" libraryid="6" albumid="373" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_210_Girl_Pop/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Tyler Van Den Berg" comment="Une batterie punchy avec des guitares fuzz et un refrain accrocheur." styleid="5" lengthseconds="147" time="2:27" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_210_Girl_Pop/WOM210_trk014_GIRLS_CAN_TOO_(B)_Tyler_Van_Den_Berg_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="14" tracktotal="" search="Une batterie punchy avec des guitares fuzz et un refrain accrocheur. POP, PRÉ-ADOLESCENT, POP, ALTERNATIF, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, TV, RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), GROUPE DE ROCK, GROUPE DE FILLES, VOCAL, FÉMININ, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 90, PERIODE, PRE-ADOLESCENT, FEMININ, 20E SIECLE, TELE REALITE, ANNEES 90 Knallende Drums, verzerrte Gitarren und ein eingängiger Chorus mit reichlich Girl-Power. POP, TWEEN, POP, ALTERNATIVE, TV, RADIO, KINDER, JUGENDPROGRAMM, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, TV, RADIO, REALITY TV, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MITTLERES TEMPO (ANDANTE), ROCKBAND, GIRLBAND, VOCALS, WEIBLICH, ZEITALTER, MODERNE ZEIT, VOR 20. JHD., 90ER, FROHLICH wom 210 tk014 tyler van den berg girls can too (b) wom 210 girl pop west one music pop pop tween pop alternate tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle tv radio reality tv happy happy happy upbeat tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) rock band girl group vocals female time period modern era 20th century 1990s punchy drums with fuzz guitars and catchy chorus. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="3425" name="Manhattan Style (a)" code="TSH 027 tk001" libraryid="5" albumid="100" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_027_Swing_of_the_City/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Keith Mansfield" comment="Du swing relax et plein d'aisance." styleid="18" lengthseconds="64" time="1:04" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_027_Swing_of_the_City/TSH027_trk001_MANHATTAN_STYLE_(A)_Keith_Mansfield_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="Du swing relax et plein d'aisance. JAZZ, SWING, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 50, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PAISIBLE, DÉTENDU, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, ASCENSEUR, EN ATTENTE, MUSIQUE DE FOND POUR MAGASINS, TV, RADIO, SITCOM, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, NUIT,, AMERIQUE DU NORD, PERIODE, ETATS-UNIS, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETENDU, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 50, JOURNEE Entspannter und lässiger Swing. JAZZ, SWING, NORDAMERIKA, USA, ZEITALTER, MODERNE ZEIT, VOR 20. JHD., 50ER, HAUPTVERSION, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), FRIEDLICH, ENTSPANNT, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, STADT, URBAN, LEBENSRAUM, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, FAHRSTUHL, WARTESCHLEIFE, HINTERGRUNDMUSIK FÜR EINZELHANDEL, TV, RADIO, SITCOM, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, UNTERHALTUNG, DAYTIME - TV, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, UNTERHALTUNG, LATE-NIGHT, AKTIVITATEN, HINTERGRUNDMUSIK FUR EINZELHANDEL tsh 027 tk001 keith mansfield manhattan style (a) tsh 027 swing of the city the scoring house jazz jazz swing north america usa time period modern era 20th century 1950s main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) peaceful relaxed activities settings city urban human environment activities settings elevator on hold retail background music tv radio sitcom tv radio talkshow relaxed easy swing. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" lc="24186"/>
    <item id="13304" name="Broken Bones (a)" code="WOM 119 tk003" libraryid="6" albumid="281" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_119_Psychedelic_Rock/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Geoffrey James Pidcock Holroyde / Jeff Coates / Vezio Bacci" comment="Des riffs de rock revêche et bluesy." styleid="4" lengthseconds="96" time="1:36" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_119_Psychedelic_Rock/WOM119_trk003_BROKEN_BONES_(A)_Geoffrey_James_Pidcock_Holroyde_Jeff_Coates_Vezio_Bacci_West_One_Music_L.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="Des riffs de rock revêche et bluesy. BLUES, BLUES ROCK, ROCK, PSYCHÉDÉLIQUE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, ROAD MOVIE, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), GROUPE DE ROCK, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 70, PERIODE, PSYCHEDELIQUE, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), ANNEES 2000, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 20, ANNEES 70 Kantiger, bluesiger und rifflastiger Rock. BLUES, BLUESROCK, ROCK, PSYCHEDELISCH, HAUPTVERSION, FILME, MENSCHLICHE DRAMEN, FILME, ROAD MOVIE, FILME, URBAN DRAMA, FRÖHLICH, GUT GELAUNT, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MITTELSCHNELL (MODERATO), ROCKBAND, ZEITALTER, MODERNE ZEIT, 2000ER, ZEITALTER, MODERNE ZEIT, VOR 20. JHD., 70ER, FROHLICH wom 119 tk003 geoffrey james pidcock holroyde jeff coates vezio bacci broken bones (a) wom 119 psychedelic rock west one music rock blues blues rock rock psychedelic main movies human drama movies road movie movies urban drama happy feel good tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) rock band time period modern era 2000s time period modern era 20th century 1970s spiky bluesy riffed up rock. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="4299" name="My Way Home" code="TSH 043 tk015" libraryid="5" albumid="113" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_043_An_American_Journey/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Clive Michael Oliver Carroll" comment="Une guitare ragtime chaleureuse et relax." styleid="22" lengthseconds="152" time="2:32" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_043_An_American_Journey/TSH043_trk015_MY_WAY_HOME_Clive_Michael_Oliver_Carroll_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="15" tracktotal="" search="Une guitare ragtime chaleureuse et relax. FOLK CONTEMPORAINE, JAZZ, RAGTIME, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, ROAD MOVIE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, PAISIBLE, DÉTENDU, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN NYLON, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN MÉTAL, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, AMERIQUE DU NORD, ETATS-UNIS, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETENDU, ELEMENTS, CORDES EN METAL Ein warmes und unbeschwertes Theme mit Ragtime-Gitarre. ZEITGENÖSSISCHER FOLK, JAZZ, RAGTIME, HAUPTVERSION, DOKUMENTATION, FILME, ROAD MOVIE, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LÄNDLICH, LANDSCHAFT, IDYLLISCH, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, ESSEN, FREIZEIT, HEIM, GARTEN, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, REISEN, FRIEDLICH, ENTSPANNT, ZÄRTLICH, WARM, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), SAITENINSTRUMENTE, GITARRE - AKUSTIK, NYLONSAITEN, SAITENINSTRUMENTE, GITARRE - AKUSTIK, STAHLSAITEN, NORDAMERIKA, USA, LANDLICH, ZARTLICH, ZEITGENOSSISCH, ZEITGENOSSISCHER FOLK tsh 043 tk015 clive michael oliver carroll my way home tsh 043 an american journey the scoring house country folk contemporary folk jazz ragtime main documentary movies road movie nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden tv radio leisure lifestyle travel peaceful relaxed tender warm tempo warm relaxed ragtime guitar. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" lc="24186"/>
    <item id="17607" name="On Whom You Gaze (b)" code="WOM 216 tk014" libraryid="6" albumid="380" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_216_Catch_the_Sun/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Ian Mccutcheon" comment="Du folk-rock californien superbe et sincère. Avec un banjo, une pedal steel guitare." styleid="4" lengthseconds="168" time="2:48" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_216_Catch_the_Sun/WOM216_trk014_ON_WHOM_YOU_GAZE_(B)_Ian_Mccutcheon_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="14" tracktotal="" search="Du folk-rock californien superbe et sincère. Avec un banjo, une pedal steel guitare. COUNTRY, COUNTRY ROCK, COUNTRY, COUNTRY ROCK, POP, UNDERSCORE, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TENDRE, MIGNON, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CORDES, BANJO, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 60, AMERIQUE DU NORD, PERIODE, ETATS-UNIS, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 60 Grandioser Folk-Rock der Westküste, der von Herzen kommt. Mit Banjo und Pedal-Steel-Gitarre. COUNTRY, COUNTRY ROCK, COUNTRY, COUNTRY ROCK, POP, UNDERSCORE, TV, RADIO, KINDER, JUGENDPROGRAMM, ZÄRTLICH, SÜß, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), SAITENINSTRUMENTE, BANJO, NORDAMERIKA, USA, ZEITALTER, MODERNE ZEIT, VOR 20. JHD., 60ER, SUSZ, ZARTLICH wom 216 tk014 ian mccutcheon on whom you gaze (b) wom 216 catch the sun west one music rock country country rock country country rock pop underscore tv radio children youth tv tender sweet tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) strings banjo north america usa time period modern era 20th century 1960s gorgeous heartfelt west coast folk-rock. featuring banjo and pedal steel. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="4308" name="Endless Roads" code="TSH 043 tk024" libraryid="5" albumid="113" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_043_An_American_Journey/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Clive Michael Oliver Carroll" comment="Un morceau solitaire et atmosphérique pour planter le décor, avec un dobro solo." styleid="22" lengthseconds="154" time="2:34" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_043_An_American_Journey/TSH043_trk024_ENDLESS_ROADS_Clive_Michael_Oliver_Carroll_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="24" tracktotal="" search="Un morceau solitaire et atmosphérique pour planter le décor, avec un dobro solo. BLUES, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ROAD MOVIE, FILMS, WESTERN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, CHAUD, DÉSERT, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CORDES, GUITARE, BOTTLENECK, SLIDE, CORDES, GUITARE, DOBRO, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 30, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 40, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 50, AMERIQUE DU NORD, PERIODE, ETATS-UNIS, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 30, ANNEES 40, ANNEES 50, ELEMENTS, DESERT Atmosphärischer und einsamer Scene-Setter mit Dobro-Gitarre. BLUES, HAUPTVERSION, FILME, ROAD MOVIE, FILME, WESTERN, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, HEIß, WÜSTE, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LÄNDLICH, LANDSCHAFT, IDYLLISCH, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, REISEN, TRAURIG, BEDRÜCKEND, EINSAM, TRAURIG, BEDRÜCKEND, TRAURIG, ZÄRTLICH, NACHDENKLICH, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), SAITENINSTRUMENTE, GITARRE - BOTTLENECK, SLIDE, SAITENINSTRUMENTE, GITARRE - DOBRO, NORDAMERIKA, USA, ZEITALTER, MODERNE ZEIT, VOR 20. JHD., 30ER, ZEITALTER, MODERNE ZEIT, VOR 20. JHD., 40ER, ZEITALTER, MODERNE ZEIT, VOR 20. JHD., 50ER, BEDRUCKEND, LANDLICH, WUSTE, ZARTLICH tsh 043 tk024 clive michael oliver carroll endless roads tsh 043 an american journey the scoring house country folk blues main movies road movie movies western nature wildlife the elements land hot desert nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral tv radio leisure lifestyle travel sad depressing lonely sad depressing sad tender reflective tempo lonely atmospheric scene-setter featuring solo dobro. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" lc="24186"/>
    <item id="4312" name="Appalachian Hoedown" code="TSH 044 tk001" libraryid="5" albumid="114" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_044_My_American_Story/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Francis Richard Shaw" comment="Bal populaire orchestral plein d'entrain." styleid="22" lengthseconds="109" time="1:49" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_044_My_American_Story/TSH_044_trk001_APPALACHIAN_HOEDOWN_Francis_Richard_Shaw_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="Bal populaire orchestral plein d'entrain. BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, WESTERN SPAGHETTI, FILMS, WESTERN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, HEUREUX, VIF, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), ETHNIQUE, VIOLON, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, PÉRIODE, PRÉ-20E SIÈCLE, 19E SIÈCLE, AMERIQUE DU NORD, PERIODE, ETATS-UNIS, PRE-20E SIECLE, 20E SIECLE, 19E SIECLE, ELEMENTS Munterer orchestraler Hoedown. FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, HAUPTVERSION, DOKUMENTATION, BIOGRAFISCH, HISTORISCH, KÜNSTE, FILME, SPAGHETTI WESTERN, FILME, WESTERN, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LÄNDLICH, LANDSCHAFT, IDYLLISCH, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, REISEN, FRÖHLICH, HEITER, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MITTLERES TEMPO (ANDANTE), ETHNISCH, GEIGE, NORDAMERIKA, USA, ZEITALTER, VOR 20 JHD., 18. JAHRHUNDERT, FROHLICH, KUNSTE, LANDLICH tsh 044 tk001 francis richard shaw appalachian hoedown tsh 044 my american story the scoring house country folk film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral main documentary biographical historical the arts movies spaghetti western movies western nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral tv radio leisure lifestyle travel happy bright tempo spirited orchestral hoedown. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" lc="24186"/>
    <item id="17429" name="Nothing to Lose (b)" code="WOM 212 tk013" libraryid="6" albumid="376" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_212_Twisted_Country/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Harvey Lee Summers" comment="Un rythme de country blues décontracté." styleid="22" lengthseconds="160" time="2:40" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_212_Twisted_Country/WOM212_trk013_NOTHING_TO_LOSE_(B)_Harvey_Lee_Summers_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="13" tracktotal="" search="Un rythme de country blues décontracté. FOLK ETHNIQUE TRADITIONNEL, INTERNATIONAL ET ETHNIQUE, DANSE FOLK NATIONALE, COUNTRY, WESTERN, COUNTRY, COUNTRY ROCK, UNDERSCORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, SOLEIL, CHALEUR, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), DUO, VOCAL, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, FOLK TRADITIONNEL, DANSE ETHNIQUE, LINE DANCE, AMERIQUE DU NORD, ETATS-UNIS, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ELEMENTS, METEO, ETE Relaxter Country-Blues. TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, NATIONAL UND ETHNISCH, NATIONALER VOLKSTANZ, COUNTRY, WESTERN, COUNTRY, COUNTRY ROCK, UNDERSCORE, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LÄNDLICH, LANDSCHAFT, IDYLLISCH, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, SONNE, TROPISCH, KÜSTENLANDSCHAFT, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, WETTER, SONNE, HITZE, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, REISEN, BEFLÜGELND, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, TREIBEND, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), GESANGSDUETT, VOCALS, NORDAMERIKA, USA, TRADITIONELLE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, ETHNISCHER TANZ, LINE DANCE, BEFLUGELND, KUSTENLANDSCHAFT, LANDLICH, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, TRADITIONELLE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, VOLKSTUMLICH wom 212 tk013 harvey lee summers nothing to lose (b) wom 212 twisted country west one music country folk traditional ethnic folk national and ethnic national folk dance country western country country rock underscore nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral nature wildlife the elements land sun tropical seaside nature wildlife the elements weather sun heat laid-back country blues groove. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="14910" name="Surfers' Paradise (a)" code="WOM 156 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="320" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_156_Carefree_Acoustic/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Alistair Bruce Henry Friend" comment="Un morceau d'americana joyeux et optimiste, avec un harmonica léger et une guitare acoustique." styleid="22" lengthseconds="162" time="2:42" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_156_Carefree_Acoustic/WOM156_trk001_SURFERS'_PARADISE_(A)_Alistair_Bruce_Henry_Friend_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="Un morceau d'americana joyeux et optimiste, avec un harmonica léger et une guitare acoustique. ENFANTS, FOLK CONTEMPORAINE, ACOUSTIQUE NOUVELLE, POP, PRINCIPAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, TENDRE, LÉGER, ACOUSTIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN NYLON, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN MÉTAL, BOIS, HARMONICA, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, AMERIQUE DU NORD, PERIODE, ETATS-UNIS, LEGER, ANNEES 2000, ANNEES 20, ELEMENTS, CORDES EN METAL, JOURNEE Upbeat Americana mit fröhlichem Charakter, leichter Mundharmonika und Akustikgitarre. KINDER, ZEITGENÖSSISCHER FOLK, NEW ACOUSTIC, POP, HAUPTVERSION, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, SONNE, TROPISCH, KÜSTENLANDSCHAFT, TV, RADIO, KINDER, JUGENDPROGRAMM, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, ESSEN, FREIZEIT, HEIM, GARTEN, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, REISEN, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, UNTERHALTUNG, DAYTIME - TV, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, ZÄRTLICH, MILD, AKUSTISCH, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, TREIBEND, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MITTLERES TEMPO (ANDANTE), SAITENINSTRUMENTE, GITARRE - AKUSTIK, NYLONSAITEN, SAITENINSTRUMENTE, GITARRE - AKUSTIK, STAHLSAITEN, HOLZBLASINSTRUMENTE, MUNDHARMONIKA, NORDAMERIKA, USA, ZEITALTER, MODERNE ZEIT, 2000ER, FROHLICH, KUSTENLANDSCHAFT, ZARTLICH, ZEITGENOSSISCH, ZEITGENOSSISCHER FOLK wom 156 tk001 alistair bruce henry friend surfers' paradise (a) wom 156 carefree acoustic west one music country folk children contemporary folk new acoustic pop main nature wildlife the elements land sun tropical seaside tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio talkshow entertainment daytime happy joyful upbeat americana featuring light harmonica and acoustic guitar tune. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="20008" name="Raise it Up (b)" code="WOM 269 tk017" libraryid="6" albumid="436" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_269_Hitlist/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Tyler Van Den Berg / Kevin Ronnie Mcpherson" comment="De la soul 70's sombre avec un soupçon de hip hop. Avec des guitares stridentes et des cuivres punchy." styleid="5" lengthseconds="152" time="2:32" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_269_Hitlist/WOM269_trk017_RAISE_IT_UP_(B)_Tyler_Van_Den_Berg_Kevin_Ronnie_Mcpherson_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="17" tracktotal="" search="De la soul 70's sombre avec un soupçon de hip hop. Avec des guitares stridentes et des cuivres punchy. HIP HOP, URBAIN, HIP HOP, FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, R &amp; B CLASSIQUE, POP, R&amp;B CONTEMPORAIN, UNDERSCORE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, HOLLYWOOD, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, TEXTURE VOCALE, TWIST, DEFILE DE MODE, DEFILE Spannender Soul im Stil der 70er Jahre. Garniert mit einer kleinen Portion Hip Hop, klaren Gitarren und knackigen Bläsereinsätzen. HIP HOP, URBAN, HIP HOP, FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, CLASSIC R&amp;B, POP, ZEITGENÖSSISCHER R&amp;B, UNDERSCORE, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, MODENSCHAU, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, SHOWBUSINESS, HOLLYWOOD, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, FASHION, STIL, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, UNTERHALTUNG, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, GLAMOURÖS, LUXURIÖS, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MITTLERES TEMPO (ANDANTE), VOCALS, GESANGSTEXTUREN, STIMMTEXTUREN, TWIST, AKTIVITATEN, FROHLICH, GLAMOUROS, LUXURIOS, ZEITGENOSSISCH, ZEITGENOSSISCHER R&amp;B wom 269 tk017 tyler van den berg kevin ronnie mcpherson raise it up (b) wom 269 hitlist west one music pop hip hop urban hip hop funk soul r&amp;b classic r&amp;b pop contemporary r&amp;b underscore activities settings fashion show activities settings showbiz hollywood tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio talkshow entertainment happy upbeat glamorous luxurious tempo brooding 70s soul with a hip hop twist. featuring wailing guitars and punchy brass. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="18706" name="Dark-Hearted Man (b)" code="WOM 239 tk014" libraryid="6" albumid="405" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_239_Devils_&amp;_Demons/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jay Price" comment="Du swamp rock grondant." styleid="4" lengthseconds="151" time="2:31" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_239_Devils_&amp;_Demons/WOM239_trk014_DARK-HEARTED_MAN_(B)_Jay_Price_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="14" tracktotal="" search="Du swamp rock grondant. BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BLUES, ROCK, ROCK, ROCK 'N' ROLL, UNDERSCORE, FILMS, ROAD MOVIE, NEUTRE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, BOIS, HARMONICA, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ELECTRIQUE Dreckiger Sumpfrock. FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BLUES, ROCK, ROCK, ROCK &amp; ROLL, UNDERSCORE, FILME, ROAD MOVIE, NEUTRAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), SAITENINSTRUMENTE, GITARRE - ELEKTRISCH, HOLZBLASINSTRUMENTE, MUNDHARMONIKA wom 239 tk014 jay price dark-hearted man (b) wom 239 devils &amp; demons west one music rock film score orchestral trailer blues rock rock rock &amp; roll underscore movies road movie neutral tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) strings guitar electric woodwinds harmonica growling swamp-rock. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="17436" name="The Perpetual Bachelor (b)" code="WOM 212 tk020" libraryid="6" albumid="376" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_212_Twisted_Country/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Harvey Lee Summers" comment="Une ballade nostalgique teintée de nuances celtiques avec un accordéon et un fiddle." styleid="22" lengthseconds="192" time="3:12" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_212_Twisted_Country/WOM212_trk020_THE_PERPETUAL_BACHELOR_(B)_Harvey_Lee_Summers_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="20" tracktotal="" search="Une ballade nostalgique teintée de nuances celtiques avec un accordéon et un fiddle. COUNTRY, COUNTRY ROCK, UNDERSCORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, SOLEIL, CHALEUR, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, BALADE, AMERIQUE DU NORD, ETATS-UNIS, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, ELEMENTS, METEO, ETE Sehnsüchtige Ballade mit Akkordeon, Fidel und keltischem Vibe. COUNTRY, COUNTRY ROCK, UNDERSCORE, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LÄNDLICH, LANDSCHAFT, IDYLLISCH, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, SONNE, TROPISCH, KÜSTENLANDSCHAFT, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, WETTER, SONNE, HITZE, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, REISEN, TRAURIG, BEDRÜCKEND, EINSAM, TRAURIG, BEDRÜCKEND, SCHMERZLICH, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), NORDAMERIKA, USA, BALLADE, BEDRUCKEND, KUSTENLANDSCHAFT, LANDLICH wom 212 tk020 harvey lee summers the perpetual bachelor (b) wom 212 twisted country west one music country folk country country rock underscore nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral nature wildlife the elements land sun tropical seaside nature wildlife the elements weather sun heat tv radio leisure lifestyle travel sad depressing lonely sad depressing wistful celtic tinged ballad with accordion and fiddle. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="4357" name="My Country Home (a)" code="TSH 044 tk046" libraryid="5" albumid="114" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_044_My_American_Story/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Francis Richard Shaw / Graham Donald Harry Preskett" comment="Humeur douce et évocatrice à l'harmonica." styleid="22" lengthseconds="30" time="0:30" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_044_My_American_Story/TSH_044_trk046_MY_COUNTRY_HOME_(A)_Francis_Richard_Shaw_Graham_Donald_Harry_Preskett_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="46" tracktotal="" search="Humeur douce et évocatrice à l'harmonica. COUNTRY, WESTERN, COWBOY, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, WESTERN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), BOIS, HARMONICA, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, AMERIQUE DU NORD, ETATS-UNIS, DEPRIMANT, ELEMENTS Behutsames Theme mit Mundharmoinka. COUNTRY, WESTERN, COWBOY, HAUPTVERSION, FILME, WESTERN, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LÄNDLICH, LANDSCHAFT, IDYLLISCH, TRAURIG, BEDRÜCKEND, EINSAM, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MITTLERES TEMPO (ANDANTE), HOLZBLASINSTRUMENTE, MUNDHARMONIKA, NORDAMERIKA, USA, BEDRUCKEND, LANDLICH tsh 044 tk046 francis richard shaw graham donald harry preskett my country home (a) tsh 044 my american story the scoring house country folk country western cowboy main movies western nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral sad depressing lonely tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) woodwinds harmonica north america usa gentle evocative mood for solo harmonica. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" lc="24186"/>
    <item id="19952" name="Gods of Rock" code="WOM 268 tk005" libraryid="6" albumid="435" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_268_Monster_Rock/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jack Saturday / Warren Martinez" comment="Du blues rock épique, avec une slide guitare, des influences orientales et une batterie monstrueuse." styleid="4" lengthseconds="136" time="2:16" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_268_Monster_Rock/WOM268_trk005_GODS_OF_ROCK_Jack_Saturday_Warren_Martinez_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="Du blues rock épique, avec une slide guitare, des influences orientales et une batterie monstrueuse. BLUES, BLUES ROCK, GROUPE DE ROCK, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 70, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), ROCK, HARD ROCK, ROCK, ROCK DE STADE, FORT, ÉPIQUE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, HOLLYWOOD, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, SPORT, CORDES, GUITARE, BOTTLENECK, SLIDE, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE,, AMERIQUE DU NORD, PERIODE, ETATS-UNIS, EPIQUE, 20E SIECLE, ELECTRIQUE, ANNEES 70 Mächtiger Blues-Rock mit Slide-Gitarre, monströsen Drums und östlichem Einschlag. BLUES, BLUESROCK, ROCKBAND, NORDAMERIKA, USA, ZEITALTER, MODERNE ZEIT, VOR 20. JHD., 70ER, HAUPTVERSION, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MITTLERES TEMPO (ANDANTE), ROCK, HARD ROCK, ROCK, STADION ROCK, KRÄFTIG, EPISCH, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, SHOWBUSINESS, HOLLYWOOD, FILME, EPISCH, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, REISEN, TV, RADIO, SPORT, SPORT, SAITENINSTRUMENTE, GITARRE - BOTTLENECK, SLIDE, SAITENINSTRUMENTE, GITARRE - ELEKTRISCH, AKTIVITATEN, KRAFTIG wom 268 tk005 jack saturday warren martinez gods of rock wom 268 monster rock west one music rock blues blues rock rock band north america usa time period modern era 20th century 1970s main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) rock hard rock rock stadium rock strong epic activities settings showbiz hollywood movies epic tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio sports epic blues-rock featuring slide guitar eastern influences and monstrous drums. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="4339" name="An American Story (a)" code="TSH 044 tk028" libraryid="5" albumid="114" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_044_My_American_Story/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Francis Richard Shaw" comment="Ambiance Américaine evocative." styleid="22" lengthseconds="68" time="1:08" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_044_My_American_Story/TSH_044_trk028_AN_AMERICAN_STORY_(A)_Francis_Richard_Shaw_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="28" tracktotal="" search="Ambiance Américaine evocative. BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, FAMILIAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 30, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 40, PÉRIODE, PRÉ-20E SIÈCLE, 19E SIÈCLE, AMERIQUE DU NORD, PERIODE, ETATS-UNIS, PRE-20E SIECLE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), 20E SIECLE, 19E SIECLE, ANNEES 30, ANNEES 40, ELEMENTS Scene-Setter mit der Essenz des frühen Amerikas. FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, IDYLLISCH, HAUPTVERSION, DOKUMENTATION, BIOGRAFISCH, HISTORISCH, KÜNSTE, FILME, FAMILIE, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LANDSCHAFTEN, PANORAMA, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LÄNDLICH, LANDSCHAFT, IDYLLISCH, ZÄRTLICH, WEHMÜTIG, ZÄRTLICH, ROMANTISCH, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), KLASSISCH &amp; SEMIKLASSISCH, SINFONIEORCHESTER, NORDAMERIKA, USA, ZEITALTER, MODERNE ZEIT, VOR 20. JHD., 30ER, ZEITALTER, MODERNE ZEIT, VOR 20. JHD., 40ER, ZEITALTER, VOR 20 JHD., 18. JAHRHUNDERT, KUNSTE, LANDLICH, WEHMUTIG, ZARTLICH tsh 044 tk028 francis richard shaw an american story (a) tsh 044 my american story the scoring house country folk film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral pastoral main documentary biographical historical the arts movies family nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral tender nostalgic tender evocative american scene setter. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" lc="24186"/>
    <item id="15179" name="Sweet Soul Sugar (b)" code="WOM 164 tk015" libraryid="6" albumid="326" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_164_Southern_Fried_Funk_&amp;_Soul/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Damian John Hand / Charles James Nicholas Casey" comment="Un soul band super funky en plein swing." styleid="29" lengthseconds="143" time="2:23" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_164_Southern_Fried_Funk_&amp;_Soul/WOM164_trk015_SWEET_SOUL_SUGAR_(B)_Damian_John_Hand_Charles_James_Nicholas_Casey_West_One_Mus.mp3" track="15" tracktotal="" search="Un soul band super funky en plein swing. FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, SOUL CLASSIQUE, FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, SOUL CONTEMPORAINE, FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, NORTHERN SOUL, POP, UNDERSCORE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, FETE, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 70, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 80, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 90, PERIODE, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 70, ANNEES 80, ANNEES 90 Soul Band Sound mit überschäumendem Funk-Vibe. FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, CLASSIC SOUL, FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, ZEITGENÖSSISCHER SOUL, FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, NORTHERN SOUL, POP, UNDERSCORE, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, PARTY, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MITTLERES TEMPO (ANDANTE), ZEITALTER, MODERNE ZEIT, VOR 20. JHD., 70ER, ZEITALTER, MODERNE ZEIT, VOR 20. JHD., 80ER, ZEITALTER, MODERNE ZEIT, VOR 20. JHD., 90ER, AKTIVITATEN, FROHLICH, ZEITGENOSSISCH, ZEITGENOSSISCHER SOUL wom 164 tk015 damian john hand charles james nicholas casey sweet soul sugar (b) wom 164 southern fried funk &amp; soul west one music r&amp;b soul funk soul r&amp;b club electronica funk soul r&amp;b classic soul funk soul r&amp;b contemporary soul funk soul r&amp;b northern soul pop underscore activities settings party happy upbeat tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) time period modern era 20th century 1970s time period modern era super-funkin' soul band in full swing. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="18252" name="Let the Music Take You (a)" code="WOM 231A tk003" libraryid="6" albumid="396" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_231A_Showtime/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Paul Reeves (Gb 2)" comment="Une bossa nova élégante avec un arrangement luxueux et une voix d'homme." styleid="8" lengthseconds="165" time="2:45" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_231A_Showtime/WOM231A_trk003_LET_THE_MUSIC_TAKE_YOU_(A)_Paul_Reeves_(Gb_2)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="Une bossa nova élégante avec un arrangement luxueux et une voix d'homme. STYLES DE DANSE TRADITIONNEL, EASY LISTENING, LOUNGE, JAZZ, LATIN, STYLES DE DANSE LATINE, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, BAR, BAR À COCKTAILS, RESTAURANT, BAR À COCKTAILS, BAR , SPECTACLE LIVE, THÉÂTRE, COMÉDIE MUSICALE, BROADWAY, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, SOPHISTIQUÉ, GLOSSY, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), VOCAL, CROONER, VOCAL, MASCULIN, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, DANSE DE SALON, BOSSA NOVA, ARRANGEMENT, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 60, AMERIQUE DU NORD, PERIODE, SOPHISTIQUE, ETATS-UNIS, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), THEATRE, COMEDIE, COMEDIE MUSICALE, 20E SIECLE, BAR A COCKTAILS, ANNEES 60 Schillernder Bossa Nova mit ausladendem Arrangement und männlichem Gesang. TRADITIONELLELE AMERIKANISCHE TÄNZE, EASY LISTENING, LOUNGE, JAZZ, LATIN, LATEINAMERIKANISCHE TÄNZE, HAUPTVERSION, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, BAR, COCKTAIL LOUNGE, RESTAURANT, COCKTAIL LOUNGE, BAR, LIVE-UNTERHALTUNG, THEATER, MUSICALS, BROADWAY, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, UNTERHALTUNG, ZÄRTLICH, WEHMÜTIG, ZÄRTLICH, ROMANTISCH, ZÄRTLICH, GEFÜHLVOLL, RAFFINIERT, GLATT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), VOCALS, SCHNULZIGER GESANG, VOCALS, MÄNNLICH, NORDAMERIKA, USA, GESELLSCHAFTSTANZ, BOSSA NOVA, ARRANGEMENT, ZEITALTER, MODERNE ZEIT, VOR 20. JHD., 60ER, AKTIVITATEN, GEFUHLVOLL, LATEINAMERIKANISCHE TANZE, MANNLICH, TRADITIONELLELE AMERIKANISCHE TANZE, WEHMUTIG, ZARTLICH wom 231a tk003 paul reeves (gb 2) let the music take you (a) wom 231a showtime west one music period vintage traditional dance styles easy listening lounge jazz latin latin dance styles main activities settings bar cocktail lounge restaurant cocktail lounge bar live entertainment theater musicals broadway tv radio talkshow entertainment tender nostalgic tender romantic tender slick bossa nova with lush arrangement and male vocal. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="21050" name="Let it Burn (b)" code="WOM 292 tk020" libraryid="6" albumid="462" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_292_The_Skiffle_Sessions/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Alistair Bruce Henry Friend / Ted Brett Barnes" comment="Rock'n'roll country menacant et sombre." styleid="22" lengthseconds="137" time="2:17" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_292_The_Skiffle_Sessions/WOM_292_trk020_LET_IT_BURN_(B)_Alistair_Bruce_Henry_Friend_Ted_Brett_Barnes_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="20" tracktotal="" search="Rock'n'roll country menacant et sombre. BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, COUNTRY, WESTERN, JAZZ, JUG BAND, SKIFFLE, UNDERSCORE, FILMS, ROAD MOVIE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, EFFRAYANT, MENAÇANT, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 50, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 60, AMERIQUE DU NORD, PERIODE, ETATS-UNIS, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), MENACANT, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 50, ANNEES 60 Rock 'n' Roll mit Country-Note. FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, COUNTRY, WESTERN, JAZZ, JUG BAND, SKIFFLE, UNDERSCORE, FILME, ROAD MOVIE, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, REISEN, VERSTÖREND, DÜSTER, FURCHTERREGEND, BEDROHLICH, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MITTELSCHNELL (MODERATO), NORDAMERIKA, USA, ZEITALTER, MODERNE ZEIT, VOR 20. JHD., 50ER, ZEITALTER, MODERNE ZEIT, VOR 20. JHD., 60ER, DUSTER, VERSTOREND wom 292 tk020 alistair bruce henry friend ted brett barnes let it burn (b) wom 292 the skiffle sessions west one music country folk film score orchestral trailer country western jazz jug band skiffle underscore movies road movie tv radio leisure lifestyle travel disturbing dark scary menacing tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) north america usa time period modern era 20th century 1950s time period dark menacing country-tinged rock 'n' roll. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="21162" name="California Breeze (a)" code="WOM 295 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="465" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_295_Freewheeling_Americana/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Patrick West / Matt Round / Anthony Dominic / Luke Bullen" comment="De douces guitares et une batterie légère décrivent un jour chaud et sans soucis" styleid="22" lengthseconds="175" time="2:55" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_295_Freewheeling_Americana/WOM_295_trk001_CALIFORNIA_BREEZE_(A)_Patrick_West_Matt_Round_Anthony_Dominic_Luke_Bullen_West_One_Music_.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="De douces guitares et une batterie légère décrivent un jour chaud et sans soucis COUNTRY, COUNTRY ROCK, EASY LISTENING, MIDDLE OF THE ROAD, POP, PRINCIPAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, SOLEIL, CHALEUR, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, TENDRE, LÉGER, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, AMERIQUE DU NORD, ETATS-UNIS, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), LEGER, ELEMENTS, METEO, ETE Warme Gitarre und leichte Drums erzeugen das typische Gefühl unbeschwerter und warmer Sommertage. COUNTRY, COUNTRY ROCK, EASY LISTENING, MIDDLE OF THE ROAD, POP, HAUPTVERSION, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, SONNE, TROPISCH, KÜSTENLANDSCHAFT, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, WETTER, SONNE, HITZE, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, ESSEN, FREIZEIT, HEIM, GARTEN, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, REISEN, FRÖHLICH, GUT GELAUNT, ZÄRTLICH, MILD, ZÄRTLICH, WARM, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MITTELSCHNELL (MODERATO), NORDAMERIKA, USA, FROHLICH, KUSTENLANDSCHAFT, ZARTLICH wom 295 tk001 patrick west matt round anthony dominic luke bullen california breeze (a) wom 295 freewheeling americana west one music country folk country country rock easy listening middle of the road pop main nature wildlife the elements land sun tropical seaside nature wildlife the elements weather sun heat tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden tv radio leisure lifestyle travel happy feel good gentle guitars and light drums depict warm carefree days. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="18751" name="This Is My Year (b)" code="WOM 240 tk019" libraryid="6" albumid="406" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_240_Hip_Hop_USA/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jerome Henry Spence / Sylvester Maurice Manning / Rudy Michael Jr. Covington / Felisha Aileen Booker / Ronald Agee" comment="Un piano qui claque, des riffs de guitare." styleid="27" lengthseconds="184" time="3:04" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_240_Hip_Hop_USA/WOM240_trk019_THIS_IS_MY_YEAR_(B)_Jerome_Henry_Spence_Sylvester_Maurice_Manning_Rudy_Michael_Jr._Covington_F.mp3" track="19" tracktotal="" search="Un piano qui claque, des riffs de guitare. CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HIP HOP, URBAIN, HIP HOP, HIP HOP, URBAIN, RAP, UNDERSCORE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, HOLLYWOOD, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, FORT, IMPLACABLE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), VOCAL Knallende Gitarren- und Pianoriffs. CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HIP HOP, URBAN, HIP HOP, HIP HOP, URBAN, RAP, UNDERSCORE, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, SHOWBUSINESS, HOLLYWOOD, TV, RADIO, KINDER, JUGENDPROGRAMM, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, FASHION, STIL, KRÄFTIG, UNNACHGIEBIG, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MITTLERES TEMPO (ANDANTE), VOCALS, AKTIVITATEN, KRAFTIG wom 240 tk019 jerome henry spence sylvester maurice manning rudy michael jr. covington felisha aileen booker ronald agee this is my year (b) wom 240 hip hop usa west one music hip-hop urban club electronica hip hop urban hip hop hip hop urban rap underscore activities settings showbiz hollywood tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style strong relentless tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) vocals slamming piano and guitar riffs. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="21204" name="Mojo Filter (a)" code="WOM 296 tk005" libraryid="6" albumid="466" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_296_Dirty_Bluesy_Rock/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Patrick Robert Murdoch" comment="Un riff hurlant de guitare et des grooves gras et sales." styleid="4" lengthseconds="168" time="2:48" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_296_Dirty_Bluesy_Rock/WOM296_trk005_MOJO_FILTER_(A)_Patrick_Robert_Murdoch_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="Un riff hurlant de guitare et des grooves gras et sales. BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BLUES, ROCK, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ROCK, HARD ROCK, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ROAD MOVIE, SPORT, SPORTS EXTREMES, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, BOUCLE, RIFF, AMERIQUE DU NORD, ETATS-UNIS, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETERMINE, ENERGIQUE Stampfender Song mit einem kreischenden Leadgitarren-Riff und einem bodenständigen, massiven Groove. FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BLUES, ROCK, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ROCK, HARD ROCK, HAUPTVERSION, FILME, ROAD MOVIE, SPORT, EXTREMSPORT, TV, RADIO, KINDER, JUGENDPROGRAMM, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, REISEN, TV, RADIO, SPORT, KRÄFTIG, ENTSCHLOSSEN, KRÄFTIG, ENERGIEGELADEN, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, TREIBEND, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, ROBUST, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), NORDAMERIKA, USA, LOOP, RIFF, KRAFTIG wom 296 tk005 patrick robert murdoch mojo filter (a) wom 296 dirty bluesy rock west one music rock film score orchestral trailer blues rock film score orchestral trailer rock hard rock main movies road movie sports extreme sports tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio sports strong determined strong energetic movement rhythmic howling lead guitar riff and low-down greasy grooves. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="20403" name="Push it Out (b)" code="WOM 278 tk018" libraryid="6" albumid="445" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_278_Drums_Rule_the_World/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Emre Ramazanoglu / Geoffrey James Pidcock Holroyde" comment="Des rythmes rétro-funk contagieux et punchy, avec des cuivres funky." styleid="21" lengthseconds="168" time="2:48" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_278_Drums_Rule_the_World/WOM278_trk018_PUSH_IT_OUT_(B)_Emre_Ramazanoglu_Geoffrey_James_Pidcock_Holroyde_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="18" tracktotal="" search="Des rythmes rétro-funk contagieux et punchy, avec des cuivres funky. WORLD BEAT, STYLES ETHNIQUES, INFLUENCE LATINE, ALTERNATIF, OCCASIONS SPÉCIALES, VACANCES, VACANCES HORS USA, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CUIVRES, TROMPETTE, CORNET, BATTERIE, AMÉRIQUE LATINE, AMÉRIQUE DU SUD, AMERIQUE LATINE, OCCASIONS SPECIALES, AMERIQUE DU SUD, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO) Ansteckender Retro-Groove mit jeder Menge Funk, Punch und Bläsern. WORLD BEAT, ETHNISCHE INTERPRETATIONEN, LATIN BEEINFLUSST, ALTERNATIVE, BESONDERE ANLÄSSE, FEIERTAGE, NICHTAMERIKANISCHE FEIERTAGE, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, FASHION, STIL, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), BLÄSER, TROMPETE, KORNETT, DRUMS, LATEINAMERIKA, SÜDAMERIKA, BESONDERE ANLASSE, BLASER, FROHLICH, SUDAMERIKA wom 278 tk018 emre ramazanoglu geoffrey james pidcock holroyde push it out (b) wom 278 drums rule the world west one music sport world beat ethnic stylings latin influenced alternate special occasions holidays non usa holidays tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style happy upbeat tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) brass trumpet cornet drums latin america south america infectious and punchy retro-funk grooves featuring funky brass. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
  </items>
</librarycollection>
