<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<librarycollection>
  <items>
    <item id="24698" name="Colourful Future (a)" code="WOM 335 tk005" libraryid="6" albumid="536" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_335_Inspiring_Minimalism/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="jono Buchanan" comment="Thème au piano léger, percutant et positif avec pizzicati de cordes, guitare acoustique et claquements de mains." styleid="6" lengthseconds="112" time="1:52" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_335_Inspiring_Minimalism/WOM_335_trk005_COLOURFUL_FUTURE_(A)_jono_Buchanan_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="Thème au piano léger, percutant et positif avec pizzicati de cordes, guitare acoustique et claquements de mains. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, COMMUNICATION, ACTUALITÉS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, HEUREUX, BONDISSANT, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, JOYEUX, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, FUN, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, GUILLERET, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, BONDISSANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, SAUTER, ACOUSTIQUE, ENFANTIN, PIZZICATO, ÉTINCELANT, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, ENFANTS, MATERNELLE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, AMBIANCES ET FONDS SONORES POUR PROJETS, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, MATERNELLE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, CLAVIER, CELESTE, CLAVIER, PIANO, JOUET, INHABITUEL, PERCUSSION CORPORELLE, PERCUSSION, MARIMBA, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN NYLON, ETINCELANT, ACTUALITES Ein leichtes, perkussives Theme mit Piano-Fokus, Pizzicato-Streichern Akustikgitarre und Klatschen. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, HEITER, OPTIMISTISCH, SAITENINSTRUMENTE, STREICHERSEKTION, HAUPTVERSION, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, BETTEN, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, KOMMUNIKATION, NACHRICHTEN, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, DOKUMENTATION, FRÖHLICH, FEDERND, FRÖHLICH, HEITER, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, GUT GELAUNT, FRÖHLICH, SPAß, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, KECK, FRÖHLICH, VERSPIELT, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, BEFLÜGELND, INSPIRIEREND, BEFLÜGELND, OPTIMISTISCH, BEFLÜGELND, POSITIV, BEFLÜGELND, BEFLÜGELND, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, FEDERND, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, SPRUNGHAFT, AKUSTISCH, KINDLICH, PIZZICATO, SCHILLERND, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, KINDER, VORSCHULE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, WISSENSCHAFT, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, BETTEN FÜR DESIGN, TV, RADIO, KINDER, JUGENDPROGRAMM, VORSCHULE, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, ESSEN, FREIZEIT, HEIM, GARTEN, KEYBOARD, CELESTA, KEYBOARD, PIANO - SPIELZEUG, UNGEWÖHNLICH, BODY PERCUSSION, PERCUSSION, MARIMBA, SAITENINSTRUMENTE, GITARRE - AKUSTIK, NYLONSAITEN, AKTIVITATEN, BEFLUGELND, BETTEN FUR DESIGN, FROHLICH, UNGEWOHNLICH wom 335 tk005 jono buchanan colourful future (a) wom 335 inspiring minimalism west one music film score orchestral business corporate bright optimistic strings string section main business corporate beds business corporate communication news film score orchestral documentary happy bouncy happy bright happy cheerful happy feel good happy fun happy happy happy perky happy playful light percussive and positive piano-led theme with pizzicato strings acoustic guitar and handclaps. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="44" name="Loop Wash (b)" code="EDS 007 tk014" libraryid="1" albumid="2" albumartpath="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_007_Chillwave_Glo-fi/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Israel Medina / Sample Magic / David Felton" comment="Création Electronica chaleureuse, évolutive et euphorique." styleid="1" lengthseconds="239" time="3:59" samplefile="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_007_Chillwave_Glo-fi/EDS_007_trk014_LOOP_WASH_(B)_Israel_Medina_Sample_Magic_David_Felton_Electronic_Dance_Series.mp3" track="14" tracktotal="" search="Création Electronica chaleureuse, évolutive et euphorique. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CHILL OUT, DOWNTEMPO, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRO, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HOUSE, ELECTRO HOUSE, DANSE ETHNIQUE, STYLE POP, UNDERSCORE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, SOLEIL, CHALEUR, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, COOL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), MOYEN-ORIENT, DEFILE DE MODE, DEFILE, ELEMENTS, METEO, ETE Warme, sich entfaltende und euphorische Elektronica. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CHILL OUT, DOWNTEMPO, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRO, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HOUSE, ELECTRO HOUSE, ETHNISCHER TANZ, POPPIG, UNDERSCORE, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, MODENSCHAU, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, SONNE, TROPISCH, KÜSTENLANDSCHAFT, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, WETTER, SONNE, HITZE, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, FASHION, STIL, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, REISEN, ZÄRTLICH, WARM, BEFLÜGELND, EUPHORISCH, COOL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MITTLERES TEMPO (ANDANTE), MITTLERER OSTEN, AKTIVITATEN, BEFLUGELND, KUSTENLANDSCHAFT, ZARTLICH eds 007 tk014 israel medina sample magic david felton loop wash (b) eds 007 chillwave &amp; glo-fi electronic dance series dance electro club electronica chill out downtempo club electronica club electronica club electronica electro club electronica club electronica house electro house ethnic dance pop style underscore activities settings fashion show nature wildlife the elements land sun tropical seaside warm evolving and euphoric electronica. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="Electronic Dance Series" cae="00666407133" lc="28024"/>
    <item id="12262" name="Original Brixton Rockers (b)" code="WOM 092 tk018" libraryid="6" albumid="252" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_092_Jazzadelica/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Damian John Hand / Charles James Nicholas Casey" comment="Un beat skank légèrement dub." styleid="14" lengthseconds="152" time="2:32" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_092_Jazzadelica/WOM092_trk018_ORIGINAL_BRIXTON_ROCKERS_(B)_Damian_John_Hand_Charles_James_Nicholas_Casey_West_One_Music_Limi.mp3" track="18" tracktotal="" search="Un beat skank légèrement dub. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, JAZZ, ALTERNATIF, FILMS, COMÉDIE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, COMÉDIE ROMANTIQUE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, CAFARD, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ÉLECTRONIQUE, BOIS, SAXOPHONE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 50, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 60, ELECTRONIQUE, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, COMEDIE, COMEDIE ROMANTIQUE, 20E SIECLE, DETECTIVE, ANNEES 50, ANNEES 60, MYSTERE Schwungvoller Blue Beat Skank. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, JAZZ, ALTERNATIVE, FILME, KOMÖDIEN, FILME, CRIME, DETEKTIV, MYSTERY, FILME, ROMANTISCHE KOMÖDIE, TRAURIG, BEDRÜCKEND, BETRÜBT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), ELEKTRONISCH, HOLZBLASINSTRUMENTE, SAXOPHON, ZEITALTER, MODERNE ZEIT, VOR 20. JHD., 50ER, ZEITALTER, MODERNE ZEIT, VOR 20. JHD., 60ER, BEDRUCKEND, BETRUBT, KOMODIEN, ROMANTISCHE KOMODIE wom 092 tk018 damian john hand charles james nicholas casey original brixton rockers (b) wom 092 jazzadelica west one music quirky jazz alternate movies comedy movies crime detective mystery movies romantic comedy sad depressing blue tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) electronic woodwinds saxophone time period modern era 20th century 1950s time period modern era 20th century 1960s dubby blue beat skank. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="13860" name="Brick Lane (a)" code="WOM 131 tk006" libraryid="6" albumid="294" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_131_Jazz_on_Groove/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Philip Hochstrate" comment="Excentrique et enjoué, tonique et métronomique avec des cuivres superposés." styleid="18" lengthseconds="184" time="3:04" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_131_Jazz_on_Groove/WOM131_trk006_BRICK_LANE_(A)_Philip_Hochstrate_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="6" tracktotal="" search="Excentrique et enjoué, tonique et métronomique avec des cuivres superposés. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, JAZZ, FUSION, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), JAZZ, NU JAZZ, JAZZ, MODERN JAZZ, POP, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, RÉPÉTITIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, HOLLYWOOD, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, LAS VEGAS, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, NUIT,, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), DECALE, REPETITIF, ACCELERE Schräger und verspielter 8Bit-Groove mit Dynamik, metronomischem Beat und mehrlagigen Hörnern. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, JAZZ, FUSION, HAUPTVERSION, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MITTELSCHNELL (MODERATO), JAZZ, FUTURE JAZZ, JAZZ, MODERN JAZZ, POP, FRÖHLICH, VERSPIELT, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, LUSTIG, SCHRÄG, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, WIEDERHOLEND, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, BESCHLEUNIGT, ZEITRAFFER, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, SHOWBUSINESS, HOLLYWOOD, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, SHOWBUSINESS, LAS VEGAS, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, UNTERHALTUNG, LATE-NIGHT, AKTIVITATEN, FROHLICH, SCHRAG wom 131 tk006 philip hochstrate brick lane (a) wom 131 jazz on groove west one music jazz jazz fusion main tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) jazz future jazz jazz modern jazz pop happy playful happy upbeat funny quirky movement rhythmic repetitive movement rhythmic speeded up time lapse activities settings showbiz hollywood activities settings showbiz quirky and playful upbeat and metronomic with layered horns. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="20311" name="Flute Salad (b)" code="WOM 276 tk016" libraryid="6" albumid="443" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_276_Freestyle_Beats/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Russell Mcnamara" comment="Des accroches de flûtes samplées et des rythmes terriblement funky." styleid="1" lengthseconds="176" time="2:56" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_276_Freestyle_Beats/WOM276_trk016_FLUTE_SALAD_(B)_Russell_Mcnamara_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="16" tracktotal="" search="Des accroches de flûtes samplées et des rythmes terriblement funky. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, GROOVES, UNDERSCORE, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, HEUREUX, ENJOUÉ, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, FORT, CONFIANT, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), DECALE, ENJOUE Gesamplete Flöten-Hook und ein Groove dem der Funk aus allen Poren tropft. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, GROOVES, UNDERSCORE, TV, RADIO, KINDER, JUGENDPROGRAMM, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, FASHION, STIL, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, UNTERHALTUNG, LUSTIG, SCHRÄG, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, VERSPIELT, KRÄFTIG, ZUVERSICHTLICH, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MITTLERES TEMPO (ANDANTE), FROHLICH, KRAFTIG, SCHRAG wom 276 tk016 russell mcnamara flute salad (b) wom 276 freestyle beats west one music dance electro club electronica breakbeat club electronica grooves underscore tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio talkshow entertainment funny quirky happy lighthearted happy playful strong confident tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) sampled flute hooks and insanely funky grooves. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="19233" name="Get it Back Together (b)" code="WOM 251A tk017" libraryid="6" albumid="418" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_251A_Breakbeat_Deluxe/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Steven Guy Hellier / Charles James Nicholas Casey" comment="La rencontre d'un gros beat avec du gospel et du rock 60's. Alléluia !" styleid="1" lengthseconds="167" time="2:47" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_251A_Breakbeat_Deluxe/WOM251A_trk017_GET_IT_BACK_TOGETHER_(B)_Steven_Guy_Hellier_Charles_James_Nicholas_Casey_West_One_Musi.mp3" track="17" tracktotal="" search="La rencontre d'un gros beat avec du gospel et du rock 60's. Alléluia ! TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, RELIGIEUX, CHRÉTIEN, PROTESTANT, CHANSONS GOSPEL, NEGRO SPIRITUALS, ALTERNATIF, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, HOLLYWOOD, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, JEU, QUIZZ, SPECTACLE DE VARIÉTÉS, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, VOIX TRAITÉES, MODIFIÉES, CHRETIEN, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEFILE DE MODE, DEFILE, VOIX TRAITEES, MODIFIEES, SPECTACLE DE VARIETES, ETE Big Beat trifft auf Gospel und Rock der 60er. Halleluja Bruder! TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, RELIGIÖS, CHRISTLICH, PROTESTANTISCH, GOSPEL SONGS, SPIRITUALS, ALTERNATIVE, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, MODENSCHAU, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, SHOWBUSINESS, HOLLYWOOD, TV, RADIO, KINDER, JUGENDPROGRAMM, TV, RADIO, SPIEL, QUIZ, UNERHALTUNGSSHOW, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, FASHION, STIL, FRÖHLICH, GUT GELAUNT, GLAMOURÖS, LUXURIÖS, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), VOCALS, GESANGSTEXTUREN, VERFREMDETE VOCALS, AKTIVITATEN, FROHLICH, GLAMOUROS, LUXURIOS, RELIGIOS wom 251a tk017 steven guy hellier charles james nicholas casey get it back together (b) wom 251a breakbeat deluxe west one music dance electro club electronica breakbeat religious christian protestant gospel songs spirituals alternate activities settings fashion show activities settings showbiz hollywood tv radio children youth tv tv radio game quiz variety show tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style happy big beat meets gospel and 60s rock. hallelujah brother! without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="21251" name="The Style Files" code="WOM 297 tk016" libraryid="6" albumid="467" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_297_Something_Simple/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Thomas Greenberg" comment="Guitares indie toutes en angles avec un accompagnement qui réchauffe le coeur." styleid="14" lengthseconds="102" time="1:42" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_297_Something_Simple/WOM297_trk016_THE_STYLE_FILES_Thomas_Greenberg_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="16" tracktotal="" search="Guitares indie toutes en angles avec un accompagnement qui réchauffe le coeur. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, POP, POP POUR ENFANTS, ENFANTS, POP, POP POUR ENFANTS, PRINCIPAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), ELEMENTS, JOURNEE Knackige Indie-Gitarren und der dynamische Rhythmus verbreiten einfach gute Laune. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, POP, KINDERPOP, KINDER, POP, KINDERPOP, HAUPTVERSION, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, SONNE, TROPISCH, KÜSTENLANDSCHAFT, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, ESSEN, FREIZEIT, HEIM, GARTEN, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, REISEN, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, UNTERHALTUNG, DAYTIME - TV, FRÖHLICH, GUT GELAUNT, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, VERSPIELT, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MITTLERES TEMPO (ANDANTE), FROHLICH, KUSTENLANDSCHAFT wom 297 tk016 thomas greenberg the style files wom 297 something simple west one music quirky pop kiddie pop children pop kiddie pop main nature wildlife the elements land sun tropical seaside tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio sports tv radio talkshow entertainment daytime happy feel good happy angular indie guitars and feelgood backing. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="20006" name="You Make Me Smile (b)" code="WOM 269 tk015" libraryid="6" albumid="436" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_269_Hitlist/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Tyler Van Den Berg / Kevin Ronnie Mcpherson" comment="Du new wave/R&amp;B qui se met au gospel. Vibrant, euphorique et terriblement entraînant." styleid="5" lengthseconds="152" time="2:32" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_269_Hitlist/WOM269_trk015_YOU_MAKE_ME_SMILE_(B)_Tyler_Van_Den_Berg_Kevin_Ronnie_Mcpherson_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="15" tracktotal="" search="Du new wave/R&amp;B qui se met au gospel. Vibrant, euphorique et terriblement entraînant. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, POP, POP POUR ENFANTS, FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, SOUL CONTEMPORAINE, POP, R&amp;B CONTEMPORAIN, POP, RELIGIEUX, CHRÉTIEN, PROTESTANT, CHANSONS GOSPEL, NEGRO SPIRITUALS, UNDERSCORE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CHRETIEN, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEFILE DE MODE, DEFILE Nu Wave R&amp;B trifft auf Gospel. Euphorische, vor Leben sprühende und verdammt eingängige Nummer. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, POP, KINDERPOP, FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, ZEITGENÖSSISCHER SOUL, POP, ZEITGENÖSSISCHER R&amp;B, POP, RELIGIÖS, CHRISTLICH, PROTESTANTISCH, GOSPEL SONGS, SPIRITUALS, UNDERSCORE, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, MODENSCHAU, TV, RADIO, KINDER, JUGENDPROGRAMM, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, FASHION, STIL, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, UNTERHALTUNG, FRÖHLICH, GUT GELAUNT, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, BEFLÜGELND, EUPHORISCH, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), AKTIVITATEN, BEFLUGELND, FROHLICH, RELIGIOS, ZEITGENOSSISCH, ZEITGENOSSISCHER R&amp;B, ZEITGENOSSISCHER SOUL wom 269 tk015 tyler van den berg kevin ronnie mcpherson you make me smile (b) wom 269 hitlist west one music pop pop kiddie pop funk soul r&amp;b contemporary soul pop contemporary r&amp;b pop religious christian protestant gospel songs spirituals underscore activities settings fashion show tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio talkshow nu-wave r&amp;b goes gospel. vibrant euphoric and catchy as hell. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="19872" name="A Walk in the Park (a)" code="WOM 266 tk004" libraryid="6" albumid="433" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_266_Quirky_Orchestral/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jack Wall" comment="Une ouverture excentrique et étrange mène à des mélodies de cordes glorieuses et une section centrale enchantée et magique." styleid="14" lengthseconds="183" time="3:03" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_266_Quirky_Orchestral/WOM266_trk004_A_WALK_IN_THE_PARK_(A)_Jack_Wall_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="Une ouverture excentrique et étrange mène à des mélodies de cordes glorieuses et une section centrale enchantée et magique. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, ENFANTS, CONTES, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, ANGLETERRE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), ENFANTS, CONTES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, MAGIQUE, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, FAMILIAL, FILMS, COMÉDIE ROMANTIQUE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL,, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), DECALE, COMEDIE, COMEDIE ROMANTIQUE, ELEMENTS Dem schrullig schrägen Intro mit herrlichen Streichermelodien folgt ein bezaubernder, magischer Mittelteil. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, KINDER, KINDERGESCHICHTEN, KLASSISCH &amp; SEMIKLASSISCH, SINFONIEORCHESTER, EUROPA, NORDEUROPA, ENGLAND, HAUPTVERSION, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MITTELSCHNELL (MODERATO), KINDER, KINDERGESCHICHTEN, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, IDYLLISCH, LUSTIG, SCHRÄG, MAGISCH, FILME, KINDER, KINDERGESCHICHTEN, FILME, FAMILIE, FILME, ROMANTISCHE KOMÖDIE, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LÄNDLICH, LANDSCHAFT, IDYLLISCH, LANDLICH, ROMANTISCHE KOMODIE, SCHRAG wom 266 tk004 jack wall a walk in the park (a) wom 266 quirky orchestral west one music quirky children storytelling classical and semi classical symphony orchestra europe northern europe england main tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) children storytelling film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral pastoral funny quirky magical movies children storytelling a quirky off-kilter opening leads to glorious string melodies and an enchanting magical middle section. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="20200" name="In it to Win It (a)" code="WOM 274 tk007" libraryid="6" albumid="441" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_274_Electro_Swing/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Sandor Mihaly Jozsa / Paul James Borg" comment="Le vintage se met à la pop. De la pop moderne habile et percutante avec une importante influence vintage." styleid="14" lengthseconds="162" time="2:42" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_274_Electro_Swing/WOM274_trk007_IN_IT_TO_WIN_IT_(A)_Sandor_Mihaly_Jozsa_Paul_James_Borg_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="Le vintage se met à la pop. De la pop moderne habile et percutante avec une importante influence vintage. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, REMIXES, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, TWIST, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT,, PERIODE, DEFILE DE MODE, ANNEES 2000, DEFILE, ANNEES 20 Vintage goes Pop. Eleganter und schwungvoller moderner Pop mit einem dicken Vintage-Anstrich. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ZEITALTER, MODERNE ZEIT, 2000ER, HAUPTVERSION, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MITTLERES TEMPO (ANDANTE), CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, REMIXE, FRÖHLICH, GUT GELAUNT, GLAMOURÖS, LUXURIÖS, TWIST, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, MODENSCHAU, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, SHOWBUSINESS, TV, RADIO, KINDER, JUGENDPROGRAMM, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, FASHION, STIL, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, UNTERHALTUNG, AKTIVITATEN, FROHLICH, GLAMOUROS, LUXURIOS wom 274 tk007 sandor mihaly jozsa paul james borg in it to win it (a) wom 274 electro swing west one music quirky club electronica time period modern era 2000s main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) club electronica breakbeat club electronica remixes happy feel good glamorous luxurious twist activities settings fashion show activities settings showbiz tv radio children youth tv tv vintage goes pop. smart snappy modern pop with a heavy vintage twist. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="20296" name="Freaky Friday (a)" code="WOM 276 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="443" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_276_Freestyle_Beats/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Russell Mcnamara" comment="Une intro filtrée bascule sur des breaks old school contagieux et des cuivres." styleid="1" lengthseconds="198" time="3:18" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_276_Freestyle_Beats/WOM276_trk001_FREAKY_FRIDAY_(A)_Russell_Mcnamara_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="Une intro filtrée bascule sur des breaks old school contagieux et des cuivres. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, GROOVES, PRINCIPAL, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, ENJOUÉ, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), ENJOUE Dem durch den Filter gejagten Intro folgt ein lässiger Track mit fantastischen Old-Skool-Breaks und Bläsern. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, GROOVES, HAUPTVERSION, TV, RADIO, KINDER, JUGENDPROGRAMM, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, FASHION, STIL, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, UNTERHALTUNG, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, VERSPIELT, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MITTLERES TEMPO (ANDANTE), FROHLICH wom 276 tk001 russell mcnamara freaky friday (a) wom 276 freestyle beats west one music dance electro club electronica breakbeat club electronica grooves main tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio talkshow entertainment happy happy happy lighthearted happy playful tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) filtered intro breaks to infectious old-skool breaks and brass. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="18447" name="Making Waves (a)" code="WOM 233 tk007" libraryid="6" albumid="399" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_233_Atmospheric_Indie/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Matthew James Robertson / Mike Reed / Tom Howe" comment="Une batterie battante et tonique et un piano progressent vers un final anthémique." styleid="34" lengthseconds="168" time="2:48" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_233_Atmospheric_Indie/WOM233_trk007_MAKING_WAVES_(A)_Matthew_James_Robertson_Mike_Reed_Tom_Howe_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="Une batterie battante et tonique et un piano progressent vers un final anthémique. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, ROCK, INDIE, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, SOLEIL, CHALEUR, SPORT, JEUX OLYMPIQUES, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EMBLÉMATIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EVOLUTIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), GROUPE DE ROCK, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), EMBLEMATIQUE, REVELER, ELEMENTS, METEO, ETE, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Stampfende und motivierende Drums bewegen sich gemeinsam mit Piano dem hymnischen Finale entgegen. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, HEITER, OPTIMISTISCH, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, MOTIVIEREND, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTHÜLLUNG, LAUNCH, ROCK, INDIE, HAUPTVERSION, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, WETTER, SONNE, HITZE, SPORT, OLYMPISCHE SPIELE, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, REISEN, TV, RADIO, SPORT, FRÖHLICH, GUT GELAUNT, KRÄFTIG, PRESTIGETRÄCHTIG, BEFLÜGELND, HYMNISCH, BEFLÜGELND, MOTIVIEREND, BEFLÜGELND, BEFLÜGELND, AUFBAUEND, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, TREIBEND, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, ROBUST, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), ROCKBAND, BEFLUGELND, ENTHULLUNG, FROHLICH, KRAFTIG, PRESTIGETRACHTIG wom 233 tk007 matthew james robertson mike reed tom howe making waves (a) wom 233 atmospheric indie west one music indie business corporate bright optimistic business corporate motivational business corporate reveal launch rock indie main business corporate nature wildlife the elements weather sun heat sports olympics tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio sports happy feel good pounding uplifting drums and piano building to anthemic finale. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="6449" name="All Together (a)" code="TSH 069 tk015" libraryid="5" albumid="142" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_069_Live_Life_Happy/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Alexander Rudd / Zach Lemmon" comment="Gaité légère, enjouée." styleid="15" lengthseconds="113" time="1:53" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_069_Live_Life_Happy/TSH_069_trk015_ALL_TOGETHER_(A)_Alexander_Rudd_Zach_Lemmon_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="15" tracktotal="" search="Gaité légère, enjouée. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, POP, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, PRINCIPAL, ROCK, INDIE, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, JOYEUX, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EMBLÉMATIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, SOLEIL, CHALEUR, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, FORMATIONS GENERALES, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, EMBLEMATIQUE, ELEMENTS, METEO, JOURNEE, ETE Ausgelassen, positiv und lebhaft. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, POP, ALLGEMEINE BESETZUNGEN, ELEKTRONISCH UND AKUSTISCH, HAUPTVERSION, ROCK, INDIE, FRÖHLICH, HEITER, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, GUT GELAUNT, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, BEFLÜGELND, HYMNISCH, BEFLÜGELND, MOTIVIEREND, BEFLÜGELND, POSITIV, BEFLÜGELND, BEFLÜGELND, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, TREIBEND, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, WETTER, SONNE, HITZE, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, ESSEN, FREIZEIT, HEIM, GARTEN, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, UNTERHALTUNG, DAYTIME - TV, BEFLUGELND, FROHLICH tsh 069 tk015 alexander rudd zach lemmon all together (a) tsh 069 live life happy the scoring house documentary pop general lineups electronic and acoustic main rock indie happy bright happy cheerful happy feel good happy upbeat uplifting anthemic uplifting motivational uplifting positive uplifting uplifting movement rhythmic driving nature wildlife the elements weather sun heat bright upbeat cheerfulness. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" lc="24186"/>
    <item id="2037" name="Glamour Bubble Breaks" code="RFM 031 tk001" libraryid="4" albumid="72" albumartpath="Music/Refuel Music/RFM_031_Ultimate_Archive_Killah_Funk_Collection/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Keith Andrew Roberts" comment="Version breakbeat et funky de &quot;Glamour Bubble&quot;. Remixé par Alexander S. Gray." styleid="7" lengthseconds="155" time="2:35" samplefile="Music/Refuel Music/RFM_031_Ultimate_Archive_Killah_Funk_Collection/RFM031_trk001_GLAMOUR_BUBBLE_BREAKS_Keith_Andrew_Roberts_Refuel_Music.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="Version breakbeat et funky de &quot;Glamour Bubble&quot;. Remixé par Alexander S. Gray. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, REMIXES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, SEXY, COOL, FORT, CONFIANT, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 60, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 70, STYLE VINTAGE, ENREGISTREMENT D'ARCHIVE, PERIODE, 20E SIECLE, DETECTIVE, ANNEES 60, ANNEES 70, MYSTERE Eine funkige Breakbeat-Version von &quot;Glamour Bubble&quot;, geremixt von Alexander S. Gray. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, REMIXE, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, HAUPTVERSION, FILME, ACTION ABENTEUER, FILME, CRIME, DETEKTIV, MYSTERY, FILME, SPIONAGE, SPION, TV, RADIO, KINDER, JUGENDPROGRAMM, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, FASHION, STIL, FRÖHLICH, GUT GELAUNT, SEXY, COOL, KRÄFTIG, ZUVERSICHTLICH, GLAMOURÖS, LUXURIÖS, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MITTLERES TEMPO (ANDANTE), ZEITALTER, MODERNE ZEIT, VOR 20. JHD., 60ER, ZEITALTER, MODERNE ZEIT, VOR 20. JHD., 70ER, VINTAGE-STIL, ARCHIVAUFNAHMEN, FROHLICH, GLAMOUROS, KRAFTIG, LUXURIOS rfm 031 tk001 keith andrew roberts glamour bubble breaks rfm 031 ultimate archive killah funk collection refuel music kitsch retro club electronica breakbeat club electronica remixes film score orchestral trailer funk soul r&amp;b main movies action adventure movies crime detective mystery movies espionage spy tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style happy feel good sexy funky breakbeat version of 'glamour bubble' remixed by alexander s. gray. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Refuel Music" cae="00617450359" lc="24189"/>
    <item id="14157" name="Swingin' Out (a)" code="WOM 140A tk009" libraryid="6" albumid="303" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_140A_Quirky_Vintage_A/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Paul Reeves (Gb 2)" comment="Une ligne de basse répétitive qui progresse vers un climax de clarinette frénétique." styleid="7" lengthseconds="63" time="1:03" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_140A_Quirky_Vintage_A/WOM140A_trk009_SWINGIN'_OUT_(A)_Paul_Reeves_(Gb_2)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="Une ligne de basse répétitive qui progresse vers un climax de clarinette frénétique. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), JAZZ, SWING, STYLE VINTAGE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, EVOLUTIF, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, FILMS, COMÉDIE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, BOIS, CLARINETTE,, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ESPIEGLE, DECALE, COMEDIE, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Sich wiederholende Bassline auf dem Weg zu einem rasenden Klarinetten-Höhepunkt. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, HAUPTVERSION, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), JAZZ, SWING, VINTAGE-STIL, FRÖHLICH, GUT GELAUNT, LUSTIG, KOMÖDIANTISCH, LUSTIG, EXZENTRISCH, LUSTIG, HINTERLISTIG, LUSTIG, SCHRÄG, AUFBAUEND, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, SHOWBUSINESS, FILME, KOMÖDIEN, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, FASHION, STIL, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, REISEN, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, UNTERHALTUNG, HOLZBLASINSTRUMENTE, KLARINETTE, AKTIVITATEN, FROHLICH, KOMODIANTISCH, KOMODIEN, SCHRAG wom 140a tk009 paul reeves (gb 2) swingin' out (a) wom 140a quirky vintage a west one music kitsch retro film score orchestral trailer main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) jazz swing vintage style happy feel good funny comedic funny eccentric funny mischievous funny quirky building activities settings showbiz movies comedy tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio repeating bass line building to frenzied clarinet climax. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="117" name="Can You Believe (b)" code="EDS 009 tk016" libraryid="1" albumid="4" albumartpath="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_009_Dance-Punk_Electro/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Huw Williams" comment="Hymne dance-punk inspirant." styleid="1" lengthseconds="186" time="3:06" samplefile="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_009_Dance-Punk_Electro/EDS_009_trk016_CAN_YOU_BELIEVE_(B)_Huw_Williams_Electronic_Dance_Series.mp3" track="16" tracktotal="" search="Hymne dance-punk inspirant. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CHEMICAL BEATS, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRO, UNDERSCORE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, SPORT, EXERCICE, FITNESS, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEFILE DE MODE, DEFILE Mitreißender und sofort ins Ohr gehender Dance-Punk für den Dancefloor. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CHEMICAL BEATS, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRO, UNDERSCORE, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, MODENSCHAU, SPORT, TRAINING, FITNESS, TV, RADIO, KINDER, JUGENDPROGRAMM, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, FASHION, STIL, TV, RADIO, SPORT, BEFLÜGELND, BEFLÜGELND, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), AKTIVITATEN, BEFLUGELND eds 009 tk016 huw williams can you believe (b) eds 009 dance-punk electro electronic dance series dance electro club electronica chemical beats club electronica electro underscore activities settings fashion show sports exercise fitness tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio sports uplifting uplifting tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) uplifting dance-punk anthem. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without vocal" publisher="Electronic Dance Series" cae="00666407133" lc="28024"/>
    <item id="22136" name="An English Summer (a)" code="WOM 317 tk007" libraryid="6" albumid="487" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_317_Weird_and_Wonderful/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Bill Connor" comment="Délicat et majestueux, pour manigances de gens très comme il faut." styleid="14" lengthseconds="121" time="2:01" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_317_Weird_and_Wonderful/WOM_317_trk007_AN_ENGLISH_SUMMER_(A)_Bill_Connor_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="Délicat et majestueux, pour manigances de gens très comme il faut. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, ENFANTS, CONTES, ENFANTS, MATERNELLE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, ENFANTS, MATERNELLE, NOËL, ENFANTS, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, FAMILIAL, HEUREUX, ENJOUÉ, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, DÉTENDU, TENDRE, DÉLICAT, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, INNOCENT, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, PIZZICATO, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, CORDES, CORDES PIZZICATO, NOEL, ENJOUE, DETENDU, DELICAT Alles geht taktvoll und sittsam seinen geregelten Weg. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, KINDER, KINDERGESCHICHTEN, KINDER, VORSCHULE, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, IDYLLISCH, HAUPTVERSION, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, KINDER, VORSCHULE, WEIHNACHTEN, KINDER, DOKUMENTATION, FILME, KINDER, KINDERGESCHICHTEN, FILME, FAMILIE, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, VERSPIELT, FRIEDLICH, ZUFRIEDEN, FRIEDLICH, FRIEDLICH, FRIEDLICH, ENTSPANNT, ZÄRTLICH, ZART, ZÄRTLICH, HOFFNUNGSVOLL, ZÄRTLICH, UNSCHULDIG, ZÄRTLICH, WARM, PIZZICATO, KLASSISCH &amp; SEMIKLASSISCH, SINFONIEORCHESTER, SAITENINSTRUMENTE, PIZZICATO-STREICHER, AKTIVITATEN, FROHLICH, ZARTLICH wom 317 tk007 bill connor an english summer (a) wom 317 weird and wonderful west one music quirky children storytelling children pre school film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral pastoral main activities settings children pre school christmas children documentary movies children storytelling movies family happy lighthearted happy playful peaceful delicate and stately for prim and proper goings-on. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="23268" name="Bright Young Things (a)" code="WOM 336A tk003" libraryid="6" albumid="507" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_336A_Supercharger_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jay Price" comment="Indie enthousiaste et exaltante." styleid="34" lengthseconds="130" time="2:10" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_336A_Supercharger_2/WOM_336A_trk003_BRIGHT_YOUNG_THINGS_(A)_Jay_Price_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="Indie enthousiaste et exaltante. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, ROCK, GROUPE DE ROCK, PRINCIPAL, POP, ROCK, INDIE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, ROAD TRIP, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, SANTÉ, BIEN-ÊTRE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, SANTE, BIEN-ETRE Positiver, vor Leben sprühender Indie. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, ROCK, ROCKBAND, HAUPTVERSION, POP, ROCK, INDIE, FRÖHLICH, GUT GELAUNT, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, BEFLÜGELND, INSPIRIEREND, BEFLÜGELND, MOTIVIEREND, BEFLÜGELND, POSITIV, BEFLÜGELND, BEFLÜGELND, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, TREIBEND, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, ROAD TRIP, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, ESSEN, FREIZEIT, HEIM, GARTEN, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, GESUNDHEIT, WELLNESS, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, REISEN, TV, RADIO, SPORT, AKTIVITATEN, BEFLUGELND, FROHLICH wom 336a tk003 jay price bright young things (a) wom 336a supercharger 2 west one music indie rock rock band main pop rock indie happy feel good happy happy uplifting inspirational uplifting motivational uplifting positive uplifting uplifting movement rhythmic driving activities settings road trip tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden tv radio vibrant and uplifting indie. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="20537" name="Losing My Attention (b)" code="WOM 282 tk021" libraryid="6" albumid="449" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_282_Planet_Pop/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Celetia Martin / Jonathan David Lipsey" comment="Imposant, assuré et funky. Entraînant, cool et plein d'attitude." styleid="5" lengthseconds="156" time="2:36" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_282_Planet_Pop/WOM282_trk021_LOSING_MY_ATTENTION_(B)_Celetia_Martin_Jonathan_David_Lipsey_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="21" tracktotal="" search="Imposant, assuré et funky. Entraînant, cool et plein d'attitude. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, POP, FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, SOUL CLASSIQUE, FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, SOUL CONTEMPORAINE, UNDERSCORE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEFILE DE MODE, ANNEES 2000, DEFILE, ANNEES 20 Kraftvoll, edel und funky. Eingängiger und cooler Song mit einer Extraportion Attitude. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, POP, FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, CLASSIC SOUL, FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, ZEITGENÖSSISCHER SOUL, UNDERSCORE, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, MODENSCHAU, TV, RADIO, KINDER, JUGENDPROGRAMM, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, FASHION, STIL, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), ZEITALTER, MODERNE ZEIT, 2000ER, AKTIVITATEN, FROHLICH, ZEITGENOSSISCH, ZEITGENOSSISCHER SOUL wom 282 tk021 celetia martin jonathan david lipsey losing my attention (b) wom 282 planet pop west one music pop pop funk soul r&amp;b classic soul funk soul r&amp;b contemporary soul underscore activities settings fashion show tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style happy upbeat tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) time period modern era 2000s big bold and funky. catchy cool and full of attitude. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="20475" name="The Afterlife" code="WOM 280 tk012" libraryid="6" albumid="447" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_280_Cinematic_Indie/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Timothy Stephen Pierce / Brett Carr Boyett" comment="Une introduction optimiste entame une progression épique à 2:18. Inspirant et cinématographique." styleid="34" lengthseconds="282" time="4:42" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_280_Cinematic_Indie/WOM280_trk012_THE_AFTERLIFE_Timothy_Stephen_Pierce_Brett_Carr_Boyett_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="Une introduction optimiste entame une progression épique à 2:18. Inspirant et cinématographique. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, ENFANTS, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), ROCK, ROCK ALTERNATIF, ROCK, INDIE, FORT, ÉPIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE,, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), EPIQUE Ein optimistisches Intro ist der Einstieg zu einem mächtigen Indie-Track, der seine inspirierende und cineastische Wirkung ab 2:18 voll entfaltet. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, KINDER, HAUPTVERSION, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MITTELSCHNELL (MODERATO), ROCK, ALTERNATIVE ROCK, ROCK, INDIE, KRÄFTIG, EPISCH, BEFLÜGELND, OPTIMISTISCH, FILME, EPISCH, TV, RADIO, KINDER, JUGENDPROGRAMM, BEFLUGELND, KRAFTIG wom 280 tk012 timothy stephen pierce brett carr boyett the afterlife wom 280 cinematic indie west one music indie children main tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) rock alternative rock rock indie strong epic uplifting optimistic movies epic tv radio children youth tv optimistic introduction starts epic build at 2:18. inspiring and cinematic. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="790" name="Beyond the Abyss (a)" code="FEM 020 tk004" libraryid="2" albumid="24" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_020_Legends_of_Time/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Robert Leslie Bennett" comment="Fantaisie orchestrale, des ténèbres à la lumière. Une mise en place orchestrale qui n'augure rien de bon amène doucement un drop plein de tension qui dure 3 secondes à 0:56. Cordes et choeur féminin éthéré amènent un thème orchestral spectaculaire, émouvant et exaltant à partir de 1:09, qui se développe continuellement jusqu'à un backend énorme avec accents de cuivre et choeur." styleid="2" lengthseconds="149" time="2:29" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_020_Legends_of_Time/FEM_020_trk004_BEYOND_THE_ABYSS_(A)_Robert_Leslie_Bennett_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="Fantaisie orchestrale, des ténèbres à la lumière. Une mise en place orchestrale qui n'augure rien de bon amène doucement un drop plein de tension qui dure 3 secondes à 0:56. Cordes et choeur féminin éthéré amènent un thème orchestral spectaculaire, émouvant et exaltant à partir de 1:09, qui se développe continuellement jusqu'à un backend énorme avec accents de cuivre et choeur. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, CUIVRES, SECTION DE CUIVRES, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, GROUPES VOCAUX, CHOEUR, CHOEURS MIXTES, PRINCIPAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, TROUBLANT, ANXIEUX, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, DRAMATIQUE, PASSIONNÉ, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, SÉRIEUX, DIGNE, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, COURAGEUX, FORT, ÉPIQUE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, HÉROIQUE, FORT, MAJESTUEUX, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, JAILLIR, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, MACHO, ARROGANCE, SUPERHÉROS, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, SERIEUX, SUPERHEROS, PASSIONNE, EPIQUE, HEROIQUE, ELEMENTS Ein sich unaufhörlich nach oben schraubender Fantasy-Cue mit bewegendem Chor und Orchester sowie intensivem Back-End. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BLÄSER, BLÄSERSEKTION, SAITENINSTRUMENTE, STREICHERSEKTION, GESANGSFORMATIONEN, CHOR, GEMISCHTER CHOR, HAUPTVERSION, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMA, VERSTÖREND, BESORGT, VERSTÖREND, DÜSTER, DRAMATISCH, INTENSIV, DRAMATISCH, LEIDENSCHAFTLICH, FURCHTERREGEND, UNHEILVOLL, ERNST, WÜRDEVOLL, ERNST, ERNST, KRÄFTIG, ZUVERSICHTLICH, KRÄFTIG, MUTIG, KRÄFTIG, EPISCH, KRÄFTIG, AUFREGEND, KRÄFTIG, HEROISCH, KRÄFTIG, MAJESTÄTISCH, KRÄFTIG, PRESTIGETRÄCHTIG, KRÄFTIG, KRÄFTIG, BEFLÜGELND, EMPORSTEIGEND, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, TREIBEND, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, ROBUST, MACHO, STOLZIEREND, SUPERHELD, FILME, ACTION ABENTEUER, FILME, EPISCH, FILME, FANTASY ABENTEUER, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LANDSCHAFTEN, PANORAMA, TRAILER, TRAILER TRACK, BEFLUGELND, BLASER, BLASERSEKTION, DUSTER, KRAFTIG, MAJESTATISCH, PRESTIGETRACHTIG, VERSTOREND, WURDEVOLL fem 020 tk004 robert leslie bennett beyond the abyss (a) fem 020 legends of time fired earth music trailer film score orchestral trailer brass brass section strings string section vocal groupings chorus mixed chorus main film score orchestral panoramic disturbing anxious disturbing dark dramatic intense dramatic passionate scary ominous serious dignified serious serious strong orchestral fantasy. dark into light. ominous orchestral set-up slowly builds to a tense three-second drop down at 0:56. strings and ethereal female choir lead into the dramatic emotive and uplifting orchestral theme from 1:09. continual build to the huge backend featuring brass stabs and choir. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284" lc="23000"/>
    <item id="23787" name="Walk Into the Light (b)" code="WOM 345 tk017" libraryid="6" albumid="516" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_345_Electro_Indie_Alternative/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Philip Hochstrate" comment="Electro indie expansive et éthérée, avec de gros synthétiseurs et une batterie jouant un rythme de half time shuffle." styleid="34" lengthseconds="184" time="3:04" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_345_Electro_Indie_Alternative/WOM_345_trk017_WALK_INTO_THE_LIGHT_(B)_Philip_Hochstrate_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="17" tracktotal="" search="Electro indie expansive et éthérée, avec de gros synthétiseurs et une batterie jouant un rythme de half time shuffle. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, ROCK, INDIE, POP, ELECTRO POP, UNDERSCORE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, HEUREUX, FESTIF, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EMBLÉMATIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EVOLUTIF, COOL, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, GROUPE DE ROCK, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, FORMATIONS GENERALES, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, DETERMINE, EMBLEMATIQUE, ELECTRIQUE, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Alles umschließender Electro Indie mit riesigen Synthies und half-time Drums. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, ROCK, INDIE, POP, ELECTRO POP, UNDERSCORE, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, STADT, URBAN, LEBENSRAUM, TV, RADIO, KINDER, JUGENDPROGRAMM, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, FASHION, STIL, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, REISEN, TV, RADIO, SPORT, FRÖHLICH, FEIERLICH, FRÖHLICH, GUT GELAUNT, KRÄFTIG, ENTSCHLOSSEN, KRÄFTIG, KRÄFTIG, BEFLÜGELND, HYMNISCH, BEFLÜGELND, INSPIRIEREND, BEFLÜGELND, POSITIV, BEFLÜGELND, BEFLÜGELND, AUFBAUEND, COOL, ALLGEMEINE BESETZUNGEN, ELEKTRONISCH UND AKUSTISCH, ROCKBAND, SAITENINSTRUMENTE, GITARRE - ELEKTRISCH, AKTIVITATEN, BEFLUGELND, FROHLICH, KRAFTIG wom 345 tk017 philip hochstrate walk into the light (b) wom 345 electro indie alternative west one music indie rock indie pop electro pop underscore activities settings city urban human environment tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio sports happy celebratory happy feel good strong determined strong expansive and ethereal indie electro with big synths and half time drums. underscore" waveformpath="" version="Underscore" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="21674" name="Building Thunder (a)" code="WOM 307 tk010" libraryid="6" albumid="477" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_307_Epic_World_/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Daniel Law Heath" comment="Percussion brutale, charangos miroitants et cordes dramatiques tendues. Un final épique commence à 1:21." styleid="2" lengthseconds="129" time="2:09" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_307_Epic_World_/WOM_307_trk010_BUILDING_THUNDER_(A)_Daniel_Law_Heath_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="10" tracktotal="" search="Percussion brutale, charangos miroitants et cordes dramatiques tendues. Un final épique commence à 1:21. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, FILMS, GUERRE, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, TENDU, FORT, ÉPIQUE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), EPIQUE Die intensive Percussion erzeugt in Verbindung mit den dramatischen Streichern eine angespannte Atmosphäre, die sich ab 1:21 im mächtigen Back-End entlädt. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, HAUPTVERSION, FILME, ACTION ABENTEUER, FILME, ACTION DRAMA, FILME, FANTASY ABENTEUER, FILME, KRIEG, TRAILER, TRAILER TRACK, VERSTÖREND, ANGESPANNT, KRÄFTIG, EPISCH, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), KRAFTIG, VERSTOREND wom 307 tk010 daniel law heath building thunder (a) wom 307 epic world west one music trailer film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral trailer main movies action adventure movies action drama movies fantasy adventure movies war trailers trailer track disturbing tense strong epic tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) brutal percussion and tense dramatic strings. epic back-end begins at 1:21. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="1227" name="Night (c)" code="FEM 015 tk023" libraryid="2" albumid="30" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_015_Zeitgeist/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Stephen Dean Hilton" comment="Des batterie entrainantes et une guitare morne créent cette piste pour bande-annonce moderne et e2nergique." styleid="2" lengthseconds="136" time="2:16" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_015_Zeitgeist/FEM_015_trk023_NIGHT_(C)_Stephen_Dean_Hilton_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="23" tracktotal="" search="Des batterie entrainantes et une guitare morne créent cette piste pour bande-annonce moderne et e2nergique. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ROCK, INDIE, ALTERNATIF, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, FILMS INDÉPENDANTS, FILMS, ROAD MOVIE, SPORT, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, FORT, PUISSANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, POURSUITE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COURANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ENERGIQUE, FILMS INDEPENDANTS Ein vor Energie sprühender moderner Trailer-Track mit treibenden Drums und Gitarre. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ROCK, INDIE, ALTERNATIVE, FILME, ACTION ABENTEUER, FILME, INDIE-FILME, FILME, ROAD MOVIE, SPORT, TRAILER, TRAILER TRACK, KRÄFTIG, ENERGIEGELADEN, KRÄFTIG, KRAFTVOLL, BEFLÜGELND, INSPIRIEREND, BEFLÜGELND, MOTIVIEREND, BEFLÜGELND, POSITIV, BEFLÜGELND, BEFLÜGELND, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, VERFOLGUNGSJAGD, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, TREIBEND, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, ROBUST, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, RENNEN, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), BEFLUGELND, KRAFTIG fem 015 tk023 stephen dean hilton night (c) fem 015 zeitgeist fired earth music trailer film score orchestral trailer rock indie alternate movies action adventure movies indie films movies road movie sports trailers trailer track strong energetic strong powerful uplifting inspirational uplifting motivational uplifting positive uplifting uplifting movement driving drums and moody guitar create a cool and energetic modern trailer track. alternative" waveformpath="" version="Alternative" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284" lc="23000"/>
    <item id="3881" name="Great Expectations (a)" code="TSH 035 tk011" libraryid="5" albumid="108" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_035_A_Winner_is_Born/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Mark Lasker" comment="Un motif minimaliste de cordes montant vers un climax et une reprise." styleid="21" lengthseconds="117" time="1:57" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_035_A_Winner_is_Born/TSH035_trk011_GREAT_EXPECTATIONS_(A)_Mark_Lasker_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="11" tracktotal="" search="Un motif minimaliste de cordes montant vers un climax et une reprise. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, CLASSIQUE, STYLE MINIMALISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, PRESTIGE , BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FORMATION, INFORMATION, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EVOLUTIF, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COURANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, MONTÉE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), MONTEE, DEPRIMANT, ACCELERE, AERIEN, REVELER, ELEMENTS, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Ein simpel gehaltenes Streichermotiv steigert sich langsam zu Höhepunkt und Reprise. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTHÜLLUNG, LAUNCH, KLASSISCH, MINIMALISTISCHER STIL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, LUXUS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, MOTIVIEREND, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, PRESTIGE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, TRAINING, INFORMATION, HAUPTVERSION, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, DOKUMENTATION, FILME, MENSCHLICHE DRAMEN, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, NATURKUNDE, WILDNIS, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TRAURIG, BEDRÜCKEND, SCHMERZLICH, TRAURIG, BEDRÜCKEND, TRAURIG, KRÄFTIG, PRESTIGETRÄCHTIG, ZÄRTLICH, GEFÜHLVOLL, BEFLÜGELND, MOTIVIEREND, AUFBAUEND, GLAMOURÖS, LUXURIÖS, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, UHRENARTIG, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, RENNEN, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, BESCHLEUNIGT, ZEITRAFFER, BEWEGUNG, SMOOTH, HIMMEL / LUFT, FLIEGEN, BEWEGUNG, SMOOTH, AUFSTEIGEND, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MITTLERES TEMPO (ANDANTE), BEDRUCKEND, BEFLUGELND, ENTHULLUNG, GEFUHLVOLL, GLAMOUROS, KRAFTIG, LUXURIOS, PRESTIGETRACHTIG, ZARTLICH tsh 035 tk011 mark lasker great expectations (a) tsh 035 a winner is born the scoring house sport business corporate reveal launch classical minimalist style business corporate luxury business corporate motivational business corporate prestige business corporate training information main business corporate documentary movies human drama nature wildlife the elements building minimalist string motif to climax and reprise. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" lc="24186"/>
    <item id="20119" name="Inside the Helix" code="WOM 272 tk004" libraryid="6" albumid="439" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_272_L_A_Beat_Scene/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Thavius Ajabu Beck" comment="Quand la science rencontre la fiction. Le son du future." styleid="1" lengthseconds="184" time="3:04" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_272_L_A_Beat_Scene/WOM272_trk004_INSIDE_THE_HELIX_Thavius_Ajabu_Beck_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="Quand la science rencontre la fiction. Le son du future. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, DUBSTEP, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRO, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, HI TECH, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PERIODE, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), DEFILE DE MODE, ANNEES 2000, DEFILE, ANNEES 20 Gegenwart trifft Zukunft. Der Sound eines neuen Zeitalters. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, DUBSTEP, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRO, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, WISSENSCHAFT, TECHNOLOGIE, HAUPTVERSION, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, MODENSCHAU, WISSENSCHAFT, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, HI-TECH, TV, RADIO, KINDER, JUGENDPROGRAMM, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, FASHION, STIL, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MITTELSCHNELL (MODERATO), ZEITALTER, MODERNE ZEIT, 2000ER, AKTIVITATEN, FROHLICH wom 272 tk004 thavius ajabu beck inside the helix wom 272 l.a. beat scene west one music dance electro club electronica club electronica dubstep club electronica electro business corporate science technology main activities settings fashion show science technology industry hi tech tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style happy upbeat tempo where science meets fiction. the sounds of the future. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="625" name="Infinite, Immortal (a)" code="FEM 014 tk003" libraryid="2" albumid="20" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_014_Heroes/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Mark John Petrie" comment="Ouverture à suspense, couveuse et pleine d'anticipation avec un thème de corde cahin-caha à partir de 00:48 se transforme en une piste héroïque toute puissante avec une fin magistrale accompagnée d'un synthé et un chœur d'hommes." styleid="2" lengthseconds="151" time="2:31" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_014_Heroes/FEM014_trk003_INFINITE,_IMMORTAL_(A)_Mark_John_Petrie_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="Ouverture à suspense, couveuse et pleine d'anticipation avec un thème de corde cahin-caha à partir de 00:48 se transforme en une piste héroïque toute puissante avec une fin magistrale accompagnée d'un synthé et un chœur d'hommes. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, BACK END, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, SCIENCE FICTION, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, TENDU, FORT, ÉPIQUE, FORT, HÉROIQUE, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, FORT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, DÉFILÉ, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, PERIODE, EPIQUE, HEROIQUE, 20E SIECLE, DEFILE Unglaublich mitreißender und heldenhafter Track mit unheilvollem Einstieg und Steigerung mit Synthies und Männerchor hin zum gewaltigen Back-End. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMA, HAUPTVERSION, FILME, ACTION ABENTEUER, FILME, BACK-END, FILME, EPISCH, FILME, SCIENCE FICTION, TRAILER, TRAILER TRACK, VERSTÖREND, ANGESPANNT, KRÄFTIG, EPISCH, KRÄFTIG, HEROISCH, KRÄFTIG, KRAFTVOLL, KRÄFTIG, KRÄFTIG, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, TREIBEND, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, MARSCHIEREN, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, ROBUST, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MITTLERES TEMPO (ANDANTE), ZEITALTER, MODERNE ZEIT, VOR 20. JHD., KRAFTIG, VERSTOREND fem 014 tk003 mark john petrie infinite immortal (a) fem 014 heroes fired earth music trailer film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic main movies action adventure movies back end movies epic movies science fiction trailers trailer track disturbing tense strong epic strong heroic strong powerful strong strong movement rhythmic driving brooding thriller opening full of anticipation with chugging string theme from 00:48 evolves into an almighty heroic epic at 01:08 with huge backend featuring synth and male choir. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284" lc="23000"/>
    <item id="7258" name="Take to the Sky (a)" code="TSH 029 tk009" libraryid="5" albumid="155" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_029_Symphonic_Fantasia/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Arthur Rhodes" comment="Une ouverture lyrique et atmosphérique vers une conclusion panoramique et une reprise." styleid="6" lengthseconds="148" time="2:28" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_029_Symphonic_Fantasia/TSH029_trk009_TAKE_TO_THE_SKY_(A)_Simon_Arthur_Rhodes_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="Une ouverture lyrique et atmosphérique vers une conclusion panoramique et une reprise. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, FILMS, SCIENCE FICTION, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, PAISIBLE, LYRIQUE, FORT, MAJESTUEUX, MÉLODIQUE, LYRIQUE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, RALENTI, TEMPO, 66 - 76 À L'AISE (ADAGIO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 90, PERIODE, MELODIQUE, 66 - 76 A L'AISE (ADAGIO), EPIQUE, 20E SIECLE, AERIEN, ELEGANT, ANNEES 90, ELEMENTS Ein gefühlvolles und atmosphärisches Intro öffnet sich zu einem majestätischen, schweifenden Theme mit Reprise. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMA, HAUPTVERSION, FILME, EPISCH, FILME, FANTASY ABENTEUER, FILME, SCIENCE FICTION, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LANDSCHAFTEN, PANORAMA, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, HIMMEL, HIMMEL, LUFT, WOLKEN, FRIEDLICH, SCHWÄRMERISCH, KRÄFTIG, MAJESTÄTISCH, MELODISCH, SCHWÄRMERISCH, BEWEGUNG, SMOOTH, HIMMEL / LUFT, FLIEGEN, BEWEGUNG, SMOOTH, ELEGANT, BEWEGUNG, SMOOTH, ANMUTIG, BEWEGUNG, SMOOTH, ZEITLUPE, TEMPO, 66 - 76 GETRAGEN (ADAGIO), KLASSISCH &amp; SEMIKLASSISCH, SINFONIEORCHESTER, ZEITALTER, MODERNE ZEIT, VOR 20. JHD., 90ER, KRAFTIG, MAJESTATISCH, SCHWARMERISCH tsh 029 tk009 simon arthur rhodes take to the sky (a) tsh 029 symphonic fantasia the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic main movies epic movies fantasy adventure movies science fiction nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife the elements sky aerial clouds peaceful lyrical strong majestic melodic lyrical atmospheric opening to majestic panoramic conclusion and reprise. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" lc="24186"/>
    <item id="1206" name="Laura's Theme (a)" code="FEM 015 tk002" libraryid="2" albumid="30" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_015_Zeitgeist/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Stephen Dean Hilton" comment="Des sonorités irréelles et optimistiques ouvrent cette piste pour bande-annonce édifiante. Des percussions entrainantes et sensibles s'ajoutent à 1:07 pour nous emporter dans un thème romantique et sa solution élegante." styleid="2" lengthseconds="176" time="2:56" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_015_Zeitgeist/FEM_015_trk002_LAURA'S_THEME_(A)_Stephen_Dean_Hilton_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="Des sonorités irréelles et optimistiques ouvrent cette piste pour bande-annonce édifiante. Des percussions entrainantes et sensibles s'ajoutent à 1:07 pour nous emporter dans un thème romantique et sa solution élegante. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, PRESTIGE , BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, FAMILIAL, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, FILMS INDÉPENDANTS, FILMS, IDYLLE, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, JAILLIR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EVOLUTIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, MONTÉE, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), MONTEE, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), FILMS INDEPENDANTS, AERIEN, ELEGANT, REVELER, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Surreale, optimistische Soundgebilde führen durch dieses romantische Theme und werden ab 1:15 von hallender Percussion begleitet. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, PRESTIGE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTHÜLLUNG, LAUNCH, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMA, HAUPTVERSION, FILME, FAMILIE, FILME, MENSCHLICHE DRAMEN, FILME, INDIE-FILME, FILME, ROMANTIK, TRAILER, TRAILER TRACK, KRÄFTIG, PRESTIGETRÄCHTIG, ZÄRTLICH, ROMANTISCH, ZÄRTLICH, WARM, BEFLÜGELND, INSPIRIEREND, BEFLÜGELND, OPTIMISTISCH, BEFLÜGELND, EMPORSTEIGEND, BEFLÜGELND, BEFLÜGELND, AUFBAUEND, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, TREIBEND, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, ROBUST, BEWEGUNG, SMOOTH, HIMMEL / LUFT, FLIEGEN, BEWEGUNG, SMOOTH, ELEGANT, BEWEGUNG, SMOOTH, AUFSTEIGEND, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MITTELSCHNELL (MODERATO), BEFLUGELND, ENTHULLUNG, KRAFTIG, PRESTIGETRACHTIG, ZARTLICH fem 015 tk002 stephen dean hilton laura's theme (a) fem 015 zeitgeist fired earth music trailer film score orchestral trailer business corporate prestige business corporate reveal launch film score orchestral panoramic main movies family movies human drama movies indie films movies romance trailers trailer track strong prestigious tender romantic tender warm optimistic yet surreal soundscapes open this uplifting trailer track. driving and emotive percussion joins from 1:07 leading the romantic theme into its elegant resolve. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284" lc="23000"/>
    <item id="21592" name="Path to Success (a)" code="WOM 306 tk004" libraryid="6" albumid="476" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_306_Success_Stories/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Paul Reeves (Gb 2)" comment="Montée jusqu'au final, subtile et puissante." styleid="9" lengthseconds="188" time="3:08" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_306_Success_Stories/WOM_306_trk004_PATH_TO_SUCCESS_(A)_Paul_Reeves_(Gb_2)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="Montée jusqu'au final, subtile et puissante. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, CLASSIQUE, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, PÉRIODE, PRÉ-20E SIÈCLE, 19E SIÈCLE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, PRESTIGE , BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, FORT, ÉPIQUE, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, EVOLUTIF, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, WESTERN, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA,, AMERIQUE DU NORD, PERIODE, ETATS-UNIS, PRE-20E SIECLE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), EPIQUE, 20E SIECLE, 19E SIECLE, REVELER, ELEMENTS, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Zurückhaltendes und doch kraftvolles Theme, das sich zu einem mitreißenden Höhepunkt steigert. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, KLASSISCH, KLASSISCH &amp; SEMIKLASSISCH, SINFONIEORCHESTER, NORDAMERIKA, USA, ZEITALTER, VOR 20 JHD., 18. JAHRHUNDERT, ZEITALTER, MODERNE ZEIT, VOR 20. JHD., HAUPTVERSION, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), KLASSISCH, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, PRESTIGE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTHÜLLUNG, LAUNCH, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMA, KRÄFTIG, EPISCH, KRÄFTIG, KRAFTVOLL, KRÄFTIG, PRESTIGETRÄCHTIG, AUFBAUEND, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, FILME, EPISCH, FILME, WESTERN, DOKUMENTATION, BIOGRAFISCH, HISTORISCH, KÜNSTE, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LANDSCHAFTEN, PANORAMA, ENTHULLUNG, KRAFTIG, KUNSTE, PRESTIGETRACHTIG wom 306 tk004 paul reeves (gb 2) path to success (a) wom 306 success stories west one music corporate business classical classical and semi classical symphony orchestra north america usa time period pre 20th century 1800s time period modern era 20th century main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) classical business corporate prestige business corporate reveal launch film score orchestral understated yet powerful build leading to an epic climax. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="21558" name="Turning the Tide (a)" code="WOM 305 tk008" libraryid="6" albumid="475" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_305_Inspiring_Indie/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Matthew James Robertson / Mike Reed / Tom Howe" comment="Une introduction menée au piano mène à un hymne indie qui ne cesse de grandir." styleid="34" lengthseconds="153" time="2:33" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_305_Inspiring_Indie/WOM_305_trk008_TURNING_THE_TIDE_(A)_Matthew_James_Robertson_Mike_Reed_Tom_Howe_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="8" tracktotal="" search="Une introduction menée au piano mène à un hymne indie qui ne cesse de grandir. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, ROCK, INDIE, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, RALENTI, EVOLUTIF, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, SPORT, JEUX OLYMPIQUES,, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), REVELER, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Das noch zurückhaltende Piano-Intro weicht einer beeindruckenden Indie-Hymne. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTHÜLLUNG, LAUNCH, HAUPTVERSION, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), BUSINESS, CORPORATE, MOTIVIEREND, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTHÜLLUNG, LAUNCH, ROCK, INDIE, KRÄFTIG, PRESTIGETRÄCHTIG, BEFLÜGELND, MOTIVIEREND, BEWEGUNG, SMOOTH, ZEITLUPE, AUFBAUEND, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, SPORT, OLYMPISCHE SPIELE, BEFLUGELND, ENTHULLUNG, KRAFTIG, PRESTIGETRACHTIG wom 305 tk008 matthew james robertson mike reed tom howe turning the tide (a) wom 305 inspiring indie west one music indie business corporate reveal launch main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) business corporate motivational business corporate reveal launch rock indie strong prestigious uplifting motivational movement smooth slow motion building business corporate tv radio sports sports piano-based introduction leads to ever-growing indie anthem. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="1607" name="Celestial Ascension (a)" code="NRF 008 tk001" libraryid="3" albumid="41" albumartpath="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_008_Lumos/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Christian Telford, Koichi C. Sanchez-Imahashi, Shinnosuke Miyazawa, Kenneth E. Belcher" comment="Des rythmes énergiques de piano et guitare évoluent en un ostinato stimulant. Glorieux et plein d'espoir. Conclusion paroxystique une envolée de cuivres et violons." styleid="6" lengthseconds="171" time="2:51" samplefile="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_008_Lumos/NRF_008_trk001_CELESTIAL_ASCENSION_(A)_Christian_Telford,_Koichi_C._Sanchez-Imahashi,_Shinnosuke_Miyazawa,_Kenneth_E._Bel.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="Des rythmes énergiques de piano et guitare évoluent en un ostinato stimulant. Glorieux et plein d'espoir. Conclusion paroxystique une envolée de cuivres et violons. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, ORCHESTRAL HYBRIDE , BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ART ET ESSAI, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, FAMILIAL, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, FILMS INDÉPENDANTS, FILMS, IDYLLE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, DRAME FAMILIAL, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EMBLÉMATIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, BEAU, EVOLUTIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, CLAVIER, PIANO, FORMATIONS GENERALES, ENERGIQUE, FILMS INDEPENDANTS, EMBLEMATIQUE, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Ein energiegeladenes Piano steigert sich mit Gitarrenrhythmen zu einem Finale mit Violinen und Hörnern. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRALER HYBRID, DOKUMENTATION, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, DOKUMENTATION, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, ORCHESTRALER HYBRID, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMA, HAUPTVERSION, FILME, ART HOUSE, FILME, KINDER, KINDERGESCHICHTEN, FILME, FAMILIE, FILME, MENSCHLICHE DRAMEN, FILME, INDIE-FILME, FILME, ROMANTIK, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TV, RADIO, TV-DRAMA, FAMILIENDRAMA, KRÄFTIG, ENERGIEGELADEN, ZÄRTLICH, HOFFNUNGSVOLL, ZÄRTLICH, WEHMÜTIG, ZÄRTLICH, WARM, BEFLÜGELND, HYMNISCH, BEFLÜGELND, INSPIRIEREND, BEFLÜGELND, BEFLÜGELND, SCHÖN, AUFBAUEND, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, TREIBEND, ALLGEMEINE BESETZUNGEN, AKUSTISCH, SAITENINSTRUMENTE, STREICHERSEKTION, KEYBOARD, PIANO, BEFLUGELND, KRAFTIG, SCHON, WEHMUTIG, ZARTLICH nrf 008 tk001 christian telford koichi c. sanchez-imahashi shinnosuke miyazawa kenneth e. belcher celestial ascension (a) nrf 008 lumos noise refinery film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral documentary film score orchestral orchestral hybrid film score orchestral panoramic main movies art house movies children storytelling movies family movies human drama movies indie films movies romance tv radio sports tv energetic piano and guitar rhythms grow to an inspirational ostinato. hopeful and glorious. climactic conclusion with soaring violins and horns. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Noise Refinery" cae="00719510644" lc="31000"/>
    <item id="23289" name="Hey Yeah (b)" code="WOM 336A tk024" libraryid="6" albumid="507" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_336A_Supercharger_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jay Price" comment="Une intro au développement lent se heurte à 0:26 à un chorus épique et euphorique." styleid="34" lengthseconds="113" time="1:53" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_336A_Supercharger_2/WOM_336A_trk024_HEY_YEAH_(B)_Jay_Price_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="24" tracktotal="" search="Une intro au développement lent se heurte à 0:26 à un chorus épique et euphorique. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, ROCK, GROUPE DE ROCK, ALTERNATIF, ROCK, INDIE, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, ROAD TRIP, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TELE REALITE Ein grandioser Chorus, der von einem sich langsam steigernden Intro eingeleitet wird. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, ROCK, ROCKBAND, ALTERNATIVE, ROCK, INDIE, KRÄFTIG, ZUVERSICHTLICH, KRÄFTIG, KRÄFTIG, BEFLÜGELND, INSPIRIEREND, BEFLÜGELND, MOTIVIEREND, BEFLÜGELND, POSITIV, BEFLÜGELND, BEFLÜGELND, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, TREIBEND, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, ROAD TRIP, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, ESSEN, FREIZEIT, HEIM, GARTEN, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, REISEN, TV, RADIO, REALITY TV, TV, RADIO, SPORT, AKTIVITATEN, BEFLUGELND, KRAFTIG wom 336a tk024 jay price hey yeah (b) wom 336a supercharger 2 west one music indie rock rock band alternate rock indie strong confident strong strong uplifting inspirational uplifting motivational uplifting positive uplifting uplifting movement rhythmic driving activities settings road trip tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden tv slowly building intro hits epic euphoric chorus at 0:26. no vocal" waveformpath="" version="No Vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="372" name="Absolute Magnitude (a)" code="FEM 007 tk007" libraryid="2" albumid="12" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_007_Ultimatum/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jesper Kyd" comment="Une bande-annonce orchestrale épique et envoûtante. Une ouverture émouvante conduit à un thème vaillant avec des percussions massives et des chœurs célestes." styleid="2" lengthseconds="132" time="2:12" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_007_Ultimatum/FEM007_trk007_ABSOLUTE_MAGNITUDE_(A)_Jesper_Kyd_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="Une bande-annonce orchestrale épique et envoûtante. Une ouverture émouvante conduit à un thème vaillant avec des percussions massives et des chœurs célestes. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, DRAMATIQUE, PASSIONNÉ, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, ÉPIQUE, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EVOLUTIF, FORT EN ÉMOTIONS, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), CHOEUR, PÉRIODE, CIVILISATIONS ANCIENNES, ROME ANTIQUE (500 AV. J-C - 476 AP. J-C), PERIODE, FORT EN EMOTIONS, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), PASSIONNE, DEPRIMANT, EPIQUE, PERIODES, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Ein mitreißender orchestraler Trailercue mit einem gefühlvollem Beginn, der zu einer heroischen Komposition mit gewaltiger Percussion und himmlischem Chor anwächst. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMA, HAUPTVERSION, FILME, ACTION ABENTEUER, FILME, EPISCH, FILME, ÄRA, HISTORISCH, KOSTÜMDRAMA, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LANDSCHAFTEN, PANORAMA, TRAILER, TRAILER TRACK, VERSTÖREND, ANGESPANNT, DRAMATISCH, INTENSIV, DRAMATISCH, LEIDENSCHAFTLICH, TRAURIG, BEDRÜCKEND, SCHMERZLICH, TRAURIG, BEDRÜCKEND, TRAURIG, KRÄFTIG, ZUVERSICHTLICH, KRÄFTIG, EPISCH, KRÄFTIG, PRESTIGETRÄCHTIG, BEFLÜGELND, EUPHORISCH, BEFLÜGELND, BEFLÜGELND, AUFBAUEND, MITREIßEND, BEWEGUNG, SMOOTH, HIMMEL / LUFT, FLIEGEN, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MITTELSCHNELL (MODERATO), CHOR, ZEITALTER, ALTE ZIVILISATIONEN, ALTES ROM (500 V. CHR. - 476 V. CHR.), ARA, BEDRUCKEND, BEFLUGELND, KOSTUMDRAMA, KRAFTIG, PRESTIGETRACHTIG, VERSTOREND fem 007 tk007 jesper kyd absolute magnitude (a) fem 007 ultimatum fired earth music trailer film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic main movies action adventure movies epic movies period historical costume drama nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama trailers trailer track disturbing tense dramatic intense dramatic passionate sweeping epic orchestral trailer cue. emotive opening leads into valiant theme with huge percussion and heavenly chorus. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284" lc="23000"/>
    <item id="69" name="Tidal Wave" code="EDS 008 tk010" libraryid="1" albumid="3" albumartpath="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_008_Extreme_Dubstep/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Samuel Rupert Cole Sutton / Alexander David Bachell" comment="Cette intro avec un ligne de synthé répetitive et nappe chaude évolue en une gigantesque ligne de basse." styleid="1" lengthseconds="173" time="2:53" samplefile="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_008_Extreme_Dubstep/EDS_008_trk010_TIDAL_WAVE_Samuel_Rupert_Cole_Sutton_Alexander_David_Bachell_Electronic_Dance_Series.mp3" track="10" tracktotal="" search="Cette intro avec un ligne de synthé répetitive et nappe chaude évolue en une gigantesque ligne de basse. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, DUBSTEP, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, HOLLYWOOD, SPORT, SPORTS EXTREMES, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, PUISSANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, NERVEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INDUSTRIE, MACHINES, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, ÉLECTRONIQUE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, ELECTRONIQUE, PERIODE, ANNEES 2000, ANNEES 20 Eine sich wiederholende Synthie-Hook und warme Pads werden von dröhnendem Bass nach vorne gepresst. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, DUBSTEP, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HAUPTVERSION, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, STADT, URBAN, LEBENSRAUM, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, SHOWBUSINESS, HOLLYWOOD, SPORT, EXTREMSPORT, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, FASHION, STIL, TV, RADIO, SPORT, KRÄFTIG, ZUVERSICHTLICH, KRÄFTIG, AUFREGEND, KRÄFTIG, KRAFTVOLL, BEFLÜGELND, EUPHORISCH, BEFLÜGELND, MOTIVIEREND, BEFLÜGELND, BEFLÜGELND, EDGY, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, TREIBEND, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, INDUSTRIE, MASCHINEN, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, ROBUST, ELEKTRONISCH, ZEITALTER, MODERNE ZEIT, 2000ER, AKTIVITATEN, BEFLUGELND, KRAFTIG eds 008 tk010 samuel rupert cole sutton alexander david bachell tidal wave eds 008 extreme dubstep electronic dance series dance electro club electronica dubstep club electronica club electronica main activities settings city urban human environment activities settings showbiz hollywood sports extreme sports tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio sports strong confident strong exciting strong repetitive synth hook and warm pad intro evolves to a mammoth bassline drop. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Electronic Dance Series" cae="00666407133" lc="28024"/>
    <item id="23646" name="The Battle Begins (a)" code="WOM 342 tk003" libraryid="6" albumid="513" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_342_Urban_Strings_&amp;_Beats/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Christopher J. Harvey, Rupert F. C. Garvey" comment="Ouverture avec un thème de cordes héroique, suivie de cordes énergiques et de beats agressifs." styleid="2" lengthseconds="131" time="2:11" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_342_Urban_Strings_&amp;_Beats/WOM_342_trk003_THE_BATTLE_BEGINS_(A)_Christopher_J._Harvey,_Rupert_F._C._Garvey_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="Ouverture avec un thème de cordes héroique, suivie de cordes énergiques et de beats agressifs. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, ORCHESTRAL HYBRIDE , CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, PRINCIPAL, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BIG BEAT, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, HIP HOP, URBAIN, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, SOUND DESIGN, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, DRAMATIQUE, PASSIONNÉ, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, FORT, COURAGEUX, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, FORT, ÉPIQUE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, HÉROIQUE, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, FORT, FORT, TRIOMPHAL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, JAILLIR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, EVOLUTIF, QUI A DU CRAN, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, SPORT, TV, RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TV, RADIO, SPORT, BATTERIE, BOITE À RYTHMES, BATTERIE ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELEMENTS SONORES, ELECTRONIQUE, SERIEUX, ATMOSPHERES, PASSIONNE, DETERMINE, ENERGIQUE, EPIQUE, HEROIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, TELE REALITE, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, ELEMENTS, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Heroische und entschlossene Streicher zusammen mit aggressiven Beats. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, ORCHESTRALER HYBRID, SAITENINSTRUMENTE, STREICHERSEKTION, HAUPTVERSION, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BIG BEAT, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, HIP HOP, URBAN, SOUNDELEMENTE, ATMOSPHÄREN, SOUNDDESIGN, DRAMATISCH, INTENSIV, DRAMATISCH, LEIDENSCHAFTLICH, ERNST, ENTSCHLOSSEN, ERNST, ERNST, KRÄFTIG, MUTIG, KRÄFTIG, ENTSCHLOSSEN, KRÄFTIG, ENERGIEGELADEN, KRÄFTIG, EPISCH, KRÄFTIG, AUFREGEND, KRÄFTIG, HEROISCH, KRÄFTIG, KRAFTVOLL, KRÄFTIG, KRÄFTIG, KRÄFTIG, TRIUMPHIEREND, BEFLÜGELND, INSPIRIEREND, BEFLÜGELND, EMPORSTEIGEND, BEFLÜGELND, BEFLÜGELND, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, TREIBEND, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, ROBUST, AUFBAUEND, RAU, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, STADT, URBAN, LEBENSRAUM, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, FUTURISTISCH, SPORT, TV, RADIO, REALITY TV, TV, RADIO, SPORT, DRUMS, DRUM MACHINE, ELEKTRONISCHE DRUMS, AKTIVITATEN, ATMOSPHAREN, BEFLUGELND, KRAFTIG wom 342 tk003 christopher j. harvey rupert f. c. garvey the battle begins (a) wom 342 urban strings &amp; beats west one music trailer film score orchestral orchestral hybrid strings string section main club electronica big beat film score orchestral trailer hip hop urban sound elements atmospheres sound design dramatic intense dramatic passionate serious determined serious serious strong courageous strong heroic opening string theme into energetic strings and aggressive beats. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="23266" name="We Won’t Break (a)" code="WOM 336A tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="507" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_336A_Supercharger_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Tyler Van Den Berg / Kevin Ronnie Mcpherson" comment="Indie emblématique, épique et exaltante." styleid="34" lengthseconds="121" time="2:01" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_336A_Supercharger_2/WOM_336A_trk001_WE_WONT_BREAK_(A)_Tyler_Van_Den_Berg_Kevin_Ronnie_Mcpherson_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="Indie emblématique, épique et exaltante. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, ROCK, GROUPE DE ROCK, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, PRESTIGE , ROCK, INDIE, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, JAILLIR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, ROAD TRIP, SPORT, JEUX OLYMPIQUES, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TELE REALITE Eine energiegeladene und mitreißende Indie-Hymne. TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, ROCK, ROCKBAND, HAUPTVERSION, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, PRESTIGE, ROCK, INDIE, KRÄFTIG, ZUVERSICHTLICH, KRÄFTIG, AUFREGEND, KRÄFTIG, KRÄFTIG, BEFLÜGELND, INSPIRIEREND, BEFLÜGELND, MOTIVIEREND, BEFLÜGELND, POSITIV, BEFLÜGELND, EMPORSTEIGEND, BEFLÜGELND, BEFLÜGELND, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, TREIBEND, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, ROAD TRIP, SPORT, OLYMPISCHE SPIELE, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, REISEN, TV, RADIO, REALITY TV, TV, RADIO, SPORT, AKTIVITATEN, BEFLUGELND, KRAFTIG wom 336a tk001 tyler van den berg kevin ronnie mcpherson we won’t break (a) wom 336a supercharger 2 west one music indie rock rock band main business corporate prestige rock indie strong confident strong exciting strong strong uplifting inspirational uplifting motivational uplifting positive uplifting soaring uplifting uplifting movement rhythmic driving activities settings road trip an epic and uplifting indie anthem. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
  </items>
</librarycollection>
