<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<librarycollection>
  <items>
    <item id="5059" name="Golden Glitz" code="TSH 052 tk066" libraryid="5" albumid="124" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_052_The_Mighty_Wurlitzer/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Leonard George Rawle" comment="Introduction showbiz effervescente et exhuberante." styleid="16" lengthseconds="60" time="1:00" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_052_The_Mighty_Wurlitzer/TSH052_trk066_GOLDEN_GLITZ_Leonard_George_Rawle_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="66" tracktotal="" search="Introduction showbiz effervescente et exhuberante. KITSCH, RETRO, CHEESY, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 30, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 40, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 50, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), KITSCH, RETRO, CHEESY, STYLE VINTAGE, DROLE, MANIÉRÉ, DROLE, COMIQUE, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, CLAVIER, WURLITZER,, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), MANIERE, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 30, ANNEES 40, ANNEES 50 Ausladender und überschäumender Schowbiz-Opener. KITSCH, RETRO, KITSCHIG, ZEITALTER, MODERNE ZEIT, VOR 20. JHD., 30ER, ZEITALTER, MODERNE ZEIT, VOR 20. JHD., 40ER, ZEITALTER, MODERNE ZEIT, VOR 20. JHD., 50ER, HAUPTVERSION, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), KITSCH, RETRO, KITSCHIG, VINTAGE-STIL, LUSTIG, ÜBERSPITZT, LUSTIG, KOMÖDIANTISCH, ZÄRTLICH, WEHMÜTIG, ZÄRTLICH, ROMANTISCH, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, SHOWBUSINESS, KEYBOARD, ORGEL - WURLITZER, AKTIVITATEN, KOMODIANTISCH, UBERSPITZT, WEHMUTIG, ZARTLICH tsh 052 tk066 leonard george rawle golden glitz tsh 052 the mighty wurlitzer the scoring house comedy kitsch retro cheesy time period modern era 20th century 1930s time period modern era 20th century 1940s time period modern era 20th century 1950s main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) kitsch retro cheesy vintage style funny campy funny comedic tender nostalgic tender ebullient effervescent showbiz introduction. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" lc="24186"/>
    <item id="4375" name="Fun Stuff (a)" code="TSH 045 tk002" libraryid="5" albumid="115" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_045_Groove_Factory/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Curtis Frederick Schwartz / James Thomas Maddren / Yuri Goloubev" comment="Groove culotté et rebondissant." styleid="18" lengthseconds="199" time="3:19" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_045_Groove_Factory/TSH_045_trk002_FUN_STUFF_(A)_Curtis_Frederick_Schwartz_James_Thomas_Maddren_Yuri_Goloubev_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="Groove culotté et rebondissant. BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), JAZZ, HEUREUX, BONDISSANT, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, EMPOTÉ, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, BONDISSANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, OCCUPÉ, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, CORDES, BASSE, CONTREBASSE, CONTREBASSE,, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), ESPIEGLE, DECALE, IRREGULIER, EMPOTE, OCCUPE, JOURNEE Lebhaft springender Groove mit frechem Charme. BUSINESS, CORPORATE, BETTEN, HAUPTVERSION, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MITTELSCHNELL (MODERATO), JAZZ, FRÖHLICH, FEDERND, FRÖHLICH, GUT GELAUNT, FRÖHLICH, VERSPIELT, LUSTIG, KOMÖDIANTISCH, LUSTIG, EXZENTRISCH, LUSTIG, HINTERLISTIG, LUSTIG, SCHRÄG, BEWEGUNG, UNGLEICHMÄßIG, TOLLPATSCHIG, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, FEDERND, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, GESCHÄFTIG, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, ESSEN, FREIZEIT, HEIM, GARTEN, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, REISEN, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, UNTERHALTUNG, DAYTIME - TV, SAITENINSTRUMENTE, KONTRABASS, KONTRABASS, FROHLICH, GESCHAFTIG, KOMODIANTISCH, SCHRAG, UNGLEICHMASZIG tsh 045 tk002 curtis frederick schwartz james thomas maddren yuri goloubev fun stuff (a) tsh 045 groove factory the scoring house jazz business corporate beds main tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) jazz happy bouncy happy feel good happy playful funny comedic funny eccentric funny mischievous funny quirky movement irregular bumbling movement rhythmic bouncy movement rhythmic busy business bouncy cheeky groove. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" lc="24186"/>
    <item id="7193" name="Celestial Journeys (a)" code="TSH 026A tk001" libraryid="5" albumid="153" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_026A_Dimensions/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Dave Hewson / Alexander Balanescu" comment="L'imagerie légère et nébuleuse de l'errance." styleid="6" lengthseconds="134" time="2:14" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_026A_Dimensions/TSH026A_trk001_CELESTIAL_JOURNEYS_(A)_Dave_Hewson_Alexander_Balanescu_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="L'imagerie légère et nébuleuse de l'errance. ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PRINCIPAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, DIVIN, CÉLESTE, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TENDRE, LÉGER, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, CORDES, VIOLON, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), LEGER, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, CELESTE Leichte, verworrene und fließende Bildsprache. SOUNDELEMENTE, ATMOSPHÄREN, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, IDYLLISCH, HAUPTVERSION, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LANDSCHAFTEN, PANORAMA, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LÄNDLICH, LANDSCHAFT, IDYLLISCH, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, NATURKUNDE, WILDNIS, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, HIMMEL, HIMMEL, LUFT, WOLKEN, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, HIMMEL, HIMMLISCH, HIMMEL, FRIEDLICH, VERTRÄUMT, FRIEDLICH, FRIEDLICH, ZÄRTLICH, MILD, BEWEGUNG, SMOOTH, HIMMEL / LUFT, DAHINTREIBEN, BEWEGUNG, SMOOTH, HIMMEL / LUFT, FLIEGEN, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), KLASSISCH &amp; SEMIKLASSISCH, SINFONIEORCHESTER, SAITENINSTRUMENTE, VIOLINE, ATMOSPHAREN, LANDLICH, VERTRAUMT, ZARTLICH tsh 026a tk001 dave hewson alexander balanescu celestial journeys (a) tsh 026a dimensions the scoring house film score orchestral sound elements atmospheres film score orchestral pastoral main nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife nature wildlife the elements sky aerial light nebulous drifting imagery. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" lc="24186"/>
    <item id="4288" name="Fire on the Strings" code="TSH 043 tk004" libraryid="5" albumid="113" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_043_An_American_Journey/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Clive Michael Oliver Carroll" comment="Une belle démonstration de folk bluegrass au tempo rapide, avec du banjo, de la mandoline et de la guitare." styleid="22" lengthseconds="108" time="1:48" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_043_An_American_Journey/TSH043_trk004_FIRE_ON_THE_STRINGS_Clive_Michael_Oliver_Carroll_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="Une belle démonstration de folk bluegrass au tempo rapide, avec du banjo, de la mandoline et de la guitare. COUNTRY, BLUEGRASS, COUNTRY, WESTERN, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, ROAD TRIP, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, INSENSÉ, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, OCCUPÉ, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, POURSUITE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ETHNIQUE, MANDOLINE, CORDES, BANJO, CORDES, MANDOLINE, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, AMERIQUE DU NORD, ETATS-UNIS, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), INSENSE, ESPIEGLE, OCCUPE, ACCELERE, TELE REALITE Bluegrass-Nummer mit hohem Tempo, Banjo, Gitarre und Mandoline. COUNTRY, BLUEGRASS, COUNTRY, WESTERN, HAUPTVERSION, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, ROAD TRIP, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, ESSEN, FREIZEIT, HEIM, GARTEN, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, REISEN, TV, RADIO, REALITY TV, LUSTIG, KOMÖDIANTISCH, LUSTIG, VERRÜCKT, LUSTIG, HINTERLISTIG, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, GESCHÄFTIG, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, VERFOLGUNGSJAGD, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, BESCHLEUNIGT, ZEITRAFFER, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), ETHNISCH, MANDOLINE, SAITENINSTRUMENTE, BANJO, SAITENINSTRUMENTE, MANDOLINE, NORDAMERIKA, USA, AKTIVITATEN, GESCHAFTIG, KOMODIANTISCH, VERRUCKT tsh 043 tk004 clive michael oliver carroll fire on the strings tsh 043 an american journey the scoring house country folk country bluegrass country western main activities settings road trip tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio reality tv funny comedic funny madcap funny mischievous movement rhythmic busy movement rhythmic up-tempo bluegrass workout featuring banjo mandolin and guitar. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" lc="24186"/>
    <item id="4183" name="Fond Memories" code="TSH 039 tk003" libraryid="5" albumid="111" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_039_Life_in_Colour/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Alexander Paul Rudd / Zach Lemmon Lemmon" comment="Un thème nostalgique et chaleureux." styleid="19" lengthseconds="187" time="3:07" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_039_Life_in_Colour/TSH039_trk003_FOND_MEMORIES_Alexander_Paul_Rudd_Zach_Lemmon_Lemmon_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="Un thème nostalgique et chaleureux. ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), PAISIBLE, REVEUR, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, DOCUMENTAIRE, CLAVIER, PIANO,, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, DEPRIMANT, ELEMENTS Wehmütiger Song mit viel Wärme. SOUNDELEMENTE, ATMOSPHÄREN, HAUPTVERSION, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MITTLERES TEMPO (ANDANTE), FRIEDLICH, VERTRÄUMT, ZÄRTLICH, VERTRAUT, ZÄRTLICH, WEHMÜTIG, ZÄRTLICH, NACHDENKLICH, ZÄRTLICH, ROMANTISCH, ZÄRTLICH, WARM, TRAURIG, BEDRÜCKEND, TRAURIG, DOKUMENTATION, KEYBOARD, PIANO, ATMOSPHAREN, BEDRUCKEND, VERTRAUMT, WEHMUTIG, ZARTLICH tsh 039 tk003 alexander paul rudd zach lemmon lemmon fond memories tsh 039 life in colour the scoring house children sound elements atmospheres main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) peaceful dreamy tender intimate tender nostalgic tender reflective tender romantic tender warm sad depressing sad documentary keyboard piano warm nostalgic theme. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" lc="24186"/>
    <item id="4066" name="Barfly Blues (a)" code="TSH 038 tk012" libraryid="5" albumid="110" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_038_Oddities/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Paul Reeves (Gb 2)" comment="Douce ébriété avec un trombone." styleid="16" lengthseconds="61" time="1:01" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_038_Oddities/TSH038_trk012_BARFLY_BLUES_(A)_Paul_Reeves_(Gb_2)_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="Douce ébriété avec un trombone. BLUES, BLUES FOLK, JAZZ, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ANIMATION, TV, RADIO, DESSINS ANIMÉS, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, HUMORISTIQUE, DROLE, MÉLODRAMATIQUE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, HEUREUX, FUN, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, SEXY, GRIVOIS, SEXY, SEXY, IVRE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, CHALOUPÉ , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, RALENTI, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CUIVRES, TROMBONE, STYLE VINTAGE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), MELODRAMATIQUE, DECALE, DEPRIMANT, CHALOUPE, DESSINS ANIMES Betrunken und entspannt. Gemächliches Theme mit Posaune. BLUES, FOLK-BLUES, JAZZ, HAUPTVERSION, FILME, ANIMATION, TV, RADIO, CARTOONS, LUSTIG, KOMÖDIANTISCH, LUSTIG, EXZENTRISCH, LUSTIG, WITZIG, LUSTIG, MELODRAMATISCH, LUSTIG, SCHRÄG, FRÖHLICH, SPAß, TRAURIG, BEDRÜCKEND, TRAURIG, SEXY, SCHLÜPFRIG, SEXY, SEXY, BETRUNKEN, BEWEGUNG, SMOOTH, AUFREIZEND, BEWEGUNG, SMOOTH, ZEITLUPE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), BLÄSER, POSAUNE, VINTAGE-STIL, BEDRUCKEND, BLASER, FROHLICH, KOMODIANTISCH, SCHLUPFRIG, SCHRAG tsh 038 tk012 paul reeves (gb 2) barfly blues (a) tsh 038 oddities the scoring house comedy blues blues folk jazz main movies animation tv radio cartoons funny comedic funny eccentric funny humorous funny melodramatic funny quirky happy fun sad depressing sad sexy saucy sexy sexy drunken movement smooth slinky movement smooth slow motion tempo mellow inebriation featuring trombone. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" lc="24186"/>
    <item id="7794" name="Digit Dance" code="TSH 041 tk004" libraryid="5" albumid="162" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_041_Through_the_Lens/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Colin John Riley" comment="Un minimalisme fluide et complexe construit au fil du morceau." styleid="24" lengthseconds="210" time="3:30" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_041_Through_the_Lens/TSH041_trk004_DIGIT_DANCE_Colin_John_Riley_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="Un minimalisme fluide et complexe construit au fil du morceau. BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, COMMUNICATION, ACTUALITÉS, CLASSIQUE, STYLE MINIMALISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, AMBIANCES ET FONDS SONORES POUR PROJETS, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, MÉDICAL, SCIENCES DE LA VIE, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, JOURNALISME D'INVESTIGATION, ABSTRAIT, SIMPLE, EVOLUTIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, OCCUPÉ, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, RÉPÉTITIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, FUTURISTE, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), OCCUPE, REPETITIF, ACCELERE, ACTUALITES, MEDICAL, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Komplexer Minimalismus, der ruhig dahinfließt und sich langsam entfaltet. BUSINESS, CORPORATE, KOMMUNIKATION, NACHRICHTEN, KLASSISCH, MINIMALISTISCHER STIL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, WISSENSCHAFT, TECHNOLOGIE, HAUPTVERSION, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, DOKUMENTATION, WISSENSCHAFT, TECHNOLOGIE, WISSENSCHAFT, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, BETTEN FÜR DESIGN, WISSENSCHAFT, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, MEDIZINISCH, BIOWISSENSCHAFTEN, TV, RADIO, NACHRICHTEN UND AKTUELLE THEMEN, INVESTIGATIVJOURNALISMUS, ABSTRAKT, SCHLICHT, AUFBAUEND, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, GESCHÄFTIG, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, WIEDERHOLEND, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, BESCHLEUNIGT, ZEITRAFFER, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), ZEITALTER, MODERNE ZEIT, FUTURISTISCH, BETTEN FUR DESIGN, GESCHAFTIG tsh 041 tk004 colin john riley digit dance tsh 041 through the lens the scoring house science new technology business corporate communication news classical minimalist style business corporate science technology main business corporate documentary science technology science technology industry design beds science technology industry medical life science tv radio fluid complex minimalism building throughout. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" lc="24186"/>
    <item id="2721" name="Amiable Amble (a)" code="TSH 014A tk001" libraryid="5" albumid="87" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_014A_Smile-_A_Most_Cheerful_Earful/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Graham Donald Harry Preskett" comment="Une réflexion enjouée et insouciante avec un basson obligato." styleid="16" lengthseconds="83" time="1:23" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_014A_Smile-_A_Most_Cheerful_Earful/TSH_014A_trk001_AMIABLE_AMBLE_(A)_Graham_Donald_Harry_Preskett_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="Une réflexion enjouée et insouciante avec un basson obligato. ENFANTS, ENFANTS, MATERNELLE, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, ENFANTS, MATERNELLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, TV, RADIO, DESSINS ANIMÉS, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, MATERNELLE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, HUMORISTIQUE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, DROLE, IRONIQUE, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, ENJOUÉ, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, EMPOTÉ, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, EXCENTRIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, MARCHE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), BOIS, BASSON, DECALE, ENJOUE, IRREGULIER, EMPOTE, DESSINS ANIMES, ELEMENTS Ein gut gelauntes, witziges und unbeschwertes Theme mit Fagott. KINDER, KINDER, VORSCHULE, HAUPTVERSION, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, KINDER, VORSCHULE, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, NATURKUNDE, WILDNIS, TV, RADIO, CARTOONS, TV, RADIO, KINDER, JUGENDPROGRAMM, VORSCHULE, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, ESSEN, FREIZEIT, HEIM, GARTEN, LUSTIG, KOMÖDIANTISCH, LUSTIG, EXZENTRISCH, LUSTIG, WITZIG, LUSTIG, SCHRÄG, LUSTIG, IRONISCH, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, VERSPIELT, BEWEGUNG, UNGLEICHMÄßIG, TOLLPATSCHIG, BEWEGUNG, UNGLEICHMÄßIG, EXZENTRISCH, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, GEHEN, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MITTLERES TEMPO (ANDANTE), HOLZBLASINSTRUMENTE, FAGOTT, AKTIVITATEN, FROHLICH, KOMODIANTISCH, SCHRAG, UNGLEICHMASZIG tsh 014a tk001 graham donald harry preskett amiable amble (a) tsh 014a smile: a most cheerful earful the scoring house comedy traditional ethnic folk national and ethnic national folk dance alternate documentary biographical historical the arts nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral tv radio leisure lifestyle travel happy perky tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) europe good humoured carefree muse featuring bassoon obligato. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" lc="24186"/>
    <item id="4820" name="Hexagon (a)" code="TSH 050 tk002" libraryid="5" albumid="122" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_050_A_Curious_Mind/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Andrew Clark" comment="D'excentriques et curieux contours et formes." styleid="15" lengthseconds="118" time="1:58" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_050_A_Curious_Mind/TSH050_trk002_HEXAGON_(A)_Simon_Andrew_Clark_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="D'excentriques et curieux contours et formes. ENFANTS, CONTES, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, HUMORISTIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, EXCENTRIQUE, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, INSECTE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, MÉCANIQUE, ROBOTIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), MECANIQUE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ESPIEGLE, DECALE, IRREGULIER, ELEMENTS Verschrobene Soundgebilde mit neugieriger Note. KINDER, KINDERGESCHICHTEN, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, BETTEN, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, WISSENSCHAFT, TECHNOLOGIE, HAUPTVERSION, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, DOKUMENTATION, WISSENSCHAFT, TECHNOLOGIE, FILME, KINDER, KINDERGESCHICHTEN, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, NATURKUNDE, WILDNIS, WISSENSCHAFT, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, LUSTIG, KOMÖDIANTISCH, LUSTIG, EXZENTRISCH, LUSTIG, WITZIG, LUSTIG, HINTERLISTIG, LUSTIG, SCHRÄG, FRÖHLICH, VERSPIELT, BEWEGUNG, UNGLEICHMÄßIG, EXZENTRISCH, BEWEGUNG, UNGLEICHMÄßIG, INSEKTENARTIG, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, MECHANISCH, ROBOTERHAFT, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, SCHLEICHEND, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), FROHLICH, KOMODIANTISCH, SCHRAG, UNGLEICHMASZIG tsh 050 tk002 simon andrew clark hexagon (a) tsh 050 a curious mind the scoring house documentary children storytelling business corporate beds business corporate science technology main business corporate documentary science technology movies children storytelling nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife science technology industry funny comedic funny quirky curious shapes and forms. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" lc="24186"/>
    <item id="3959" name="Ultra Neon (a)" code="TSH 036 tk004" libraryid="5" albumid="109" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_036_The_Hard_Edge/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Robert Henry Peter White" comment="Un rythme curieux et excitant allant vers une exposition brutale." styleid="15" lengthseconds="135" time="2:15" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_036_The_Hard_Edge/TSH036_trk004_ULTRA_NEON_(A)_Robert_Henry_Peter_White_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="Un rythme curieux et excitant allant vers une exposition brutale. BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, STRIPTEASE, BURLESQUE, FILMS, FILM NOIR, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, SEXY, COCHON, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE) Ein verführerischer und fesselnder Groove mit rauem Mittelteil und Gitarre. FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, HAUPTVERSION, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, STRIPTEASE, BURLESQUE, FILME, FILM NOIR, FILME, URBAN DRAMA, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, FASHION, STIL, SEXY, ANRÜCHIG, GLAMOURÖS, LUXURIÖS, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, ROBUST, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MITTLERES TEMPO (ANDANTE), AKTIVITATEN, ANRUCHIG, GLAMOUROS, LUXURIOS tsh 036 tk004 robert henry peter white ultra neon (a) tsh 036 the hard edge the scoring house documentary film score orchestral trailer main activities settings striptease burlesque movies film noir movies urban drama tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style sexy sleazy glamorous luxurious movement rhythmic rugged tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) intriguing tantalising groove to raw exposure. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" lc="24186"/>
    <item id="7252" name="Phantasmagoria (a)" code="TSH 029 tk003" libraryid="5" albumid="155" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_029_Symphonic_Fantasia/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Arthur Rhodes" comment="Un mystère captivant, épisodique et magique." styleid="6" lengthseconds="291" time="4:51" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_029_Symphonic_Fantasia/TSH029_trk003_PHANTASMAGORIA_(A)_Simon_Arthur_Rhodes_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="Un mystère captivant, épisodique et magique. ENFANTS, CONTES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, MAGIE, ILLUSIONS, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, ANIMATION, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, JAILLIR, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 90, PERIODE, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 90 Faszinierende Stadien einer abenteuerlichen und magischen Erkundungsreise. KINDER, KINDERGESCHICHTEN, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, HAUPTVERSION, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, MAGIE, ILLUSIONEN, FILME, ACTION ABENTEUER, FILME, ANIMATION, FILME, KINDER, KINDERGESCHICHTEN, FILME, FANTASY ABENTEUER, BEFLÜGELND, EMPORSTEIGEND, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MITTELSCHNELL (MODERATO), ZEITALTER, MODERNE ZEIT, VOR 20. JHD., 90ER, AKTIVITATEN, BEFLUGELND tsh 029 tk003 simon arthur rhodes phantasmagoria (a) tsh 029 symphonic fantasia the scoring house film score orchestral children storytelling film score orchestral trailer main activities settings magic illusions movies action adventure movies animation movies children storytelling movies fantasy adventure uplifting soaring tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) time period modern era intriguing episodic magic and mystery. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" lc="24186"/>
    <item id="3427" name="Madison Avenue (a)" code="TSH 027 tk003" libraryid="5" albumid="100" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_027_Swing_of_the_City/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Keith Mansfield" comment="Un thème entraînant au cœur léger." styleid="18" lengthseconds="131" time="2:11" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_027_Swing_of_the_City/TSH027_trk003_MADISON_AVENUE_(A)_Keith_Mansfield_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="Un thème entraînant au cœur léger. BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, FILMS, FAMILIAL, FILMS, COMÉDIE ROMANTIQUE, TV, RADIO, SITCOM, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, HUMORISTIQUE, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, TENDRE, LÉGER, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, STYLE VINTAGE, AMERIQUE DU NORD, ETATS-UNIS, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), LEGER, COMEDIE, COMEDIE ROMANTIQUE Heiter durch die Straßen schlendernd. FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, HAUPTVERSION, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, STADT, URBAN, LEBENSRAUM, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, SHOWBUSINESS, FILME, FAMILIE, FILME, ROMANTISCHE KOMÖDIE, TV, RADIO, SITCOM, LUSTIG, KOMÖDIANTISCH, LUSTIG, WITZIG, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, VERSPIELT, ZÄRTLICH, MILD, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), NORDAMERIKA, USA, VINTAGE-STIL, AKTIVITATEN, FROHLICH, KOMODIANTISCH, ROMANTISCHE KOMODIE, ZARTLICH tsh 027 tk003 keith mansfield madison avenue (a) tsh 027 swing of the city the scoring house jazz film score orchestral trailer main activities settings city urban human environment activities settings showbiz movies family movies romantic comedy tv radio sitcom funny comedic funny humorous happy happy happy playful tender light tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) light-hearted catchy theme. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" lc="24186"/>
    <item id="3041" name="Happy Hands" code="TSH 018 tk017" libraryid="5" albumid="92" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_018_Say_it_With_Style/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Gwilym Raymond Simcock / Curtis Frederick Schwartz" comment="Une construction colorée." styleid="18" lengthseconds="146" time="2:26" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_018_Say_it_With_Style/TSH018_trk017_HAPPY_HANDS_Gwilym_Raymond_Simcock_Curtis_Frederick_Schwartz_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="17" tracktotal="" search="Une construction colorée. ENFANTS, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FORMATION, INFORMATION, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, CLAVIER, PIANO,, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DECALE, JOURNEE Eine bunte und knackige Komposition. KINDER, HAUPTVERSION, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), BUSINESS, CORPORATE, TRAINING, INFORMATION, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, VERSPIELT, LUSTIG, SCHRÄG, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, ESSEN, FREIZEIT, HEIM, GARTEN, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, REISEN, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, UNTERHALTUNG, DAYTIME - TV, KEYBOARD, PIANO, FROHLICH, SCHRAG tsh 018 tk017 gwilym raymond simcock curtis frederick schwartz happy hands tsh 018 say it with style the scoring house jazz children main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) business corporate training information happy happy happy playful funny quirky business corporate tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio talkshow entertainment colourful construction. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" lc="24186"/>
    <item id="2270" name="Small Wonders (a)" code="TSH 004 tk018" libraryid="5" albumid="79" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_004_Natural_Wonders/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon David Chamberlain" comment="Aperçus angulaires et intrigants." styleid="11" lengthseconds="164" time="2:44" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_004_Natural_Wonders/TSH004_trk018_SMALL_WONDERS_(A)_Simon_David_Chamberlain_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="18" tracktotal="" search="Aperçus angulaires et intrigants. BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, HUMORISTIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, EXCENTRIQUE, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, INSECTE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, FILMS, COMÉDIE, FILMS, COMÉDIE ROMANTIQUE, DOCUMENTAIRE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE,, ESPIEGLE, DECALE, IRREGULIER, COMEDIE, COMEDIE ROMANTIQUE, ELEMENTS Verblüfft forschend und stark akzentuiert. FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, HAUPTVERSION, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MITTLERES TEMPO (ANDANTE), LUSTIG, KOMÖDIANTISCH, LUSTIG, EXZENTRISCH, LUSTIG, WITZIG, LUSTIG, HINTERLISTIG, LUSTIG, SCHRÄG, BEWEGUNG, UNGLEICHMÄßIG, EXZENTRISCH, BEWEGUNG, UNGLEICHMÄßIG, INSEKTENARTIG, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, SCHLEICHEND, FILME, KOMÖDIEN, FILME, ROMANTISCHE KOMÖDIE, DOKUMENTATION, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, NATURKUNDE, WILDNIS, KOMODIANTISCH, KOMODIEN, ROMANTISCHE KOMODIE, SCHRAG, UNGLEICHMASZIG tsh 004 tk018 simon david chamberlain small wonders (a) tsh 004 natural wonders the scoring house nature wildlife film score orchestral trailer main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) funny comedic funny eccentric funny humorous funny mischievous funny quirky movement irregular eccentric movement irregular insectile movement rhythmic stealthy movies comedy movies romantic comedy intriguing angular insights. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" lc="24186"/>
    <item id="2294" name="Day to Day" code="TSH 005 tk007" libraryid="5" albumid="80" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_005_Acoustic_Groove/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Steve Baker" comment="Routines rythmiques" styleid="12" lengthseconds="115" time="1:55" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_005_Acoustic_Groove/TSH005_trk007_DAY_TO_DAY_Steve_Baker_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="Routines rythmiques JAZZ, JAZZ COOL, JAZZ, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, BAR, BAR À COCKTAILS, RESTAURANT, BAR À COCKTAILS, BAR , NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, NUIT, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, IRONIQUE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, ENJOUÉ, COOL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, MARCHE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLAVIER, PIANO, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ENJOUE, BAR A COCKTAILS, ELEMENTS Die Routine des Alltags rhythmisch und klar strukturiert. JAZZ, COOL JAZZ, JAZZ, HAUPTVERSION, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, BAR, COCKTAIL LOUNGE, RESTAURANT, COCKTAIL LOUNGE, BAR, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, SONNE, TROPISCH, KÜSTENLANDSCHAFT, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, ESSEN, FREIZEIT, HEIM, GARTEN, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, REISEN, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, UNTERHALTUNG, LATE-NIGHT, LUSTIG, KOMÖDIANTISCH, LUSTIG, IRONISCH, FRÖHLICH, GUT GELAUNT, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, COOL, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, GEHEN, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), KEYBOARD, PIANO, AKTIVITATEN, FROHLICH, KOMODIANTISCH, KUSTENLANDSCHAFT tsh 005 tk007 steve baker day to day tsh 005 acoustic groove the scoring house acoustic jazz cool jazz jazz main activities settings bar cocktail lounge restaurant cocktail lounge bar nature wildlife the elements land sun tropical seaside tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio talkshow rhythmic routines. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" lc="24186"/>
    <item id="2375" name="Dark Matter" code="TSH 007 tk026" libraryid="5" albumid="81" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_007_Beatwarpology/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="James Copperthwaite" comment="Anormalité étendue." styleid="1" lengthseconds="87" time="1:27" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_007_Beatwarpology/TSH007_trk026_DARK_MATTER_James_Copperthwaite_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="26" tracktotal="" search="Anormalité étendue. CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, TRIP HOP, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, INDUSTRIE LOURDE, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, DANGEUREUX, EFFRAYANT, MENAÇANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), MENACANT, ACCELERE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE Das Fremde breitet sich aus. CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, TRIP HOP, HAUPTVERSION, DOKUMENTATION, FILME, CRIME, DETEKTIV, MYSTERY, FILME, URBAN DRAMA, WISSENSCHAFT, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, SCHWERINDUSTRIE, TV, RADIO, TV-DRAMA, POLIZEI, RECHTLICH, JUSTIZDRAMA, VERSTÖREND, MYSTERIÖS, VERSTÖREND, SPANNEND, VERSTÖREND, ANGESPANNT, DRAMATISCH, GEFÄHRLICH, FURCHTERREGEND, BEDROHLICH, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, UHRENARTIG, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, BESCHLEUNIGT, ZEITRAFFER, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), GEFAHRLICH, MYSTERIOS, VERSTOREND tsh 007 tk026 james copperthwaite dark matter tsh 007 beatwarpology the scoring house dance electro club electronica breakbeat club electronica trip hop main documentary movies crime detective mystery movies urban drama science technology industry heavy industry tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing mysterious disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense stretched abnormality. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" lc="24186"/>
    <item id="5080" name="Keep the Car Running" code="TSH 053 tk001" libraryid="5" albumid="125" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_053_Winner_Takes_All/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="James Robert Nisbet / James Roger Graydon" comment="Entrainement à haute énergie." styleid="4" lengthseconds="215" time="3:35" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_053_Winner_Takes_All/TSH053_trk001_KEEP_THE_CAR_RUNNING_James_Robert_Nisbet_James_Roger_Graydon_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="Entrainement à haute énergie. ROCK, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), ROCK, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, SPORT, SPORTS EXTREMES,, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), JOURNEE Energiegeladener Powertrack. ROCK, HAUPTVERSION, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MITTELSCHNELL (MODERATO), ROCK, BEFLÜGELND, BEFLÜGELND, FRÖHLICH, GUT GELAUNT, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, TREIBEND, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, ROBUST, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, UNTERHALTUNG, DAYTIME - TV, SPORT, EXTREMSPORT, BEFLUGELND, FROHLICH tsh 053 tk001 james robert nisbet james roger graydon keep the car running tsh 053 winner takes all the scoring house rock rock main tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) rock uplifting uplifting happy feel good movement rhythmic driving movement rhythmic rugged tv radio leisure lifestyle tv radio sports tv radio talkshow entertainment daytime sports extreme sports high energy power workout. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" lc="24186"/>
    <item id="2353" name="Go Ape (a)" code="TSH 007 tk004" libraryid="5" albumid="81" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_007_Beatwarpology/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="James Copperthwaite" comment="Des cuivres dub et de l'espièglerie." styleid="1" lengthseconds="173" time="2:53" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_007_Beatwarpology/TSH007_trk004_GO_APE_(A)_James_Copperthwaite_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="Des cuivres dub et de l'espièglerie. BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BIG BEAT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, DUB, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, TRIP HOP, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, POP CORPORATE, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EVOLUTIF, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, RALENTI, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, FUTURISTE, PERIODE, DEFILE DE MODE, DEFILE, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Entspannter und frecher Groove mit Dub Horns. BUSINESS, CORPORATE, HEITER, OPTIMISTISCH, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BIG BEAT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, DUB, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, TRIP HOP, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, BUSINESS &amp; CORPORATE POP, HAUPTVERSION, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, MODENSCHAU, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, WISSENSCHAFT, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, FASHION, STIL, TV, RADIO, SPORT, FRÖHLICH, GUT GELAUNT, KRÄFTIG, PRESTIGETRÄCHTIG, BEFLÜGELND, MOTIVIEREND, AUFBAUEND, GLAMOURÖS, LUXURIÖS, BEWEGUNG, SMOOTH, ZEITLUPE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MITTLERES TEMPO (ANDANTE), ZEITALTER, MODERNE ZEIT, FUTURISTISCH, AKTIVITATEN, BEFLUGELND, FROHLICH, GLAMOUROS, KRAFTIG, LUXURIOS, PRESTIGETRACHTIG tsh 007 tk004 james copperthwaite go ape (a) tsh 007 beatwarpology the scoring house dance electro business corporate bright optimistic club electronica big beat club electronica breakbeat club electronica dub club electronica trip hop business corporate corporate pop main activities settings fashion show business corporate science technology industry tv radio dub horns and monkey business. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" lc="24186"/>
  </items>
</librarycollection>
