<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<librarycollection>
  <items>
    <item id="7098" name="The Long Farewell" code="TSH 006 tk035" libraryid="5" albumid="150" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_006_Destiny/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Graham Donald Harry Preskett" comment="Une sincère complainte celtique avec des cordes et une voix de soprano." styleid="6" lengthseconds="65" time="1:05" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_006_Destiny/TSH006_trk035_THE_LONG_FAREWELL_Graham_Donald_Harry_Preskett_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="35" tracktotal="" search="Une sincère complainte celtique avec des cordes et une voix de soprano. BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, FOLK ETHNIQUE TRADITIONNEL, INTERNATIONAL ET ETHNIQUE, MUSIQUE FOLK NATIONALE, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, GUERRE, MILITAIRE, HISTORIQUE, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SURNATUREL, DRAMATIQUE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRAGIQUE, SÉRIEUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, PATRIOTIQUE, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), CHOEUR, CHOEUR FÉMININ, VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, TEXTURE VOCALE, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, IRLANDE, PERIODE, SERIEUX, CHOEUR FEMININ, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), INQUIETANT, DEPRIMANT, PERIODES, FEMININ Ein tiefempfundenes keltisches Klagelied mit Solo-Gesang und Streichern. FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, NATIONAL UND ETHNISCH, NATIONALE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, HAUPTVERSION, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, KRIEG, MILITÄR, HISTORISCH, DOKUMENTATION, BIOGRAFISCH, HISTORISCH, KÜNSTE, FILME, HORROR, THRILLER, FILME, MENSCHLICHE DRAMEN, FILME, ÄRA, HISTORISCH, KOSTÜMDRAMA, VERSTÖREND, UNHEIMLICH, VERSTÖREND, MYSTERIÖS, VERSTÖREND, ÜBERNATÜRLICH, DRAMATISCH, TRAURIG, BEDRÜCKEND, TRAURIG, TRAURIG, BEDRÜCKEND, TRAGIK, ERNST, BEFLÜGELND, PATRIOTISCH, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MITTELSCHNELL (MODERATO), CHOR, FRAUENCHOR, VOCALS, GESANGSTEXTUREN, STIMMTEXTUREN, EUROPA, NORDEUROPA, IRLAND, AKTIVITATEN, ARA, BEDRUCKEND, BEFLUGELND, KOSTUMDRAMA, KUNSTE, MILITAR, MYSTERIOS, NATIONALE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, TUR, UBERNATURLICH, VERSTOREND, VOLKSTUMLICH tsh 006 tk035 graham donald harry preskett the long farewell tsh 006 destiny the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer traditional ethnic folk national and ethnic national folk music main activities settings war military historical documentary biographical historical the arts movies horror thriller movies human drama movies period historical costume drama heartfelt celtic lament with strings and soprano voice. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" lc="24186"/>
    <item id="9029" name="Sally Gardens" code="WOM 027 tk012" libraryid="6" albumid="188" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_027_Eirinn_(Celtic)/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Un morceau de cornemuse irlandaise et de whistle, de style ballade." styleid="17" lengthseconds="232" time="3:52" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_027_Eirinn_(Celtic)/WOM027_trk012_SALLY_GARDENS_Richard_Allen_Harvey_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="Un morceau de cornemuse irlandaise et de whistle, de style ballade. FOLK ETHNIQUE TRADITIONNEL, INTERNATIONAL ET ETHNIQUE, MUSIQUE FOLK NATIONALE, FOLK ETHNIQUE TRADITIONNEL, INTERNATIONAL ET ETHNIQUE, MUSIQUE FOLK NATIONALE, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CORDES, BOIS, ETHNIQUE, VENT, FLUTE, FLUTE IRLANDAISE, ETHNIQUE, VENTS, ROSEAU, CORNEMUSE, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, IRLANDE, BALADE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, EPIQUE, ELEMENTS Ein balladeskes Stück mit irischem Dudelsack und Flöte. TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, NATIONAL UND ETHNISCH, NATIONALE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, NATIONAL UND ETHNISCH, NATIONALE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, HAUPTVERSION, DOKUMENTATION, BIOGRAFISCH, HISTORISCH, KÜNSTE, FILME, EPISCH, FILME, FANTASY ABENTEUER, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LANDSCHAFTEN, PANORAMA, TRAURIG, BEDRÜCKEND, TRAURIG, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), SAITENINSTRUMENTE, HOLZBLÄSER, ETHNISCH, WIND, FLÖTE, IRISCHE FLÖTE, ETHNISCH, BLASINSTRUMENTE - BLATTINSTRUMENTE, DUDELSACK, EUROPA, NORDEUROPA, IRLAND, BALLADE, BEDRUCKEND, BLASER, FLOTE, HOLZBLASER, IRISCHE FLOTE, KUNSTE, NATIONALE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, VOLKSTUMLICH wom 027 tk012 richard allen harvey sally gardens wom 027 eirinn (celtic) west one music world traditional ethnic folk national and ethnic national folk music traditional ethnic folk national and ethnic national folk music main documentary biographical historical the arts movies epic movies fantasy adventure nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama sad ballad style uilleann pipe and whistle tune. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="7489" name="Remembering Loch Glen (a)" code="TSH 042 tk064" libraryid="5" albumid="158" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_042_A_Soldier's_Story/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Trad / Barnaby J Robson" comment="Un aire sentimental et celtique pour violon et concertina." styleid="6" lengthseconds="52" time="0:52" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_042_A_Soldier's_Story/TSH042_trk064_REMEMBERING_LOCH_GLEN_(A)_Trad_Barnaby_J_Robson_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="64" tracktotal="" search="Un aire sentimental et celtique pour violon et concertina. FOLK ETHNIQUE TRADITIONNEL, INTERNATIONAL ET ETHNIQUE, MUSIQUE FOLK NATIONALE, PRINCIPAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ETHNIQUE, VIOLON, CLAVIER, ACCORDÉON, CONCERTINA, CORDES, VIOLON , EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, ÉCOSSE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ACCORDEON, ECOSSE, ELEMENTS Gefühlvolles keltisches Theme mit Violine und Konzertina. TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, NATIONAL UND ETHNISCH, NATIONALE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, HAUPTVERSION, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LÄNDLICH, LANDSCHAFT, IDYLLISCH, ZÄRTLICH, GEFÜHLVOLL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), ETHNISCH, GEIGE, KEYBOARD, AKKORDEON, KONZERTINA, SAITENINSTRUMENTE, VIOLINE, EUROPA, NORDEUROPA, SCHOTTLAND, GEFUHLVOLL, LANDLICH, NATIONALE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, VOLKSTUMLICH, ZARTLICH tsh 042 tk064 trad barnaby j robson remembering loch glen (a) tsh 042 a soldier's story the scoring house film score orchestral traditional ethnic folk national and ethnic national folk music main nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral tender sentimental tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) ethnic fiddle keyboard accordion concertina strings violin europe northern europe scotland sentimental celtic aire for violin and concertina. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" lc="24186"/>
    <item id="19285" name="Travelling Man (a)" code="WOM 252 tk005" libraryid="6" albumid="420" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_252_Indie_Folk/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Charlie Taylor / Jake Jarvis" comment="Une ballade luxuriante de grande envergure." styleid="22" lengthseconds="163" time="2:43" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_252_Indie_Folk/WOM252_trk005_TRAVELLING_MAN_(A)_Charlie_Taylor_Jake_Jarvis_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="Une ballade luxuriante de grande envergure. FOLK CONTEMPORAINE, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), FOLK ETHNIQUE TRADITIONNEL, FOLK AMÉRICAIN TRADITIONNEL, ETHNIQUE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, FORT EN ÉMOTIONS, BALADE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, CORDES, BANJO, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN NYLON, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN MÉTAL,, AMERIQUE DU NORD, FORT EN EMOTIONS, FOLK AMERICAIN TRADITIONNEL, ETATS-UNIS, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ELEMENTS, CORDES EN METAL Eine ebenso bewegende wie strahlende Ballade. ZEITGENÖSSISCHER FOLK, NORDAMERIKA, USA, HAUPTVERSION, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, TRADITIONELLER AMERIKANISCHER FOLK, ETHNISCH, FRÖHLICH, GUT GELAUNT, MITREIßEND, BALLADE, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, REISEN, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LÄNDLICH, LANDSCHAFT, IDYLLISCH, SAITENINSTRUMENTE, BANJO, SAITENINSTRUMENTE, GITARRE - AKUSTIK, NYLONSAITEN, SAITENINSTRUMENTE, GITARRE - AKUSTIK, STAHLSAITEN, FROHLICH, LANDLICH, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, VOLKSTUMLICH, ZEITGENOSSISCH, ZEITGENOSSISCHER FOLK wom 252 tk005 charlie taylor jake jarvis travelling man (a) wom 252 indie folk west one music country folk contemporary folk north america usa main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) traditional ethnic folk traditional american folk ethnic happy feel good sweeping ballad tv radio leisure lifestyle travel nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral strings banjo lush sweeping ballad. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="9024" name="Carolan's Farewell to Music" code="WOM 027 tk007" libraryid="6" albumid="188" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_027_Eirinn_(Celtic)/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Une complainte gaélique classique." styleid="17" lengthseconds="257" time="4:17" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_027_Eirinn_(Celtic)/WOM027_trk007_CAROLAN'S_FAREWELL_TO_MUSIC_Richard_Allen_Harvey_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="Une complainte gaélique classique. FOLK ETHNIQUE TRADITIONNEL, INTERNATIONAL ET ETHNIQUE, MUSIQUE FOLK NATIONALE, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), CORDES, BOIS, ETHNIQUE, VENT, FLUTE, FLUTE IRLANDAISE, ETHNIQUE, VENT, FLUTE, PENNY WHISTLE, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, IRLANDE, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), DEPRIMANT, EPIQUE, ELEMENTS Klassiches gaelisches Klagelied. TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, NATIONAL UND ETHNISCH, NATIONALE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, HAUPTVERSION, DOKUMENTATION, BIOGRAFISCH, HISTORISCH, KÜNSTE, FILME, KINDER, KINDERGESCHICHTEN, FILME, EPISCH, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LANDSCHAFTEN, PANORAMA, TRAURIG, BEDRÜCKEND, TRAURIG, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MITTELSCHNELL (MODERATO), SAITENINSTRUMENTE, HOLZBLÄSER, ETHNISCH, WIND, FLÖTE, IRISCHE FLÖTE, ETHNISCH, WIND, FLÖTE, PENNY WHISTLE, BLECHFLÖTE, EUROPA, NORDEUROPA, IRLAND, BEDRUCKEND, BLASER, BLECHFLOTE, FLOTE, HOLZBLASER, IRISCHE FLOTE, KUNSTE, NATIONALE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, VOLKSTUMLICH wom 027 tk007 richard allen harvey carolan's farewell to music wom 027 eirinn (celtic) west one music world traditional ethnic folk national and ethnic national folk music main documentary biographical historical the arts movies children storytelling movies epic nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama sad depressing sad tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) strings classic gaelic lament. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="19793" name="Mountainside (a)" code="WOM 264 tk013" libraryid="6" albumid="431" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_264_Emotive_Acoustic/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Alistair Bruce Henry Friend / Ted Brett Barnes" comment="Des cordes somptueuses et lyriques avec une guitare jouée en finger-picking complexe." styleid="12" lengthseconds="155" time="2:35" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_264_Emotive_Acoustic/WOM264_trk013_MOUNTAINSIDE_(A)_Alistair_Bruce_Henry_Friend_Ted_Brett_Barnes_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="13" tracktotal="" search="Des cordes somptueuses et lyriques avec une guitare jouée en finger-picking complexe. BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, MUSIQUE DE CHAMBRE, ENSEMBLE CLASSIQUE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), FOLK CONTEMPORAINE, PAISIBLE, LYRIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MÉLODIQUE, LYRIQUE, PINCÉ, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, SOLEIL, CHALEUR,, MELODIQUE, PINCE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ELEMENTS, METEO, ETE In großen Gefühlen schwelgende Streicher mit raffinierter gezupfter Akustikgitarre. FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, IDYLLISCH, KLASSISCH &amp; SEMIKLASSISCH, KAMMERMUSIK, KLASSISCHES ENSEMBLE, HAUPTVERSION, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), ZEITGENÖSSISCHER FOLK, FRIEDLICH, SCHWÄRMERISCH, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, TREIBEND, MELODISCH, SCHWÄRMERISCH, GEZUPFT, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, ESSEN, FREIZEIT, HEIM, GARTEN, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, REISEN, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, SONNE, TROPISCH, KÜSTENLANDSCHAFT, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LÄNDLICH, LANDSCHAFT, IDYLLISCH, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, WETTER, SONNE, HITZE, KUSTENLANDSCHAFT, LANDLICH, SCHWARMERISCH, ZEITGENOSSISCH, ZEITGENOSSISCHER FOLK wom 264 tk013 alistair bruce henry friend ted brett barnes mountainside (a) wom 264 emotive acoustic west one music acoustic film score orchestral pastoral classical and semi classical chamber music classical ensemble main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) contemporary folk peaceful lyrical movement rhythmic driving melodic lyrical picked tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden tv radio sumptuous lyrical strings with intricate finger-picked guitar. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="9019" name="Carolan's Receipt" code="WOM 027 tk002" libraryid="6" albumid="188" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_027_Eirinn_(Celtic)/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Un slow irlandais robuste et joyeux avec une mélodie de whistle et de violon." styleid="17" lengthseconds="85" time="1:25" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_027_Eirinn_(Celtic)/WOM027_trk002_CAROLAN'S_RECEIPT_Richard_Allen_Harvey_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="Un slow irlandais robuste et joyeux avec une mélodie de whistle et de violon. FOLK ETHNIQUE TRADITIONNEL, INTERNATIONAL ET ETHNIQUE, DANSE FOLK NATIONALE, FOLK ETHNIQUE TRADITIONNEL, INTERNATIONAL ET ETHNIQUE, DANSE FOLK NATIONALE, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, HEUREUX, JOYEUX, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CORDES, BOIS, ETHNIQUE, VENT, FLUTE, FLUTE IRLANDAISE, ETHNIQUE, VENT, FLUTE, PENNY WHISTLE, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, IRLANDE, ELEMENTS Feierlicher irischer Tanz mit gemächlichem Tempo, Flöte und Violinen-Melodie. TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, NATIONAL UND ETHNISCH, NATIONALER VOLKSTANZ, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, NATIONAL UND ETHNISCH, NATIONALER VOLKSTANZ, HAUPTVERSION, DOKUMENTATION, BIOGRAFISCH, HISTORISCH, KÜNSTE, FILME, KINDER, KINDERGESCHICHTEN, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LANDSCHAFTEN, PANORAMA, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LÄNDLICH, LANDSCHAFT, IDYLLISCH, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MITTLERES TEMPO (ANDANTE), SAITENINSTRUMENTE, HOLZBLÄSER, ETHNISCH, WIND, FLÖTE, IRISCHE FLÖTE, ETHNISCH, WIND, FLÖTE, PENNY WHISTLE, BLECHFLÖTE, EUROPA, NORDEUROPA, IRLAND, BLASER, BLECHFLOTE, FLOTE, FROHLICH, HOLZBLASER, IRISCHE FLOTE, KUNSTE, LANDLICH, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, VOLKSTUMLICH wom 027 tk002 richard allen harvey carolan's receipt wom 027 eirinn (celtic) west one music world traditional ethnic folk national and ethnic national folk dance traditional ethnic folk national and ethnic national folk dance main documentary biographical historical the arts movies children storytelling nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife robust and cheery irish slow dance with whistle and violin melody. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="2749" name="Simple Folk (a)" code="TSH 014A tk029" libraryid="5" albumid="87" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_014A_Smile-_A_Most_Cheerful_Earful/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Brian Douglas Gulland" comment="Une gaieté insouciante et rustique." styleid="16" lengthseconds="116" time="1:56" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_014A_Smile-_A_Most_Cheerful_Earful/TSH_014A_trk029_SIMPLE_FOLK_(A)_Brian_Douglas_Gulland_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="29" tracktotal="" search="Une gaieté insouciante et rustique. ENFANTS, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, ANGLETERRE, PÉRIODE, ÈRES CULTURELLES, PÉRIODE VICTORIENNE (1837 - 1901), PÉRIODE, ÈRES CULTURELLES, PÉRIODE EDWARDIENNE (1901 - 1910), PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ENFANTS, MATERNELLE, FOLK ETHNIQUE TRADITIONNEL, INTERNATIONAL ET ETHNIQUE, DANSE FOLK NATIONALE, HEUREUX, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, IRONIQUE, TENDRE, INNOCENT, FOLK TRADITIONNEL, DANSE ETHNIQUE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, ENFANTS, MATERNELLE, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, MATERNELLE, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL,, PERIODE, ERES CULTURELLES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), PERIODE EDWARDIENNE (1901 - 1910), PERIODE VICTORIENNE (1837 - 1901), ELEMENTS Unbeschwert und das Leben auf dem Land genießend. KINDER, EUROPA, NORDEUROPA, ENGLAND, ZEITALTER, KULTURELLE EPOCHEN, VIKTORIANISCHES ZEITALTER (1837 - 1901), ZEITALTER, KULTURELLE EPOCHEN, EDWARDIANISCHES ZEITALTER (1901 - 1910), HAUPTVERSION, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), KINDER, VORSCHULE, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, NATIONAL UND ETHNISCH, NATIONALER VOLKSTANZ, FRÖHLICH, LUSTIG, KOMÖDIANTISCH, LUSTIG, IRONISCH, ZÄRTLICH, UNSCHULDIG, TRADITIONELLE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, ETHNISCHER TANZ, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, KINDER, VORSCHULE, TV, RADIO, KINDER, JUGENDPROGRAMM, VORSCHULE, DOKUMENTATION, BIOGRAFISCH, HISTORISCH, KÜNSTE, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LÄNDLICH, LANDSCHAFT, IDYLLISCH, AKTIVITATEN, FROHLICH, KOMODIANTISCH, KUNSTE, LANDLICH, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, TRADITIONELLE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, VOLKSTUMLICH, ZARTLICH tsh 014a tk029 brian douglas gulland simple folk (a) tsh 014a smile: a most cheerful earful the scoring house comedy children classical and semi classical chamber music classical ensemble europe northern europe england main tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) film score orchestral pastoral peaceful peaceful tender innocent tender nostalgic tender reflective tender romantic tender carefree rustic cheerfulness. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" lc="24186"/>
    <item id="19781" name="Southern Moon (a)" code="WOM 264 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="431" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_264_Emotive_Acoustic/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Alistair Bruce Henry Friend / Ted Brett Barnes" comment="Se frayer un chemin pour avancer. Une guitare acoustique euphorisante caressée, des flûtes douces et des cordes chaleureuses." styleid="12" lengthseconds="186" time="3:06" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_264_Emotive_Acoustic/WOM264_trk001_SOUTHERN_MOON_(A)_Alistair_Bruce_Henry_Friend_Ted_Brett_Barnes_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="Se frayer un chemin pour avancer. Une guitare acoustique euphorisante caressée, des flûtes douces et des cordes chaleureuses. BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PRINCIPAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, PAISIBLE, DÉTENDU, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, ACOUSTIQUE, RACLÉ, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN NYLON, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN MÉTAL, RACLE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETENDU, ELEMENTS, CORDES EN METAL Auf dem Weg in eine bessere Zukunft. Aufmunternde Akustikgitarre im Zusammenspiel mit sanften Flöten und warmen Streichern. FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, IDYLLISCH, HAUPTVERSION, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LÄNDLICH, LANDSCHAFT, IDYLLISCH, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, ESSEN, FREIZEIT, HEIM, GARTEN, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, REISEN, TV, RADIO, SPORT, FRÖHLICH, GUT GELAUNT, FRIEDLICH, ZUFRIEDEN, FRIEDLICH, ENTSPANNT, ZÄRTLICH, WARM, BEFLÜGELND, BEFLÜGELND, AKUSTISCH, ANSCHLAGEN, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), SAITENINSTRUMENTE, GITARRE - AKUSTIK, NYLONSAITEN, SAITENINSTRUMENTE, GITARRE - AKUSTIK, STAHLSAITEN, BEFLUGELND, FROHLICH, LANDLICH, ZARTLICH wom 264 tk001 alistair bruce henry friend ted brett barnes southern moon (a) wom 264 emotive acoustic west one music acoustic film score orchestral pastoral main nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio sports happy feel good peaceful contented peaceful relaxed tender warm finding a way forward. uplifting strummed acoustic guitar gentle flutes and warm strings. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="9018" name="Song of Old" code="WOM 027 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="188" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_027_Eirinn_(Celtic)/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Une vieux morceau folk anglais arrangé dans le style celtique et joué par un feadóg." styleid="17" lengthseconds="196" time="3:16" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_027_Eirinn_(Celtic)/WOM027_trk001_SONG_OF_OLD_Richard_Allen_Harvey_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="Une vieux morceau folk anglais arrangé dans le style celtique et joué par un feadóg. FOLK ETHNIQUE TRADITIONNEL, INTERNATIONAL ET ETHNIQUE, MUSIQUE FOLK NATIONALE, FOLK ETHNIQUE TRADITIONNEL, INTERNATIONAL ET ETHNIQUE, MUSIQUE FOLK NATIONALE, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, COMÉDIE ROMANTIQUE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CORDES, BOIS, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, IRLANDE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), EPIQUE, COMEDIE, COMEDIE ROMANTIQUE, ELEMENTS Im keltischen Stil arrangiertes, altes englisches Volkslied mit irischer Flöte. TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, NATIONAL UND ETHNISCH, NATIONALE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, NATIONAL UND ETHNISCH, NATIONALE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, HAUPTVERSION, DOKUMENTATION, BIOGRAFISCH, HISTORISCH, KÜNSTE, FILME, EPISCH, FILME, ROMANTISCHE KOMÖDIE, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LANDSCHAFTEN, PANORAMA, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LÄNDLICH, LANDSCHAFT, IDYLLISCH, ZÄRTLICH, WEHMÜTIG, ZÄRTLICH, NACHDENKLICH, ZÄRTLICH, GEFÜHLVOLL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), SAITENINSTRUMENTE, HOLZBLÄSER, EUROPA, NORDEUROPA, IRLAND, BLASER, GEFUHLVOLL, HOLZBLASER, KUNSTE, LANDLICH, NATIONALE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, ROMANTISCHE KOMODIE, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, VOLKSTUMLICH, WEHMUTIG, ZARTLICH wom 027 tk001 richard allen harvey song of old wom 027 eirinn (celtic) west one music world traditional ethnic folk national and ethnic national folk music traditional ethnic folk national and ethnic national folk music main documentary biographical historical the arts movies epic movies romantic comedy nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature old english folk song arranged in celtic style and performed on an irish whistle. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="4290" name="Sunset Dreamer (b)" code="TSH 043 tk006" libraryid="5" albumid="113" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_043_An_American_Journey/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Clive Michael Oliver Carroll" comment="Un morceau détendu pour planter le décor, avec du violon solo." styleid="22" lengthseconds="59" time="0:59" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_043_An_American_Journey/TSH043_trk006_SUNSET_DREAMER_(B)_Clive_Michael_Oliver_Carroll_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="6" tracktotal="" search="Un morceau détendu pour planter le décor, avec du violon solo. FOLK ETHNIQUE TRADITIONNEL, INTERNATIONAL ET ETHNIQUE, MUSIQUE FOLK NATIONALE, ALTERNATIF, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, HIVER, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ETHNIQUE, VIOLON, CORDES, VIOLE, CORDES, VIOLON , EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, IRLANDE, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, ÉCOSSE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, ECOSSE, ELEMENTS Entspannte und ruhige Atmosphäre der Weite mit Violine. TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, NATIONAL UND ETHNISCH, NATIONALE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, ALTERNATIVE, DOKUMENTATION, BIOGRAFISCH, HISTORISCH, KÜNSTE, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LANDSCHAFTEN, PANORAMA, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, JAHRESZEITEN, ZEIT, WINTER, TRAURIG, BEDRÜCKEND, TRAURIG, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), ETHNISCH, GEIGE, SAITENINSTRUMENTE, VIOLA, SAITENINSTRUMENTE, VIOLINE, EUROPA, NORDEUROPA, IRLAND, EUROPA, NORDEUROPA, SCHOTTLAND, BEDRUCKEND, KUNSTE, NATIONALE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, VOLKSTUMLICH tsh 043 tk006 clive michael oliver carroll sunset dreamer (b) tsh 043 an american journey the scoring house country folk traditional ethnic folk national and ethnic national folk music alternate documentary biographical historical the arts nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife the elements seasons time winter sad depressing sad tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) laid back gentle scene-setter for solo violin. alternative" waveformpath="" version="Alternative" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" lc="24186"/>
    <item id="4289" name="Sunset Dreamer (a)" code="TSH 043 tk005" libraryid="5" albumid="113" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_043_An_American_Journey/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Clive Michael Oliver Carroll" comment="Un morceau détendu pour planter le décor, avec du violon et de la guitare." styleid="22" lengthseconds="242" time="4:02" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_043_An_American_Journey/TSH043_trk005_SUNSET_DREAMER_(A)_Clive_Michael_Oliver_Carroll_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="Un morceau détendu pour planter le décor, avec du violon et de la guitare. COUNTRY, BLUEGRASS, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PAISIBLE, REVEUR, TENDRE, SONGEUR, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, CHAUD, DÉSERT, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, ETHNIQUE, VIOLON, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN NYLON, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN MÉTAL,, AMERIQUE DU NORD, ETATS-UNIS, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ELEMENTS, CORDES EN METAL, DESERT Entspannte und ruhige Atmosphäre der Weite mit Violine und Gitarre. COUNTRY, BLUEGRASS, NORDAMERIKA, USA, HAUPTVERSION, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), FRIEDLICH, VERTRÄUMT, ZÄRTLICH, NACHDENKLICH, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, UHRENARTIG, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, REISEN, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, HEIß, WÜSTE, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LÄNDLICH, LANDSCHAFT, IDYLLISCH, ETHNISCH, GEIGE, SAITENINSTRUMENTE, GITARRE - AKUSTIK, NYLONSAITEN, SAITENINSTRUMENTE, GITARRE - AKUSTIK, STAHLSAITEN, LANDLICH, VERTRAUMT, WUSTE, ZARTLICH tsh 043 tk005 clive michael oliver carroll sunset dreamer (a) tsh 043 an american journey the scoring house country folk country bluegrass north america usa main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) peaceful dreamy tender reflective movement rhythmic clock like tv radio leisure lifestyle travel nature wildlife the elements land hot desert nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside laid back gentle scene-setter featuring violin and guitar. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" lc="24186"/>
    <item id="9521" name="Old Irish (b)" code="WOM 038 tk012" libraryid="6" albumid="199" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_038_Anthropology/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Sonia Jessica Slany" comment="Un air rythmique majestueux." styleid="17" lengthseconds="104" time="1:44" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_038_Anthropology/WOM038_trk012_OLD_IRISH_(B)_Sonia_Jessica_Slany_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="Un air rythmique majestueux. ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, FOLK ETHNIQUE TRADITIONNEL, INTERNATIONAL ET ETHNIQUE, MUSIQUE FOLK NATIONALE, ALTERNATIF, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CORDES, BOIS, ETHNIQUE, VIOLON, ETHNIQUE, VENT, FLUTE, FLUTE IRLANDAISE, ETHNIQUE, VENTS, ROSEAU, CORNEMUSE, CORDES, VIOLON , EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, IRLANDE, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, ELEMENTS Rhythmisches und würdevolles Theme. SOUNDELEMENTE, ATMOSPHÄREN, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, NATIONAL UND ETHNISCH, NATIONALE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, ALTERNATIVE, DOKUMENTATION, BIOGRAFISCH, HISTORISCH, KÜNSTE, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LANDSCHAFTEN, PANORAMA, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, REISEN, TRAURIG, BEDRÜCKEND, EINSAM, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), SAITENINSTRUMENTE, HOLZBLÄSER, ETHNISCH, GEIGE, ETHNISCH, WIND, FLÖTE, IRISCHE FLÖTE, ETHNISCH, BLASINSTRUMENTE - BLATTINSTRUMENTE, DUDELSACK, SAITENINSTRUMENTE, VIOLINE, EUROPA, NORDEUROPA, IRLAND, ATMOSPHAREN, BEDRUCKEND, BLASER, FLOTE, HOLZBLASER, IRISCHE FLOTE, KUNSTE, NATIONALE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, VOLKSTUMLICH wom 038 tk012 sonia jessica slany old irish (b) wom 038 anthropology west one music world sound elements atmospheres traditional ethnic folk national and ethnic national folk music alternate documentary biographical historical the arts nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama tv radio leisure lifestyle travel sad depressing lonely tempo rhythmic stately air. alternative" waveformpath="" version="Alternative" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="9520" name="Old Irish (a)" code="WOM 038 tk011" libraryid="6" albumid="199" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_038_Anthropology/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Sonia Jessica Slany" comment="Un air de violon esseulé, cornemuse et whistle." styleid="17" lengthseconds="116" time="1:56" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_038_Anthropology/WOM038_trk011_OLD_IRISH_(A)_Sonia_Jessica_Slany_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="11" tracktotal="" search="Un air de violon esseulé, cornemuse et whistle. ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, FOLK ETHNIQUE TRADITIONNEL, INTERNATIONAL ET ETHNIQUE, MUSIQUE FOLK NATIONALE, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CORDES, BOIS, ETHNIQUE, VIOLON, ETHNIQUE, VENT, FLUTE, FLUTE IRLANDAISE, ETHNIQUE, VENTS, ROSEAU, CORNEMUSE, CORDES, VIOLON , EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, IRLANDE, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, ELEMENTS Lied der Einsamkeit mit Violine, Pfeife und Dudelsack. SOUNDELEMENTE, ATMOSPHÄREN, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, NATIONAL UND ETHNISCH, NATIONALE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, HAUPTVERSION, DOKUMENTATION, BIOGRAFISCH, HISTORISCH, KÜNSTE, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LANDSCHAFTEN, PANORAMA, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, REISEN, TRAURIG, BEDRÜCKEND, EINSAM, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), SAITENINSTRUMENTE, HOLZBLÄSER, ETHNISCH, GEIGE, ETHNISCH, WIND, FLÖTE, IRISCHE FLÖTE, ETHNISCH, BLASINSTRUMENTE - BLATTINSTRUMENTE, DUDELSACK, SAITENINSTRUMENTE, VIOLINE, EUROPA, NORDEUROPA, IRLAND, ATMOSPHAREN, BEDRUCKEND, BLASER, FLOTE, HOLZBLASER, IRISCHE FLOTE, KUNSTE, NATIONALE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, VOLKSTUMLICH wom 038 tk011 sonia jessica slany old irish (a) wom 038 anthropology west one music world sound elements atmospheres traditional ethnic folk national and ethnic national folk music main documentary biographical historical the arts nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama tv radio leisure lifestyle travel sad depressing lonely tempo lonely violin pipe and whistle air. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="9021" name="Carrick Fergus" code="WOM 027 tk004" libraryid="6" albumid="188" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_027_Eirinn_(Celtic)/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Des cordes réfléctives et élégantes, de la harpe et du whistle. La seconde section inclue de la cornemuse irlandaise." styleid="17" lengthseconds="240" time="4:00" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_027_Eirinn_(Celtic)/WOM027_trk004_CARRICK_FERGUS_Richard_Allen_Harvey_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="Des cordes réfléctives et élégantes, de la harpe et du whistle. La seconde section inclue de la cornemuse irlandaise. FOLK ETHNIQUE TRADITIONNEL, INTERNATIONAL ET ETHNIQUE, MUSIQUE FOLK NATIONALE, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, IRLANDE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), FOLK ETHNIQUE TRADITIONNEL, INTERNATIONAL ET ETHNIQUE, MUSIQUE FOLK NATIONALE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, ETHNIQUE, VENT, FLUTE, FLUTE IRLANDAISE, ETHNIQUE, VENT, FLUTE, PENNY WHISTLE,, ELEGANT Theme mit nachdenklichen und sanften Streichern, Harfe und Flöte, sowie irischem Dudelsack im zweiten Abschnitt. TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, NATIONAL UND ETHNISCH, NATIONALE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, EUROPA, NORDEUROPA, IRLAND, HAUPTVERSION, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MITTLERES TEMPO (ANDANTE), TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, NATIONAL UND ETHNISCH, NATIONALE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, ZÄRTLICH, NACHDENKLICH, BEWEGUNG, SMOOTH, ELEGANT, DOKUMENTATION, BIOGRAFISCH, HISTORISCH, KÜNSTE, ETHNISCH, WIND, FLÖTE, IRISCHE FLÖTE, ETHNISCH, WIND, FLÖTE, PENNY WHISTLE, BLECHFLÖTE, BLECHFLOTE, FLOTE, IRISCHE FLOTE, KUNSTE, NATIONALE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, VOLKSTUMLICH, ZARTLICH wom 027 tk004 richard allen harvey carrick fergus wom 027 eirinn (celtic) west one music world traditional ethnic folk national and ethnic national folk music europe northern europe ireland main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) traditional ethnic folk national and ethnic national folk music tender reflective movement smooth elegant documentary biographical historical reflective and elegant strings harp and whistle. second section features uilleann pipes. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="2843" name="Lost in Time (b)" code="TSH 015 tk009" libraryid="5" albumid="89" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_015_The_World_in_a_Voice/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Miriam Arlene Stockley / David Richard Mindel" comment="Air nostalgique et émouvant, avec une flûte à bec sopranino et fausset." styleid="17" lengthseconds="197" time="3:17" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_015_The_World_in_a_Voice/TSH015_trk009_LOST_IN_TIME_(B)_Miriam_Arlene_Stockley_David_Richard_Mindel_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="Air nostalgique et émouvant, avec une flûte à bec sopranino et fausset. ENFANTS, CONTES, ENFANTS, FOLK ETHNIQUE TRADITIONNEL, INTERNATIONAL ET ETHNIQUE, MUSIQUE FOLK NATIONALE, ALTERNATIF, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, SÉRIEUX, ÉMOUVANT, TENDRE, INNOCENT, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BOIS, FLUTE A BEC, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, ANGLETERRE, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, IRLANDE, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), EMOUVANT Emotionaler Song voller Wehmut und mit Sopran- sowie Sopraninoblockflöte. KINDER, KINDERGESCHICHTEN, KINDER, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, NATIONAL UND ETHNISCH, NATIONALE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, ALTERNATIVE, FILME, KINDER, KINDERGESCHICHTEN, ERNST, EMOTIONAL, ZÄRTLICH, UNSCHULDIG, ZÄRTLICH, WEHMÜTIG, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), HOLZBLASINSTRUMENTE, BLOCKFLÖTE, EUROPA, NORDEUROPA, ENGLAND, EUROPA, NORDEUROPA, IRLAND, BLOCKFLOTE, FLOTE, NATIONALE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, VOLKSTUMLICH, WEHMUTIG, ZARTLICH tsh 015 tk009 miriam arlene stockley david richard mindel lost in time (b) tsh 015 the world in a voice the scoring house world children storytelling children traditional ethnic folk national and ethnic national folk music alternate movies children storytelling serious emotional tender innocent tender nostalgic tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) woodwinds recorder europe northern europe england europe nostalgic emotional song featuring treble and sopranino recorder. instrumental" waveformpath="" version="Instrumental" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" lc="24186"/>
    <item id="9031" name="Bridget Cruise" code="WOM 027 tk014" libraryid="6" albumid="188" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_027_Eirinn_(Celtic)/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Un morceau orchestral romantique et de grande envergure." styleid="17" lengthseconds="184" time="3:04" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_027_Eirinn_(Celtic)/WOM027_trk014_BRIDGET_CRUISE_Richard_Allen_Harvey_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="14" tracktotal="" search="Un morceau orchestral romantique et de grande envergure. BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, FORT EN ÉMOTIONS, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, CORDES, BOIS, ETHNIQUE, VENT, FLUTE, FLUTE IRLANDAISE, ETHNIQUE, VENT, FLUTE, PENNY WHISTLE, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, IRLANDE, FORT EN EMOTIONS, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ELEMENTS Ein romantisches und andächtiges Stück für Orchester. FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, IDYLLISCH, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, IDYLLISCH, HAUPTVERSION, DOKUMENTATION, BIOGRAFISCH, HISTORISCH, KÜNSTE, FILME, KINDER, KINDERGESCHICHTEN, FILME, FANTASY ABENTEUER, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LÄNDLICH, LANDSCHAFT, IDYLLISCH, ZÄRTLICH, ROMANTISCH, MITREIßEND, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), KLASSISCH &amp; SEMIKLASSISCH, SINFONIEORCHESTER, SAITENINSTRUMENTE, HOLZBLÄSER, ETHNISCH, WIND, FLÖTE, IRISCHE FLÖTE, ETHNISCH, WIND, FLÖTE, PENNY WHISTLE, BLECHFLÖTE, EUROPA, NORDEUROPA, IRLAND, BLASER, BLECHFLOTE, FLOTE, HOLZBLASER, IRISCHE FLOTE, KUNSTE, LANDLICH, ZARTLICH wom 027 tk014 richard allen harvey bridget cruise wom 027 eirinn (celtic) west one music world film score orchestral pastoral film score orchestral pastoral main documentary biographical historical the arts movies children storytelling movies fantasy adventure nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral tender romantic sweeping tempo romantic sweeping orchestral tune. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="11135" name="Meadow Lands" code="WOM 067 tk015" libraryid="6" albumid="227" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_067_Simple_Strings/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Patrick Thomas Hawes" comment="Un violon au son folk se greffe sur une simple mélodie de cordes de chambre." styleid="23" lengthseconds="146" time="2:26" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_067_Simple_Strings/WOM067_trk015_MEADOW_LANDS_Patrick_Thomas_Hawes_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="15" tracktotal="" search="Un violon au son folk se greffe sur une simple mélodie de cordes de chambre. CLASSIQUE, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, MUSIQUE DE CHAMBRE, ENSEMBLE CLASSIQUE, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, ANGLETERRE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, SÉRIEUX, DIGNE, ABSTRAIT, SIMPLE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, ART, ANTIQUITÉS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, CORDES, VIOLON ,, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ELEMENTS, ANTIQUITES Schlichte Kammermusik-Streicher werden von einer folkloristischen Violine geführt. KLASSISCH, KLASSISCH &amp; SEMIKLASSISCH, KAMMERMUSIK, KLASSISCHES ENSEMBLE, EUROPA, NORDEUROPA, ENGLAND, HAUPTVERSION, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, IDYLLISCH, ERNST, WÜRDEVOLL, ABSTRAKT, SCHLICHT, BEWEGUNG, SMOOTH, FLIEßEN, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, KUNST, ANTIQUITÄTEN, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LÄNDLICH, LANDSCHAFT, IDYLLISCH, SAITENINSTRUMENTE, VIOLINE, ANTIQUITATEN, LANDLICH, WURDEVOLL wom 067 tk015 patrick thomas hawes meadow lands wom 067 simple strings west one music drama classical classical and semi classical chamber music classical ensemble europe northern europe england main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) film score orchestral pastoral serious dignified abstract simple movement smooth flowing tv radio leisure lifestyle arts antiques folk-like violin joining simple chamber string melody. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="2770" name="Happy Street (a) (60)" code="TSH 014A tk050" libraryid="5" albumid="87" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_014A_Smile-_A_Most_Cheerful_Earful/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Graham Donald Harry Preskett" comment="Des journées pleines de fun." styleid="16" lengthseconds="62" time="1:02" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_014A_Smile-_A_Most_Cheerful_Earful/TSH_014A_trk050_HAPPY_STREET_(A)_(60)_Graham_Donald_Harry_Preskett_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="50" tracktotal="" search="Des journées pleines de fun. ENFANTS, PRINCIPAL, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, FUN, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, ENJOUÉ, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, OCCUPÉ, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ENJOUE, OCCUPE, JOURNEE Ein schöner Tag voll Freude, Spaß und Unterhaltung KINDER, HAUPTVERSION, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, ESSEN, FREIZEIT, HEIM, GARTEN, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, REISEN, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, UNTERHALTUNG, DAYTIME - TV, FRÖHLICH, GUT GELAUNT, FRÖHLICH, SPAß, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, VERSPIELT, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, GESCHÄFTIG, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), FROHLICH, GESCHAFTIG tsh 014a tk050 graham donald harry preskett happy street (a) (60) tsh 014a smile: a most cheerful earful the scoring house comedy blues alternate movies comedy tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio sitcom tv radio talkshow entertainment daytime funny comedic funny humorous funny wry happy playful peaceful contented tempo fun filled fun days. 60 second" waveformpath="" version="60 Second" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" lc="24186"/>
    <item id="793" name="Celtic Knights (a)" code="FEM 020 tk007" libraryid="2" albumid="24" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_020_Legends_of_Time/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="John David Buckley" comment="Action aventure familiale qui en met plein les yeux. Réchauffe le coeur, victorieux, avec un rythme cadencé." styleid="2" lengthseconds="105" time="1:45" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_020_Legends_of_Time/FEM_020_trk007_CELTIC_KNIGHTS_(A)_John_David_Buckley_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="Action aventure familiale qui en met plein les yeux. Réchauffe le coeur, victorieux, avec un rythme cadencé. BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, CUIVRES, SECTION DE CUIVRES, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, GROUPES VOCAUX, CHOEUR, CHOEURS MIXTES, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, IRLANDE, IRLANDE, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, ÉCOSSE, PRINCIPAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, DRAMATIQUE, PASSIONNÉ, SÉRIEUX, DIGNE, SÉRIEUX, ÉMOUVANT, SÉRIEUX, NOBLE, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, ÉPIQUE, FORT, HÉROIQUE, FORT, MAJESTUEUX, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, FORT, FORT, FORT, TRIOMPHAL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, FIER, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, JAILLIR, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, SYNCOPÉ, PERCUSSIF, SUPERHÉROS, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, NAVIGATION, PIRATES, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, FAMILIAL, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, SERIEUX, SUPERHEROS, PASSIONNE, EMOUVANT, EPIQUE, HEROIQUE, IRREGULIER, ECOSSE, SYNCOPE Pure Familienunterhaltung mit einem optimistischen, siegesgewissen Feeling.  FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BLÄSER, BLÄSERSEKTION, SAITENINSTRUMENTE, STREICHERSEKTION, GESANGSFORMATIONEN, CHOR, GEMISCHTER CHOR, EUROPA, NORDEUROPA, IRLAND, IRLAND, EUROPA, NORDEUROPA, SCHOTTLAND, HAUPTVERSION, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMA, DRAMATISCH, INTENSIV, DRAMATISCH, LEIDENSCHAFTLICH, ERNST, WÜRDEVOLL, ERNST, EMOTIONAL, ERNST, VORNEHM, ERNST, ERNST, KRÄFTIG, ZUVERSICHTLICH, KRÄFTIG, EPISCH, KRÄFTIG, HEROISCH, KRÄFTIG, MAJESTÄTISCH, KRÄFTIG, PRESTIGETRÄCHTIG, KRÄFTIG, KRÄFTIG, KRÄFTIG, TRIUMPHIEREND, BEFLÜGELND, STOLZ, BEFLÜGELND, EMPORSTEIGEND, BEWEGUNG, UNGLEICHMÄßIG, SYNKOPIERT, PERKUSSIV, SUPERHELD, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, SEEFAHRT, PIRATEN, FILME, ACTION ABENTEUER, FILME, EPISCH, FILME, FAMILIE, TRAILER, TRAILER TRACK, AKTIVITATEN, BEFLUGELND, BLASER, BLASERSEKTION, KRAFTIG, MAJESTATISCH, PRESTIGETRACHTIG, UNGLEICHMASZIG, WURDEVOLL fem 020 tk007 john david buckley celtic knights (a) fem 020 legends of time fired earth music trailer film score orchestral trailer brass brass section strings string section vocal groupings chorus mixed chorus europe northern europe ireland republic of ireland europe northern europe scotland main film score orchestral panoramic dramatic intense dramatic passionate serious pure family cinematic action adventure. heartwarming and victorious with a marching rhythm. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284" lc="23000"/>
    <item id="9020" name="The Blackbird" code="WOM 027 tk003" libraryid="6" albumid="188" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_027_Eirinn_(Celtic)/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Des cordes douces et atmosphérique, de la harpe et du whistle." styleid="17" lengthseconds="201" time="3:21" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_027_Eirinn_(Celtic)/WOM027_trk003_THE_BLACKBIRD_Richard_Allen_Harvey_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="Des cordes douces et atmosphérique, de la harpe et du whistle. FOLK ETHNIQUE TRADITIONNEL, INTERNATIONAL ET ETHNIQUE, MUSIQUE FOLK NATIONALE, FOLK ETHNIQUE TRADITIONNEL, INTERNATIONAL ET ETHNIQUE, MUSIQUE FOLK NATIONALE, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, TENDRE, MIGNON, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CORDES, BOIS, ETHNIQUE, VENT, FLUTE, PENNY WHISTLE, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, IRLANDE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ELEMENTS Zarte und atmosphärische Streicher im Zusammenspiel mit Harfe und Flöte. TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, NATIONAL UND ETHNISCH, NATIONALE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, NATIONAL UND ETHNISCH, NATIONALE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, HAUPTVERSION, DOKUMENTATION, BIOGRAFISCH, HISTORISCH, KÜNSTE, FILME, KINDER, KINDERGESCHICHTEN, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LANDSCHAFTEN, PANORAMA, ZÄRTLICH, SÜß, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), SAITENINSTRUMENTE, HOLZBLÄSER, ETHNISCH, WIND, FLÖTE, PENNY WHISTLE, BLECHFLÖTE, EUROPA, NORDEUROPA, IRLAND, BLASER, BLECHFLOTE, FLOTE, HOLZBLASER, KUNSTE, NATIONALE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, SUSZ, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, VOLKSTUMLICH, ZARTLICH wom 027 tk003 richard allen harvey the blackbird wom 027 eirinn (celtic) west one music world traditional ethnic folk national and ethnic national folk music traditional ethnic folk national and ethnic national folk music main documentary biographical historical the arts movies children storytelling nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama tender sweet gentle and atmospheric strings harp and whistle. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="19281" name="Morning Star (a)" code="WOM 252 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="420" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_252_Indie_Folk/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Charlie Taylor / Jake Jarvis" comment="Une progression lente vers des refrains euphoriques." styleid="22" lengthseconds="200" time="3:20" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_252_Indie_Folk/WOM252_trk001_MORNING_STAR_(A)_Charlie_Taylor_Jake_Jarvis_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="Une progression lente vers des refrains euphoriques. BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), FOLK CONTEMPORAINE, FOLK ETHNIQUE TRADITIONNEL, FOLK AMÉRICAIN TRADITIONNEL, ETHNIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, EVOLUTIF, FILMS, ROAD MOVIE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, SOLEIL, CHALEUR,, AMERIQUE DU NORD, FOLK AMERICAIN TRADITIONNEL, ETATS-UNIS, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ELEMENTS, METEO, ETE, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Mit einer langsamen Steigerung wird zu dem euphorischen Chorus hingeführt. FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, NORDAMERIKA, USA, HAUPTVERSION, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), ZEITGENÖSSISCHER FOLK, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, TRADITIONELLER AMERIKANISCHER FOLK, ETHNISCH, BEFLÜGELND, EUPHORISCH, FRÖHLICH, GUT GELAUNT, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, AUFBAUEND, FILME, ROAD MOVIE, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, REISEN, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, SONNE, TROPISCH, KÜSTENLANDSCHAFT, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LÄNDLICH, LANDSCHAFT, IDYLLISCH, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, WETTER, SONNE, HITZE, BEFLUGELND, FROHLICH, KUSTENLANDSCHAFT, LANDLICH, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, VOLKSTUMLICH, ZEITGENOSSISCH, ZEITGENOSSISCHER FOLK wom 252 tk001 charlie taylor jake jarvis morning star (a) wom 252 indie folk west one music country folk film score orchestral trailer north america usa main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) contemporary folk traditional ethnic folk traditional american folk ethnic uplifting euphoric happy feel good happy happy building movies road movie tv radio leisure lifestyle travel nature slowly building to euphoric choruses. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="2850" name="A Distant Shore (b)" code="TSH 015 tk016" libraryid="5" albumid="89" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_015_The_World_in_a_Voice/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Miriam Arlene Stockley / David Richard Mindel" comment="Un refrain celtique évocateur et chaleureux avec un psaltérion, des whistles et des flûtes à bec." styleid="17" lengthseconds="126" time="2:06" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_015_The_World_in_a_Voice/TSH015_trk016_A_DISTANT_SHORE_(B)_Miriam_Arlene_Stockley_David_Richard_Mindel_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="16" tracktotal="" search="Un refrain celtique évocateur et chaleureux avec un psaltérion, des whistles et des flûtes à bec. FOLK ETHNIQUE TRADITIONNEL, INTERNATIONAL ET ETHNIQUE, MUSIQUE FOLK NATIONALE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, ALTERNATIF, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, OCCASIONS SPÉCIALES, VACANCES, ST PATRICK, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, IRLANDE, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, ÉCOSSE, OCCASIONS SPECIALES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, ECOSSE, ELEMENTS Ein warmes und atmosphärisches keltisches Theme mit Psalter und Flöten. TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, NATIONAL UND ETHNISCH, NATIONALE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, IDYLLISCH, ALTERNATIVE, DOKUMENTATION, BIOGRAFISCH, HISTORISCH, KÜNSTE, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LÄNDLICH, LANDSCHAFT, IDYLLISCH, BESONDERE ANLÄSSE, FEIERTAGE, ST. PATRICK'S DAY, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, REISEN, TRAURIG, BEDRÜCKEND, TRAURIG, ZÄRTLICH, GEFÜHLVOLL, ZÄRTLICH, WARM, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), EUROPA, NORDEUROPA, IRLAND, EUROPA, NORDEUROPA, SCHOTTLAND, BEDRUCKEND, BESONDERE ANLASSE, GEFUHLVOLL, KUNSTE, LANDLICH, NATIONALE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, VOLKSTUMLICH, ZARTLICH tsh 015 tk016 miriam arlene stockley david richard mindel a distant shore (b) tsh 015 the world in a voice the scoring house world traditional ethnic folk national and ethnic national folk music film score orchestral pastoral alternate documentary biographical historical the arts nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral special occasions holidays st. patrick's day tv radio leisure warm evocative celtic refrain featuring psaltery whistles and recorders. instrumental" waveformpath="" version="Instrumental" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" lc="24186"/>
    <item id="3308" name="The Journey Begins (b)" code="TSH 022 tk007" libraryid="5" albumid="97" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_022_Human_Stories/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Michael Price / Laurence Love Greed" comment="Un whistle celtique clair et expressif." styleid="15" lengthseconds="62" time="1:02" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_022_Human_Stories/TSH022_trk007_THE_JOURNEY_BEGINS_(B)_Michael_Price_Laurence_Love_Greed_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="Un whistle celtique clair et expressif. WORLD BEAT, STYLES ETHNIQUES, GLOBAL, FOLK ETHNIQUE TRADITIONNEL, INTERNATIONAL ET ETHNIQUE, MUSIQUE FOLK NATIONALE, ALTERNATIF, DOCUMENTAIRE, PAISIBLE, SEREIN, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ETHNIQUE, VENT, FLUTE, FLUTE IRLANDAISE, ETHNIQUE, VENT, FLUTE, SIFFLET DIPHONIQUE, BOIS, FLUTE, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, IRLANDE, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, ÉCOSSE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ECOSSE Eine luftige und ausdruckstarke Celtic Whistle. WORLD BEAT, ETHNISCHE INTERPRETATIONEN, GLOBAL, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, NATIONAL UND ETHNISCH, NATIONALE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, ALTERNATIVE, DOKUMENTATION, FRIEDLICH, GELASSEN, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), ETHNISCH, WIND, FLÖTE, IRISCHE FLÖTE, ETHNISCH, WIND, FLÖTE, OVERTON FLÖTE, HOLZBLASINSTRUMENTE, FLÖTE, EUROPA, NORDEUROPA, IRLAND, EUROPA, NORDEUROPA, SCHOTTLAND, FLOTE, IRISCHE FLOTE, NATIONALE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, OVERTON FLOTE, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, VOLKSTUMLICH tsh 022 tk007 michael price laurence love greed the journey begins (b) tsh 022 human stories the scoring house documentary world beat ethnic stylings global traditional ethnic folk national and ethnic national folk music alternate documentary peaceful serene tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) ethnic wind flute irish flute ethnic wind flute overton whistle woodwinds flute europe northern europe airy expressive celtic whistle. alternative" waveformpath="" version="Alternative" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" lc="24186"/>
    <item id="9022" name="Carolan's Favourite" code="WOM 027 tk005" libraryid="6" albumid="188" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_027_Eirinn_(Celtic)/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Un medley de gigues orchestrales animées croissant sur le tempo." styleid="17" lengthseconds="215" time="3:35" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_027_Eirinn_(Celtic)/WOM027_trk005_CAROLAN'S_FAVOURITE_Richard_Allen_Harvey_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="Un medley de gigues orchestrales animées croissant sur le tempo. FOLK ETHNIQUE TRADITIONNEL, INTERNATIONAL ET ETHNIQUE, DANSE FOLK NATIONALE, FOLK ETHNIQUE TRADITIONNEL, INTERNATIONAL ET ETHNIQUE, DANSE FOLK NATIONALE, FOLK ETHNIQUE TRADITIONNEL, INTERNATIONAL ET ETHNIQUE, MUSIQUE FOLK NATIONALE, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, HEUREUX, JOYEUX, HEUREUX, ENJOUÉ, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CORDES, BOIS, ETHNIQUE, VENT, FLUTE, FLUTE IRLANDAISE, ETHNIQUE, VENT, FLUTE, PENNY WHISTLE, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, IRLANDE, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, ÉCOSSE, ENJOUE, ECOSSE, ELEMENTS Medley von orchestralen Motiven, die sich im Tempo steigern. TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, NATIONAL UND ETHNISCH, NATIONALER VOLKSTANZ, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, NATIONAL UND ETHNISCH, NATIONALER VOLKSTANZ, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, NATIONAL UND ETHNISCH, NATIONALE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, HAUPTVERSION, DOKUMENTATION, BIOGRAFISCH, HISTORISCH, KÜNSTE, FILME, KINDER, KINDERGESCHICHTEN, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LÄNDLICH, LANDSCHAFT, IDYLLISCH, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MITTLERES TEMPO (ANDANTE), SAITENINSTRUMENTE, HOLZBLÄSER, ETHNISCH, WIND, FLÖTE, IRISCHE FLÖTE, ETHNISCH, WIND, FLÖTE, PENNY WHISTLE, BLECHFLÖTE, EUROPA, NORDEUROPA, IRLAND, EUROPA, NORDEUROPA, SCHOTTLAND, BLASER, BLECHFLOTE, FLOTE, FROHLICH, HOLZBLASER, IRISCHE FLOTE, KUNSTE, LANDLICH, NATIONALE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, VOLKSTUMLICH wom 027 tk005 richard allen harvey carolan's favourite wom 027 eirinn (celtic) west one music world traditional ethnic folk national and ethnic national folk dance traditional ethnic folk national and ethnic national folk dance traditional ethnic folk national and ethnic national folk music main documentary biographical historical the arts movies children storytelling nature medley of animated orchestral jigs increasing in tempo. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="7055" name="The High Plains (c)" code="TSH 001 tk021" libraryid="5" albumid="149" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_001_Cinematic_Adventures/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Des cordes luxueuses, mène à un noble développement épique et panoramique avec du tin whistle celtique jusqu'à la reprise." styleid="6" lengthseconds="160" time="2:40" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_001_Cinematic_Adventures/TSH001_trk021_THE_HIGH_PLAINS_(C)_Richard_Allen_Harvey_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="21" tracktotal="" search="Des cordes luxueuses, mène à un noble développement épique et panoramique avec du tin whistle celtique jusqu'à la reprise. BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, ALTERNATIF, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, FORT, ÉPIQUE, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, PATRIOTIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EVOLUTIF, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, PÉRIODE, PRÉ-20E SIÈCLE, 19E SIÈCLE, AMERIQUE DU NORD, PERIODE, ETATS-UNIS, PRE-20E SIECLE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, EPIQUE, 20E SIECLE, 19E SIECLE, ELEMENTS, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Ausladende Streicher, die zu einem ausgedehnten, epischen Ganzen mit Celtic Whistle in der Reprise anwachsen. FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMA, ALTERNATIVE, DOKUMENTATION, BIOGRAFISCH, HISTORISCH, KÜNSTE, FILME, KINDER, KINDERGESCHICHTEN, FILME, ROMANTIK, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LANDSCHAFTEN, PANORAMA, TRAILER TRACK, TRAURIG, BEDRÜCKEND, SCHMERZLICH, TRAURIG, BEDRÜCKEND, TRAURIG, KRÄFTIG, EPISCH, ZÄRTLICH, WEHMÜTIG, ZÄRTLICH, NACHDENKLICH, ZÄRTLICH, ROMANTISCH, ZÄRTLICH, GEFÜHLVOLL, ZÄRTLICH, WARM, BEFLÜGELND, PATRIOTISCH, BEFLÜGELND, BEFLÜGELND, AUFBAUEND, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), KLASSISCH &amp; SEMIKLASSISCH, SINFONIEORCHESTER, NORDAMERIKA, USA, ZEITALTER, VOR 20 JHD., 18. JAHRHUNDERT, BEDRUCKEND, BEFLUGELND, GEFUHLVOLL, KRAFTIG, KUNSTE, WEHMUTIG, ZARTLICH tsh 001 tk021 richard allen harvey the high plains (c) tsh 001 cinematic adventures the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic alternate documentary biographical historical the arts movies children storytelling movies romance nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama trailer track sad depressing poignant sad depressing sad expansive strings building to epic panoramic development featuring celtic whistle to reprise. alternative" waveformpath="" version="Alternative" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" lc="24186"/>
    <item id="21673" name="Celtic Pride (a)" code="WOM 307 tk009" libraryid="6" albumid="477" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_307_Epic_World_/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Daniel Law Heath / Jane Antonia Cornish" comment="Une piste d'aventure optimistique et édifiante avec une forte influence Irlandaise. Mené par une flûte a bec traditionelle." styleid="2" lengthseconds="143" time="2:23" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_307_Epic_World_/WOM_307_trk009_CELTIC_PRIDE_(A)_Daniel_Law_Heath_Jane_Antonia_Cornish_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="Une piste d'aventure optimistique et édifiante avec une forte influence Irlandaise. Mené par une flûte a bec traditionelle. BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, FORT, ÉPIQUE, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BOIS, FLUTE A BEC, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, IRLANDE, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), EPIQUE, PERIODES Optimistischer und aufbauender Abenteuer-Cue mit irischem Charakter und traditioneller Flöten-Lead. FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, HAUPTVERSION, FILME, ACTION ABENTEUER, FILME, EPISCH, FILME, FANTASY ABENTEUER, FILME, ÄRA, HISTORISCH, KOSTÜMDRAMA, TRAILER, TRAILER TRACK, KRÄFTIG, EPISCH, KRÄFTIG, KRÄFTIG, BEFLÜGELND, OPTIMISTISCH, BEFLÜGELND, BEFLÜGELND, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), HOLZBLASINSTRUMENTE, BLOCKFLÖTE, EUROPA, NORDEUROPA, IRLAND, ARA, BEFLUGELND, BLOCKFLOTE, FLOTE, KOSTUMDRAMA, KRAFTIG wom 307 tk009 daniel law heath jane antonia cornish celtic pride (a) wom 307 epic world west one music trailer film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral trailer main movies action adventure movies epic movies fantasy adventure movies period historical costume drama trailers trailer track strong epic strong strong uplifting optimistic uplifting uplifting tempo uplifting and optimistic epic adventure cue with strong irish flavours. featuring traditional-style recorder lead. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="9026" name="Whiskey" code="WOM 027 tk009" libraryid="6" albumid="188" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_027_Eirinn_(Celtic)/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Une robuste chanson à boire instrumentale entrecoupée de quadrilles écossais." styleid="17" lengthseconds="213" time="3:33" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_027_Eirinn_(Celtic)/WOM027_trk009_WHISKEY_Richard_Allen_Harvey_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="Une robuste chanson à boire instrumentale entrecoupée de quadrilles écossais. FOLK ETHNIQUE TRADITIONNEL, INTERNATIONAL ET ETHNIQUE, DANSE FOLK NATIONALE, FOLK ETHNIQUE TRADITIONNEL, INTERNATIONAL ET ETHNIQUE, DANSE FOLK NATIONALE, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, PRINTEMPS, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CORDES, BOIS, ETHNIQUE, VENT, FLUTE, FLUTE IRLANDAISE, ETHNIQUE, VENT, FLUTE, PENNY WHISTLE, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, IRLANDE, ELEMENTS Ausgelassenes instrumentales Trinklied. TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, NATIONAL UND ETHNISCH, NATIONALER VOLKSTANZ, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, NATIONAL UND ETHNISCH, NATIONALER VOLKSTANZ, HAUPTVERSION, DOKUMENTATION, BIOGRAFISCH, HISTORISCH, KÜNSTE, FILME, KINDER, KINDERGESCHICHTEN, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LANDSCHAFTEN, PANORAMA, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LÄNDLICH, LANDSCHAFT, IDYLLISCH, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, JAHRESZEITEN, ZEIT, FRÜHLING, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MITTLERES TEMPO (ANDANTE), SAITENINSTRUMENTE, HOLZBLÄSER, ETHNISCH, WIND, FLÖTE, IRISCHE FLÖTE, ETHNISCH, WIND, FLÖTE, PENNY WHISTLE, BLECHFLÖTE, EUROPA, NORDEUROPA, IRLAND, BLASER, BLECHFLOTE, FLOTE, FROHLICH, FRUHLING, HOLZBLASER, IRISCHE FLOTE, KUNSTE, LANDLICH, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, VOLKSTUMLICH wom 027 tk009 richard allen harvey whiskey wom 027 eirinn (celtic) west one music world traditional ethnic folk national and ethnic national folk dance traditional ethnic folk national and ethnic national folk dance main documentary biographical historical the arts movies children storytelling nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife a rumbustious instrumental drinking song interspersed with reels. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="17436" name="The Perpetual Bachelor (b)" code="WOM 212 tk020" libraryid="6" albumid="376" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_212_Twisted_Country/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Harvey Lee Summers" comment="Une ballade nostalgique teintée de nuances celtiques avec un accordéon et un fiddle." styleid="22" lengthseconds="192" time="3:12" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_212_Twisted_Country/WOM212_trk020_THE_PERPETUAL_BACHELOR_(B)_Harvey_Lee_Summers_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="20" tracktotal="" search="Une ballade nostalgique teintée de nuances celtiques avec un accordéon et un fiddle. COUNTRY, COUNTRY ROCK, UNDERSCORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, SOLEIL, CHALEUR, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, BALADE, AMERIQUE DU NORD, ETATS-UNIS, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, ELEMENTS, METEO, ETE Sehnsüchtige Ballade mit Akkordeon, Fidel und keltischem Vibe. COUNTRY, COUNTRY ROCK, UNDERSCORE, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LÄNDLICH, LANDSCHAFT, IDYLLISCH, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, SONNE, TROPISCH, KÜSTENLANDSCHAFT, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, WETTER, SONNE, HITZE, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, REISEN, TRAURIG, BEDRÜCKEND, EINSAM, TRAURIG, BEDRÜCKEND, SCHMERZLICH, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), NORDAMERIKA, USA, BALLADE, BEDRUCKEND, KUSTENLANDSCHAFT, LANDLICH wom 212 tk020 harvey lee summers the perpetual bachelor (b) wom 212 twisted country west one music country folk country country rock underscore nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral nature wildlife the elements land sun tropical seaside nature wildlife the elements weather sun heat tv radio leisure lifestyle travel sad depressing lonely sad depressing wistful celtic tinged ballad with accordion and fiddle. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="2845" name="Hands Across the Water (b)" code="TSH 015 tk011" libraryid="5" albumid="89" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_015_The_World_in_a_Voice/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Miriam Arlene Stockley / David Richard Mindel" comment="Un refrain celtique tendre avec un violon et une flûte à bec soprano." styleid="17" lengthseconds="158" time="2:38" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_015_The_World_in_a_Voice/TSH015_trk011_HANDS_ACROSS_THE_WATER_(B)_Miriam_Arlene_Stockley_David_Richard_Mindel_The_Scoring_Ho.mp3" track="11" tracktotal="" search="Un refrain celtique tendre avec un violon et une flûte à bec soprano. WORLD BEAT, STYLES ETHNIQUES, GLOBAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, FOLK ETHNIQUE TRADITIONNEL, INTERNATIONAL ET ETHNIQUE, MUSIQUE FOLK NATIONALE, ALTERNATIF, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TENDRE, TENDRE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, PATRIOTIQUE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), BOIS, FLUTE A BEC, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, IRLANDE, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, ÉCOSSE, DEPRIMANT, ECOSSE, ELEMENTS Ein einfühlsamer keltischer Refrain mit Violine und Sopranblockflöte. WORLD BEAT, ETHNISCHE INTERPRETATIONEN, GLOBAL, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, IDYLLISCH, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, NATIONAL UND ETHNISCH, NATIONALE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, ALTERNATIVE, DOKUMENTATION, BIOGRAFISCH, HISTORISCH, KÜNSTE, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LÄNDLICH, LANDSCHAFT, IDYLLISCH, TRAURIG, BEDRÜCKEND, TRAURIG, ZÄRTLICH, GEFÜHLVOLL, ZÄRTLICH, ZÄRTLICH, BEFLÜGELND, PATRIOTISCH, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MITTLERES TEMPO (ANDANTE), HOLZBLASINSTRUMENTE, BLOCKFLÖTE, EUROPA, NORDEUROPA, IRLAND, EUROPA, NORDEUROPA, SCHOTTLAND, BEDRUCKEND, BEFLUGELND, BLOCKFLOTE, FLOTE, GEFUHLVOLL, KUNSTE, LANDLICH, NATIONALE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, VOLKSTUMLICH, ZARTLICH tsh 015 tk011 miriam arlene stockley david richard mindel hands across the water (b) tsh 015 the world in a voice the scoring house world world beat ethnic stylings global film score orchestral pastoral traditional ethnic folk national and ethnic national folk music alternate documentary biographical historical the arts nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral sad depressing sad tender tender celtic refrain featuring violin and soprano recorder. instrumental" waveformpath="" version="Instrumental" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" lc="24186"/>
    <item id="9030" name="The Lark in the Clear Air (a)" code="WOM 027 tk013" libraryid="6" albumid="188" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_027_Eirinn_(Celtic)/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Une titre folk idyllique arrangé pour whistle et cordes." styleid="17" lengthseconds="224" time="3:44" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_027_Eirinn_(Celtic)/WOM027_trk013_THE_LARK_IN_THE_CLEAR_AIR_(A)_Richard_Allen_Harvey_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="13" tracktotal="" search="Une titre folk idyllique arrangé pour whistle et cordes. FOLK ETHNIQUE TRADITIONNEL, INTERNATIONAL ET ETHNIQUE, MUSIQUE FOLK NATIONALE, FOLK ETHNIQUE TRADITIONNEL, INTERNATIONAL ET ETHNIQUE, MUSIQUE FOLK NATIONALE, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CORDES, BOIS, ETHNIQUE, VENT, FLUTE, FLUTE IRLANDAISE, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, IRLANDE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ELEMENTS Idyllisches Volkslied mit Flöte und Streichern. TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, NATIONAL UND ETHNISCH, NATIONALE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, NATIONAL UND ETHNISCH, NATIONALE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, HAUPTVERSION, DOKUMENTATION, BIOGRAFISCH, HISTORISCH, KÜNSTE, FILME, KINDER, KINDERGESCHICHTEN, FILME, FANTASY ABENTEUER, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LANDSCHAFTEN, PANORAMA, FRIEDLICH, FRIEDLICH, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), SAITENINSTRUMENTE, HOLZBLÄSER, ETHNISCH, WIND, FLÖTE, IRISCHE FLÖTE, EUROPA, NORDEUROPA, IRLAND, BLASER, FLOTE, HOLZBLASER, IRISCHE FLOTE, KUNSTE, NATIONALE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, VOLKSTUMLICH wom 027 tk013 richard allen harvey the lark in the clear air (a) wom 027 eirinn (celtic) west one music world traditional ethnic folk national and ethnic national folk music traditional ethnic folk national and ethnic national folk music main documentary biographical historical the arts movies children storytelling movies fantasy adventure nature wildlife the elements land landscapes idyllic folk tune arranged for whistle and strings. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="21668" name="Celtic Flame (a)" code="WOM 307 tk004" libraryid="6" albumid="477" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_307_Epic_World_/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Daniel Law Heath" comment="Une piste au thème Celtique impressionant. De distantes mélodies de flûte à bec se laissent aller par dessus une construction de percussions et cordes." styleid="2" lengthseconds="128" time="2:08" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_307_Epic_World_/WOM_307_trk004_CELTIC_FLAME_(A)_Daniel_Law_Heath_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="Une piste au thème Celtique impressionant. De distantes mélodies de flûte à bec se laissent aller par dessus une construction de percussions et cordes. BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, TITRE POUR TRAILER, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, MARTIAL, FORT, PUISSANT, EVOLUTIF, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BOIS, FLUTE A BEC, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, IRLANDE, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETERMINE, EPIQUE, PERIODES, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Beeindruckender Cue mit keltischem Charakter. Entfernte Flötenmelodien spielen über sich steigernde Percussion und Streicher. FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, HAUPTVERSION, DOKUMENTATION, BIOGRAFISCH, HISTORISCH, KÜNSTE, FILME, ACTION ABENTEUER, FILME, EPISCH, FILME, FANTASY ABENTEUER, FILME, ÄRA, HISTORISCH, KOSTÜMDRAMA, TRAILER TRACK, KRÄFTIG, ENTSCHLOSSEN, KRÄFTIG, MARTIALISCH, KRÄFTIG, KRAFTVOLL, AUFBAUEND, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), HOLZBLASINSTRUMENTE, BLOCKFLÖTE, EUROPA, NORDEUROPA, IRLAND, ARA, BLOCKFLOTE, FLOTE, KOSTUMDRAMA, KRAFTIG, KUNSTE wom 307 tk004 daniel law heath celtic flame (a) wom 307 epic world west one music trailer film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral trailer main documentary biographical historical the arts movies action adventure movies epic movies fantasy adventure movies period historical costume drama trailer track strong determined strong martial strong powerful impressive celtic themed cue. distant recorder melody drifts over building percussion and strings. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="4294" name="Celtic and Country" code="TSH 043 tk010" libraryid="5" albumid="113" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_043_An_American_Journey/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Clive Michael Oliver Carroll" comment="Une ballade douce et évocatrice pour fiddle et banjo." styleid="22" lengthseconds="151" time="2:31" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_043_An_American_Journey/TSH043_trk010_CELTIC_AND_COUNTRY_Clive_Michael_Oliver_Carroll_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="10" tracktotal="" search="Une ballade douce et évocatrice pour fiddle et banjo. FOLK ETHNIQUE TRADITIONNEL, INTERNATIONAL ET ETHNIQUE, MUSIQUE FOLK NATIONALE, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, IRLANDE, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, ÉCOSSE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), FOLK CONTEMPORAINE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, ETHNIQUE, VIOLON, CORDES, BANJO,, DEPRIMANT, ECOSSE Ein ruhiger und atmosphärischer Ausflug mit Fidel und Banjo. TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, NATIONAL UND ETHNISCH, NATIONALE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, EUROPA, NORDEUROPA, IRLAND, EUROPA, NORDEUROPA, SCHOTTLAND, HAUPTVERSION, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MITTLERES TEMPO (ANDANTE), ZEITGENÖSSISCHER FOLK, TRAURIG, BEDRÜCKEND, TRAURIG, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, REISEN, ETHNISCH, GEIGE, SAITENINSTRUMENTE, BANJO, BEDRUCKEND, NATIONALE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, VOLKSTUMLICH, ZEITGENOSSISCH, ZEITGENOSSISCHER FOLK tsh 043 tk010 clive michael oliver carroll celtic and country tsh 043 an american journey the scoring house country folk traditional ethnic folk national and ethnic national folk music europe northern europe ireland europe northern europe scotland main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) contemporary folk sad depressing sad tv radio leisure lifestyle travel ethnic fiddle strings banjo gentle evocative ramble for fiddle and banjo. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" lc="24186"/>
    <item id="9023" name="The Londonderry Air (a)" code="WOM 027 tk006" libraryid="6" albumid="188" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_027_Eirinn_(Celtic)/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Un fameux morceau irlandais avec une mélodie de whistle, une harpe obligée, et une seconde section avec un whistle de concert. Egalement connu sous le nom de Danny boy." styleid="17" lengthseconds="234" time="3:54" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_027_Eirinn_(Celtic)/WOM027_trk006_THE_LONDONDERRY_AIR_(A)_Richard_Allen_Harvey_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="6" tracktotal="" search="Un fameux morceau irlandais avec une mélodie de whistle, une harpe obligée, et une seconde section avec un whistle de concert. Egalement connu sous le nom de Danny boy. FOLK ETHNIQUE TRADITIONNEL, INTERNATIONAL ET ETHNIQUE, MUSIQUE FOLK NATIONALE, FOLK ETHNIQUE TRADITIONNEL, INTERNATIONAL ET ETHNIQUE, MUSIQUE FOLK NATIONALE, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, COUCHER DE SOLEIL, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CORDES, BOIS, ETHNIQUE, VENT, FLUTE, FLUTE IRLANDAISE, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, IRLANDE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ELEMENTS Ein berühmtes irisches Lied mit Flötenmelodie, Obligato der Harfe, sowie einer tiefen Flöte im zweiten Abschnitt. Auch bekannt als 'Danny Boy'. TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, NATIONAL UND ETHNISCH, NATIONALE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, NATIONAL UND ETHNISCH, NATIONALE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, HAUPTVERSION, DOKUMENTATION, BIOGRAFISCH, HISTORISCH, KÜNSTE, FILME, KINDER, KINDERGESCHICHTEN, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LANDSCHAFTEN, PANORAMA, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, JAHRESZEITEN, ZEIT, SONNENUNTERGANG, ZÄRTLICH, NACHDENKLICH, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), SAITENINSTRUMENTE, HOLZBLÄSER, ETHNISCH, WIND, FLÖTE, IRISCHE FLÖTE, EUROPA, NORDEUROPA, IRLAND, BLASER, FLOTE, HOLZBLASER, IRISCHE FLOTE, KUNSTE, NATIONALE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, VOLKSTUMLICH, ZARTLICH wom 027 tk006 richard allen harvey the londonderry air (a) wom 027 eirinn (celtic) west one music world traditional ethnic folk national and ethnic national folk music traditional ethnic folk national and ethnic national folk music main documentary biographical historical the arts movies children storytelling nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife famous irish tune with whistle melody. harp obligato. second section with a low whistle. also known as danny boy. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="19288" name="Waterford Down" code="WOM 252 tk008" libraryid="6" albumid="420" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_252_Indie_Folk/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Charlie Taylor / Jake Jarvis" comment="Des refrains celtiques entraînants avec des couplets intimes plus doux, avec un tin whistle et un banjo." styleid="22" lengthseconds="175" time="2:55" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_252_Indie_Folk/WOM252_trk008_WATERFORD_DOWN_Charlie_Taylor_Jake_Jarvis_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="8" tracktotal="" search="Des refrains celtiques entraînants avec des couplets intimes plus doux, avec un tin whistle et un banjo. FOLK ETHNIQUE TRADITIONNEL, INTERNATIONAL ET ETHNIQUE, MUSIQUE FOLK NATIONALE, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, IRLANDE, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), FOLK CONTEMPORAINE, FOLK ETHNIQUE TRADITIONNEL, FOLK AMÉRICAIN TRADITIONNEL, ETHNIQUE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, TENDRE, INTIME, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, OCCASIONS SPÉCIALES, VACANCES, ST PATRICK, CORDES, BANJO, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN NYLON, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN MÉTAL,, AMERIQUE DU NORD, OCCASIONS SPECIALES, FOLK AMERICAIN TRADITIONNEL, ETATS-UNIS, CORDES EN METAL Der ergreifende und mitreißende Chorus mit keltischem Flair wird von zurückhaltenderen Strophen mit Banjo und Blechflöte abgelöst. TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, NATIONAL UND ETHNISCH, NATIONALE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, EUROPA, NORDEUROPA, IRLAND, NORDAMERIKA, USA, HAUPTVERSION, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MITTLERES TEMPO (ANDANTE), ZEITGENÖSSISCHER FOLK, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTÜMLICHE MUSIK, TRADITIONELLER AMERIKANISCHER FOLK, ETHNISCH, FRÖHLICH, GUT GELAUNT, ZÄRTLICH, VERTRAUT, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, REISEN, BESONDERE ANLÄSSE, FEIERTAGE, ST. PATRICK'S DAY, SAITENINSTRUMENTE, BANJO, SAITENINSTRUMENTE, GITARRE - AKUSTIK, NYLONSAITEN, SAITENINSTRUMENTE, GITARRE - AKUSTIK, STAHLSAITEN, BESONDERE ANLASSE, FROHLICH, NATIONALE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, TRADITIONELLE ETHNISCHE VOLKSTUMLICHE MUSIK, VOLKSTUMLICH, ZARTLICH, ZEITGENOSSISCH, ZEITGENOSSISCHER FOLK wom 252 tk008 charlie taylor jake jarvis waterford down wom 252 indie folk west one music country folk traditional ethnic folk national and ethnic national folk music europe northern europe ireland north america usa main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) contemporary folk traditional ethnic folk traditional american folk ethnic happy feel good tender intimate tv radio leisure stirring celtic choruses with softer intimate verses featuring tin whistle and banjo. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
  </items>
</librarycollection>
