<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><librarycollection><items><item id="458" name="Exosphere (a)" code="EDS 013 tk001" libraryid="1" albumid="14" albumartpath="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_013_Future_Beats/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Laurence D. Holcolme (PRS)" comment="Chill trap reveuse avec effets vocaux atmosphériques, basse profonde et beats massifs." styleid="1" lengthseconds="171" time="2:51" samplefile="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_013_Future_Beats/EDS_013_trk001_EXOSPHERE_(A)_Laurence_D._Holcolme_(PRS)_Electronic_Dance_Series.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CHILL OUT, DOWNTEMPO, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, HIP HOP, URBAIN, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, SEXY, COOL, SEXY, SEXY, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, COOL, NERVEUX, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, GLITCHY, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, TAPIS ROULANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, ACCELERE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, AERIEN, ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BATTERIE, BOITE À RYTHMES, BATTERIE ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, VOIX TRAITÉES, MODIFIÉES, MODIFIEES, VOIX TRAITEES Chill trap reveuse avec effets vocaux atmosphériques, basse profonde et beats massifs. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz eds 013 tk001 laurence d. holcolme (prs) exosphere (a) eds 013 future beats electronic dance series dance electro club electronica club electronica chill out downtempo business corporate luxury business corporate motivational hip hop urban main activities settings city urban human environment activities settings futuristic business corporate tv radio children youth tv tv radio dreamy chill trap featuring atmospheric vocal fx deep bass and solid beats. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Electronic Dance Series" cae="00666407133" /><item id="475" name="Reaching Ground (b)" code="EDS 013 tk018" libraryid="1" albumid="14" albumartpath="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_013_Future_Beats/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Sample Magic (PRS), Lea Willis (PRS)" comment="Electro hypnotique avec synthés atmosphériques et beats relax." styleid="1" lengthseconds="136" time="2:16" samplefile="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_013_Future_Beats/EDS_013_trk018_REACHING_GROUND_(B)_Sample_Magic_(PRS),_Lea_Willis_(PRS)_Electronic_Dance_Series.mp3" track="18" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CHILL OUT, DOWNTEMPO, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FORMATION, INFORMATION, UNDERSCORE, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, NEUTRE, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, DÉTENDU, DETENDU, PAISIBLE, SOMNOLENT, PAISIBLE, APAISANT, SEXY, COOL, SEXY, SEXY, FORT, CONFIANT, COOL, NERVEUX, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, AERIEN, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, RALENTI, ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BATTERIE, BOITE À RYTHMES, BATTERIE ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE Electro hypnotique avec synthés atmosphériques et beats relax. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz eds 013 tk018 sample magic (prs) lea willis (prs) reaching ground (b) eds 013 future beats electronic dance series dance electro club electronica club electronica chill out downtempo business corporate beds business corporate luxury business corporate science technology business corporate training information underscore activities settings city urban human environment activities settings futuristic hypnotic electronica with atmospheric synths and relaxed beats. underscore" waveformpath="" version="Underscore" publisher="Electronic Dance Series" cae="00666407133" /><item id="466" name="Luminance (a)" code="EDS 013 tk009" libraryid="1" albumid="14" albumartpath="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_013_Future_Beats/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Sample Magic (PRS), Lea Willis (PRS)" comment="Electro évocatrice au ralenti avec synthés éthérés et beats re-lax." styleid="1" lengthseconds="150" time="2:30" samplefile="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_013_Future_Beats/EDS_013_trk009_LUMINANCE_(A)_Sample_Magic_(PRS),_Lea_Willis_(PRS)_Electronic_Dance_Series.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CHILL OUT, DOWNTEMPO, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FORMATION, INFORMATION, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, NEUTRE, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, DÉTENDU, DETENDU, PAISIBLE, APAISANT, SEXY, COOL, SEXY, SEXY, FORT, CONFIANT, COOL, NERVEUX, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, AERIEN, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, RALENTI, ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BATTERIE, BOITE À RYTHMES, BATTERIE ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE Electro évocatrice au ralenti avec synthés éthérés et beats re-lax. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz eds 013 tk009 sample magic (prs) lea willis (prs) luminance (a) eds 013 future beats electronic dance series dance electro club electronica club electronica chill out downtempo business corporate beds business corporate luxury business corporate science technology business corporate training information main activities settings city urban human environment activities settings futuristic atmospheric slow-motion electronica with ethereal synths and chilled beats. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Electronic Dance Series" cae="00666407133" /><item id="227" name="Counting Stars (a)" code="EDS 011 tk002" libraryid="1" albumid="7" albumartpath="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_011_Mainroom_House/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Francois Oxford / Oscar Hill / Justin Black" comment="House chaleureuse et séduisante avec synthés stylés. Un titre funky pour tard dans la nuit." styleid="1" lengthseconds="185" time="3:05" samplefile="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_011_Mainroom_House/EDS_011_trk002_COUNTING_STARS_(A)_Francois_Oxford_Oscar_Hill_Justin_Black_Electronic_Dance_Series.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HOUSE, ELECTRO HOUSE, ÉLECTRONIQUE, PRINCIPAL, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, ELECTRONIQUE, ENERGIQUE, ELEMENTS House chaleureuse et séduisante avec synthés stylés. Un titre funky pour tard dans la nuit. eds 011 tk002 francois oxford oscar hill justin black counting stars (a) eds 011 mainroom house electronic dance series dance electro club electronica house electro house electronic main club electronica club electronica happy bright happy feel good strong energetic uplifting motivational uplifting positive uplifting uplifting movement rhythmic driving nature wildlife the elements land sun tropical warm and seductive house track with stylish synths. a funky late night mover. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Electronic Dance Series" cae="00666407133" /><item id="243" name="Devotion (b)" code="EDS 011 tk018" libraryid="1" albumid="7" albumartpath="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_011_Mainroom_House/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Huw Williams" comment="Titre ÉNORME pour club. Une intro accrocheuse au synthé se développe avec des chorus exaltants." styleid="1" lengthseconds="193" time="3:13" samplefile="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_011_Mainroom_House/EDS_011_trk018_DEVOTION_(B)_Huw_Williams_Electronic_Dance_Series.mp3" track="18" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HOUSE, ELECTRO HOUSE, ÉLECTRONIQUE, UNDERSCORE, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EMBLÉMATIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INSISTANT, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, ELECTRONIQUE, ENERGIQUE, EMBLEMATIQUE, ELEMENTS Titre ÉNORME pour club. Une intro accrocheuse au synthé se développe avec des chorus exaltants. eds 011 tk018 huw williams devotion (b) eds 011 mainroom house electronic dance series dance electro club electronica house electro house electronic underscore club electronica club electronica happy bright happy feel good strong energetic uplifting anthemic uplifting euphoric uplifting motivational uplifting positive uplifting uplifting movement rhythmic driving huge energetic club monster. catchy rising synth intro builds to uplifting choruses. underscore" waveformpath="" version="Underscore" publisher="Electronic Dance Series" cae="00666407133" /><item id="238" name="Elation (b)" code="EDS 011 tk013" libraryid="1" albumid="7" albumartpath="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_011_Mainroom_House/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Samuel Rupert Cole Sutton / Alexander David Bachell" comment="Euro house positive et exaltante. Avec hooks de synthé accrocheurs et un breakdown euphorique." styleid="1" lengthseconds="154" time="2:34" samplefile="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_011_Mainroom_House/EDS_011_trk013_ELATION_(B)_Samuel_Rupert_Cole_Sutton_Alexander_David_Bachell_Electronic_Dance_Series.mp3" track="13" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HOUSE, ELECTRO HOUSE, ÉLECTRONIQUE, UNDERSCORE, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, EURO BEAT, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, ELECTRONIQUE, ENERGIQUE, ELEMENTS Euro house positive et exaltante. Avec hooks de synthé accrocheurs et un breakdown euphorique. eds 011 tk013 samuel rupert cole sutton alexander david bachell elation (b) eds 011 mainroom house electronic dance series dance electro club electronica house electro house electronic underscore club electronica club electronica club electronica euro beat happy bright happy feel good strong energetic uplifting motivational uplifting positive uplifting uplifting movement rhythmic driving nature wildlife positive and uplifting euro house. featuring catchy synth hooks and a euphoric breakdown. underscore" waveformpath="" version="Underscore" publisher="Electronic Dance Series" cae="00666407133" /><item id="164" name="Synthia (b)" code="EDS 009 tk015" libraryid="1" albumid="5" albumartpath="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_009_Dance-Punk_Electro/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Huw Williams" comment="Excitation distordue découpée et bourrée d'énergie." styleid="1" lengthseconds="218" time="3:38" samplefile="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_009_Dance-Punk_Electro/EDS_009_trk015_SYNTHIA_(B)_Huw_Williams_Electronic_Dance_Series.mp3" track="15" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CHEMICAL BEATS, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRO, UNDERSCORE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, SPORT, EXERCICE, FITNESS, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, FORT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETERMINE, DEFILE DE MODE, DEFILE Excitation distordue découpée et bourrée d'énergie. eds 009 tk015 huw williams synthia (b) eds 009 dance-punk electro electronic dance series dance electro club electronica chemical beats club electronica electro underscore activities settings fashion show sports exercise fitness tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio sports strong confident strong determined strong exciting strong super-charged cut-up distorted excitement. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without vocal" publisher="Electronic Dance Series" cae="00666407133" /><item id="21" name="2Funky 2Night (b)" code="EDS 012 tk021" libraryid="1" albumid="1" albumartpath="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_012_Electro_Techno/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Sample Magic" comment="Vibe old school, vastes pads de synthé, beat house funky." styleid="1" lengthseconds="162" time="2:42" samplefile="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_012_Electro_Techno/EDS_012_trk021_2FUNKY_2NIGHT_(B)_Sample_Magic_Electronic_Dance_Series.mp3" track="21" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, TECHNO, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRO, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HOUSE, UNDERSCORE, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, DEFILE DE MODE, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FETE, FÊTE GÉNÉRALE, FETE GENERALE, SPORT, EXERCICE, FITNESS, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, DETERMINE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, IMPLACABLE, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, QUI A DU CRAN, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INSISTANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, MÉCANIQUE, ROBOTIQUE, MECANIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, RÉPÉTITIF, REPETITIF, ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BATTERIE, BOITE À RYTHMES, BATTERIE ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE Vibe old school, vastes pads de synthé, beat house funky. eds 012 tk021 sample magic 2funky 2night (b) eds 012 electro techno electronic dance series dance electro club electronica techno club electronica breakbeat club electronica electro club electronica house underscore activities settings city urban human environment activities settings fashion show activities settings futuristic activities settings party general party sports old skool vibe wide synth pads and a funky house beat. underscore" waveformpath="" version="Underscore" publisher="Electronic Dance Series" cae="00666407133" /><item id="19" name="Acidic Nation (b)" code="EDS 012 tk019" libraryid="1" albumid="1" albumartpath="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_012_Electro_Techno/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Sample Magic" comment="Acide house funky, écrasante et pataugeuse, avec une grosse influence techno." styleid="1" lengthseconds="130" time="2:10" samplefile="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_012_Electro_Techno/EDS_012_trk019_ACIDIC_NATION_(B)_Sample_Magic_Electronic_Dance_Series.mp3" track="19" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, TECHNO, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRO, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HOUSE, ACID HOUSE, UNDERSCORE, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, DEFILE DE MODE, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FETE, FÊTE GÉNÉRALE, FETE GENERALE, SPORT, EXERCICE, FITNESS, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, DETERMINE, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, ENERGIQUE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, IMPLACABLE, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, QUI A DU CRAN, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INSISTANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, MÉCANIQUE, ROBOTIQUE, MECANIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, RÉPÉTITIF, REPETITIF, ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BATTERIE, BOITE À RYTHMES, BATTERIE ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE Acide house funky, écrasante et pataugeuse, avec une grosse influence techno. eds 012 tk019 sample magic acidic nation (b) eds 012 electro techno electronic dance series dance electro club electronica techno club electronica electro club electronica house acid house underscore activities settings city urban human environment activities settings fashion show activities settings futuristic activities settings party general party sports exercise fitness funked up and squelchy acid house influence techno. underscore" waveformpath="" version="Underscore" publisher="Electronic Dance Series" cae="00666407133" /><item id="389" name="Time to Dance" code="EDS 004 tk004" libraryid="1" albumid="12" albumartpath="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_004_Future_Disco/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Sample Magic / Colin Anthony Flynn / David Felton" comment="Des beat dansants et des mélodies baignées dans le funk." styleid="1" lengthseconds="240" time="4:00" samplefile="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_004_Future_Disco/EDS004_trk004_TIME_TO_DANCE_Sample_Magic_Colin_Anthony_Flynn_David_Felton_Electronic_Dance_Series.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, DISCO, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HOUSE, FRENCH HOUSE, PRINCIPAL, SPORT, EXERCICE, FITNESS, SPORT, SPORTS EXTREMES, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COURANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 70, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ANNEES 2000, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 20, ANNEES 70 Des beat dansants et des mélodies baignées dans le funk. eds 004 tk004 sample magic colin anthony flynn david felton time to dance eds 004 future disco electronic dance series dance electro club electronica club electronica disco club electronica house french house main sports exercise fitness sports extreme sports tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio sports happy feel good uplifting motivational uplifting driving beats and funk fuelled melodies. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Electronic Dance Series" cae="00666407133" /><item id="388" name="Neon Nights" code="EDS 004 tk003" libraryid="1" albumid="12" albumartpath="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_004_Future_Disco/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Sample Magic / David Felton / Francesca Gina Bergami" comment="De la disco house française classique." styleid="1" lengthseconds="214" time="3:34" samplefile="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_004_Future_Disco/EDS004_trk003_NEON_NIGHTS_Sample_Magic_David_Felton_Francesca_Gina_Bergami_Electronic_Dance_Series.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, DISCO, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HOUSE, DISCO HOUSE, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HOUSE, ELECTRO HOUSE, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HOUSE, FRENCH HOUSE, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, SPORT, EXERCICE, FITNESS, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, NUIT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INSISTANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 70, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEFILE DE MODE, ANNEES 2000, 20E SIECLE, DEFILE, ANNEES 20, ANNEES 70 De la disco house française classique. eds 004 tk003 sample magic david felton francesca gina bergami neon nights eds 004 future disco electronic dance series dance electro club electronica club electronica disco club electronica house disco house club electronica house electro house club electronica house french house main activities settings fashion show sports exercise fitness tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio sports classic french flavoured disco house. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Electronic Dance Series" cae="00666407133" /><item id="398" name="Just Say Yes (b)" code="EDS 004 tk013" libraryid="1" albumid="12" albumartpath="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_004_Future_Disco/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Sharooz Raoofi" comment="Des beats battants et de la disco cosmique filtrée." styleid="1" lengthseconds="227" time="3:47" samplefile="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_004_Future_Disco/EDS004_trk013_JUST_SAY_YES_(B)_Sharooz_Raoofi_Electronic_Dance_Series.mp3" track="13" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, DISCO, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HOUSE, FRENCH HOUSE, UNDERSCORE, SPORT, EXERCICE, FITNESS, SPORT, SPORTS EXTREMES, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COURANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 70, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ANNEES 2000, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 20, ANNEES 70 Des beats battants et de la disco cosmique filtrée. eds 004 tk013 sharooz raoofi just say yes (b) eds 004 future disco electronic dance series dance electro club electronica club electronica disco club electronica house french house underscore sports exercise fitness sports extreme sports tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio sports tv radio talkshow entertainment happy feel good uplifting positive uplifting foot tapping beats and filtered cosmic disco. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="Electronic Dance Series" cae="00666407133" /><item id="28967" name="Aerial Glow (a)" code="WOM 383 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="610" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_383_Elektrobeat/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Lewis (PRS), Thomas A. Swindells (PRS)" comment="Electronica immersive et exaltante, avec beats coriaces et synthés aériens." styleid="1" lengthseconds="164" time="2:44" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_383_Elektrobeat/WOM_383_trk001_AERIAL_GLOW_(A)_Richard_Lewis_(PRS),_Thomas_A._Swindells_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRONICA, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, HI TECH, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, SEXY, COOL, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, DETERMINE, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, JAILLIR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, COOL, NERVEUX, ETHNIQUE, PERCUSSION, KALIMBA, SANZA, BATTERIE, INSTRUMENTS ÉLECTRONIQUES, ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ELECTRONIQUES, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN NYLON, CORDES, HARPE, VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, VOIX TRAITÉES, MODIFIÉES, MODIFIEES, VOIX TRAITEES, ASIE Electronica immersive et exaltante, avec beats coriaces et synthés aériens. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 383 tk001 richard lewis (prs) thomas a. swindells (prs) aerial glow (a) wom 383 elektrobeat west one music dance electro western drums western electronic instruments ethnic kalimba sanza western guitar acoustic nylon string western harp vocals vocal textures treated vocal peaceful dreamy sexy cool strong confident strong determined tender nostalgic uplifting inspirational uplifting inspiring immersive electronica featuring tough beats and ethereal synths. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="28970" name="Future Technik (a)" code="WOM 383 tk004" libraryid="6" albumid="610" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_383_Elektrobeat/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Lewis (PRS), Thomas A. Swindells (PRS)" comment="Electronica alternative. Beats mécaniques, effets vocaux, synthés et guitares indie funky." styleid="1" lengthseconds="201" time="3:21" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_383_Elektrobeat/WOM_383_trk004_FUTURE_TECHNIK_(A)_Richard_Lewis_(PRS),_Thomas_A._Swindells_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRONICA, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, HI TECH, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, ABSTRAIT, ABSTRAIT, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, SERIEUX, DETERMINE, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, SERIEUX, SEXY, COOL, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, DETERMINE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, COOL, NERVEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, TAPIS ROULANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INDUSTRIE, MACHINES, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, MÉCANIQUE, ROBOTIQUE, MECANIQUE, BATTERIE, INSTRUMENTS ÉLECTRONIQUES, ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ELECTRONIQUES, VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, VOIX TRAITÉES, MODIFIÉES, MODIFIEES, VOIX TRAITEES Electronica alternative. Beats mécaniques, effets vocaux, synthés et guitares indie funky. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 383 tk004 richard lewis (prs) thomas a. swindells (prs) future technik (a) wom 383 elektrobeat west one music dance electro western drums western electronic instruments vocals vocal textures treated vocal abstract abstract serious determined serious serious sexy cool strong confident strong determined uplifting motivational tv radio program formats children youth tv activities &amp; settings city alternative electronica. mechanical beats vocal fxs and synths meet funky indie guitars. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="28975" name="Summer Beat (a)" code="WOM 383 tk009" libraryid="6" albumid="610" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_383_Elektrobeat/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Alkalein (BMI), Daniel I. T. Berry (PRS)" comment="Electronica chaleureuse et éthérée avec piano à doigts, guitare, beats et synthés." styleid="1" lengthseconds="234" time="3:54" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_383_Elektrobeat/WOM_383_trk009_SUMMER_BEAT_(A)_Alkalein_(BMI),_Daniel_I._T._Berry_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CHILL OUT, DOWNTEMPO, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, BAR, BAR À COCKTAILS, RESTAURANT, BAR À COCKTAILS, BAR, BAR A COCKTAILS, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, HI TECH, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, PAISIBLE, CALME, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, INTROSPECTIF, PAISIBLE, DÉTENDU, DETENDU, PAISIBLE, APAISANT, PAISIBLE, TRANQUILLE, SEXY, COOL, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, COOL, NERVEUX, ETHNIQUE, PERCUSSION, KALIMBA, SANZA, BATTERIE, INSTRUMENTS ÉLECTRONIQUES, ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ELECTRONIQUES, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN NYLON Electronica chaleureuse et éthérée avec piano à doigts, guitare, beats et synthés. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 383 tk009 alkalein (bmi) daniel i. t. berry (prs) summer beat (a) wom 383 elektrobeat west one music dance electro western drums western electronic instruments ethnic kalimba sanza western guitar acoustic nylon string peaceful calm peaceful contented peaceful dreamy peaceful introspective peaceful relaxed peaceful soothing peaceful tranquil sexy cool tender nostalgic tender warm tv warm and ethereal electronica with thumb piano guitar beats and synths. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="28150" name="As Good as it Gets (a)" code="WOM 382 tk002" libraryid="6" albumid="596" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_382_Indiesonix/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Rob Rewes (PRS)" comment="Le tube de l'été qui met de bonne humeur. Avec chorus euphoriques, optimistes, irrésistibles." styleid="36" lengthseconds="198" time="3:18" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_382_Indiesonix/WOM_382_trk002_AS_GOOD_AS_IT_GETS_(A)_Rob_Rewes_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, INDIE, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRO, POP, ELECTRO POP, POP, SYNTH POP, ROCK, ROCK ALTERNATIF, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, ROAD TRIP, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, FESTIF, HEUREUX, EXCITÉ, EXCITE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, ENERGIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, COOL, NERVEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, GROUPE DE ROCK, BATTERIE, INSTRUMENTS ÉLECTRONIQUES, ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ELECTRONIQUES, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE Le tube de l'été qui met de bonne humeur. Avec chorus euphoriques, optimistes, irrésistibles. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 382 tk002 rob rewes (prs) as good as it gets (a) wom 382 indiesonix west one music indie rock band western drums western electronic instruments western guitar electric vocals vocal textures vocal background happy bright happy celebratory happy excited happy feel good happy upbeat strong energetic uplifting motivational uplifting positive uplifting uplifting the feelgood hit of the summer with euphoric life-affirming choruses. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="28164" name="Inspiration Nation (b)" code="WOM 382 tk016" libraryid="6" albumid="596" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_382_Indiesonix/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Rob Rewes (PRS)" comment="Cool, vif, et infectieux avec des synthés scintillants, estivaux et une batterie pechue et entrainante." styleid="36" lengthseconds="172" time="2:52" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_382_Indiesonix/WOM_382_trk016_INSPIRATION_NATION_(B)_Rob_Rewes_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="16" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, INDIE, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRO, POP, ELECTRO POP, POP, SYNTH POP, ROCK, ROCK ALTERNATIF, UNDERSCORE, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, ROAD TRIP, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, FESTIF, HEUREUX, EXCITÉ, EXCITE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, ENERGIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, COOL, NERVEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, GROUPE DE ROCK, BATTERIE, INSTRUMENTS ÉLECTRONIQUES, ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ELECTRONIQUES, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE Cool, vif, et infectieux avec des synthés scintillants, estivaux et une batterie pechue et entrainante. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 382 tk016 rob rewes (prs) inspiration nation (b) wom 382 indiesonix west one music indie rock band western drums western electronic instruments western guitar electric happy bright happy celebratory happy excited happy feel good happy upbeat strong energetic uplifting motivational uplifting positive uplifting uplifting business corporate tv crisp infectious and cool with shimmering sunny synths and punchy driving drums. underscore" waveformpath="" version="Underscore" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="28162" name="Race to the Top (b)" code="WOM 382 tk014" libraryid="6" albumid="596" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_382_Indiesonix/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Rob Rewes (PRS)" comment="Inoubliable, irrésistible, implacable et exaltant. Des frissons et du plaisir." styleid="36" lengthseconds="197" time="3:17" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_382_Indiesonix/WOM_382_trk014_RACE_TO_THE_TOP_(B)_Rob_Rewes_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="14" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, INDIE, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRO, POP, ELECTRO POP, POP, SYNTH POP, ROCK, ROCK ALTERNATIF, UNDERSCORE, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, ROAD TRIP, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, FESTIF, HEUREUX, EXCITÉ, EXCITE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, ENERGIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, COOL, NERVEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, GROUPE DE ROCK, BATTERIE, INSTRUMENTS ÉLECTRONIQUES, ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ELECTRONIQUES, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE Inoubliable, irrésistible, implacable et exaltant. Des frissons et du plaisir. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 382 tk014 rob rewes (prs) race to the top (b) wom 382 indiesonix west one music indie rock band western drums western electronic instruments western guitar electric happy bright happy celebratory happy excited happy feel good happy upbeat strong energetic uplifting motivational uplifting positive uplifting uplifting business corporate tv relentless uplifting and anthemic. spine tinglingly good. underscore" waveformpath="" version="Underscore" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="28704" name="Big Monster (a)" code="WOM 378 tk007" libraryid="6" albumid="606" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_378_Dive_Bar_Rock/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jez Miller (PRS)" comment="Rock classique sous stéroides, avec énorme riff de guitare saturée et batterie fracassante." styleid="5" lengthseconds="100" time="1:40" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_378_Dive_Bar_Rock/WOM_378_trk007_BIG_MONSTER_(A)_Jez_Miller_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, ROCK, ROCK, ROCK CLASSIQUE, ROCK, SPEED METAL, TRASH METAL, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, BAR, BAR À COCKTAILS, RESTAURANT, RESTOROUTE, BAR DE BIKERS, BAR A COCKTAILS, FILMS, ROAD MOVIE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, DRAMATIQUE, AGRESSIF, DRAMATIQUE, DANGEUREUX, DRAMATIQUE, FOUGUEUX, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, HEUREUX, BRUYANT, HEUREUX, EXCITÉ, EXCITE, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, SEXY, COCHON, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, DETERMINE, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, ENERGIQUE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, IMPLACABLE, FORT, FORT, MACHO, ARROGANCE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, GROUPE DE ROCK, BATTERIE, BATTERIE, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE Rock classique sous stéroides, avec énorme riff de guitare saturée et batterie fracassante. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 378 tk007 jez miller (prs) big monster (a) wom 378 dive bar rock west one music rock rock classic rock speed metal thrash metal main bar restaurant roadhouse biker bar movies road movie tv radio reality tv sports dramatic aggressive dangerous fiery intense happy boisterous excited upbeat sexy sleazy strong confident determined energetic exciting classic rock on steroids featuring a huge saturated guitar riff and thrashing drums. main dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="28709" name="Surf Stampede (a)" code="WOM 378 tk012" libraryid="6" albumid="606" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_378_Dive_Bar_Rock/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jez Miller (PRS)" comment="Surf rock entrainant avec une partie de guitare inoubliable et une batterie déchainée." styleid="5" lengthseconds="73" time="1:13" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_378_Dive_Bar_Rock/WOM_378_trk012_SURF_STAMPEDE_(A)_Jez_Miller_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, ROCK, ROCK, SURF ROCK, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, BAR, BAR À COCKTAILS, RESTAURANT, RESTOROUTE, BAR DE BIKERS, BAR A COCKTAILS, FILMS, ROAD MOVIE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, DRAMATIQUE, PASSIONNÉ, PASSIONNE, HEUREUX, EXCITÉ, EXCITE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, FUN, HEUREUX, GUILLERET, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, SEXY, COOL, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, EXCITANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, MACHO, ARROGANCE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, GROUPE DE ROCK, BATTERIE, BATTERIE, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE Surf rock entrainant avec une partie de guitare inoubliable et une batterie déchainée. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 378 tk012 jez miller (prs) surf stampede (a) wom 378 dive bar rock west one music rock rock surf rock main bar restaurant roadhouse biker bar movies road movie tv radio youth tv reality tv sports dramatic passionate happy excited feel good fun perky upbeat sexy cool strong confident exciting uplifting positive macho swagger movement rhythmic driving upbeat surf rock with a memorable guitar lick featuring hyper drums. main dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="28343" name="The Games Plays (a)" code="WOM 379 tk005" libraryid="6" albumid="600" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_379_Hip_Hop_Revolution/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Stefan A. Litrownik (BMI), Dylan R. Berry (BMI)" comment="Hip hop urbain sans concession avec synthés agressifs, beats trapus, MC masculin et chorus accorcheurs." styleid="29" lengthseconds="168" time="2:48" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_379_Hip_Hop_Revolution/WOM_379_trk005_THE_GAMES_PLAYS_(A)_Stefan_A._Litrownik_(BMI),_Dylan_R._Berry_(BMI)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="HIP HOP, URBAIN, HIP HOP, HIP HOP, URBAIN, HIP HOP, DIRTY SOUTH, HIP HOP, URBAIN, HIP HOP, GANGSTA, HIP HOP, URBAIN, RAP, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FETE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, DRAMATIQUE, AGRESSIF, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, SEXY, COOL, SEXY, SEXY, SEXY, COCHON, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, DETERMINE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, FORT, NERVEUX, QUI A DU CRAN, BATTERIE, BOITE À RYTHMES, BATTERIE ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ÉLECTRONIQUES, ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ELECTRONIQUES, VOCAL, MASCULIN, MASCULIN, VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, PHRASE VOCALE, CRI, APPEL, AVEC PAROLES, SUJET DE LA CHANSON, TRIOMPHE, VICTOIRE, VAINCRE L'ADVERSITÉ, ADVERSITE, VAINCRE L'ADVERSITE, MENÉ PAR L'ARTISTE, MENE PAR L'ARTISTE Hip hop urbain sans concession avec synthés agressifs, beats trapus, MC masculin et chorus accorcheurs. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 379 tk005 stefan a. litrownik (bmi) dylan r. berry (bmi) the games plays (a) wom 379 hip hop revolution west one music hip-hop urban hip hop urban hip hop dirty south gangsta rap main activities settings city urban human environment party tv radio children youth tv leisure lifestyle fashion style sports dramatic aggressive intense sexy cool sleazy strong confident determined exciting edgy gritty gritty urban hip hop featuring aggressive synths chunky beats male mc vocals and hooky choruses. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="28347" name="Take Me all the Way (a)" code="WOM 379 tk009" libraryid="6" albumid="600" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_379_Hip_Hop_Revolution/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Stefan A. Litrownik (BMI), Dylan R. Berry (BMI)" comment="Hip hop nerveux avec des couplets puissants appuyés par un MC masculin, et des chorus pop expansifs spectaculaires." styleid="29" lengthseconds="186" time="3:06" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_379_Hip_Hop_Revolution/WOM_379_trk009_TAKE_ME_ALL_THE_WAY_(A)_Stefan_A._Litrownik_(BMI),_Dylan_R._Berry_(BMI)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="HIP HOP, URBAIN, HIP HOP, HIP HOP, URBAIN, RAP, POP, POP, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FETE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, DRAMATIQUE, PASSIONNÉ, PASSIONNE, SEXY, COOL, SEXY, SEXY, SEXY, COCHON, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, DETERMINE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EMBLÉMATIQUE, EMBLEMATIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, NERVEUX, QUI A DU CRAN, BATTERIE, BOITE À RYTHMES, BATTERIE ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ÉLECTRONIQUES, ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ELECTRONIQUES, VOCAL, MASCULIN, MASCULIN, VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, PHRASE VOCALE, CRI, APPEL, AVEC PAROLES, SUJET DE LA CHANSON, VIE, MENÉ PAR L'ARTISTE, MENE PAR L'ARTISTE Hip hop nerveux avec des couplets puissants appuyés par un MC masculin, et des chorus pop expansifs spectaculaires. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 379 tk009 stefan a. litrownik (bmi) dylan r. berry (bmi) take me all the way (a) wom 379 hip hop revolution west one music hip-hop urban hip hop urban hip hop rap pop main activities settings city urban human environment party tv radio children youth tv leisure lifestyle fashion style sports dramatic passionate sexy cool sleazy strong confident determined exciting uplifting anthemic euphoric edgy hip hop featuring deep verses with male mc vocals and epic expansive pop choruses. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="28346" name="Live Life Every Night (a)" code="WOM 379 tk008" libraryid="6" albumid="600" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_379_Hip_Hop_Revolution/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Stefan A. Litrownik (BMI), Dylan R. Berry (BMI)" comment="Hip hop classieux avec synthés clinquants, beats solides, MC masculin et chorus pop." styleid="29" lengthseconds="181" time="3:01" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_379_Hip_Hop_Revolution/WOM_379_trk008_LIVE_LIFE_EVERY_NIGHT_(A)_Stefan_A._Litrownik_(BMI),_Dylan_R._Berry_(BMI)_West_One_Music_Limi.mp3" track="8" tracktotal="" search="HIP HOP, URBAIN, HIP HOP, HIP HOP, URBAIN, HIP HOP, DIRTY SOUTH, HIP HOP, URBAIN, RAP, POP, POP, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FETE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, DRAMATIQUE, AGRESSIF, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, SEXY, COOL, SEXY, SEXY, SEXY, COCHON, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, DETERMINE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, FORT, NERVEUX, QUI A DU CRAN, BATTERIE, BOITE À RYTHMES, BATTERIE ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ÉLECTRONIQUES, ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ELECTRONIQUES, VOCAL, MASCULIN, MASCULIN, VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, PHRASE VOCALE, CRI, APPEL, AVEC PAROLES, SUJET DE LA CHANSON, VIE, MENÉ PAR L'ARTISTE, MENE PAR L'ARTISTE Hip hop classieux avec synthés clinquants, beats solides, MC masculin et chorus pop. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 379 tk008 stefan a. litrownik (bmi) dylan r. berry (bmi) live life every night (a) wom 379 hip hop revolution west one music hip-hop urban hip hop urban hip hop dirty south rap pop main activities settings city urban human environment party tv radio children youth tv leisure lifestyle fashion style sports dramatic aggressive intense sexy cool sleazy strong confident determined exciting edgy gritty drums stylish hip hop with glitzy synths tough beats male mc vocals and pop choruses. main knees up, mess piano, cockney, east london, singalong, pub joanna, piano bar, piano-bar, live" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="28619" name="Long Way Down (a)" code="WOM 376 tk002" libraryid="6" albumid="604" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_376_Rebellion_by_Gem_and_the_Deadheads/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Tristan Ivemy (PRS), Gem M. Jones (PRS)" comment="Indie rock emblématique avec chorus explosifs, riff de guitare dévastateur et chant féminin puissant." styleid="5" lengthseconds="161" time="2:41" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_376_Rebellion_by_Gem_and_the_Deadheads/WOM_376_trk002_LONG_WAY_DOWN_(A)_Tristan_Ivemy_(PRS),_Gem_M._Jones_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limi.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, ROCK, BLUES, BLUES, ROCK, ROCK, ROCK ALTERNATIF, ROCK, GRUNGE, ROCK, HARD ROCK, ROCK, INDIE, ROCK, ROCK 'N' ROLL, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, DEFILE DE MODE, FILMS, FILMS INDÉPENDANTS, FILMS INDEPENDANTS, FILMS, ROAD MOVIE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, DRAMATIQUE, FOUGUEUX, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, DRAMATIQUE, PASSIONNÉ, PASSIONNE, SEXY, COOL, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, ENERGIQUE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, IMPLACABLE, FORT, FORT, COOL, NERVEUX, QUI A DU CRAN, CRADE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, GROUPE DE ROCK, BATTERIE, BATTERIE, CORDES, BASSE, BASSE ÉLECTRIQUE, BASSE ELECTRIQUE, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE, VOCAL, FÉMININ, FÉMININ, FEMININ, AVEC PAROLES, SUJET DE LA CHANSON, TRIOMPHE, VICTOIRE, VAINCRE L'ADVERSITÉ, ADVERSITE, VAINCRE L'ADVERSITE, MENÉ PAR L'ARTISTE, MENE PAR L'ARTISTE Indie rock emblématique avec chorus explosifs, riff de guitare dévastateur et chant féminin puissant. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 376 tk002 tristan ivemy (prs) gem m. jones (prs) long way down (a) wom 376 rebellion by gem and the deadheads west one music rock rock blues rock rock alternative rock rock grunge rock hard rock rock indie rock rock &amp; roll main activities settings city urban human environment activities settings fashion show movies indie films movies road movie tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure iconic indie rock with explosive choruses featuring a devastating guitar riff and powerful female vocals. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="28618" name="Automatic Response (a)" code="WOM 376 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="604" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_376_Rebellion_by_Gem_and_the_Deadheads/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Tristan Ivemy (PRS), Gem M. Jones (PRS)" comment="Guitares saturées, batterie et chant féminin à cran, cet indie rock contagieux a un pied aux USA et un autre en Europe." styleid="5" lengthseconds="203" time="3:23" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_376_Rebellion_by_Gem_and_the_Deadheads/WOM_376_trk001_AUTOMATIC_RESPONSE_(A)_Tristan_Ivemy_(PRS),_Gem_M._Jones_(PRS)_West_One_Music.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, ROCK, BLUES, BLUES, ROCK, ROCK, ROCK ALTERNATIF, ROCK, HARD ROCK, ROCK, INDIE, ROCK, ROCK 'N' ROLL, ROCK, SURF ROCK, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, DEFILE DE MODE, FILMS, FILMS INDÉPENDANTS, FILMS INDEPENDANTS, FILMS, ROAD MOVIE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, DRAMATIQUE, FOUGUEUX, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, DRAMATIQUE, PASSIONNÉ, PASSIONNE, SEXY, COOL, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, ENERGIQUE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, IMPLACABLE, FORT, FORT, COOL, NERVEUX, QUI A DU CRAN, CRADE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, GROUPE DE ROCK, BATTERIE, BATTERIE, CORDES, BASSE, BASSE ÉLECTRIQUE, BASSE ELECTRIQUE, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE, VOCAL, FÉMININ, FÉMININ, FEMININ, AVEC PAROLES, MENÉ PAR L'ARTISTE, MENE PAR L'ARTISTE Guitares saturées, batterie et chant féminin à cran, cet indie rock contagieux a un pied aux USA et un autre en Europe. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 376 tk001 tristan ivemy (prs) gem m. jones (prs) automatic response (a) wom 376 rebellion by gem and the deadheads west one music rock rock blues rock rock alternative rock rock hard rock rock indie rock rock &amp; roll rock surf rock main activities settings city urban human environment activities settings fashion show movies indie films movies road movie tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure contagious transatlantic indie rock featuring saturated guitars drums and edgy female vocals. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="28620" name="Bang Bang There Goes My Pistol (a)" code="WOM 376 tk003" libraryid="6" albumid="604" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_376_Rebellion_by_Gem_and_the_Deadheads/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Tristan Ivemy (PRS), Gem M. Jones (PRS)" comment="Rock à l'état pur. Une intro contenue explose en des chorus monumentaux avec chant féminin brut." styleid="5" lengthseconds="217" time="3:37" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_376_Rebellion_by_Gem_and_the_Deadheads/WOM_376_trk003_BANG_BANG_THERE_GOES_MY_PISTOL_(A)_Tristan_Ivemy_(PRS),_Gem_M._Jones_(PRS)_We.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, ROCK, BLUES, BLUES, ROCK, ROCK, ROCK ALTERNATIF, ROCK, GRUNGE, ROCK, HARD ROCK, ROCK, INDIE, ROCK, ROCK 'N' ROLL, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, DEFILE DE MODE, FILMS, FILMS INDÉPENDANTS, FILMS INDEPENDANTS, FILMS, ROAD MOVIE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, DRAMATIQUE, DANGEUREUX, DRAMATIQUE, FOUGUEUX, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, DRAMATIQUE, PASSIONNÉ, PASSIONNE, DRAMATIQUE, VIOLENT, EFFRAYANT, MENAÇANT, MENACANT, SEXY, COOL, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, ENERGIQUE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, IMPLACABLE, FORT, FORT, COOL, NERVEUX, QUI A DU CRAN, CRADE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, GROUPE DE ROCK, BATTERIE, BATTERIE, CORDES, BASSE, BASSE ÉLECTRIQUE, BASSE ELECTRIQUE, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE, VOCAL, FÉMININ, FÉMININ, FEMININ, AVEC PAROLES, SUJET DE LA CHANSON, MOMENTS DIFFICILES, DANGER, SUJET DE LA CHANSON, TRIOMPHE, VICTOIRE, VAINCRE L'ADVERSITÉ, ADVERSITE, VAINCRE L'ADVERSITE, MENÉ PAR L'ARTISTE, MENE PAR L'ARTISTE Rock à l'état pur. Une intro contenue explose en des chorus monumentaux avec chant féminin brut. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 376 tk003 tristan ivemy (prs) gem m. jones (prs) bang bang there goes my pistol (a) wom 376 rebellion by gem and the deadheads west one music rock rock blues rock rock alternative rock rock grunge rock hard rock rock indie rock rock &amp; roll main activities settings city urban human environment activities settings fashion show movies indie films movies road movie tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure pure unadulterated rock. pent-up verses explode into huge choruses with raw female vocals. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="28299" name="Timestretch (a)" code="WOM 371 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="599" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_371_Nightscapes/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Yppah Yppah (ASCAP), Josef Peters (BMI)" comment="Electro onirique avec samples vocaux hachés, guitares enjouées et beats puissants." styleid="1" lengthseconds="176" time="2:56" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_371_Nightscapes/WOM_371_trk001_TIMESTRETCH_(A)_Yppah_Yppah_(ASCAP),_Josef_Peters_(BMI)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ACID LOUNGE, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CHILL OUT, DOWNTEMPO, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, FILMS, FILMS INDÉPENDANTS, FILMS INDEPENDANTS, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, HI TECH, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, SEXY, COOL, SEXY, SEXY, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, FORT, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, COOL, NERVEUX, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, ACCELERE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, AERIEN, BATTERIE, BOITE À RYTHMES, BATTERIE ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ÉLECTRONIQUES, ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ELECTRONIQUES, CORDES, BASSE, BASSE ÉLECTRIQUE, BASSE ELECTRIQUE, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN MÉTAL, CORDES EN METAL, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE, VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, VOIX TRAITÉES, MODIFIÉES, MODIFIEES, VOIX TRAITEES, MENÉ PAR L'ARTISTE, MENE PAR L'ARTISTE Electro onirique avec samples vocaux hachés, guitares enjouées et beats puissants. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 371 tk001 yppah yppah (ascap) josef peters (bmi) timestretch (a) wom 371 nightscapes west one music dance electro club electronica club electronica acid lounge club electronica house deep house main activities settings city urban human environment activities settings futuristic activities settings showbiz movies indie films movies urban drama science technology industry hi tech tv dreamscape electronica featuring chopped vocal samples breezy guitars and strong beats. main dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="428434750" /><item id="28301" name="Pacific Drive (a)" code="WOM 371 tk003" libraryid="6" albumid="599" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_371_Nightscapes/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Yppah Yppah (ASCAP), Josef Peters (BMI)" comment="Synth pop reveuse avec beats spacieux, synthés légers et guitares tranquilles." styleid="1" lengthseconds="174" time="2:54" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_371_Nightscapes/WOM_371_trk003_PACIFIC_DRIVE_(A)_Yppah_Yppah_(ASCAP),_Josef_Peters_(BMI)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRONICA, POP, SYNTH POP, ROCK, INDIE, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, FILMS, FILMS INDÉPENDANTS, FILMS INDEPENDANTS, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, HI TECH, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, SEXY, COOL, SEXY, SEXY, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, FORT, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, COOL, NERVEUX, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, ACCELERE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, AERIEN, BATTERIE, BOITE À RYTHMES, BATTERIE ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ÉLECTRONIQUES, ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ELECTRONIQUES, CORDES, BASSE, BASSE ÉLECTRIQUE, BASSE ELECTRIQUE, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE, MENÉ PAR L'ARTISTE, MENE PAR L'ARTISTE Synth pop reveuse avec beats spacieux, synthés légers et guitares tranquilles. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 371 tk003 yppah yppah (ascap) josef peters (bmi) pacific drive (a) wom 371 nightscapes west one music dance electro club electronica pop synth pop rock indie main activities settings city urban human environment activities settings futuristic activities settings showbiz movies indie films movies urban drama science technology industry hi tech tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style dreamy synth pop with spacious beats cool guitars and airy synths. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="428434750" /><item id="28304" name="Look to the Stars (a)" code="WOM 371 tk006" libraryid="6" albumid="599" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_371_Nightscapes/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Yppah Yppah (ASCAP), Josef Peters (BMI)" comment="Synth pop downbeat relax avec beats puissants et synthés hypnotiques." styleid="1" lengthseconds="141" time="2:21" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_371_Nightscapes/WOM_371_trk006_LOOK_TO_THE_STARS_(A)_Yppah_Yppah_(ASCAP),_Josef_Peters_(BMI)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="6" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ACID LOUNGE, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CHILL OUT, DOWNTEMPO, POP, SYNTH POP, ROCK, INDIE, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, FILMS, FILMS INDÉPENDANTS, FILMS INDEPENDANTS, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, HI TECH, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, SEXY, COOL, SEXY, SEXY, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, FORT, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, COOL, NERVEUX, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, ACCELERE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, AERIEN, BATTERIE, BOITE À RYTHMES, BATTERIE ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ÉLECTRONIQUES, ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ELECTRONIQUES, CORDES, BASSE, BASSE ÉLECTRIQUE, BASSE ELECTRIQUE, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE, MENÉ PAR L'ARTISTE, MENE PAR L'ARTISTE Synth pop downbeat relax avec beats puissants et synthés hypnotiques. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 371 tk006 yppah yppah (ascap) josef peters (bmi) look to the stars (a) wom 371 nightscapes west one music dance electro club electronica club electronica acid lounge pop synth pop rock indie main activities settings city urban human environment activities settings futuristic activities settings showbiz movies indie films movies urban drama science technology industry hi tech tv radio chilled downbeat synth pop with hypnotic synths and strong beats. main dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="428434750" /><item id="27945" name="X-rated" code="WOM 367 tk011" libraryid="6" albumid="591" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_367_Twerk/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Diogo do Santos (PRS), Subatomic (PRS)" comment="Trap relax, sensuel et érotique, avec un groove moelleux et un chant féminin explicite." styleid="1" lengthseconds="117" time="1:57" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_367_Twerk/WOM_367_trk011_X-RATED_Diogo_do_Santos_(PRS),_Subatomic_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="11" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CHILL OUT, DOWNTEMPO, EASY LISTENING, LOUNGE, HIP HOP, URBAIN, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, BAR, BAR À COCKTAILS, RESTAURANT, BAR À COCKTAILS, BAR, BAR A COCKTAILS, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FETE, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, STRIPTEASE, BURLESQUE, FILMS, POUR ADULTES, PORNO, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, SEXY, COOL, SEXY, ÉROTIQUE , EROTIQUE, SEXY, CHARMEUR, SEXY, GRIVOIS, SEXY, SÉDUISANT, SEDUISANT, SEXY, SEXY, SEXY, COCHON, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, ENERGIQUE, FORT, EXALTANT, FORT, FORT, TENDRE, INTIME, COOL, NERVEUX, ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BATTERIE, BOITE À RYTHMES, BATTERIE ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, VOCAL, FÉMININ, FÉMININ, FEMININ Trap relax, sensuel et érotique, avec un groove moelleux et un chant féminin explicite. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 367 tk011 diogo do santos (prs) subatomic (prs) x-rated wom 367 twerk west one music dance electro club electronica club electronica club electronica chill out downtempo easy listening lounge hip hop urban main activities settings bar cocktail lounge restaurant cocktail lounge bar activities settings party activities settings striptease burlesque movies sultry and erotic chill trap with mellow groove and explicit female vocals. main dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="428434750" /><item id="27938" name="Twerk It (a)" code="WOM 367 tk004" libraryid="6" albumid="591" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_367_Twerk/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Daniel Merlot (SESAC), Adam Aukai Le Blanc (SESAC), Aurelien R. X. Poudat (SACEM), Aurelien A. Chavoix (SACEM), Sam Mehran (BMI) Sara Lynn Choi (BMI), Rosalie Pagarigan Villanueva (ASCAP)" comment="Tube qui claque avec beats urbains profonds et chant féminin bourré d'attitude." styleid="1" lengthseconds="173" time="2:53" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_367_Twerk/WOM_367_trk004_TWERK_IT_(A)_Daniel_Merlot_(SESAC),_Adam_Aukai_Le_Blanc_(SESAC),_Aurelien_R._X._Poudat_(SACEM),_Aurelien_A.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HIP HOP, URBAIN, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FETE, FILMS, POUR ADULTES, PORNO, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, SEXY, COOL, SEXY, ÉROTIQUE , EROTIQUE, SEXY, CHARMEUR, SEXY, SÉDUISANT, SEDUISANT, SEXY, SEXY, SEXY, COCHON, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, ENERGIQUE, COOL, NERVEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, BONDISSANT, ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BATTERIE, BOITE À RYTHMES, BATTERIE ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, VOCAL, FÉMININ, FÉMININ, FEMININ Tube qui claque avec beats urbains profonds et chant féminin bourré d'attitude. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 367 tk004 daniel merlot (sesac) adam aukai le blanc (sesac) aurelien r. x. poudat (sacem) aurelien a. chavoix (sacem) sam mehran (bmi) sara lynn choi (bmi) rosalie pagarigan villanueva (ascap) twerk it (a) wom 367 twerk west one music dance electro club electronica club electronica hip hop urban main activities settings party movies adult entertainment porn movies urban drama tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio reality tv sexy cool sexy erotic sexy flirtatious sexy seductive sexy sexy sexy sleazy slamming party anthem with deep urban beats and attitude-laden female vocals. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="428434750" /><item id="27956" name="Pop it Hard (b)" code="WOM 367 tk022" libraryid="6" albumid="591" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_367_Twerk/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Laurence D. Holcombe (PRS), Sample Magic (PRS), David Felton (PRS)" comment="Hip hop style dirty south, puissant et lourd, avec synthés trap et percussions." styleid="1" lengthseconds="197" time="3:17" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_367_Twerk/WOM_367_trk022_POP_IT_HARD_(B)_Laurence_D._Holcombe_(PRS),_Sample_Magic_(PRS),_David_Felton_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="22" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HIP HOP, URBAIN, UNDERSCORE, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FETE, FILMS, POUR ADULTES, PORNO, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, SEXY, COOL, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, ENERGIQUE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, IMPLACABLE, FORT, FORT, COOL, NERVEUX, QUI A DU CRAN, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE Hip hop style dirty south, puissant et lourd, avec synthés trap et percussions. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 367 tk022 laurence d. holcombe (prs) sample magic (prs) david felton (prs) pop it hard (b) wom 367 twerk west one music dance electro club electronica club electronica hip hop urban underscore activities settings city urban human environment activities settings party movies adult entertainment porn movies urban drama tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio hard and heavy dirty southern hip hop with trap synths and percussion. underscore" waveformpath="" version="Underscore" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="428434750" /><item id="27957" name="Midnight Ecstasy (b)" code="WOM 367 tk023" libraryid="6" albumid="591" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_367_Twerk/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Huw Williams (PRS)" comment="Une intro évocatrice précède un trapstep euphorique et des synthés aiguisés comme une lame de rasoir." styleid="1" lengthseconds="119" time="1:59" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_367_Twerk/WOM_367_trk023_MIDNIGHT_ECSTASY_(B)_Huw_Williams_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="23" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, DUBSTEP, HIP HOP, URBAIN, UNDERSCORE, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FETE, FILMS, POUR ADULTES, PORNO, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, DRAMATIQUE, AGRESSIF, DRAMATIQUE, FOUGUEUX, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, SEXY, COOL, SEXY, ÉROTIQUE , EROTIQUE, SEXY, CHARMEUR, SEXY, SÉDUISANT, SEDUISANT, SEXY, SEXY, SEXY, COCHON, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, DETERMINE, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, ENERGIQUE, COOL, NERVEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, BONDISSANT, ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BATTERIE, BOITE À RYTHMES, BATTERIE ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE Une intro évocatrice précède un trapstep euphorique et des synthés aiguisés comme une lame de rasoir. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 367 tk023 huw williams (prs) midnight ecstasy (b) wom 367 twerk west one music dance electro club electronica club electronica club electronica dubstep hip hop urban underscore activities settings party movies adult entertainment porn movies urban drama tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio reality tv dramatic aggressive dramatic fiery dramatic atmospheric intro drops into euphoric trapstep with razor sharp synths. underscore" waveformpath="" version="Underscore" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="428434750" /><item id="18607" name="Standing for Freedom (a)" code="WOM 361 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="384" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_361_Female_Indie_Pop/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Victoria F. Beaumont (PRS)" comment="Synth pop positive et entrainante, avec chant féminin énergique, basse puissante et batterie." styleid="36" lengthseconds="220" time="3:40" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_361_Female_Indie_Pop/WOM_361_trk001_STANDING_FOR_FREEDOM_(A)_Victoria_F._Beaumont_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="POP, POP, POP, ELECTRO POP, POP, SYNTH POP, ROCK, ROCK ALTERNATIF, ROCK, INDIE, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, ROAD TRIP, FILMS, ƒPIQUE, EPIQUE, FILMS, FILMS INDƒPENDANTS, FILMS INDEPENDANTS, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TƒLƒ RƒALITƒ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, FESTIF, HEUREUX, EXCITƒ, EXCITE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, FUN, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, SEXY, COOL, FORT, ƒNERGIQUE, ENERGIQUE, FORT, ƒPIQUE, EPIQUE, FORT, PUISSANT, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EMBLƒMATIQUE, EMBLEMATIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EVOLUTIF, MONTEE, MONTƒE, EVOLUTION, NERVEUX, MƒLODIQUE, LYRIQUE, MELODIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, BATTERIE, BATTERIE, BATTERIE, TOMS, INSTRUMENTS ƒLECTRONIQUES, ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ELECTRONIQUES, CORDES, BASSE, BASSE ƒLECTRIQUE, BASSE ELECTRIQUE, CORDES, GUITARE, ƒLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE, VOCAL, FƒMININ, FEMININ, AVEC PAROLES, SUJET DE LA CHANSON, ESPOIR, INSPIRATION, SUJET DE LA CHANSON, VIE, PASSAGE Ë L'AGE ADULTE, PASSAGE A L'AGE ADULTE, SUJET DE LA CHANSON, TRIOMPHE, VICTOIRE, MOTIVATION, MENƒ PAR L'ARTISTE, MENE PAR L'ARTISTE Synth pop positive et entrainante, avec chant féminin énergique, basse puissante et batterie. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 361 tk001 victoria f. beaumont (prs) standing for freedom (a) wom 361 female indie pop west one music indie pop pop electro pop pop synth pop rock alternative rock rock indie main activities settings road trip movies epic movies indie films movies urban drama tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio reality tv tv radio sports happy positive and upbeat synth pop with energetic female vocals and driving bass and drums. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="428434750" /><item id="18612" name="Addicted to You (a)" code="WOM 361 tk006" libraryid="6" albumid="384" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_361_Female_Indie_Pop/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Mike Reed (PRS), Tom Howe (PRS)" comment="Chanson pop féminine émouvante avec guitares électriques décidées, piano et grosse batterie." styleid="36" lengthseconds="205" time="3:25" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_361_Female_Indie_Pop/WOM_361_trk006_ADDICTED_TO_YOU_(A)_Mike_Reed_(PRS),_Tom_Howe_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="6" tracktotal="" search="POP, POP, EASY LISTENING, MIDDLE OF THE ROAD, FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, SOUL CONTEMPORAINE, ROCK, ROCK ALTERNATIF, ROCK, INDIE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ƒPIQUE, EPIQUE, FILMS, FILMS INDƒPENDANTS, FILMS INDEPENDANTS, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TƒLƒ RƒALITƒ, TELE REALITE, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, SEXY, COOL, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, ƒNERGIQUE, ENERGIQUE, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, FORT, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, FIER, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EVOLUTIF, MONTEE, MONTƒE, EVOLUTION, NERVEUX, MƒLODIQUE, LYRIQUE, MELODIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, BATTERIE, BATTERIE, BATTERIE, TOMS, INSTRUMENTS ƒLECTRONIQUES, ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ELECTRONIQUES, CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, BASSE, BASSE ƒLECTRIQUE, BASSE ELECTRIQUE, CORDES, GUITARE, ƒLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE, VOCAL, FƒMININ, FEMININ, AVEC PAROLES, SUJET DE LA CHANSON, AMOUR, MENƒ PAR L'ARTISTE, MENE PAR L'ARTISTE Chanson pop féminine émouvante avec guitares électriques décidées, piano et grosse batterie. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 361 tk006 mike reed (prs) tom howe (prs) addicted to you (a) wom 361 female indie pop west one music indie pop easy listening middle of the road funk soul r&amp;b contemporary soul rock alternative rock rock indie main movies epic movies indie films movies urban drama tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio reality tv happy upbeat sexy soulful female vocal pop song with confident electric guitars piano and strong drums. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="428434750" /><item id="13514" name="You Should Have Known (a)" code="WOM 358 tk008" libraryid="6" albumid="263" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_358_Urban_Charts/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Nigel C. A. Thompson / Emily Taylor / Tom Canning / Robert C. E. Bagshaw" comment="Duo hip-hop explosif avec synthés puissants, basse poussée et chorus pop accrocheur." styleid="6" lengthseconds="180" time="3:00" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_358_Urban_Charts/WOM_358_trk008_YOU_SHOULD_HAVE_KNOWN_(A)_Nigel_C._A._Thompson_Emily_Taylor_Tom_Canning_Robert_C._E._Bagshaw_West_O.mp3" track="8" tracktotal="" search="HIP HOP, URBAIN, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HIP HOP, URBAIN, RAP, POP, POP, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FETE, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, ELEMENTS, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, DETERMINE, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, ENERGIQUE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EMBLÉMATIQUE, EMBLEMATIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, COOL, NERVEUX, QUI A DU CRAN, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INSISTANT, ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BATTERIE, BOITE À RYTHMES, BATTERIE ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, VOCAL, FÉMININ, FÉMININ, FEMININ, VOCAL, MASCULIN, MASCULIN, AVEC PAROLES, SUJET DE LA CHANSON, BON TEMPS, FETE, FUN, MENÉ PAR L'ARTISTE, MENE PAR L'ARTISTE Duo hip-hop explosif avec synthés puissants, basse poussée et chorus pop accrocheur. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 358 tk008 nigel c. a. thompson emily taylor tom canning robert c. e. bagshaw you should have known (a) wom 358 urban charts west one music pop hip hop urban club electronica club electronica hip hop urban rap pop main activities settings city urban human environment activities settings party activities settings showbiz nature wildlife the elements land sun tropical seaside tv radio children youth tv tv radio explosive urban hip hop duet with driving synths pumping bass and hooky pop chorus. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="13516" name="Who Got the Power (a)" code="WOM 358 tk010" libraryid="6" albumid="263" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_358_Urban_Charts/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Nigel C. A. Thompson / Emily Taylor / Robert C. E. Bagshaw" comment="Hip-hop urbain à cran et qui envoie du bois. Avec rap masculin agressif." styleid="6" lengthseconds="189" time="3:09" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_358_Urban_Charts/WOM_358_trk010_WHO_GOT_THE_POWER_(A)_Nigel_C._A._Thompson_Emily_Taylor_Robert_C._E._Bagshaw_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="10" tracktotal="" search="HIP HOP, URBAIN, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HIP HOP, URBAIN, RAP, POP, POP, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FETE, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, ELEMENTS, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, DRAMATIQUE, AGRESSIF, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, DETERMINE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, COOL, NERVEUX, QUI A DU CRAN, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INSISTANT, ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BATTERIE, BOITE À RYTHMES, BATTERIE ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, VOCAL, MASCULIN, MASCULIN, AVEC PAROLES, SUJET DE LA CHANSON, TRIOMPHE, VICTOIRE, VAINCRE L'ADVERSITÉ, ADVERSITE, VAINCRE L'ADVERSITE, MENÉ PAR L'ARTISTE, MENE PAR L'ARTISTE Hip-hop urbain à cran et qui envoie du bois. Avec rap masculin agressif. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 358 tk010 nigel c. a. thompson emily taylor robert c. e. bagshaw who got the power (a) wom 358 urban charts west one music pop hip hop urban club electronica club electronica hip hop urban rap pop main activities settings city urban human environment activities settings party activities settings showbiz nature wildlife the elements land sun tropical seaside tv radio children youth tv tv radio pumping gritty urban hip hop with aggressive male rapping. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="13525" name="Rooftops (b)" code="WOM 358 tk019" libraryid="6" albumid="263" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_358_Urban_Charts/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Emily Taylor / Tara Chinn / Robert C. E. Bagshaw" comment="Pop urbaine qui claque avec synthés dubstep." styleid="6" lengthseconds="184" time="3:04" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_358_Urban_Charts/WOM_358_trk019_ROOFTOPS_(B)_Emily_Taylor_Tara_Chinn_Robert_C._E._Bagshaw_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="19" tracktotal="" search="HIP HOP, URBAIN, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, DUBSTEP, FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, R &amp; B CLASSIQUE, POP, POP, UNDERSCORE, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FETE, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, ELEMENTS, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, SEXY, SÉDUISANT, SEDUISANT, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, DETERMINE, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EMBLÉMATIQUE, EMBLEMATIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, COOL, NERVEUX, QUI A DU CRAN, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INSISTANT, ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BATTERIE, BOITE À RYTHMES, BATTERIE ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE Pop urbaine qui claque avec synthés dubstep. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 358 tk019 emily taylor tara chinn robert c. e. bagshaw rooftops (b) wom 358 urban charts west one music pop hip hop urban club electronica dubstep funk soul r&amp;b classic r&amp;b pop underscore activities settings city urban human environment activities settings party activities settings showbiz nature wildlife the elements land sun tropical seaside tv radio children youth tv tv slamming urban pop featuring dubstep synths. underscore" waveformpath="" version="Underscore" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="694" name="Mojave (a)" code="FEM 023 tk001" libraryid="2" albumid="21" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_023_Unbreakable/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Daniel Heath" comment="Pour trailer pop sexy. S'ouvre sur des bois tordus, des effets sonores sinistres et un cri féminin déformé à 0:08, pour amener un thème de guitare western emblématique à partir de 0:17. Carillon et ambiances sci-fi cool à 0:35. Coup et carillon à 0:52, ensuite une montée de cordes apporte une certaine émotion. À 1:09, coup et carillon et changement de la mélodie de guitare. Drop à 1:26 avec une partie de cordes haletantes et batterie qui crée le drame. Drop à 1:43 en un back-end de cordes et batterie qui se développe jusqu'à 2:23." styleid="2" lengthseconds="154" time="2:34" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_023_Unbreakable/FEM_023_trk001_MOJAVE_(A)_Daniel_Heath_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, ORCHESTRAL HYBRIDE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, POP, POP, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ART ET ESSAI, FILMS, BACK END, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, FILMS INDÉPENDANTS, FILMS INDEPENDANTS, FILMS, IDYLLE, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, FILMS, WESTERN, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, MÉLANCOLIE, DEPRIMANT, MELANCOLIE, SÉRIEUX, ÉMOUVANT, SERIEUX, EMOUVANT, SÉRIEUX, ATTENTIONNÉ, SERIEUX, ATTENTIONNE, SEXY, SÉDUISANT, SEDUISANT, SEXY, SEXY, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, DETERMINE, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, FORT, BEAU, EVOLUTIF, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, CUIVRES, SECTION DE CUIVRES, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, BOIS, SECTION DE BOIS, BATTERIE, BATTERIE, BATTERIE, TIMBALES, BATTERIE, TOMS, CORDES, GUITARE, BOTTLENECK, SLIDE, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE Pour trailer pop sexy. S'ouvre sur des bois tordus, des effets sonores sinistres et un cri féminin déformé à 0:08, pour amener un thème de guitare western emblématique à partir de 0:17. Carillon et ambiances sci-fi cool à 0:35. Coup et carillon à 0:52, ensuite une montée de cordes apporte une certaine émotion. À 1:09, coup et carillon et changement de la mélodie de guitare. Drop à 1:26 avec une partie de cordes haletantes et batterie qui crée le drame. Drop à 1:43 en un back-end de cordes et batterie qui se développe jusqu'à 2:23. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz fem 023 tk001 daniel heath mojave (a) fem 023 unbreakable fired earth music trailer film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral orchestral hybrid film score orchestral panoramic pop main movies art house movies back end movies crime detective mystery movies human drama movies indie films movies romance movies urban drama movies western sexy commercial pop trailer track. opens with twisted woodwind eerie modern sound effects warped female vocal cry at 0:08 into iconic western guitar theme from 0:17. cool atmospheres and chime at 0:35. hit and chime at 0:52 then strings swell and create emotion. 1:09 chime and hit and change in guitar melody. drop down at 1:26 into chugging string and drum section building drama. drop out at 1:43 into driving string and drum back-end building to 2:23. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215285" /><item id="10823" name="Don't Make Me Wait (a)" code="WOM 388 tk005" libraryid="6" albumid="211" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_388_EDM/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Patrick P. P. Hagenaar (PRS)" comment="House exaltante façon EDM avec drops qui mettent de bonne humeur, beats solides et samples hachés de voix." styleid="1" lengthseconds="211" time="3:31" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_388_EDM/WOM_388_trk005_DON'T_MAKE_ME_WAIT_(A)_Patrick_P._P._Hagenaar_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HOUSE, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FETE, FÊTE GÉNÉRALE, FETE GENERALE, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, HEUREUX, FESTIF, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, FUN, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, SEXY, COOL, SEXY, SEXY, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, ENERGIQUE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EMBLÉMATIQUE, EMBLEMATIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, COOL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, RÉPÉTITIF, REPETITIF, ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BATTERIE, BOITE À RYTHMES, BATTERIE ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, PHRASE VOCALE, CRI, APPEL House exaltante façon EDM avec drops qui mettent de bonne humeur, beats solides et samples hachés de voix. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 388 tk005 patrick p. p. hagenaar (prs) don't make me wait (a) wom 388 edm west one music dance electro main cool sexy cool happy fun sexy sexy electronic happy upbeat strong strong happy feel good strong exciting strong confident strong energetic happy celebratory movies urban drama uplifting anthemic uplifting euphoric uplifting positive uplifting uplifting club uplifting edm house featuring feelgood drops strong beats and chopped vocal samples. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="10829" name="Glowstick (a)" code="WOM 388 tk011" libraryid="6" albumid="211" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_388_EDM/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Laurence D. Holcombe (PRS), Michele Russi (PRS)" comment="Euro house ƒestive façon EDM, avec synthés pleins de vie et beats four-to-the-floor qui claquent." styleid="1" lengthseconds="154" time="2:34" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_388_EDM/WOM_388_trk011_GLOWSTICK_(A)_Laurence_D._Holcombe_(PRS),_Michele_Russi_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="11" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HOUSE, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FETE, FÊTE GÉNÉRALE, FETE GENERALE, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, HEUREUX, FESTIF, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, FUN, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, SEXY, COOL, SEXY, SEXY, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, ENERGIQUE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EMBLÉMATIQUE, EMBLEMATIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, COOL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, RÉPÉTITIF, REPETITIF, ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BATTERIE, BOITE À RYTHMES, BATTERIE ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE Euro house ƒestive façon EDM, avec synthés pleins de vie et beats four-to-the-floor qui claquent. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 388 tk011 laurence d. holcombe (prs) michele russi (prs) glowstick (a) wom 388 edm west one music dance electro main cool sexy cool happy fun sexy sexy electronic happy upbeat strong strong strong exciting happy feel good strong confident strong energetic happy celebratory uplifting anthemic uplifting euphoric uplifting positive movies urban drama uplifting uplifting club celebratory euro edm house featuring lively synths and slamming 4-to-the-floor beats. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="10820" name="Surround Me (a)" code="WOM 388 tk002" libraryid="6" albumid="211" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_388_EDM/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Etostone (PRS), Kid Moxie (BMI)" comment="Electro pop éthérée façon EDM, avec synthés cool, beats imparables et chant féminin reveur." styleid="1" lengthseconds="186" time="3:06" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_388_EDM/WOM_388_trk002_SURROUND_ME_(A)_Etostone_(PRS),_Kid_Moxie_(BMI)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HOUSE, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, EURO POP, POP, ELECTRO POP, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FETE, FÊTE GÉNÉRALE, FETE GENERALE, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, SPORT, EXERCICE, FITNESS, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, SEXY, COOL, SEXY, CHARMEUR, SEXY, SÉDUISANT, SEDUISANT, SEXY, SEXY, SEXY, SENSUEL, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, ENERGIQUE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, COOL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BATTERIE, BOITE À RYTHMES, BATTERIE ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, VOCAL, FÉMININ, FÉMININ, FEMININ, AVEC PAROLES, SUJET DE LA CHANSON, AMOUR, TENSION SEXUELLE, MENÉ PAR L'ARTISTE, MENE PAR L'ARTISTE Electro pop éthérée façon EDM, avec synthés cool, beats imparables et chant féminin reveur. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 388 tk002 etostone (prs) kid moxie (bmi) surround me (a) wom 388 edm west one music dance electro main cool sexy sexy sexy cool electronic has lyrics sexy sultry strong strong artist-driven sexy seductive peaceful dreamy strong exciting pop electro pop sexy flirtatious strong confident strong energetic uplifting euphoric uplifting positive movies urban drama ethereal electro pop edm with cool synths driving beats and dreamy female vocals. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="417" name="Screw It (a)" code="EDS 015 tk004" libraryid="1" albumid="13" albumartpath="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_015_Trap/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jerry Torres (SOCAN)" comment="Trap urbain crade avec synthés vicelards, drops monumentaux et effets vocaux tordus." styleid="1" lengthseconds="166" time="2:46" samplefile="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_015_Trap/EDS_015_trk004_SCREW_IT_(A)_Jerry_Torres_(SOCAN)_Electronic_Dance_Series.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HIP HOP, URBAIN, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FETE, FÊTE GÉNÉRALE, FETE GENERALE, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, DRAMATIQUE, AGRESSIF, DRAMATIQUE, DANGEUREUX, DRAMATIQUE, FOUGUEUX, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, SEXY, COOL, SEXY, ÉROTIQUE , EROTIQUE, SEXY, COCHON, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, ENERGIQUE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, FORT, COOL, NERVEUX, GLITCHY, QUI A DU CRAN, ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BATTERIE, BOITE À RYTHMES, BATTERIE ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, VOIX TRAITÉES, MODIFIÉES, MODIFIEES, VOIX TRAITEES Trap urbain crade avec synthés vicelards, drops monumentaux et effets vocaux tordus. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz eds 015 tk004 jerry torres (socan) screw it (a) eds 015 trap electronic dance series dance electro main cool edgy gritty glitchy sexy cool electronic sexy erotic sexy sleazy hip hop urban strong strong dramatic fiery strong exciting dramatic intense strong confident strong energetic dramatic dangerous movies urban drama dramatic aggressive tv radio program formats filthy urban trap with sleazy synths huge drops and twisted vocal fx. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Electronic Dance Series" cae="00666407133" /><item id="415" name="Headcase (a)" code="EDS 015 tk002" libraryid="1" albumid="13" albumartpath="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_015_Trap/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Oscar Hill (PRS), Justin Black (PRS)" comment="Trap de l'underground glitchy avec développements atmosphériques et drops puissants avec bouts de voix." styleid="1" lengthseconds="203" time="3:23" samplefile="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_015_Trap/EDS_015_trk002_HEADCASE_(A)_Oscar_Hill_(PRS),_Justin_Black_(PRS)_Electronic_Dance_Series.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HIP HOP, URBAIN, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FETE, FÊTE GÉNÉRALE, FETE GENERALE, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, DRAMATIQUE, AGRESSIF, DRAMATIQUE, DANGEUREUX, DRAMATIQUE, FOUGUEUX, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, SEXY, COOL, SEXY, ÉROTIQUE , EROTIQUE, SEXY, COCHON, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, ENERGIQUE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, FORT, COOL, NERVEUX, GLITCHY, QUI A DU CRAN, ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BATTERIE, BOITE À RYTHMES, BATTERIE ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, PHRASE VOCALE, CRI, APPEL Trap de l'underground glitchy avec développements atmosphériques et drops puissants avec bouts de voix. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz eds 015 tk002 oscar hill (prs) justin black (prs) headcase (a) eds 015 trap electronic dance series dance electro main cool edgy gritty glitchy sexy cool electronic sexy erotic sexy sleazy hip hop urban strong strong dramatic fiery strong exciting dramatic intense strong confident strong energetic dramatic dangerous movies urban drama dramatic aggressive activities &amp; settings glitchy underground trap with atmospheric builds and deep drops with vocal chops. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Electronic Dance Series" cae="00666407133" /><item id="29443" name="Circuit Bender (a)" code="WOM 386 tk003" libraryid="6" albumid="620" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_386_Future_Glitch/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Samuel R. C. Sutton (PRS), Daniel Bewick (PRS)" comment="Electro sombre et atmosphérique qui se développe jusqu'à des drops euphoriques avec beats coriaces et synthés glitchy." styleid="1" lengthseconds="146" time="2:26" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_386_Future_Glitch/WOM_386_trk003_CIRCUIT_BENDER_(A)_Samuel_R._C._Sutton_(PRS),_Daniel_Bewick_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, DUBSTEP, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, INDUSTRIE LOURDE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, DRAMATIQUE, PASSIONNÉ, PASSIONNE, SEXY, COOL, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, ENERGIQUE, FORT, ÉPIQUE, EPIQUE, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, IMPLACABLE, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, JAILLIR, NERVEUX, GLITCHY, QUI A DU CRAN, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INDUSTRIE, MACHINES, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, MÉCANIQUE, ROBOTIQUE, MECANIQUE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, AERIEN, BATTERIE, BOITE À RYTHMES, BATTERIE ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ÉLECTRONIQUES, ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ELECTRONIQUES Electro sombre et atmosphérique qui se développe jusqu'à des drops euphoriques avec beats coriaces et synthés glitchy. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 386 tk003 samuel r. c. sutton (prs) daniel bewick (prs) circuit bender (a) wom 386 future glitch west one music dance electro main edgy gritty glitchy sexy cool strong epic disturbing dark powerful confident dramatic intense energetic relentless uplifting soaring euphoric movies urban drama passionate mysterious suspenseful club electronica dubstep movement rhythmic driving western atmospheric dark electronica builds to euphoric drops featuring tough beats and glitched-up synths. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="508" name="A New Revolution (a)" code="EDS 014 tk011" libraryid="1" albumid="15" albumartpath="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_014_Dubstep_Breaks_Glitch_Hop/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jesse L. Josefsson (BMI), John A. Pregler (ASCAP)" comment="Dubstep indus glitchy avec beats coriaces, synthés club et samples de voix." styleid="1" lengthseconds="115" time="1:55" samplefile="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_014_Dubstep_Breaks_Glitch_Hop/EDS_014_trk011_A_NEW_REVOLUTION_(A)_Jesse_L._Josefsson_(BMI),_John_A._Pregler_(ASCAP)_Electronic_Danc.mp3" track="11" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, DUBSTEP, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FETE, SOIRÉE, SOIREE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, HI TECH, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, DRAMATIQUE, FOUGUEUX, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, SEXY, COOL, SEXY, SÉDUISANT, SEDUISANT, SEXY, SEXY, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, DETERMINE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, IMPLACABLE, FORT, FORT, COOL, NERVEUX, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, GLITCHY, QUI A DU CRAN, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INDUSTRIE, MACHINES, ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BATTERIE, BOITE À RYTHMES, BATTERIE ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, VOIX TRAITÉES, MODIFIÉES, MODIFIEES, VOIX TRAITEES Dubstep indus glitchy avec beats coriaces, synthés club et samples de voix. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz eds 014 tk011 jesse l. josefsson (bmi) john a. pregler (ascap) a new revolution (a) eds 014 dubstep breaks &amp; glitch hop electronic dance series dance electro main cool edgy gritty glitchy sexy cool sexy sexy electronic strong strong dramatic fiery sexy seductive disturbing dark strong exciting dramatic intense strong confident strong determined strong relentless glamorous luxurious disturbing mysterious club electronica industrial glitched-up dubstep with tough beats clubby synths and vocal samples. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Electronic Dance Series" cae="00666407133" /><item id="498" name="Beach Riot (a)" code="EDS 014 tk001" libraryid="1" albumid="15" albumartpath="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_014_Dubstep_Breaks_Glitch_Hop/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Huw Williams (PRS), Victoria E. Harrison (PRS), The Octopus (PRS)" comment="Dubstep euphorique avec beats coriaces, synthés pechus et chant féminin atmosphérique." styleid="1" lengthseconds="210" time="3:30" samplefile="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_014_Dubstep_Breaks_Glitch_Hop/EDS_014_trk001_BEACH_RIOT_(A)_Huw_Williams_(PRS),_Victoria_E._Harrison_(PRS),_The_Octopus_(PRS)_Elect.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, DUBSTEP, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FETE, SOIRÉE, SOIREE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, HI TECH, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, SEXY, COOL, SEXY, SÉDUISANT, SEDUISANT, SEXY, SEXY, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, DETERMINE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, IMPLACABLE, FORT, FORT, COOL, NERVEUX, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, GLITCHY, QUI A DU CRAN, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INDUSTRIE, MACHINES, ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BATTERIE, BOITE À RYTHMES, BATTERIE ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, VOCAL, FÉMININ, FÉMININ, FEMININ Dubstep euphorique avec beats coriaces, synthés pechus et chant féminin atmosphérique. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live eds 014 tk001 huw williams (prs) victoria e. harrison (prs) the octopus (prs) beach riot (a) eds 014 dubstep breaks &amp; glitch hop electronic dance series dance electro main cool edgy gritty glitchy sexy cool sexy sexy electronic strong strong sexy seductive strong exciting strong confident strong determined strong relentless vocals female female glamorous luxurious club electronica dubstep activities &amp; settings futuristic tv euphoric dubstep featuring tough beats pumping synths and atmospheric female vocals. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Electronic Dance Series" cae="00666407133" /><item id="499" name="Kinetic Shift (a)" code="EDS 014 tk002" libraryid="1" albumid="15" albumartpath="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_014_Dubstep_Breaks_Glitch_Hop/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Huw Williams (PRS)" comment="Dubstep glitch hop énergique avec synthés surexcités, basse qui gronde et voix modifiées." styleid="1" lengthseconds="134" time="2:14" samplefile="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_014_Dubstep_Breaks_Glitch_Hop/EDS_014_trk002_KINETIC_SHIFT_(A)_Huw_Williams_(PRS)_Electronic_Dance_Series.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, DUBSTEP, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FETE, SOIRÉE, SOIREE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, HI TECH, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, SEXY, COOL, SEXY, SÉDUISANT, SEDUISANT, SEXY, SEXY, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, DETERMINE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, IMPLACABLE, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, COOL, NERVEUX, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, GLITCHY, QUI A DU CRAN, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INDUSTRIE, MACHINES, ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BATTERIE, BOITE À RYTHMES, BATTERIE ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, VOIX TRAITÉES, MODIFIÉES, MODIFIEES, VOIX TRAITEES Dubstep glitch hop énergique avec synthés surexcités, basse qui gronde et voix modifiées. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz eds 014 tk002 huw williams (prs) kinetic shift (a) eds 014 dubstep breaks &amp; glitch hop electronic dance series dance electro main cool edgy gritty glitchy sexy cool sexy sexy electronic strong strong sexy seductive strong exciting strong confident strong determined strong relentless uplifting euphoric uplifting positive uplifting uplifting glamorous luxurious uplifting motivational club energetic dubstep glitch hop with hyper synths growling bass processed vocals. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Electronic Dance Series" cae="00666407133" /><item id="28973" name="Fast Forward (a)" code="WOM 383 tk007" libraryid="6" albumid="610" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_383_Elektrobeat/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Lewis (PRS), Thomas A. Swindells (PRS)" comment="Electronica évocatrice et positive avec harpe, breaks béton et effets vocaux qui s'estompent." styleid="1" lengthseconds="188" time="3:08" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_383_Elektrobeat/WOM_383_trk007_FAST_FORWARD_(A)_Richard_Lewis_(PRS),_Thomas_A._Swindells_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRONICA, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, HI TECH, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, SERIEUX, DETERMINE, SEXY, COOL, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, DETERMINE, FORT, EXALTANT, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, COOL, NERVEUX, BATTERIE, INSTRUMENTS ÉLECTRONIQUES, ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ELECTRONIQUES, CORDES, HARPE, VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, VOIX TRAITÉES, MODIFIÉES, MODIFIEES, VOIX TRAITEES Electronica évocatrice et positive avec harpe, breaks béton et effets vocaux qui s'estompent. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 383 tk007 richard lewis (prs) thomas a. swindells (prs) fast forward (a) wom 383 elektrobeat west one music dance electro western drums western electronic instruments western harp vocals vocal textures treated vocal peaceful dreamy serious determined sexy cool strong confident strong determined strong exhilarating tender nostalgic tender warm uplifting inspirational uplifting motivational positive atmospheric electronica featuring harp solid breaks and washy vocal fx. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="28971" name="Infinite Sky (a)" code="WOM 383 tk005" libraryid="6" albumid="610" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_383_Elektrobeat/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Lewis (PRS), Thomas A. Swindells (PRS)" comment="Electronica envoutante et exaltante, avec de solides beats, des synthés et des effets vocaux atmosphériques." styleid="1" lengthseconds="182" time="3:02" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_383_Elektrobeat/WOM_383_trk005_INFINITE_SKY_(A)_Richard_Lewis_(PRS),_Thomas_A._Swindells_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRONICA, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, HI TECH, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, SERIEUX, DETERMINE, SEXY, COOL, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, DETERMINE, FORT, EXALTANT, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EMBLÉMATIQUE, EMBLEMATIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, JAILLIR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, COOL, NERVEUX, BATTERIE, INSTRUMENTS ÉLECTRONIQUES, ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ELECTRONIQUES, VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, VOIX TRAITÉES, MODIFIÉES, MODIFIEES, VOIX TRAITEES Electronica envoutante et exaltante, avec de solides beats, des synthés et des effets vocaux atmosphériques. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 383 tk005 richard lewis (prs) thomas a. swindells (prs) infinite sky (a) wom 383 elektrobeat west one music dance electro western drums western electronic instruments vocals vocal textures treated vocal peaceful dreamy serious determined sexy cool strong confident strong determined strong exhilarating tender nostalgic uplifting anthemic uplifting inspirational uplifting motivational uplifting mesmerising inspiring electronica with strong beats synths and atmospheric vocal fx. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="28969" name="Show Me What You Want (a)" code="WOM 383 tk003" libraryid="6" albumid="610" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_383_Elektrobeat/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Alkalein (BMI), Adam E. C. Reeve (BMI), Joe Jacquest (BMI)" comment="Electronica mainstream avec beats coriaces, synthés pulsants et chant masculin sophistiqué." styleid="1" lengthseconds="203" time="3:23" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_383_Elektrobeat/WOM_383_trk003_SHOW_ME_WHAT_YOU_WANT_(A)_Alkalein_(BMI),_Adam_E._C._Reeve_(BMI),_Joe_Jacquest_(BMI)_West_One_Music_.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRONICA, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, NUIT, ELEMENTS, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, HI TECH, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, SERIEUX, SEXY, COOL, SEXY, SÉDUISANT, SEDUISANT, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, DETERMINE, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, ENERGIQUE, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, FIER, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, COOL, NERVEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, BATTERIE, INSTRUMENTS ÉLECTRONIQUES, ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ELECTRONIQUES, VOCAL, MASCULIN, MASCULIN, VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, VOIX TRAITÉES, MODIFIÉES, MODIFIEES, VOIX TRAITEES Electronica mainstream avec beats coriaces, synthés pulsants et chant masculin sophistiqué. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 383 tk003 alkalein (bmi) adam e. c. reeve (bmi) joe jacquest (bmi) show me what you want (a) wom 383 elektrobeat west one music dance electro western drums western electronic instruments vocals male male vocals vocal textures treated vocal serious serious sexy cool sexy seductive strong confident strong determined strong energetic strong strong uplifting proud uplifting uplifting tv radio program formats mainstream electronica featuring tough beats pulsing synths and a slick male vocal. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /></items></librarycollection>