<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<librarycollection>
  <items>
    <item id="21474" name="Escape the Skies (a)" code="WOM 364 tk009" libraryid="6" albumid="460" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_364_Euphorica/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jonathan B. Buchanan (PRS), Harry Angstrom (PRS)" comment="Une intro au synthé, sombre et nerveuse, se développe avec des cordes imparables jusqu'à un chorus épique à 1:40, avec lead de synthé qui monte en fleche et batterie." styleid="34" lengthseconds="188" time="3:08" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_364_Euphorica/WOM_364_trk009_ESCAPE_THE_SKIES_(A)_Jonathan_B._Buchanan_(PRS),_Harry_Angstrom_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, POST ROCK, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRO, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, ORCHESTRAL HYBRIDE, ROCK, INDIE, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, EPIQUE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, MODERNE, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, DRAMATIQUE, PASSIONNÉ, PASSIONNE, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, SERIEUX, DETERMINE, SÉRIEUX, DIGNE, SERIEUX, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, SERIEUX, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, COURAGEUX, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, DETERMINE, FORT, ÉPIQUE, EPIQUE, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EMBLÉMATIQUE, EMBLEMATIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, JAILLIR, EVOLUTIF, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION, COOL, NERVEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES Une intro au synthé, sombre et nerveuse, se développe avec des cordes imparables jusqu'à un chorus épique à 1:40, avec lead de synthé qui monte en fleche et batterie. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 364 tk009 jonathan b. buchanan (prs) harry angstrom (prs) escape the skies (a) wom 364 euphorica west one music indie rock post rock club electronica electro film score orchestral documentary film score orchestral orchestral hybrid rock indie main activities settings city urban human environment movies action drama movies epic movies human drama movies modern movies urban drama tv dark and edgy synth intro building with driving strings to an epic chorus at 1:40 with soaring synth lead and drums. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="428434750"/>
    <item id="13781" name="The Trace (a)" code="WOM 088 tk007" libraryid="6" albumid="278" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_088_Forensic_Beats/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Tord Jungsten" comment="Du rock indé américain rythmé et thématique. Atmosphérique avec une basse lead puissante." styleid="14" lengthseconds="118" time="1:58" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_088_Forensic_Beats/WOM088_trk007_THE_TRACE_(A)_Tord_Jungsten_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, INDIE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), FORT, FORT, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, CORDES, BASSE, BASSE ÉLECTRIQUE,, DETECTIVE, ELECTRIQUE, BASSE ELECTRIQUE, MYSTERE Du rock indé américain rythmé et thématique. Atmosphérique avec une basse lead puissante. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 088 tk007 tord jungsten the trace (a) wom 088 forensic beats west one music drama rock indie main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) strong strong movies crime detective mystery tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama strings bass electric bass pacey thematic american indie rock. atmospheric with a strong bass lead. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="15781" name="The Temptress" code="WOM 136 tk005" libraryid="6" albumid="330" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_136_High_Drama/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Johnny Bernstein" comment="Une atmosphère étrange d'investigation, progressant vers un morceau d'action dramatique avec une batterie crunchy et des guitares électriques." styleid="14" lengthseconds="168" time="2:48" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_136_High_Drama/WOM136_trk005_THE_TEMPTRESS_Johnny_Bernstein_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRO, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, ÉTRANGE , TROUBLANT, BIZARRE, EVOLUTIF, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELEMENTS SONORES, ELECTRONIQUE, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), INQUIETANT, ETRANGE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Une atmosphère étrange d'investigation, progressant vers un morceau d'action dramatique avec une batterie crunchy et des guitares électriques. wom 136 tk005 johnny bernstein the temptress wom 136 high drama west one music drama film score orchestral club electronica electro film score orchestral trailer sound elements atmospheres main movies action drama movies crime detective mystery movies urban drama tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing eerie disturbing mysterious eerie investigation building to dramatic action cue with crunchy drums and electric guitars. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="13731" name="The Hustle" code="WOM 087 tk003" libraryid="6" albumid="277" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_087_The_Hustle_and_Con/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jay Price" comment="Un underscore décontracté et super funky." styleid="14" lengthseconds="155" time="2:35" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_087_The_Hustle_and_Con/WOM087_trk003_THE_HUSTLE_Jay_Price_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, JAZZ, JAZZ FUNK, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, PAISIBLE, DÉTENDU, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), GROUPE DE ROCK, CLAVIER, PIANO, BOIS, SAXOPHONE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 70, PERIODE, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), DETENDU, 20E SIECLE, DETECTIVE, ANNEES 70, MYSTERE Un underscore décontracté et super funky. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 087 tk003 jay price the hustle wom 087 the hustle and con west one music drama funk soul r&amp;b jazz jazz funk main movies crime detective mystery tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama peaceful relaxed tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) rock band keyboard piano woodwinds saxophone time period modern era 20th century 1970s laid back super funky underscore. main dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="15618" name="Slider (a)" code="WOM 131 tk009" libraryid="6" albumid="325" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_131_Jazz_on_Groove/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Philip Hochstrate" comment="Un rythme funk décontracté avec des petites touches contemporaines." styleid="19" lengthseconds="199" time="3:19" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_131_Jazz_on_Groove/WOM131_trk009_SLIDER_(A)_Philip_Hochstrate_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="JAZZ, BIG BAND, JAZZ, FUSION, JAZZ, NU JAZZ, JAZZ, JAZZ FUNK, JAZZ, MODERN JAZZ, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, HOLLYWOOD, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, LAS VEGAS, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, NUIT, PAISIBLE, DÉTENDU, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CUIVRES, BIG BAND, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ENSEMBLE DE JAZZ, GROUPE DE JAZZ, FORMATIONS GENERALES, DETENDU Un rythme funk décontracté avec des petites touches contemporaines. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 131 tk009 philip hochstrate slider (a) wom 131 jazz on groove west one music jazz jazz big band jazz fusion jazz future jazz jazz jazz funk jazz modern jazz main activities settings showbiz hollywood activities settings showbiz las vegas tv radio talkshow entertainment late night peaceful relaxed glamorous luxurious tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) laid back funk groove with contemporary twists. main dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="25500" name="Machine Revolt (a)" code="WOM 341 tk006" libraryid="6" albumid="546" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_341_Twisted_Urban_Drama/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Scott James, David Edward Bloor" comment="Drame sombre bourré d'énergie avec un piano troublant, de gros beats, une basse épaisse et des cordes battantes." styleid="1" lengthseconds="216" time="3:36" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_341_Twisted_Urban_Drama/WOM_341_trk006_MACHINE_REVOLT_(A)_Scott_James,_David_Edward_Bloor_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="6" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, PRINCIPAL, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BIG BEAT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, SOUND DESIGN, TROUBLANT, AGITÉ, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, SÉRIEUX, INQUIET, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, FORT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, COOL, NERVEUX, QUI A DU CRAN, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, BASSE, BASSE ÉLECTRIQUE, ELEMENTS SONORES, SERIEUX, ATMOSPHERES, AGITE, DETERMINE, ENERGIQUE, DETECTIVE, ELECTRIQUE, BASSE ELECTRIQUE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS Drame sombre bourré d'énergie avec un piano troublant, de gros beats, une basse épaisse et des cordes battantes. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 341 tk006 scott james david edward bloor machine revolt (a) wom 341 twisted urban drama west one music dance electro club electronica strings string section main club electronica big beat club electronica breakbeat film score orchestral documentary sound elements atmospheres sound design disturbing restless disturbing tense dramatic intense serious concerned strong determined strong high-energy dark drama featuring haunting piano big beats chunky bass and driving strings. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="3025" name="Breakneck (a)" code="TSH 079 tk002" libraryid="5" albumid="97" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_079_Viral/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Robert J. Foster (PRS), Richard E. L. Wells (PRS)" comment="Frénétique, palpitant, en un mot, tete baissée!" styleid="14" lengthseconds="131" time="2:11" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_079_Viral/TSH_079_trk002_BREAKNECK_(A)_Robert_J._Foster_(PRS),_Richard_E._L._Wells_(PRS)_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, JEUX VIDÉOS, JEUX VIDEOS, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, GUERRE, MILITAIRE, HISTORIQUE, GUERRE MODERNE, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, MODERNE, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, SPORT, SPORTS EXTREMES, TRAILERS, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, AGRESSIF, DRAMATIQUE, FOUGUEUX, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, SERIEUX, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, DETERMINE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, EXALTANT, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, IMPLACABLE, FORT, FORT, COOL, NERVEUX, QUI A DU CRAN, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INSISTANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, RÉPÉTITIF, REPETITIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE Frénétique, palpitant, en un mot, tete baissée! cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz tsh 079 tk002 robert j. foster (prs) richard e. l. wells (prs) breakneck (a) tsh 079 viral the scoring house drama film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral documentary main activities settings city urban human environment activities settings video games activities settings war military historical modern warfare movies action drama movies modern movies urban drama sports frenetic pounding headlong impulsion. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="615215382"/>
    <item id="14961" name="Hustler (a)" code="WOM 116 tk011" libraryid="6" albumid="309" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_116_The_Classic_Cool/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Clifford Eric Haywood" comment="Action et aventure d'espion en costume Savile Row..." styleid="8" lengthseconds="160" time="2:40" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_116_The_Classic_Cool/WOM116_trk011_HUSTLER_(A)_Clifford_Eric_Haywood_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="11" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, FORT, AVENTUREUX, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), GROUPE DE ROCK, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 60, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 70, STYLE VINTAGE, PERIODE, DETERMINE, 20E SIECLE, DETECTIVE, ANNEES 60, ANNEES 70, MYSTERE Action et aventure d'espion en costume Savile Row... wom 116 tk011 clifford eric haywood hustler (a) wom 116 the classic cool west one music kitsch retro film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral trailer main movies action drama movies crime detective mystery movies espionage spy strong adventurous strong confident strong determined tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) rock band time period modern era 20th century action and adventure in saville row suits. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="17847" name="Skunk Funk" code="WOM 180A tk027" libraryid="6" albumid="376" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_180A_Livewire_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Lewis (Gb 3) (PRS)" comment="De la funk rétro tunée avec une flûte lead." styleid="1" lengthseconds="62" time="1:02" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_180A_Livewire_2/WOM_180A_trk027_SKUNK_FUNK_Richard_Lewis_(Gb_3)_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="27" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTROCLASH, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, GROOVES, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HOUSE, JAZZ HOUSE, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, SPORT, EXERCICE, FITNESS, TV, RADIO, JEU, QUIZZ, SPECTACLE DE VARIÉTÉS, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, FUN, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, FORT, CONFIANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ÉLECTRONIQUE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, ELECTRONIQUE, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DECALE, DEFILE DE MODE, ANNEES 2000, DEFILE, ANNEES 20, SPECTACLE DE VARIETES, ETE De la funk rétro tunée avec une flûte lead. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 180a tk027 richard lewis (gb 3) (prs) skunk funk wom 180a livewire 2 west one music dance electro sports football extreme sports promos youth streets olympics pimped-up retro funk with flute lead. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="17015" name="Depth Charge (a)" code="WOM 162 tk005" libraryid="6" albumid="357" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_162_Future_Dub/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Caspar John Valentine Kedros / Scott Doran" comment="Un titre sombre et menaçant. Une grosse basse fuzz avec des boucles rétro crunchy et des effets tripants." styleid="1" lengthseconds="154" time="2:34" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_162_Future_Dub/WOM162_trk005_DEPTH_CHARGE_(A)_Caspar_John_Valentine_Kedros_Scott_Doran_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CLUB, ELECTRONICA, DUB, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, LEFTFIELD, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, TRIP HOP, DANSE ETHNIQUE, STYLE POP, REGGAE, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, EFFRAYANT, MENAÇANT, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, NUIT,, PERIODE, MENACANT, ANNEES 2000, ANNEES 20 Un titre sombre et menaçant. Une grosse basse fuzz avec des boucles rétro crunchy et des effets tripants. wom 162 tk005 caspar john valentine kedros scott doran depth charge (a) wom 162 future dub west one music dance electro club electronica time period modern era 2000s main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) club electronica dub club electronica leftfield club electronica trip hop ethnic dance pop style reggae disturbing dark scary menacing tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure dark and menacing. fat fuzz bass with crunchy retro loops and tripped-out effects. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="16343" name="The Heist" code="WOM 147 tk014" libraryid="6" albumid="342" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_147_Spy_Fi_Grooves/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jay Price" comment="Des beats urban groovy avec des guitares cool d'espionnage." styleid="14" lengthseconds="167" time="2:47" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_147_Spy_Fi_Grooves/WOM147_trk014_THE_HEIST_Jay_Price_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="14" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, GROOVES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, POP, ROCK, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, STRIPTEASE, BURLESQUE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, FILMS, WESTERN SPAGHETTI, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, GROOVY, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), SOUND DESIGN, SERIEUX, DETERMINE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE Des beats urban groovy avec des guitares cool d'espionnage. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 147 tk014 jay price the heist wom 147 spy fi grooves west one music drama club electronica club electronica grooves film score orchestral trailer pop rock main activities settings striptease burlesque movies crime detective mystery movies espionage spy movies spaghetti western tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama dramatic intense groovy urban beats with cool spy guitars. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="19732" name="Beyond the Dusk (a)" code="WOM 221A tk007" libraryid="6" albumid="420" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_221A_Big_Chill_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Gavin Skinner" comment="Des vagues de contrebasse et une batterie jazzy, fusionnées avec des cordes maussades." styleid="15" lengthseconds="209" time="3:29" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_221A_Big_Chill_2/WOM221A_trk007_BEYOND_THE_DUSK_(A)_Gavin_Skinner_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="EASY LISTENING, LOUNGE, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, STRIPTEASE, BURLESQUE, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, JOURNALISME D'INVESTIGATION, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, NUIT, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, AGITÉ, SEXY, ÉROTIQUE , SEXY, SEXY, SEXY, SENSUEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLAVIER, ORGUE HAMMOND, CORDES, BASSE, CONTREBASSE, CONTREBASSE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), AGITE, EROTIQUE, ACTUALITES Des vagues de contrebasse et une batterie jazzy, fusionnées avec des cordes maussades. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 221a tk007 gavin skinner beyond the dusk (a) wom 221a big chill 2 west one music ambient chill easy listening lounge main activities settings striptease burlesque movies urban drama tv radio news and current affairs investigative reporting tv radio talkshow entertainment late night tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing restless sexy erotic sexy rolling double bass and jazzy drums fused with brooding strings. main dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="17848" name="The Championship" code="WOM 180A tk028" libraryid="6" albumid="376" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_180A_Livewire_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Lewis (Gb 3) (PRS)" comment="La course pour le prix commence !" styleid="1" lengthseconds="62" time="1:02" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_180A_Livewire_2/WOM_180A_trk028_THE_CHAMPIONSHIP_Richard_Lewis_(Gb_3)_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="28" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, AMBIENT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTROCLASH, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, GROOVES, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, SPORT, TV, RADIO, JEU, QUIZZ, SPECTACLE DE VARIÉTÉS, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TROUBLANT, TENDU, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, TENDRE, SONGEUR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, EVOLUTIF, COOL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, RALENTI, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ÉLECTRONIQUE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, AIR CONNU, ELEMENTS SONORES, ELECTRONIQUE, PERIODE, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEFILE DE MODE, ANNEES 2000, DEFILE, ANNEES 20, ELEMENTS, SPECTACLE DE VARIETES, ETE, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION La course pour le prix commence ! cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 180a tk028 richard lewis (gb 3) (prs) the championship wom 180a livewire 2 west one music dance electro sports football extreme sports promos youth streets olympics the race for the prize is on. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="15619" name="Sunset City" code="WOM 131 tk010" libraryid="6" albumid="325" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_131_Jazz_on_Groove/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Philip Hochstrate" comment="Une bande son sombre et menaçante." styleid="19" lengthseconds="192" time="3:12" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_131_Jazz_on_Groove/WOM131_trk010_SUNSET_CITY_Philip_Hochstrate_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="10" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CHILL OUT, DOWNTEMPO, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, LOUNGECORE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, JAZZ, BIG BAND, JAZZ, NU JAZZ, JAZZ, MODERN JAZZ, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, HOLLYWOOD, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, EFFRAYANT, MENAÇANT, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CUIVRES, BIG BAND, MENACANT, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE Une bande son sombre et menaçante. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 131 tk010 philip hochstrate sunset city wom 131 jazz on groove west one music jazz club electronica chill out downtempo club electronica loungecore film score orchestral trailer jazz big band jazz future jazz jazz modern jazz main activities settings showbiz hollywood movies crime detective mystery movies espionage spy movies urban drama tv radio moody and menacing urban soundtrack. main dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="13737" name="Thieves in Suits (a)" code="WOM 087 tk009" libraryid="6" albumid="277" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_087_The_Hustle_and_Con/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jay Price" comment="Déterminé et funky. Des beats cool avec un saxo et une flûte." styleid="14" lengthseconds="158" time="2:38" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_087_The_Hustle_and_Con/WOM087_trk009_THIEVES_IN_SUITS_(A)_Jay_Price_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="JAZZ, JAZZ FUNK, ROCK, JAZZ ROCK, PRINCIPAL, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), GROUPE DE ROCK, BOIS, FLUTE, BOIS, SAXOPHONE, SERIEUX, DETERMINE Déterminé et funky. Des beats cool avec un saxo et une flûte. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 087 tk009 jay price thieves in suits (a) wom 087 the hustle and con west one music drama jazz jazz funk rock jazz rock main tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama serious determined strong determined uplifting uplifting tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) rock band woodwinds flute woodwinds saxophone determined and funky. cool beats with sax and flute. main dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="16331" name="Secret Service" code="WOM 147 tk002" libraryid="6" albumid="342" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_147_Spy_Fi_Grooves/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Deep Sounds" comment="Joyeux et nerveux, une bande son d'espionnage écrasante avec des beats contemporains, une basse funky et des cuivres massifs." styleid="14" lengthseconds="165" time="2:45" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_147_Spy_Fi_Grooves/WOM147_trk002_SECRET_SERVICE_Deep_Sounds_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BIG BEAT, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 70, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLUB, ELECTRONICA, GROOVES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, STYLE VINTAGE, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, NERVEUX, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, LAS VEGAS, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE,, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), 20E SIECLE, DETECTIVE, ANNEES 70, MYSTERE Joyeux et nerveux, une bande son d'espionnage écrasante avec des beats contemporains, une basse funky et des cuivres massifs. wom 147 tk002 deep sounds secret service wom 147 spy fi grooves west one music drama club electronica big beat time period modern era 20th century 1970s main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) club electronica grooves film score orchestral trailer funk soul r&amp;b vintage style happy upbeat edgy activities settings showbiz las vegas movies action adventure upbeat and edgy slamming spy soundtrack with contemporary beats funkin'' bass and big horns. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="24054" name="Axiom (a)" code="WOM 316 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="521" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_316_Cinematica/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Benson Taylor" comment="Paysage sonores éthérés et beats dubstep percutants avec de belles lignes de cordes." styleid="2" lengthseconds="199" time="3:19" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_316_Cinematica/WOM_316_trk001_AXIOM_(A)_Benson_Taylor_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, DUBSTEP, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, TV, RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, AGITÉ, TROUBLANT, TENDU, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, BEAU, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INSISTANT, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, AMERIQUE DU NORD, SERIEUX, ETATS-UNIS, AGITE, DETECTIVE, TELE REALITE, MYSTERE Paysage sonores éthérés et beats dubstep percutants avec de belles lignes de cordes. wom 316 tk001 benson taylor axiom (a) wom 316 cinematica west one music trailer film score orchestral trailer club electronica dubstep club electronica business corporate luxury main activities settings city urban human environment movies crime detective mystery movies espionage spy tv radio reality tv tv radio tv drama police legal ethereal soundscapes and snappy dubstep beats with beautiful string lines. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="21120" name="Shattered and Battered" code="WOM 251A tk007" libraryid="6" albumid="452" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_251A_Breakbeat_Deluxe/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Russell Mcnamara" comment="Des breaks trash et fracassants avec des samples jazzy et des sons atmosphériques sombres." styleid="1" lengthseconds="256" time="4:16" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_251A_Breakbeat_Deluxe/WOM251A_trk007_SHATTERED_AND_BATTERED_Russell_Mcnamara_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, MÉLODRAMATIQUE, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, DONNE LA CHAIR DE POULE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE,, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), MELODRAMATIQUE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE Des breaks trash et fracassants avec des samples jazzy et des sons atmosphériques sombres. wom 251a tk007 russell mcnamara shattered and battered wom 251a breakbeat deluxe west one music dance electro club electronica breakbeat main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) film score orchestral trailer funny comedic funny melodramatic disturbing dark disturbing spooky movies crime detective mystery movies espionage spy tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle trashy smashed-up breaks with jazzy samples and dark atmospherics. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="25515" name="Breathe the Sound (b)" code="WOM 341 tk021" libraryid="6" albumid="546" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_341_Twisted_Urban_Drama/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Thomas Arthur Swindells, Richard Lewis (Gb 3)" comment="Introduction de beatbox atmosphérique qui se développe en beats énergiques avec synthétiseurs sales." styleid="1" lengthseconds="133" time="2:13" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_341_Twisted_Urban_Drama/WOM_341_trk021_BREATHE_THE_SOUND_(B)_Thomas_Arthur_Swindells,_Richard_Lewis_(Gb_3)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="21" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ÉLECTRONIQUE, UNDERSCORE, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BIG BEAT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, DUB, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, FORT, FORT, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, COOL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, ELECTRONIQUE, ENERGIQUE, AERIEN Introduction de beatbox atmosphérique qui se développe en beats énergiques avec synthétiseurs sales. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 341 tk021 thomas arthur swindells richard lewis (gb 3) breathe the sound (b) wom 341 twisted urban drama west one music dance electro club electronica electronic underscore club electronica big beat club electronica breakbeat club electronica dub film score orchestral documentary happy feel good peaceful dreamy strong energetic strong strong tender warm uplifting positive uplifting uplifting movement atmospheric beat boxing intro builds into energetic beats with dirty synths. underscore" waveformpath="" version="Underscore" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="1388" name="Sandpaper (a)" code="FEM 015 tk010" libraryid="2" albumid="35" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_015_Zeitgeist/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Stephen Dean Hilton" comment="Des cordes magnifiques, un rythme électronique et du sound-design. Des éléments futuristes fusionnés avec un thème de cordes classique et élégant. Une construction constante jusqu'au final." styleid="2" lengthseconds="159" time="2:39" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_015_Zeitgeist/FEM_015_trk010_SANDPAPER_(A)_Stephen_Dean_Hilton_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="10" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ROCK, INDIE, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, SOUND DESIGN, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, FILMS INDÉPENDANTS, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TRAILERS, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TITRE POUR TRAILER, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, IMPLACABLE, FORT, FORT, EVOLUTIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, PIÉTINEMENT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, FUTURISTE, ELEMENTS SONORES, PERIODE, ATMOSPHERES, DETERMINE, FILMS INDEPENDANTS, PIETINEMENT, ELEGANT, ELEMENTS, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Des cordes magnifiques, un rythme électronique et du sound-design. Des éléments futuristes fusionnés avec un thème de cordes classique et élégant. Une construction constante jusqu'au final. fem 015 tk010 stephen dean hilton sandpaper (a) fem 015 zeitgeist fired earth music trailer film score orchestral trailer rock indie sound elements atmospheres sound design main movies action drama movies indie films movies urban drama trailers tv radio sports trailer track strong confident strong determined strong powerful strong relentless strong strong stunning strings stomping electronic beats and sound design. futuristic elements fused with classic elegant string theme. constantly building in emotion and drive to end. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
    <item id="8379" name="Heroes and Villains" code="TSH 071A tk015" libraryid="5" albumid="179" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_071A_One_Liners/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Keith C. Nichols" comment="Poursuite palpitante." styleid="16" lengthseconds="32" time="0:32" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_071A_One_Liners/TSH_071_trk015_HEROES_AND_VILLAINS_Keith_C._Nichols_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="15" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, KITSCH, RETRO, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, COMÉDIE, POURSUITE, FILMS, COMÉDIE, PARODIE, SATIRE, FILMS, COMÉDIE, DISCRÉTION, BASSESSE, FILMS, FILM MUET, MÉLODRAME, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, INSENSÉ, DROLE, MÉLODRAMATIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, POURSUITE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLAVIER, PIANO, SOLO, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 20, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), INSENSE, MELODRAMATIQUE, ESPIEGLE, COMEDIE, 20E SIECLE, DISCRETION, MELODRAME, ANNEES 20 Poursuite palpitante. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 071a tk015 keith c. nichols heroes and villains tsh 071a one liners the scoring house quirky film score orchestral trailer kitsch retro main movies comedy chase movies comedy spoof satire movies comedy stealth villany movies silent movie melodrama tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden funny comedic funny madcap funny melodramatic funny thrilling chase. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="12248" name="Gumshoe (a)" code="WOM 057 tk013" libraryid="6" albumid="247" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_057_Kids_TV/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Mr Stix" comment="Un mystérieux dessin animé des années 1970." styleid="20" lengthseconds="85" time="1:25" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_057_Kids_TV/WOM057_trk013_GUMSHOE_(A)_Mr_Stix_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="13" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, FILMS, ANIMATION, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, TV, RADIO, DESSINS ANIMÉS,, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ESPIEGLE, DETECTIVE, DESSINS ANIMES, MYSTERE Un mystérieux dessin animé des années 1970. wom 057 tk013 mr stix gumshoe (a) wom 057 kids tv west one music children film score orchestral trailer main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) film score orchestral trailer funny comedic funny mischievous movement rhythmic stealthy movies animation movies crime detective mystery movies espionage spy tv radio cartoons 1970s cartoon mystery. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="5449" name="Mr Big" code="TSH 053 tk002" libraryid="5" albumid="138" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_053_Winner_Takes_All/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="James Robert Nisbet / James Roger Graydon" comment="Un groove gras qui se pavane." styleid="6" lengthseconds="176" time="2:56" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_053_Winner_Takes_All/TSH053_trk002_MR_BIG_James_Robert_Nisbet_James_Roger_Graydon_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ROCK, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, HUMORISTIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, MARCHE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE,, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ESPIEGLE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, JOURNEE Un groove gras qui se pavane. tsh 053 tk002 james robert nisbet james roger graydon mr big tsh 053 winner takes all the scoring house rock film score orchestral trailer main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) film score orchestral trailer rock funny comedic funny humorous funny mischievous movement rhythmic stealthy movement rhythmic walking movies crime detective mystery movies espionage spy tv radio big fat strutting groove. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="15911" name="Cafe Paris (a)" code="WOM 140A tk008" libraryid="6" albumid="334" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_140A_Quirky_Vintage_A/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Paul Reeves (Gb 2)" comment="Un morceau fier à la française dans le style Hot-Club." styleid="8" lengthseconds="62" time="1:02" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_140A_Quirky_Vintage_A/WOM140A_trk008_CAFE_PARIS_(A)_Paul_Reeves_(Gb_2)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="8" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, JAZZ, HOT CLUB DE FRANCE, JAZZ, LATIN JAZZ, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, COMÉDIE, FILMS, CINÉMA FRANCAIS, FILMS, CINÉMA ITALIEN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, PAISIBLE, DÉTENDU, MACHO, ARROGANCE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ENSEMBLE DE JAZZ, GROUPE DE JAZZ, EUROPE, EUROPE DU SUD, ITALIE, EUROPE, EUROPE DE L'OUEST, FRANCE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 30, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 40, STYLE VINTAGE, FORMATIONS GENERALES, PERIODE, ESPIEGLE, DECALE, DETENDU, COMEDIE, CINEMA FRANCAIS, CINEMA ITALIEN, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 30, ANNEES 40 Un morceau fier à la française dans le style Hot-Club. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 140a tk008 paul reeves (gb 2) cafe paris (a) wom 140a quirky vintage a west one music kitsch retro film score orchestral trailer jazz hot club of france jazz latin jazz main movies comedy movies french cinema movies italian cinema tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden tv radio leisure lifestyle travel funny comedic funny eccentric funny mischievous relaxed french swagger in hot-club style. main dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="13979" name="The Bureau" code="WOM 092 tk013" libraryid="6" albumid="282" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_092_Jazzadelica/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Damian John Hand / Charles James Nicholas Casey" comment="Tranquille mais tonique : la traque des méchants. Avec des cuivres et un Rhodes sur une ligne de basse." styleid="16" lengthseconds="120" time="2:00" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_092_Jazzadelica/WOM092_trk013_THE_BUREAU_Damian_John_Hand_Charles_James_Nicholas_Casey_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="13" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 60, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 70, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), JAZZ, JAZZ COOL, JAZZ, JAZZ FUNK, JAZZ, MODERN JAZZ, STYLE VINTAGE, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, CHASSE TRADITIONNELLE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE,, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), 20E SIECLE, DETECTIVE, ANNEES 60, ANNEES 70, MYSTERE Tranquille mais tonique : la traque des méchants. Avec des cuivres et un Rhodes sur une ligne de basse. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 092 tk013 damian john hand charles james nicholas casey the bureau wom 092 jazzadelica west one music quirky film score orchestral trailer time period modern era 20th century 1960s time period modern era 20th century 1970s main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) jazz cool jazz jazz jazz funk jazz modern jazz vintage style happy upbeat activities settings showbiz activities settings cooled out but upbeat featuring brass and rhodes hunting down the bad guys over a groovin bass line. main dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="8444" name="Spy Guy" code="TSH 071A tk080" libraryid="5" albumid="179" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_071A_One_Liners/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Benjamin Richard Lord, Robin Lawrence Datta" comment="Thème furtif pour espions et détectives privés." styleid="16" lengthseconds="32" time="0:32" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_071A_One_Liners/TSH_071_trk080_SPY_GUY_Benjamin_Richard_Lord,_Robin_Lawrence_Datta_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="80" tracktotal="" search="KITSCH, RETRO, CHEESY, KITSCH, RETRO, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, COMÉDIE, TARTE A LA CRÈME, FILMS, COMÉDIE, PARODIE, SATIRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, TV, RADIO, DESSINS ANIMÉS, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, DROLE, DROLE, IDIOT, DROLE, IRONIQUE, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, EXCENTRIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, STYLE VINTAGE, IRREGULIER, COMEDIE, TARTE A LA CREME, DESSINS ANIMES Thème furtif pour espions et détectives privés. tsh 071a tk080 benjamin richard lord robin lawrence datta spy guy tsh 071a one liners the scoring house quirky film score orchestral documentary jazz ragtime main activities settings war military historical world war 1 documentary biographical historical the arts movies comedy slapstick movies comedy spoof satire movies silent movie melodrama happy bright happy cheerful happy furtive detective spy theme. main dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="13978" name="Spy Breaker" code="WOM 092 tk012" libraryid="6" albumid="282" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_092_Jazzadelica/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Damian John Hand / Charles James Nicholas Casey" comment="Une tension qui enfreint toutes les règles, avec des attaques de cuivres, une guitare exaltante et des rythmes syncopés." styleid="16" lengthseconds="212" time="3:32" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_092_Jazzadelica/WOM092_trk012_SPY_BREAKER_Damian_John_Hand_Charles_James_Nicholas_Casey_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 60, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 70, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), JAZZ, FUSION, JAZZ, JAZZ FUNK, STYLE VINTAGE, FORT, EXCITANT, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, SYNCOPÉ, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, TV, RADIO,, PERIODE, IRREGULIER, 20E SIECLE, SYNCOPE, DETECTIVE, ANNEES 60, ANNEES 70, MYSTERE Une tension qui enfreint toutes les règles, avec des attaques de cuivres, une guitare exaltante et des rythmes syncopés. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 092 tk012 damian john hand charles james nicholas casey spy breaker wom 092 jazzadelica west one music quirky film score orchestral trailer time period modern era 20th century 1960s time period modern era 20th century 1970s main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) jazz fusion jazz jazz funk vintage style strong exciting movement irregular syncopated movies action adventure movies classic code breaking tension featuring brass stabs exciting guitar and syncopated rhythms. main dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="23225" name="The Running Man" code="WOM 297 tk018" libraryid="6" albumid="502" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_297_Something_Simple/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Thomas Greenberg" comment="Piano trépidant, animé, avec claquements de mains et roulements de batterie." styleid="16" lengthseconds="102" time="1:42" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_297_Something_Simple/WOM297_trk018_THE_RUNNING_MAN_Thomas_Greenberg_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="18" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SPORT, EXERCICE, FITNESS, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, OCCUPÉ, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COURANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UN TRAIN, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), OCCUPE, JOURNEE Piano trépidant, animé, avec claquements de mains et roulements de batterie. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 297 tk018 thomas greenberg the running man wom 297 something simple west one music quirky business corporate bright optimistic business corporate bright optimistic main business corporate sports exercise fitness tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio talkshow entertainment daytime happy feel good busy bustling piano with handclaps and rolling drums. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="16340" name="Percussive Hustle" code="WOM 147 tk011" libraryid="6" albumid="342" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_147_Spy_Fi_Grooves/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Deep Sounds" comment="Une batterie solo vivante, excentrique et sans complexe." styleid="14" lengthseconds="191" time="3:11" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_147_Spy_Fi_Grooves/WOM147_trk011_PERCUSSIVE_HUSTLE_Deep_Sounds_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="11" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, EXCENTRIQUE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, BATTERIE,, IRREGULIER, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE Une batterie solo vivante, excentrique et sans complexe. wom 147 tk011 deep sounds percussive hustle wom 147 spy fi grooves west one music drama film score orchestral trailer main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) funny eccentric movement irregular eccentric movies crime detective mystery movies espionage spy drums lively eccentric and unabashed drum solo. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="2225" name="Shakedown Street" code="RFM 001 tk008" libraryid="4" albumid="57" albumartpath="Music/Refuel Music/RFM_001_Refuelled_Funk_and_Soul/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Alan Moorhouse" comment="Un rythme pour la conduite et l'action. Authentique enregistrement d'époque." styleid="8" lengthseconds="151" time="2:31" samplefile="Music/Refuel Music/RFM_001_Refuelled_Funk_and_Soul/RFM001_trk008_SHAKEDOWN_STREET_Alan_Moorhouse_Refuel_Music.mp3" track="8" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, KITSCH, RETRO, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, FORT, CONFIANT, GROOVY, MACHO, ARROGANCE, RETRO, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 60, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 70, STYLE VINTAGE, ENREGISTREMENT D'ARCHIVE, PERIODE, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 60, ANNEES 70 Un rythme pour la conduite et l'action. Authentique enregistrement d'époque. rfm 001 tk008 alan moorhouse shakedown street rfm 001 refuelled funk and soul refuel music kitsch retro film score orchestral trailer funk soul r&amp;b kitsch retro main activities settings showbiz movies action adventure movies espionage spy strong confident groovy macho swagger retro movement rhythmic driving tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) time period modern era driving action groove. authentic period recording. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Refuel Music" cae="00617450359"/>
    <item id="16898" name="The Sleuth (a)" code="WOM 359 tk015" libraryid="6" albumid="356" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_359_Modern_Dramedy/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Thomas Greenberg (PRS)" comment="Intrigue et enquete: secrets inavouables mis à jour. Des beats urbains s'ajoutent à des guitares pleines de tensions et des percussions. Pour dramedy." styleid="16" lengthseconds="108" time="1:48" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_359_Modern_Dramedy/WOM_359_trk015_THE_SLEUTH_(A)_Thomas_Greenberg_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="15" tracktotal="" search="HIP HOP, URBAIN, POP, POP, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, CRIME, DƒTECTIVE, MYSTéRE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TƒLƒ RƒALITƒ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SITCOM, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SOAP OPERA, TELENOVELA, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, ESPIéGLE, ESPIEGLE, SƒRIEUX, SƒRIEUX, SERIEUX, PIZZICATO, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, BATTERIE, BOITE Ë RYTHMES, BATTERIE ƒLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ƒLECTRONIQUES, ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ELECTRONIQUES, CLAVIER, CELESTE, CORDES, GUITARE, ƒLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE Intrigue et enquete: secrets inavouables mis à jour. Des beats urbains s'ajoutent à des guitares pleines de tensions et des percussions. Pour dramedy. wom 359 tk015 thomas greenberg (prs) the sleuth (a) wom 359 modern dramedy west one music quirky hip hop urban pop main activities settings city urban human environment documentary movies crime detective mystery movies espionage spy tv radio reality tv tv radio sitcom tv radio soap opera telenovela disturbing mysterious disturbing suspenseful funny comedic funny intrigue &amp; investigation: uncovering dirty secrets. urban beats join tense guitars and percussion. dramedy. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="428434750"/>
    <item id="14952" name="Blackjack (a)" code="WOM 116 tk002" libraryid="6" albumid="309" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_116_The_Classic_Cool/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Clifford Eric Haywood" comment="Un shuffle de film d'espion, doux et mélancolique." styleid="8" lengthseconds="175" time="2:55" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_116_The_Classic_Cool/WOM116_trk002_BLACKJACK_(A)_Clifford_Eric_Haywood_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 60, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 70, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, JAZZ, STYLE VINTAGE, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, SEXY, SEXY, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, TRAINER LES PIEDS, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, MARCHE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, BOIS, SAXOPHONE,, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ESPIEGLE, 20E SIECLE, DETECTIVE, ANNEES 60, ANNEES 70, MYSTERE Un shuffle de film d'espion, doux et mélancolique. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 116 tk002 clifford eric haywood blackjack (a) wom 116 the classic cool west one music kitsch retro film score orchestral trailer time period modern era 20th century 1960s time period modern era 20th century 1970s main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) film score orchestral trailer jazz vintage style funny comedic funny mischievous sexy sexy movement rhythmic shuffle smooth soulful spy shuffle. main dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="8443" name="Super Sleuth" code="TSH 071A tk079" libraryid="5" albumid="179" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_071A_One_Liners/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Benjamin Richard Lord, Robin Lawrence Datta" comment="Activités furtives." styleid="16" lengthseconds="31" time="0:31" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_071A_One_Liners/TSH_071_trk079_SUPER_SLEUTH_Benjamin_Richard_Lord,_Robin_Lawrence_Datta_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="79" tracktotal="" search="KITSCH, RETRO, CHEESY, KITSCH, RETRO, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, COMÉDIE, TARTE A LA CRÈME, FILMS, COMÉDIE, PARODIE, SATIRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, TV, RADIO, DESSINS ANIMÉS, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, DROLE, DROLE, IDIOT, DROLE, IRONIQUE, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, EXCENTRIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, STYLE VINTAGE, IRREGULIER, COMEDIE, TARTE A LA CREME, DESSINS ANIMES Activités furtives. tsh 071a tk079 benjamin richard lord robin lawrence datta super sleuth tsh 071a one liners the scoring house quirky kitsch retro cheesy kitsch retro main movies comedy slapstick movies comedy spoof satire movies espionage spy tv radio cartoons funny comedic funny eccentric funny funny funny silly funny wry movement irregular eccentric movement rhythmic stealthy vintage style stealthy goings on. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="16330" name="Vegas Strip" code="WOM 147 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="342" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_147_Spy_Fi_Grooves/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Deep Sounds" comment="Un morceau punchy et déterminé. Cool, groovy et funktastic 70's thème." styleid="14" lengthseconds="151" time="2:31" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_147_Spy_Fi_Grooves/WOM147_trk001_VEGAS_STRIP_Deep_Sounds_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 70, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, STYLE VINTAGE, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, GROOVY, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, LAS VEGAS, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION,, PERIODE, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETERMINE, 20E SIECLE, DETECTIVE, ANNEES 70, MYSTERE Un morceau punchy et déterminé. Cool, groovy et funktastic 70's thème. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 147 tk001 deep sounds vegas strip wom 147 spy fi grooves west one music drama funk soul r&amp;b time period modern era 20th century 1970s main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) club electronica film score orchestral trailer vintage style strong determined serious determined groovy activities settings showbiz las vegas movies action adventure movies crime punchy and determined. cool groovy and funktastic 70s theme. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="26998" name="Coming of Age (a)" code="WOM 350A tk007" libraryid="6" albumid="579" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_350A_British_Drama/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Michael Price, Nicholas Hill" comment="Thèmes orchestraux enjoués avec puissantes cordes staccato et timbales." styleid="14" lengthseconds="85" time="1:25" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_350A_British_Drama/WOM_350A_trk007_COMING_OF_AGE_(A)_Michael_Price,_Nicholas_Hill_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, FAMILIAL, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, PERIODE, PERIODES, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, ELEMENTS, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, ART, ANTIQUITÉS, ANTIQUITES, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, DRAME TV, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, FESTIF, HEUREUX, JOYEUX, HEUREUX, EXCITÉ, EXCITE, HEUREUX, ENJOUÉ, ENJOUE, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, CUIVRES, SECTION DE CUIVRES, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, BOIS, SECTION DE BOIS, BATTERIE, TIMBALES, CORDES, HARPE, BOIS, CLARINETTE, BOIS, FLUTE, BOIS, HAUTBOIS, HAUTBOIS, COR ANGLAIS, DRAME, BRITANNIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL Thèmes orchestraux enjoués avec puissantes cordes staccato et timbales. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede wom 350a tk007 michael price nicholas hill coming of age (a) wom 350a british drama west one music drama film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral pastoral main movies children storytelling movies family movies human drama movies period historical costume drama movies romance nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral tv radio leisure lifestyle playful orchestral themes with driving staccato strings and timpani. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="8107" name="On the Brink (a)" code="TSH 050 tk016" libraryid="5" albumid="176" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_050_A_Curious_Mind/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Andrew Clark" comment="Repartie mélodramatique au coeur léger." styleid="10" lengthseconds="110" time="1:50" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_050_A_Curious_Mind/TSH050_trk016_ON_THE_BRINK_(A)_Simon_Andrew_Clark_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="16" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, TV, RADIO, SITCOM, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, MÉLODRAMATIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, TENDRE, LÉGER, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, EXCENTRIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), MELODRAMATIQUE, ESPIEGLE, LEGER, IRREGULIER, ELEMENTS Repartie mélodramatique au coeur léger. tsh 050 tk016 simon andrew clark on the brink (a) tsh 050 a curious mind the scoring house documentary film score orchestral trailer main nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife tv radio sitcom funny comedic funny melodramatic funny mischievous tender light movement irregular eccentric movement rhythmic stealthy tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) light-hearted melodramatic repartee. dramedy. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="13968" name="Snake Eyes" code="WOM 092 tk002" libraryid="6" albumid="282" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_092_Jazzadelica/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Damian John Hand / Charles James Nicholas Casey" comment="Un film 70's rapide avec tout le tralala." styleid="16" lengthseconds="164" time="2:44" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_092_Jazzadelica/WOM092_trk002_SNAKE_EYES_Damian_John_Hand_Charles_James_Nicholas_Casey_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, JAZZ, JAZZ FUNK, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, FORT, COURAGEUX, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), GROUPE DE ROCK, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 70, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETERMINE, ENERGIQUE, 20E SIECLE, DETECTIVE, ANNEES 70, MYSTERE Un film 70's rapide avec tout le tralala. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 092 tk002 damian john hand charles james nicholas casey snake eyes wom 092 jazzadelica west one music quirky film score orchestral trailer jazz jazz funk main movies action adventure movies crime detective mystery movies espionage spy strong courageous strong determined strong energetic tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) rock band time period modern era 20th century 1970s high paced 70s cop flick with all the trimmings. main dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="16335" name="Groove Control" code="WOM 147 tk006" libraryid="6" albumid="342" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_147_Spy_Fi_Grooves/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Deep Sounds" comment="Un thème rétro espiègle et au tempo rapide avec un rythme urgent. Une progression dynamique, audacieuse et cuivrée." styleid="14" lengthseconds="216" time="3:36" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_147_Spy_Fi_Grooves/WOM147_trk006_GROOVE_CONTROL_Deep_Sounds_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="6" tracktotal="" search="JAZZ, JAZZ, JAZZ FUNK, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, MAGIE, ILLUSIONS, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, EVOLUTIF, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MAGIQUE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ENSEMBLE DE JAZZ, GROUPE DE JAZZ, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 70, FORMATIONS GENERALES, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ESPIEGLE, 20E SIECLE, DETECTIVE, ANNEES 70, MYSTERE, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Un thème rétro espiègle et au tempo rapide avec un rythme urgent. Une progression dynamique, audacieuse et cuivrée. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 147 tk006 deep sounds groove control wom 147 spy fi grooves west one music drama jazz jazz jazz funk main activities settings magic illusions activities settings showbiz movies crime detective mystery movies espionage spy funny comedic funny mischievous building glamorous luxurious magical tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) general lineups jazz ensemble up tempo and cheeky retro theme with urgent pace. building dynamics bold and brassy. main dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="7906" name="Sleuth on the Loose (a)" code="TSH 038 tk006" libraryid="5" albumid="174" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_038_Oddities/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Paul Reeves (Gb 2)" comment="Intrigue détective classique avec un mystérieux saxophone ténor et un quintette jazz." styleid="17" lengthseconds="62" time="1:02" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_038_Oddities/TSH038_trk006_SLEUTH_ON_THE_LOOSE_(A)_Paul_Reeves_(Gb_2)_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="6" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, JAZZ, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, MAGIE, ILLUSIONS, FILMS, ANIMATION, FILMS, COMÉDIE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, MÉLODRAMATIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, HEUREUX, FUN, MAGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), BOIS, SAXOPHONE, SAXOPHONE TÉNOR, STYLE VINTAGE, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), MELODRAMATIQUE, ESPIEGLE, DECALE, COMEDIE, DETECTIVE, SAXOPHONE TENOR, TENOR, MYSTERE Intrigue détective classique avec un mystérieux saxophone ténor et un quintette jazz. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz tsh 038 tk006 paul reeves (gb 2) sleuth on the loose (a) tsh 038 oddities the scoring house comedy film score orchestral trailer jazz main activities settings magic illusions movies animation movies comedy movies crime detective mystery movies espionage spy disturbing mysterious funny comedic funny melodramatic funny mischievous funny quirky happy fun magical classic detective intrigue with mysterious tenor sax and jazz quintet. main dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="1328" name="Walkie-Talkie" code="FEM 008 tk006" libraryid="2" albumid="33" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_008_Spirited/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jeff Tymoschuk" comment="Une opération sous couverture, avec un esprit d'aventure familiale ! Une mission classique d'espionnage seventies avec du suspense, du fun, du drame, et une cadence tonique." styleid="2" lengthseconds="140" time="2:20" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_008_Spirited/FEM008_trk006_WALKIE-TALKIE_Jeff_Tymoschuk_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="6" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, ENFANTS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ANIMATION, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, COMÉDIE, FILMS, FAMILIAL, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, HUMORISTIQUE, DROLE, INSENSÉ, DROLE, MÉLODRAMATIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, HEUREUX, FUN, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, POURSUITE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), VOCAL, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), INSENSE, MELODRAMATIQUE, ESPIEGLE, DECALE, DETERMINE, ENERGIQUE, COMEDIE Une opération sous couverture, avec un esprit d'aventure familiale ! Une mission classique d'espionnage seventies avec du suspense, du fun, du drame, et une cadence tonique. fem 008 tk006 jeff tymoschuk walkie-talkie fem 008 spirited fired earth music trailer children storytelling children film score orchestral trailer main movies animation movies children storytelling movies comedy movies family trailers trailer track funny comedic funny humorous funny madcap funny melodramatic funny mischievous funny quirky happy fun covert operation family adventure style! classic 1970's spy mission cue with suspense fun drama and energetic pace. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
    <item id="2231" name="High Stakes" code="RFM 001 tk014" libraryid="4" albumid="57" albumartpath="Music/Refuel Music/RFM_001_Refuelled_Funk_and_Soul/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Alan Moorhouse" comment="Un thème d'aventure, sophistiqué et exaltant. Authentique enregistrement d'époque." styleid="8" lengthseconds="149" time="2:29" samplefile="Music/Refuel Music/RFM_001_Refuelled_Funk_and_Soul/RFM001_trk014_HIGH_STAKES_Alan_Moorhouse_Refuel_Music.mp3" track="14" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 60, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 70, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, KITSCH, RETRO, STYLE VINTAGE, ENREGISTREMENT D'ARCHIVE, FORT, EXALTANT, SOPHISTIQUÉ, CLASSE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION,, PERIODE, SOPHISTIQUE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 60, ANNEES 70 Un thème d'aventure, sophistiqué et exaltant. Authentique enregistrement d'époque. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz rfm 001 tk014 alan moorhouse high stakes rfm 001 refuelled funk and soul refuel music kitsch retro film score orchestral trailer time period modern era 20th century 1960s time period modern era 20th century 1970s main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) funk soul r&amp;b kitsch retro vintage style archival recording strong exhilarating sophisticated classy activities settings exhilarating sophisticated adventure theme. authentic period recording. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Refuel Music" cae="00617450359"/>
    <item id="3024" name="Subterfuge" code="TSH 079 tk001" libraryid="5" albumid="97" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_079_Viral/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Robert J. Foster (PRS), Richard E. L. Wells (PRS)" comment="Situation tendue, crispée, intrigante en développement." styleid="14" lengthseconds="107" time="1:47" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_079_Viral/TSH_079_trk001_SUBTERFUGE_Robert_J._Foster_(PRS),_Richard_E._L._Wells_(PRS)_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, TROUBLANT, TROUBLANT, CRAINTIF, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, TROUBLÉ, TROUBLE, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, EFFRAYANT, FAIRE PEUR, EFFRAYANT, MENAÇANT, MENACANT, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, SERIEUX, EVOLUTIF, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION, QUI A DU CRAN, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INSISTANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, RÉPÉTITIF, REPETITIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE Situation tendue, crispée, intrigante en développement. tsh 079 tk001 robert j. foster (prs) richard e. l. wells (prs) subterfuge tsh 079 viral the scoring house drama film score orchestral documentary film score orchestral trailer main activities settings city urban human environment movies crime detective mystery movies urban drama tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing dark disturbing disturbing disturbing fearful taut intriguing tension build. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="615215382"/>
    <item id="9762" name="Near the Truth" code="WOM 008 tk008" libraryid="6" albumid="198" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_008_Conspiracy_(Drama)/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Howard James Davidson" comment="Piano suspendu et atmosphère de cordes." styleid="14" lengthseconds="128" time="2:08" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_008_Conspiracy_(Drama)/WOM008_trk008_NEAR_THE_TRUTH_Howard_James_Davidson_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="8" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ACCOMPAGNEMENT AU PIANO, SOUND DESIGN, CLAVIER, PIANO, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), DEPRIMANT, AERIEN, ELEMENTS Piano suspendu et atmosphère de cordes. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 008 tk008 howard james davidson near the truth wom 008 conspiracy (drama) west one music drama film score orchestral trailer main movies human drama nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife the elements sky aerial clouds peaceful dreamy sad depressing lonely movement smooth aerial floating tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) suspended piano and strings atmosphere. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="2818" name="Twisted City (a)" code="TSH 003 tk005" libraryid="5" albumid="94" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_003_Deeper_Minimal/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Robert John Foster" comment="Menaces urbaines planantes." styleid="12" lengthseconds="79" time="1:19" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_003_Deeper_Minimal/TSH003_trk005_TWISTED_CITY_(A)_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, JOURNALISME D'INVESTIGATION, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, DANGEUREUX, EFFRAYANT, HORREUR, EFFRAYANT, MENAÇANT, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, SÉRIEUX, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ELEMENTS SONORES, SERIEUX, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), MENACANT, DETECTIVE, ACTUALITES, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS Menaces urbaines planantes. tsh 003 tk005 robert john foster twisted city (a) tsh 003 deeper minimal the scoring house atmospheres sound elements atmospheres main movies crime detective mystery movies horror thriller movies urban drama nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife tv radio news and current affairs investigative reporting disturbing mysterious disturbing suspenseful disturbing threatening urban undercurrents. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="8120" name="Trail of Evidence (a)" code="TSH 050 tk029" libraryid="5" albumid="176" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_050_A_Curious_Mind/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Andrew Clark" comment="Enquête concentrée." styleid="10" lengthseconds="89" time="1:29" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_050_A_Curious_Mind/TSH050_trk029_TRAIL_OF_EVIDENCE_(A)_Simon_Andrew_Clark_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="29" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, JOURNALISME D'INVESTIGATION, TV, RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, PULSATION, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), DETECTIVE, ACTUALITES, TELE REALITE, MYSTERE Enquête concentrée. tsh 050 tk029 simon andrew clark trail of evidence (a) tsh 050 a curious mind the scoring house documentary film score orchestral trailer main movies crime detective mystery movies urban drama tv radio news and current affairs investigative reporting tv radio reality tv tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense movement rhythmic focused investigation. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="2814" name="Waiting and Watching" code="TSH 003 tk001" libraryid="5" albumid="94" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_003_Deeper_Minimal/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Robert John Foster" comment="Fond sonore raffiné et plein de suspense." styleid="12" lengthseconds="72" time="1:12" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_003_Deeper_Minimal/TSH003_trk001_WAITING_AND_WATCHING_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, CHAUD, DÉSERT, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, ESPACE, INTERSIDÉRAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, FROID, STÉRILE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, SOLEIL, CHALEUR, TROUBLANT, STÉRILE, TROUBLANT, FROID , TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SURNATUREL, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), EFFETS SONORES, SIFFLEMENT, CRÉPITEMENT, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), STERILE, INQUIETANT, CREPITEMENT, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS, METEO, DESERT, ETE, INTERSIDERAL Fond sonore raffiné et plein de suspense. tsh 003 tk001 robert john foster waiting and watching tsh 003 deeper minimal the scoring house atmospheres sound elements atmospheres business corporate science technology main movies crime detective mystery nature wildlife the elements land hot desert nature wildlife the elements sky space outer space nature wildlife the elements weather cold barren nature wildlife understated suspenseful bed. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="8117" name="Cypher Code (a)" code="TSH 050 tk026" libraryid="5" albumid="176" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_050_A_Curious_Mind/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Andrew Clark" comment="Activité tendue, sous couverture." styleid="10" lengthseconds="91" time="1:31" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_050_A_Curious_Mind/TSH050_trk026_CYPHER_CODE_(A)_Simon_Andrew_Clark_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="26" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, JOURNALISME D'INVESTIGATION, TV, RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, TENDU, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), DETECTIVE, ACTUALITES, TELE REALITE, MYSTERE Activité tendue, sous couverture. tsh 050 tk026 simon andrew clark cypher code (a) tsh 050 a curious mind the scoring house documentary film score orchestral documentary main movies crime detective mystery tv radio news and current affairs investigative reporting tv radio reality tv tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing tense tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) tense undercover activity. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="13738" name="Spooks" code="WOM 087 tk010" libraryid="6" albumid="277" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_087_The_Hustle_and_Con/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jay Price" comment="Un piano méditatif sur une ambiance sonore atmosphérique et percussive." styleid="14" lengthseconds="178" time="2:58" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_087_The_Hustle_and_Con/WOM087_trk010_SPOOKS_Jay_Price_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="10" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PAISIBLE, DÉTENDU, TENDRE, SONGEUR, PERCUSSIF, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, CLAVIER, PIANO,, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETENDU, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS Un piano méditatif sur une ambiance sonore atmosphérique et percussive. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 087 tk010 jay price spooks wom 087 the hustle and con west one music drama sound elements atmospheres main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) peaceful relaxed tender reflective percussive movies crime detective mystery tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama keyboard piano reflective piano over atmospheric and percussive soundscape. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="8113" name="Watch and Wait (a)" code="TSH 050 tk022" libraryid="5" albumid="176" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_050_A_Curious_Mind/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Andrew Clark" comment="Bed déterminé et tendu." styleid="10" lengthseconds="113" time="1:53" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_050_A_Curious_Mind/TSH050_trk022_WATCH_AND_WAIT_(A)_Simon_Andrew_Clark_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="22" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, JOURNALISME D'INVESTIGATION, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ACCELERE, DETECTIVE, ACTUALITES, MYSTERE Bed déterminé et tendu. tsh 050 tk022 simon andrew clark watch and wait (a) tsh 050 a curious mind the scoring house documentary business corporate science technology main documentary science technology movies crime detective mystery science technology industry tv radio news and current affairs investigative reporting tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense purposeful bed. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="27051" name="Descending Darkness (a)" code="WOM 366 tk011" libraryid="6" albumid="580" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_366_Electronic_Noir/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Andrew C. Pye (PRS), Paul S. Brown (PRS), James R. Cooper (PRS)" comment="Un piano morose prépare le terrain pour un thème mélodieux sombre avec orgue et sound design inquiétant." styleid="14" lengthseconds="161" time="2:41" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_366_Electronic_Noir/WOM_366_trk011_DESCENDING_DARKNESS_(A)_Andrew_C._Pye_(PRS),_Paul_S._Brown_(PRS),_James_R._Cooper_(PRS)_West_One.mp3" track="11" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, LEFTFIELD, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, ATMOSPHÈRES, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, SOUND DESIGN, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, FILMS, FILM NOIR, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, DRAME TV, ABSTRAIT, ABSTRAIT, ABSTRAIT, ANGULEUX, DÉCOUSU, DECOUSU, ABSTRAIT, CLAIRSEMÉ, CLAIRSEME, TROUBLANT, ANXIEUX, TROUBLANT, STÉRILE, STERILE, TROUBLANT, FLIPPANT, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, TROUBLANT, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SURNATUREL, TROUBLANT, TENDU, TROUBLANT, BIZARRE, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, SERIEUX, SÉRIEUX, SOLENNEL, SERIEUX, NERVEUX, GLITCHY, SOUND DESIGN, INSTRUMENTS ÉLECTRONIQUES, ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ELECTRONIQUES, CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE Un piano morose prépare le terrain pour un thème mélodieux sombre avec orgue et sound design inquiétant. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 366 tk011 andrew c. pye (prs) paul s. brown (prs) james r. cooper (prs) descending darkness (a) wom 366 electronic noir west one music drama club electronica club electronica leftfield sound elements atmospheres sound elements atmospheres sound design main activities settings city urban human environment activities settings futuristic documentary movies crime detective mystery movies film noir movies horror moody piano builds into a dark melodic theme with organ and eerie sound design. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="428434750"/>
    <item id="8221" name="Poison Pen" code="TSH 051 tk034" libraryid="5" albumid="177" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_051_Nearfield/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Everard Lawrence Wells / Robert John Foster" comment="Piano éparse et insidieux." styleid="10" lengthseconds="79" time="1:19" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_051_Nearfield/TSH051_trk034_POISON_PEN_Richard_Everard_Lawrence_Wells_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="34" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, JOURNALISME D'INVESTIGATION, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, ABSTRAIT, CLAIRSEMÉ, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SURNATUREL, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, SÉRIEUX, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ELEMENTS SONORES, SERIEUX, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), CLAIRSEME, INQUIETANT, DETECTIVE, ACTUALITES, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS Piano éparse et insidieux. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 051 tk034 richard everard lawrence wells robert john foster poison pen tsh 051 nearfield the scoring house documentary sound elements atmospheres main documentary movies crime detective mystery movies horror thriller tv radio news and current affairs investigative reporting tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama abstract sparse disturbing eerie disturbing mysterious disturbing sparse insidious piano. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="2851" name="Serious Intent" code="TSH 003 tk038" libraryid="5" albumid="94" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_003_Deeper_Minimal/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Robert John Foster" comment="Un beat insistant et déterminé." styleid="12" lengthseconds="83" time="1:23" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_003_Deeper_Minimal/TSH003_trk038_SERIOUS_INTENT_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="38" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, JOURNALISME D'INVESTIGATION, TV, RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INSISTANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, PULSATION, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETERMINE, DETECTIVE, ACTUALITES, TELE REALITE, MYSTERE Un beat insistant et déterminé. tsh 003 tk038 robert john foster serious intent tsh 003 deeper minimal the scoring house atmospheres film score orchestral documentary main documentary movies crime detective mystery tv radio news and current affairs investigative reporting tv radio reality tv tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense serious determined strong insistent determined pulse. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="8125" name="Edge of Certainty (a)" code="TSH 050 tk034" libraryid="5" albumid="176" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_050_A_Curious_Mind/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Andrew Clark" comment="Suspense calme et impérieux." styleid="10" lengthseconds="89" time="1:29" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_050_A_Curious_Mind/TSH050_trk034_EDGE_OF_CERTAINTY_(A)_Simon_Andrew_Clark_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="34" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, JOURNALISME D'INVESTIGATION, TV, RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, PAISIBLE, DOUX, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETECTIVE, ACTUALITES, TELE REALITE, MYSTERE Suspense calme et impérieux. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz tsh 050 tk034 simon andrew clark edge of certainty (a) tsh 050 a curious mind the scoring house documentary film score orchestral trailer main documentary movies crime detective mystery tv radio news and current affairs investigative reporting tv radio reality tv tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense peaceful quiet tempo quiet compelling suspense. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="4614" name="Hidden Depths" code="TSH 035 tk010" libraryid="5" albumid="125" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_035_A_Winner_is_Born/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Mark Lasker" comment="Un développement rythmique mystérieux et énigmatique, et une reprise." styleid="22" lengthseconds="180" time="3:00" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_035_A_Winner_is_Born/TSH035_trk010_HIDDEN_DEPTHS_Mark_Lasker_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="10" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, COMMUNICATION, ACTUALITÉS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FORMATION, INFORMATION, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, JOURNALISME D'INVESTIGATION, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, CRAINTIF, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, TENDU, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), DETECTIVE, ACTUALITES, MYSTERE Un développement rythmique mystérieux et énigmatique, et une reprise. tsh 035 tk010 mark lasker hidden depths tsh 035 a winner is born the scoring house sport business corporate beds business corporate communication news business corporate science technology business corporate training information main documentary science technology movies crime detective mystery movies urban drama tv radio news and current affairs mysterious enigmatic rhythmic development and reprise. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="3026" name="Silent Killer" code="TSH 079 tk003" libraryid="5" albumid="97" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_079_Viral/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Robert J. Foster (PRS), Richard E. L. Wells (PRS)" comment="Paysage sonore isolé, troublant." styleid="14" lengthseconds="109" time="1:49" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_079_Viral/TSH_079_trk003_SILENT_KILLER_Robert_J._Foster_(PRS),_Richard_E._L._Wells_(PRS)_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, ATMOSPHÈRES, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, SOUND DESIGN, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, NEIGE, GLACE, ELEMENTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, ESPACE, INTERSIDÉRAL, ELEMENTS, INTERSIDERAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, FROID, STÉRILE, STERILE, ELEMENTS, ETE, METEO, TROUBLANT, ANXIEUX, TROUBLANT, STÉRILE, STERILE, TROUBLANT, FROID, TROUBLANT, FLIPPANT, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, INQUIETANT, TROUBLANT, MAL, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, ÉTRANGE , ETRANGE, TROUBLANT, SURNATUREL, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, EFFRAYANT, FAIRE PEUR, EFFRAYANT, HORREUR, EFFRAYANT, MENAÇANT, MENACANT, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, EFFRAYANT, EFFRAYANT, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, SERIEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE Paysage sonore isolé, troublant. tsh 079 tk003 robert j. foster (prs) richard e. l. wells (prs) silent killer tsh 079 viral the scoring house drama film score orchestral documentary film score orchestral trailer sound elements atmospheres sound elements atmospheres sound design main activities settings city urban human environment activities settings futuristic documentary science technology movies crime detective lonely disturbing soundscape. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="615215382"/>
    <item id="8227" name="Heart of the Machine" code="TSH 051 tk040" libraryid="5" albumid="177" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_051_Nearfield/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Everard Lawrence Wells / Robert John Foster" comment="Battement de coeur pulsatif et tendu." styleid="10" lengthseconds="92" time="1:32" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_051_Nearfield/TSH051_trk040_HEART_OF_THE_MACHINE_Richard_Everard_Lawrence_Wells_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="40" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, EFFETS SONORES, HUMAIN, BATTEMENTS DE COEUR, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, PULSATION, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE,, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS Battement de coeur pulsatif et tendu. tsh 051 tk040 richard everard lawrence wells robert john foster heart of the machine tsh 051 nearfield the scoring house documentary sound elements atmospheres effects sound effects human heartbeat main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense movement rhythmic pulsing movies crime detective mystery tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama pulsating tense heartbeat. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="3112" name="Darker Waters" code="TSH 008 tk003" libraryid="5" albumid="99" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_008_Ambient_Spirit/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Everard Lawrence Wells / Robert John Foster" comment="Un fond sonore anxieux et dérangeant avec des ponctuations graves." styleid="15" lengthseconds="74" time="1:14" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_008_Ambient_Spirit/TSH008_trk003_DARKER_WATERS_Richard_Everard_Lawrence_Wells_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, TROUBLANT, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, NERVEUX, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MER, SOUS-MARIN, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, ATMOSPHÈRE SCIENTIFIQUE,, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), INQUIETANT, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS, ATMOSPHERE SCIENTIFIQUE Un fond sonore anxieux et dérangeant avec des ponctuations graves. tsh 008 tk003 richard everard lawrence wells robert john foster darker waters tsh 008 ambient spirit the scoring house ambient chill sound elements atmospheres main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) business corporate science technology disturbing dark disturbing disturbing disturbing eerie disturbing mysterious edgy movies crime detective mystery tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama documentary edgy disturbing bed with low punctuations. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="15775" name="The Right Track (b)" code="WOM 135 tk023" libraryid="6" albumid="329" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_135_Modern_Drama/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Caspar John Valentine Kedros / Scott Doran" comment="Une atmosphère positive, puissante et fluide." styleid="14" lengthseconds="185" time="3:05" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_135_Modern_Drama/WOM135_trk023_THE_RIGHT_TRACK_(B)_Caspar_John_Valentine_Kedros_Scott_Doran_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="23" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ALTERNATIF, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, TENDU, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, DÉTENDU, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELEMENTS SONORES, ELECTRONIQUE, ATMOSPHERES, DETENDU, ACCELERE, DETECTIVE, TELE REALITE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS Une atmosphère positive, puissante et fluide. wom 135 tk023 caspar john valentine kedros scott doran the right track (b) wom 135 modern drama west one music drama sound elements atmospheres club electronica alternate documentary movies crime detective mystery movies urban drama tv radio reality tv tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing mysterious disturbing tense peaceful dreamy peaceful relaxed strong strong positive strong flowing atmosphere. alternative" waveformpath="" version="Alternative" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="27045" name="Embers (a)" code="WOM 366 tk005" libraryid="6" albumid="580" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_366_Electronic_Noir/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Andrew C. Pye (PRS), Paul S. Brown (PRS), James R. Cooper (PRS)" comment="Voyage musical changeant constamment, entre guitares pleines de tension, orgue et sound design." styleid="14" lengthseconds="179" time="2:59" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_366_Electronic_Noir/WOM_366_trk005_EMBERS_(A)_Andrew_C._Pye_(PRS),_Paul_S._Brown_(PRS),_James_R._Cooper_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRONICA, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, ATMOSPHÈRES, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, SOUND DESIGN, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, FILM NOIR, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, FILMS INDÉPENDANTS, FILMS INDEPENDANTS, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, DRAME TV, ABSTRAIT, ABSTRAIT, ABSTRAIT, CLAIRSEMÉ, CLAIRSEME, TROUBLANT, ANXIEUX, TROUBLANT, STÉRILE, STERILE, TROUBLANT, FROID, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, TROUBLANT, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, INQUIETANT, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SURNATUREL, TROUBLANT, TENDU, TROUBLANT, BIZARRE, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, EFFRAYANT, MENAÇANT, MENACANT, EFFRAYANT, CAUCHEMARDESQUE, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, SERIEUX, SÉRIEUX, SOLENNEL, SERIEUX, SOUND DESIGN, CLOCHES, CARILLONS, CLOCHES D'ÉGLISE, CARILLONS, CLOCHES D'EGLISE, BATTERIE, BOITE À RYTHMES, BATTERIE ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ÉLECTRONIQUES, ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ELECTRONIQUES, CLAVIER, ORGUE HAMMOND, CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE Voyage musical changeant constamment, entre guitares pleines de tension, orgue et sound design. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 366 tk005 andrew c. pye (prs) paul s. brown (prs) james r. cooper (prs) embers (a) wom 366 electronic noir west one music drama club electronica sound elements atmospheres sound elements atmospheres sound design main activities settings city urban human environment activities settings futuristic documentary movies film noir movies human drama movies indie films tv radio tv drama abstract abstract evolving journey of tense guitars organ and sound design. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="428434750"/>
    <item id="3651" name="With Intent (c)" code="TSH 016 tk027" libraryid="5" albumid="107" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_016_A_Clearer_Vision/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Andrew Clark" comment="Fond sonore calme d'anticipation." styleid="11" lengthseconds="51" time="0:51" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_016_A_Clearer_Vision/TSH016_trk027_WITH_INTENT_(C)_Simon_Andrew_Clark_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="27" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, COMMUNICATION, ACTUALITÉS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, ALTERNATIF, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, ESPACE, INTERSIDÉRAL, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, ATMOSPHÈRE SCIENTIFIQUE, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, JOURNALISME D'INVESTIGATION, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, PAISIBLE, DOUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ACCELERE, ACTUALITES, ELEMENTS, ATMOSPHERE SCIENTIFIQUE, INTERSIDERAL Fond sonore calme d'anticipation. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz tsh 016 tk027 simon andrew clark with intent (c) tsh 016 a clearer vision the scoring house corporate business sound elements atmospheres business corporate communication news business corporate science technology alternate business corporate documentary science technology nature wildlife the elements sky space outer space science technology industry scientific atmospheres tv radio quiet anticipatory bed. alternative" waveformpath="" version="Alternative" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="25985" name="Night Watchman (a)" code="WOM 356 tk002" libraryid="6" albumid="556" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_356_Cinematic_Atmospheres/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Tom Vedvik / Martin Tillmann" comment="Drones graves évoluant sur un violoncelle avec un effet delay et des battements de coeur." styleid="14" lengthseconds="161" time="2:41" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_356_Cinematic_Atmospheres/WOM_356_trk002_NIGHT_WATCHMAN_(A)_Tom_Vedvik_Martin_Tillmann_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, DRONES, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, SOUND DESIGN, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ELEMENTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, DIVIN, CÉLESTE, CELESTE, ELEMENTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, ESPACE, INTERSIDÉRAL, ELEMENTS, INTERSIDERAL, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, ATMOSPHÈRE SCIENTIFIQUE, ATMOSPHERE SCIENTIFIQUE, ABSTRAIT, ABSTRAIT, TROUBLANT, ANXIEUX, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, INQUIETANT, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, AGITÉ, AGITE, TROUBLANT, ÉTRANGE , ETRANGE, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, TROUBLANT, BIZARRE, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, PULSATION, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, AERIEN, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, RALENTI, ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, CORDES, VIOLONCELLE Drones graves évoluant sur un violoncelle avec un effet delay et des battements de coeur. wom 356 tk002 tom vedvik martin tillmann night watchman (a) wom 356 cinematic atmospheres west one music drama sound elements atmospheres film score orchestral documentary sound elements atmospheres drones sound elements atmospheres sound design main activities settings futuristic documentary science technology movies crime detective mystery nature wildlife the elements nature study deep drones building with anxious cello delays and pulsing heartbeat. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="8255" name="Pursuit of Evidence (b)" code="TSH 051 tk068" libraryid="5" albumid="177" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_051_Nearfield/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Everard Lawrence Wells / Robert John Foster" comment="Bed investigateur impérieux." styleid="10" lengthseconds="93" time="1:33" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_051_Nearfield/TSH051_trk068_PURSUIT_OF_EVIDENCE_(B)_Richard_Everard_Lawrence_Wells_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="68" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ALTERNATIF, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, JOURNALISME D'INVESTIGATION, TV, RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, TENDU, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETECTIVE, ACTUALITES, TELE REALITE, MYSTERE Bed investigateur impérieux. tsh 051 tk068 richard everard lawrence wells robert john foster pursuit of evidence (b) tsh 051 nearfield the scoring house documentary film score orchestral trailer alternate documentary movies crime detective mystery tv radio news and current affairs investigative reporting tv radio reality tv tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing tense tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) compelling investigative bed. alternative" waveformpath="" version="Alternative" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="23401" name="Security Threat (a)" code="WOM 301 tk009" libraryid="6" albumid="507" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_301_Dark_Motion/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Christian Telford / Matthew St. Laurent / Galileo Seven / Koichi Sanchez-Imahashi / Nigel William Graham" comment="Textures mystérieuses et fascinantes, en constante évolution." styleid="14" lengthseconds="168" time="2:48" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_301_Dark_Motion/WOM301_trk009_SECURITY_THREAT_(A)_Christian_Telford_Matthew_St._Laurent_Galileo_Seven_Koichi_Sanchez-Imahash.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, JOURNALISME D'INVESTIGATION, TV, RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, TENDU, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), DETECTIVE, ACTUALITES, TELE REALITE, MYSTERE Textures mystérieuses et fascinantes, en constante évolution. wom 301 tk009 christian telford matthew st. laurent galileo seven koichi sanchez-imahashi nigel william graham security threat (a) wom 301 dark motion west one music drama business corporate science technology business corporate science technology main movies crime detective mystery movies urban drama tv radio news and current affairs investigative reporting tv radio reality tv tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing mysterious captivating textures continuously evolving. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="9972" name="Murmur (a)" code="WOM 357 tk008" libraryid="6" albumid="202" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_357_Drama_and_Intrigue/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Cliff Haywood" comment="Un rythme de basse cogneur plante un décor inquiétant. Évolue continuellement avec une batterie, une guitare électrique et des atmosphères tourbillonantes." styleid="10" lengthseconds="144" time="2:24" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_357_Drama_and_Intrigue/WOM_357_trk008_MURMUR_(A)_Cliff_Haywood_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="8" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, ART ET ESSAI, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, MODERNE, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, DRAME TV, TROUBLANT, ANXIEUX, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, TROUBLANT, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, INQUIETANT, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, AGITÉ, AGITE, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, EFFRAYANT, PRIS DE PANIQUE, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, SERIEUX, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, DETERMINE, FORT, FORT, NERVEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INSISTANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, RÉPÉTITIF, REPETITIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BATTERIE, BOITE À RYTHMES, BATTERIE ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE Un rythme de basse cogneur plante un décor inquiétant. Évolue continuellement avec une batterie, une guitare électrique et des atmosphères tourbillonantes. wom 357 tk008 cliff haywood murmur (a) wom 357 drama and intrigue west one music documentary film score orchestral documentary film score orchestral trailer main documentary movies art house movies crime detective mystery movies espionage spy movies human drama movies modern movies urban drama tv radio tv drama disturbing anxious disturbing dark disturbing pounding bass rhythm sets an ominous scene. evolving throughout with swirling atmospheres drums and electric guitar. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="6401" name="Dark City (a)" code="TSH 066 tk005" libraryid="5" albumid="150" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_066_Discreet_Emotive/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Paul Reeves (Gb 2) / Jay Price" comment="Plante un décor sombre, agité. Se développe progressivement." styleid="14" lengthseconds="169" time="2:49" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_066_Discreet_Emotive/TSH066_trk005_DARK_CITY_(A)_Paul_Reeves_(Gb_2)_Jay_Price_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, PRINCIPAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, TROUBLANT, ANXIEUX, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, CRAINTIF, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, AGITÉ, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, FORT, FORT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, EVOLUTIF, QUI A DU CRAN, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, FORMATIONS GENERALES, SERIEUX, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, AGITE, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Plante un décor sombre, agité. Se développe progressivement. tsh 066 tk005 paul reeves (gb 2) jay price dark city (a) tsh 066 discreet emotive the scoring house drama film score orchestral documentary general lineups electronic and acoustic main film score orchestral trailer disturbing anxious disturbing dark disturbing fearful disturbing mysterious disturbing restless disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense serious serious strong strong dark restless scene setter gradually building. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="22094" name="Night Pressure" code="WOM 272 tk007" libraryid="6" albumid="474" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_272_L_A_Beat_Scene/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Take" comment="Des synthés rétro chaleureux et atmosphériques fusionnés avec des beats brisés." styleid="1" lengthseconds="225" time="3:45" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_272_L_A_Beat_Scene/WOM272_trk007_NIGHT_PRESSURE_Take_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRO, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, TRIP HOP, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, HI TECH, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, NUIT, DROLE, COMIQUE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, EXCENTRIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INDUSTRIE, MACHINES, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, MÉCANIQUE, ROBOTIQUE, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PERIODE, MECANIQUE, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), IRREGULIER, ANNEES 2000, ANNEES 20 Des synthés rétro chaleureux et atmosphériques fusionnés avec des beats brisés. wom 272 tk007 take night pressure wom 272 l.a. beat scene west one music dance electro club electronica club electronica electro club electronica club electronica trip hop business corporate science technology main documentary science technology science technology industry hi tech tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv warm and atmospheric retro synths fused with broken beats. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="4696" name="Shadowmaker (a)" code="TSH 036 tk007" libraryid="5" albumid="126" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_036_The_Hard_Edge/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Robert Henry Peter White" comment="Une ouverture éparse d'anticipation vers une transition et une fin pleine de suspense." styleid="10" lengthseconds="136" time="2:16" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_036_The_Hard_Edge/TSH036_trk007_SHADOWMAKER_(A)_Robert_Henry_Peter_White_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, STRIPTEASE, BURLESQUE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, NUIT, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, ABSTRAIT, CLAIRSEMÉ, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), CLAIRSEME, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS Une ouverture éparse d'anticipation vers une transition et une fin pleine de suspense. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede tsh 036 tk007 robert henry peter white shadowmaker (a) tsh 036 the hard edge the scoring house documentary sound elements atmospheres main activities settings striptease burlesque movies crime detective mystery movies urban drama tv radio talkshow entertainment late night tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama abstract sparse disturbing mysterious tempo sparse anticipatory opening to transition and uneasy resolve. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="15794" name="Science Fiction (b)" code="WOM 136 tk018" libraryid="6" albumid="330" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_136_High_Drama/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Johnny Bernstein" comment="Un thriller urban grungy, captivant et atmosphérique." styleid="14" lengthseconds="175" time="2:55" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_136_High_Drama/WOM136_trk018_SCIENCE_FICTION_(B)_Johnny_Bernstein_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="18" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ALTERNATIF, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, JOURNALISME D'INVESTIGATION, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, TENDU, CRADE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELEMENTS SONORES, ELECTRONIQUE, ATMOSPHERES, DETECTIVE, ACTUALITES, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS Un thriller urban grungy, captivant et atmosphérique. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 136 tk018 johnny bernstein science fiction (b) wom 136 high drama west one music drama sound elements atmospheres club electronica alternate movies crime detective mystery movies horror thriller movies urban drama tv radio news and current affairs investigative reporting tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing dark disturbing mysterious grungy absorbing and atmospheric urban thriller. alternative" waveformpath="" version="Alternative" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="16640" name="Dirty Tricks" code="WOM 155 tk006" libraryid="6" albumid="350" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_155_Dub_&amp;_Breakbeat_Sessions_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Justin John Shearn / Itchy Kid" comment="Un downbeat sombre et déterminé, avec un piano brumeux et une guitare acoustique." styleid="1" lengthseconds="196" time="3:16" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_155_Dub_&amp;_Breakbeat_Sessions_2/WOM155_trk006_DIRTY_TRICKS_Justin_John_Shearn_Itchy_Kid_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="6" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, GROOVES, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, FILMS INDÉPENDANTS, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, AGITÉ, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, FORT, ACOUSTIQUE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PERIODE, SERIEUX, AGITE, DETERMINE, FILMS INDEPENDANTS, ANNEES 2000, ANNEES 20 Un downbeat sombre et déterminé, avec un piano brumeux et une guitare acoustique. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 155 tk006 justin john shearn itchy kid dirty tricks wom 155 dub &amp; breakbeat sessions 2 west one music dance electro club electronica club electronica breakbeat club electronica club electronica grooves main activities settings city urban human environment activities settings futuristic movies human drama movies indie films tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style disturbing brooding and determined down-beat with smoky piano and acoustic guitar. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="18647" name="Twisted Menace (a)" code="WOM 199 tk002" libraryid="6" albumid="395" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_199_Murder_Files/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Johnny Bernstein" comment="Des atmoshères sonores compliquées et industrielles avec des beats sombres et tordus." styleid="14" lengthseconds="178" time="2:58" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_199_Murder_Files/WOM199_trk002_TWISTED_MENACE_(A)_Johnny_Bernstein_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), TROUBLANT, DÉSORIENTÉ, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, CRAINTIF, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, ÉTRANGE , TROUBLANT, SURNATUREL, TROUBLANT, BIZARRE, EFFRAYANT, HORREUR, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, BATTERIE, CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, VIOLON ,, DESORIENTE, INQUIETANT, ETRANGE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE Des atmoshères sonores compliquées et industrielles avec des beats sombres et tordus. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 199 tk002 johnny bernstein twisted menace (a) wom 199 murder files west one music drama film score orchestral trailer main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) disturbing confused disturbing dark disturbing eerie disturbing fearful disturbing mysterious disturbing strange disturbing supernatural disturbing weird scary horror scary ominous movies crime detective uneasy industrial soundscapes with dark twisted beats. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="23398" name="Settling Dust (a)" code="WOM 301 tk006" libraryid="6" albumid="507" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_301_Dark_Motion/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Christian Telford / Matthew St. Laurent / Galileo Seven / Koichi Sanchez-Imahashi / Nigel William Graham" comment="Des textures electro évocatrices et un piano majestueux plantent le décor de cette fresque urbaine irrésisitible." styleid="14" lengthseconds="142" time="2:22" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_301_Dark_Motion/WOM301_trk006_SETTLING_DUST_(A)_Christian_Telford_Matthew_St._Laurent_Galileo_Seven_Koichi_Sanchez-Imahashi_.mp3" track="6" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, TENDU, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS Des textures electro évocatrices et un piano majestueux plantent le décor de cette fresque urbaine irrésisitible. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 301 tk006 christian telford matthew st. laurent galileo seven koichi sanchez-imahashi nigel william graham settling dust (a) wom 301 dark motion west one music drama film score orchestral trailer sound elements atmospheres main documentary movies crime detective mystery movies human drama movies urban drama tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing mysterious disturbing tense sad depressing lonely sad depressing compelling urban scene-setter with evocative electronic textures stately piano. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="13775" name="The Garage (a)" code="WOM 088 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="278" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_088_Forensic_Beats/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Tord Jungsten" comment="Des synthés rétro lancinants avec des beats crasseux de R&amp;B et de soul." styleid="14" lengthseconds="174" time="2:54" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_088_Forensic_Beats/WOM088_trk001_THE_GARAGE_(A)_Tord_Jungsten_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CHEMICAL BEATS, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, LEFTFIELD, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, FILMS, SCIENCE FICTION, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, ABSTRAIT, ABSTRAIT, TROUBLANT, TENDU, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE Des synthés rétro lancinants avec des beats crasseux de R&amp;B et de soul. wom 088 tk001 tord jungsten the garage (a) wom 088 forensic beats west one music drama club electronica chemical beats club electronica leftfield main movies crime detective mystery movies espionage spy movies science fiction tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama abstract abstract disturbing tense tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) electronic haunting retro synths with grimy r&amp;b and soul beats. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="25507" name="Fight the Fear (a)" code="WOM 341 tk013" libraryid="6" albumid="546" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_341_Twisted_Urban_Drama/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Steven Stern" comment="Sound design dangeureux et intimidant qui se développe jusqu'à un climax fait de grandes percussions, piano et guitares pleines de distorsion." styleid="1" lengthseconds="139" time="2:19" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_341_Twisted_Urban_Drama/WOM_341_trk013_FIGHT_THE_FEAR_(A)_Steven_Stern_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="13" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, PRINCIPAL, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, SOUND DESIGN, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, EFFRAYANT, MENAÇANT, SÉRIEUX, INQUIET, FORT, FORT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, MÉCANIQUE, ROBOTIQUE, COOL, NERVEUX, QUI A DU CRAN, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, GUITARE, DISTORSION, ELEMENTS SONORES, SERIEUX, ATMOSPHERES, MECANIQUE, INQUIETANT, MENACANT, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS Sound design dangeureux et intimidant qui se développe jusqu'à un climax fait de grandes percussions, piano et guitares pleines de distorsion. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 341 tk013 steven stern fight the fear (a) wom 341 twisted urban drama west one music dance electro club electronica main club electronica breakbeat film score orchestral documentary sound elements atmospheres sound design disturbing dark disturbing eerie disturbing mysterious disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense dramatic intense scary menacing serious concerned dangerous and intimidating sound design builds to a climax with big percussion piano and distorted guitars. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="3108" name="Prelude to Fear" code="TSH 007 tk025" libraryid="5" albumid="98" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_007_Beatwarpology/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="James Copperthwaite" comment="Anticipation menaçante." styleid="1" lengthseconds="181" time="3:01" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_007_Beatwarpology/TSH007_trk025_PRELUDE_TO_FEAR_James_Copperthwaite_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="25" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, TRIP HOP, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, MAGIE, ILLUSIONS, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, DANGEUREUX, EFFRAYANT, MENAÇANT, MAGIQUE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), MENACANT, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE Anticipation menaçante. tsh 007 tk025 james copperthwaite prelude to fear tsh 007 beatwarpology the scoring house dance electro club electronica trip hop main activities settings magic illusions documentary movies crime detective mystery movies urban drama tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing mysterious disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense dramatic dangerous scary menacing anticipation. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="337" name="Sleepwalker" code="EDS 001 tk006" libraryid="1" albumid="10" albumartpath="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_001_Dubstep_Grime/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Steven Alexander Young / Sample Magic / David Felton" comment="Beats punchy et basses tremblantes, pour une atmosphère sonore brute et menaçante au-delà de la noirceur." styleid="1" lengthseconds="222" time="3:42" samplefile="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_001_Dubstep_Grime/EDS001_trk006_SLEEPWALKER_Steven_Alexander_Young_Sample_Magic_David_Felton_Electronic_Dance_Series.mp3" track="6" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, 2 STEP, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, DUBSTEP, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, SCIENCE FICTION, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, ESPACE, INTERSIDÉRAL, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, ATMOSPHÈRE SCIENTIFIQUE, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, ÉTRANGE , TROUBLANT, BIZARRE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, EXCENTRIQUE, ETRANGE, IRREGULIER, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS, ATMOSPHERE SCIENTIFIQUE, INTERSIDERAL Beats punchy et basses tremblantes, pour une atmosphère sonore brute et menaçante au-delà de la noirceur. eds 001 tk006 steven alexander young sample magic david felton sleepwalker eds 001 dubstep &amp; grime electronic dance series dance electro club electronica 2 step club electronica dubstep business corporate science technology film score orchestral trailer main documentary science technology movies crime detective mystery movies science fiction nature wildlife the elements sky space outer space science gritty ominous soundscapes float over dark wobbling bass and punchy beats. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Electronic Dance Series" cae="00666407133"/>
    <item id="3166" name="Searching for Answers (b)" code="TSH 008 tk057" libraryid="5" albumid="99" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_008_Ambient_Spirit/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Everard Lawrence Wells / Robert John Foster" comment="Des ondulations inquiétantes au piano avec une boucle de batterie émergente." styleid="15" lengthseconds="114" time="1:54" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_008_Ambient_Spirit/TSH008_trk057_SEARCHING_FOR_ANSWERS_(B)_Richard_Everard_Lawrence_Wells_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="57" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, ALTERNATIF, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, ATMOSPHÈRE SCIENTIFIQUE, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, JOURNALISME D'INVESTIGATION, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, AGITÉ, TROUBLANT, ÉTRANGE , TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, TROUBLANT, BIZARRE, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLAVIER, PIANO, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), AGITE, ETRANGE, ACCELERE, DETECTIVE, ACTUALITES, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS, ATMOSPHERE SCIENTIFIQUE Des ondulations inquiétantes au piano avec une boucle de batterie émergente. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 008 tk057 richard everard lawrence wells robert john foster searching for answers (b) tsh 008 ambient spirit the scoring house ambient chill sound elements atmospheres business corporate science technology alternate documentary science technology movies crime detective mystery science technology industry scientific atmospheres tv radio news and current affairs investigative reporting tv radio tv drama police restless piano ripples with emerging drum loop. alternative" waveformpath="" version="Alternative" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="23394" name="Panic Attack (a)" code="WOM 301 tk002" libraryid="6" albumid="507" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_301_Dark_Motion/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Christian Telford / Matthew St. Laurent / Galileo Seven / Koichi Sanchez-Imahashi / Nigel William Graham" comment="Interaction electro ondoyante entre percussion et lead de synthétiseur tordu." styleid="14" lengthseconds="152" time="2:32" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_301_Dark_Motion/WOM301_trk002_PANIC_ATTACK_(A)_Christian_Telford_Matthew_St._Laurent_Galileo_Seven_Koichi_Sanchez-Imahashi_N.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, TENDU, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, POURSUITE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, PULSATION, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, TELE REALITE, ELEMENTS Interaction electro ondoyante entre percussion et lead de synthétiseur tordu. wom 301 tk002 christian telford matthew st. laurent galileo seven koichi sanchez-imahashi nigel william graham panic attack (a) wom 301 dark motion west one music drama film score orchestral trailer sound elements atmospheres main movies action drama movies urban drama tv radio reality tv tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing tense movement rhythmic chase movement rhythmic pulsing tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) undulating electronic interplay featuring percussion distorted synth lead. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="25513" name="Take Me Down (b)" code="WOM 341 tk019" libraryid="6" albumid="546" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_341_Twisted_Urban_Drama/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Thomas Arthur Swindells, Richard Lewis (Gb 3)" comment="Basse profonde et retentissante et beats bien en place combinés avec des synthétiseurs atmosphériques." styleid="1" lengthseconds="137" time="2:17" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_341_Twisted_Urban_Drama/WOM_341_trk019_TAKE_ME_DOWN_(B)_Thomas_Arthur_Swindells,_Richard_Lewis_(Gb_3)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="19" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ÉLECTRONIQUE, UNDERSCORE, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, ABSTRAIT, ANGULEUX, DÉCOUSU, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, SEXY, COOL, SEXY, SENSUEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, COOL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, SOLEIL, CHALEUR, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, VOCAL, MASCULIN, MASCULIN, ELECTRONIQUE, DECOUSU, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, METEO, ETE Basse profonde et retentissante et beats bien en place combinés avec des synthétiseurs atmosphériques. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 341 tk019 thomas arthur swindells richard lewis (gb 3) take me down (b) wom 341 twisted urban drama west one music dance electro club electronica electronic underscore club electronica breakbeat film score orchestral documentary abstract angular disjointed peaceful dreamy sexy cool sexy sultry uplifting uplifting movement smooth aerial floating movement smooth aerial flying cool activities deep resounding bass and effected beats fuse with atmospheric synths. underscore" waveformpath="" version="Underscore" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="24658" name="Hinterland (a)" code="WOM 326 tk003" libraryid="6" albumid="531" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_326_Dark_Evolutions/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Rod Abernethy" comment="Drone pulsant de mauvais augure. Avec mélodie évocatrice." styleid="14" lengthseconds="168" time="2:48" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_326_Dark_Evolutions/WOM326_trk003_HINTERLAND_(A)_Rod_Abernethy_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, PRINCIPAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, ORCHESTRAL HYBRIDE , ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, DRONES, TROUBLANT, ANXIEUX, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, EFFRAYANT, MENAÇANT, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, PULSATION, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, ELEMENTS SONORES, FORMATIONS GENERALES, SERIEUX, ATMOSPHERES, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, MENACANT, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS Drone pulsant de mauvais augure. Avec mélodie évocatrice. wom 326 tk003 rod abernethy hinterland (a) wom 326 dark evolutions west one music drama film score orchestral trailer general lineups electronic and acoustic strings string section main film score orchestral orchestral hybrid sound elements atmospheres drones disturbing anxious disturbing dark disturbing mysterious disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense ominous pulsing drone with evocative melody. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="20864" name="Midnight Drive (a)" code="WOM 245 tk003" libraryid="6" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_245_Night_Music/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Caspar John Valentine Kedros / Scott Doran" comment="Entraînant et déterminé. Une batterie electro punchy et des guitares tendues et anxieuses." styleid="34" lengthseconds="169" time="2:49" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_245_Night_Music/WOM245_trk003_MIDNIGHT_DRIVE_(A)_Caspar_John_Valentine_Kedros_Scott_Doran_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ROCK, INDIE, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, TENDU, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, NERVEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), SERIEUX, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), DEPRIMANT, DETERMINE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE Entraînant et déterminé. Une batterie electro punchy et des guitares tendues et anxieuses. wom 245 tk003 caspar john valentine kedros scott doran midnight drive (a) wom 245 night music west one music indie business corporate beds film score orchestral trailer rock indie main business corporate movies crime detective mystery movies human drama movies urban drama tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing tense sad depressing lonely serious determined edgy driving and purposeful. punchy electro drums and tense edgy guitars. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="19734" name="Recurring Dreams (a)" code="WOM 221A tk009" libraryid="6" albumid="420" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_221A_Big_Chill_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Tom Player" comment="Des atmosphères sonores sombres et lancinantes menant à un climax épique." styleid="15" lengthseconds="162" time="2:42" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_221A_Big_Chill_2/WOM221A_trk009_RECURRING_DREAMS_(A)_Tom_Player_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, LEFTFIELD, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, JOURNALISME D'INVESTIGATION, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, AGITÉ, TROUBLANT, TENDU, FORT, ÉPIQUE, EVOLUTIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), AGITE, EPIQUE, ACCELERE, DETECTIVE, ACTUALITES, MYSTERE, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Des atmosphères sonores sombres et lancinantes menant à un climax épique. wom 221a tk009 tom player recurring dreams (a) wom 221a big chill 2 west one music ambient chill club electronica leftfield film score orchestral trailer main documentary movies crime detective mystery movies urban drama tv radio news and current affairs investigative reporting tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing dark disturbing restless dark throbbing soundscapes building to an epic climax. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="3109" name="Dark Matter" code="TSH 007 tk026" libraryid="5" albumid="98" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_007_Beatwarpology/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="James Copperthwaite" comment="Anormalité étendue." styleid="1" lengthseconds="87" time="1:27" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_007_Beatwarpology/TSH007_trk026_DARK_MATTER_James_Copperthwaite_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="26" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, TRIP HOP, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, INDUSTRIE LOURDE, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, DANGEUREUX, EFFRAYANT, MENAÇANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), MENACANT, ACCELERE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE Anormalité étendue. tsh 007 tk026 james copperthwaite dark matter tsh 007 beatwarpology the scoring house dance electro club electronica breakbeat club electronica trip hop main documentary movies crime detective mystery movies urban drama science technology industry heavy industry tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing mysterious disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense stretched abnormality. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="26020" name="Claustrophobia (a)" code="WOM 352 tk005" libraryid="6" albumid="557" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_352_Cinematic_Indie_Drama/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Dylan Parsons / Dan Cassady" comment="Sombre et grésillant. Cithare et guitare atmosphériques avec une batterie hypnotique et un drone plein d'appréhension." styleid="14" lengthseconds="118" time="1:58" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_352_Cinematic_Indie_Drama/WOM_352_trk005_CLAUSTROPHOBIA_(A)_Dylan_Parsons_Dan_Cassady_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, FILMS INDÉPENDANTS, FILMS INDEPENDANTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, ELEMENTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, SOLEIL, CHALEUR, ELEMENTS, ETE, METEO, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, DRAME TV, ABSTRAIT, CLAIRSEMÉ, CLAIRSEME, TROUBLANT, ANXIEUX, TROUBLANT, STÉRILE, STERILE, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, AGITÉ, AGITE, TROUBLANT, TENDU, NEUTRE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, LOURD, DEPRIMANT, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, SERIEUX, DETERMINE, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, SERIEUX, SÉRIEUX, ATTENTIONNÉ, SERIEUX, ATTENTIONNE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, NERVEUX, GLITCHY, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, DÉFILÉ, DEFILE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, RÉPÉTITIF, REPETITIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, ACCELERE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, PIÉTINEMENT, PIETINEMENT, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, FORMATIONS GENERALES, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, ETHNIQUE, CITHARE, BATTERIE, GROSSE CAISSE, BATTERIE, TOMS, CLAVIER, HARMONIUM, CORDES, BASSE, CONTREBASSE, CONTREBASSE, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE Sombre et grésillant. Cithare et guitare atmosphériques avec une batterie hypnotique et un drone plein d'appréhension. wom 352 tk005 dylan parsons dan cassady claustrophobia (a) wom 352 cinematic indie drama west one music drama film score orchestral trailer main movies human drama movies indie films nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife the elements sky aerial clouds nature wildlife the elements weather sun heat tv radio tv drama abstract sparse disturbing dark and scratchy. atmospheric zither and guitar with hypnotic drums and an apprehensive drone. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="4692" name="Generator" code="TSH 036 tk003" libraryid="5" albumid="126" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_036_The_Hard_Edge/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Robert Henry Peter White" comment="Un rythme intense et pulsant." styleid="10" lengthseconds="126" time="2:06" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_036_The_Hard_Edge/TSH036_trk003_GENERATOR_Robert_Henry_Peter_White_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, GUERRE, MILITAIRE, HISTORIQUE, GUERRE MODERNE, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, SPORT, TV, RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), 20E SIECLE, TELE REALITE Un rythme intense et pulsant. tsh 036 tk003 robert henry peter white generator tsh 036 the hard edge the scoring house documentary business corporate science technology main activities settings war military historical modern warfare movies urban drama sports tv radio reality tv tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense dramatic intense movement rhythmic intense pulsating groove. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="27041" name="Alone In Space (a)" code="WOM 366 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="580" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_366_Electronic_Noir/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Andrew C. Pye (PRS), Paul S. Brown (PRS), James R. Cooper (PRS)" comment="Une intro évocatrice évolue progressivement en un beat déterminé." styleid="14" lengthseconds="165" time="2:45" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_366_Electronic_Noir/WOM_366_trk001_ALONE_IN_SPACE_(A)_Andrew_C._Pye_(PRS),_Paul_S._Brown_(PRS),_James_R._Cooper_(PRS)_West_One_Musi.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, LEFTFIELD, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, ATMOSPHÈRES, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, SOUND DESIGN, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, FILMS, FILM NOIR, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, DRAME TV, TROUBLANT, ANXIEUX, TROUBLANT, STÉRILE, STERILE, TROUBLANT, FLIPPANT, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, TROUBLANT, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SURNATUREL, TROUBLANT, TENDU, TROUBLANT, BIZARRE, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, EFFRAYANT, FAIRE PEUR, EFFRAYANT, MENAÇANT, MENACANT, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, SERIEUX, SÉRIEUX, SOLENNEL, SERIEUX, NERVEUX, GLITCHY, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, TAPIS ROULANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INDUSTRIE, MACHINES, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INSISTANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, MÉCANIQUE, ROBOTIQUE, MECANIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, ACCELERE, SOUND DESIGN, BATTERIE, BOITE À RYTHMES, BATTERIE ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ÉLECTRONIQUES, ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ELECTRONIQUES, CLAVIER, PIANO, ÉLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE Une intro évocatrice évolue progressivement en un beat déterminé. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 366 tk001 andrew c. pye (prs) paul s. brown (prs) james r. cooper (prs) alone in space (a) wom 366 electronic noir west one music drama club electronica club electronica leftfield sound elements atmospheres sound elements atmospheres sound design main activities settings city urban human environment activities settings futuristic documentary movies crime detective mystery movies film noir movies horror atmospheric intro gradually builds into a purposeful beat. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="428434750"/>
    <item id="23393" name="Dark Elements (a)" code="WOM 301 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="507" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_301_Dark_Motion/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Christian Telford / Matthew St. Laurent / Galileo Seven / Koichi Sanchez-Imahashi / Nigel William Graham" comment="Pulsations de synthétiseurs et percussion lancinante. Tendu, dramatique, engageant." styleid="14" lengthseconds="135" time="2:15" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_301_Dark_Motion/WOM301_trk001_DARK_ELEMENTS_(A)_Christian_Telford_Matthew_St._Laurent_Galileo_Seven_Koichi_Sanchez-Imahashi_.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, TENDU, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, POURSUITE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, PULSATION, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), TELE REALITE Pulsations de synthétiseurs et percussion lancinante. Tendu, dramatique, engageant. wom 301 tk001 christian telford matthew st. laurent galileo seven koichi sanchez-imahashi nigel william graham dark elements (a) wom 301 dark motion west one music drama film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral trailer main movies action drama movies human drama movies urban drama tv radio reality tv tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing tense movement rhythmic chase movement rhythmic pulsing tempo pulsating synths throbbing percussion. tense engaging dramatic. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="1690" name="Rising Vector (a)" code="NRF 013 tk002" libraryid="3" albumid="44" albumartpath="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_013_Fractals/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Mauricio Yazigi (BMI)" comment="Cordes et piano curieux échangent des phrases anguleuses sur un riff de bass vibrant. À 1:20, le morceau se développe avec des synthés organiques et des percussions." styleid="4" lengthseconds="173" time="2:53" samplefile="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_013_Fractals/NRF_013_trk002_RISING_VECTOR_(A)_Mauricio_Yazigi_(BMI)_Noise_Refinery.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, ORCHESTRAL HYBRIDE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, ABSTRAIT, ANGULEUX, DÉCOUSU, DECOUSU, TROUBLANT, ANXIEUX, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, AGITÉ, AGITE, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, SÉRIEUX, INQUIET, SERIEUX, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, SERIEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, PULSATION, ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, CLAVIER, PIANO, PERCUSSION, CORDES, BASSE, BASSE ÉLECTRIQUE, BASSE ELECTRIQUE Cordes et piano curieux échangent des phrases anguleuses sur un riff de bass vibrant. À 1:20, le morceau se développe avec des synthés organiques et des percussions. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live nrf 013 tk002 mauricio yazigi (bmi) rising vector (a) nrf 013 fractals noise refinery film score orchestral film score orchestral orchestral hybrid film score orchestral documentary film score orchestral trailer main activities settings city urban human environment documentary movies crime detective mystery movies espionage spy movies horror thriller movies human drama movies inquisitive piano and strings exchange angular phrases over a pulsating bass riff. piece develops with organic synths and percussion at 1:20. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Noise Refinery" cae="719510644"/>
    <item id="9766" name="Sinister Discovery (a)" code="WOM 008 tk012" libraryid="6" albumid="198" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_008_Conspiracy_(Drama)/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Howard James Davidson" comment="Un morceau tendu et atmosphérique qui se révèle progressivement." styleid="14" lengthseconds="106" time="1:46" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_008_Conspiracy_(Drama)/WOM008_trk012_SINISTER_DISCOVERY_(A)_Howard_James_Davidson_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), TROUBLANT, TENDU, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE,, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), DETECTIVE, MYSTERE Un morceau tendu et atmosphérique qui se révèle progressivement. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 008 tk012 howard james davidson sinister discovery (a) wom 008 conspiracy (drama) west one music drama film score orchestral trailer main tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) disturbing tense movies crime detective mystery movies human drama movies espionage spy tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama tense atmospheric cue gradually revealing. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="9591" name="Kinetic" code="WOM 004 tk005" libraryid="6" albumid="194" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_004_Redemption_(Drama)/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Une toile de fond en progression, anxieuse et battante vers la fin du morceau." styleid="14" lengthseconds="221" time="3:41" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_004_Redemption_(Drama)/WOM004_trk005_KINETIC_Richard_Allen_Harvey_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), TROUBLANT, ANXIEUX, EVOLUTIF, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER,, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Une toile de fond en progression, anxieuse et battante vers la fin du morceau. wom 004 tk005 richard allen harvey kinetic wom 004 redemption (drama) west one music drama film score orchestral trailer main tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) disturbing anxious building movies action adventure movies action drama movies human drama movies horror thriller anxious pulsating backdrop builds near end. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="26672" name="Illusion" code="WOM 012 tk007" libraryid="6" albumid="572" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_012_Clarity/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon David Chamberlain" comment="Impulsif et rythmique, progressant en intensité." styleid="4" lengthseconds="153" time="2:33" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_012_Clarity/WOM012_trk007_ILLUSION_Simon_David_Chamberlain_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="CLASSIQUE, CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIÈCLE, CLASSIQUE, STYLE MINIMALISTE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, DRAMATIQUE, PASSIONNÉ, EVOLUTIF, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ACCOMPAGNEMENT AU PIANO, CORDES, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, PERIODE, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIECLE, PASSIONNE, 20E SIECLE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Impulsif et rythmique, progressant en intensité. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 012 tk007 simon david chamberlain illusion wom 012 clarity west one music film score orchestral classical classical 20th century classical style classical minimalist style film score orchestral trailer main documentary movies crime detective mystery movies human drama tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama dramatic passionate building tempo impulsive and rhythmic building in intensity. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="11743" name="Spooks" code="WOM 047 tk021" libraryid="6" albumid="237" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_047_Big_Screen/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Terry Howard Devine-King" comment="Une ouverture tendue et inquiétante mène à un morceau de drame punchy et moderne." styleid="2" lengthseconds="63" time="1:03" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_047_Big_Screen/WOM047_trk021_SPOOKS_Terry_Howard_Devine-King_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="21" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), TROUBLANT, TENDU, EFFRAYANT, HORREUR, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE,, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), PERIODES, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE Une ouverture tendue et inquiétante mène à un morceau de drame punchy et moderne. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede wom 047 tk021 terry howard devine-king spooks wom 047 big screen west one music trailer film score orchestral trailer main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) disturbing tense scary horror movies crime detective mystery movies espionage spy movies horror thriller movies period historical costume drama tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama tense brooding opening leads to punchy and modern drama-action cue. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="18235" name="Entrapment (a)" code="WOM 190 tk005" libraryid="6" albumid="386" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_190_Urban_Thriller/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="John Shoto David Buckley" comment="Brut, nerveux et excitant. Des motifs de cordes en forte progression et des percussions électrifiantes." styleid="14" lengthseconds="159" time="2:39" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_190_Urban_Thriller/WOM190_trk005_ENTRAPMENT_(A)_John_Shoto_David_Buckley_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, CRAINTIF, TROUBLANT, ÉTRANGE , TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, TROUBLANT, BIZARRE, EFFRAYANT, HORREUR, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, FORT, EXCITANT, EVOLUTIF, NERVEUX, MONTÉE, ASCENDANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, MONTÉE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CORDES, VIOLON, SERIEUX, MONTEE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ETRANGE, DETERMINE, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Brut, nerveux et excitant. Des motifs de cordes en forte progression et des percussions électrifiantes. wom 190 tk005 john shoto david buckley entrapment (a) wom 190 urban thriller west one music drama film score orchestral trailer main movies action adventure movies action drama movies horror thriller movies urban drama trailers trailer track disturbing fearful disturbing strange disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense disturbing weird scary horror serious determined hard edgy and exciting. rising string motifs and electrifying percussion. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="18646" name="The Subterfuge (a)" code="WOM 199 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="395" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_199_Murder_Files/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Johnny Bernstein" comment="Une bande son lente et dramatique avec des lignes douces de piano sur un design sonore pulsant et des cordes atmosphériques." styleid="14" lengthseconds="216" time="3:36" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_199_Murder_Files/WOM199_trk001_THE_SUBTERFUGE_(A)_Johnny_Bernstein_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, SOUND DESIGN, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, ÉTRANGE , TROUBLANT, SURNATUREL, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, TROUBLANT, BIZARRE, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, PULSATION, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, VIOLON, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, INQUIETANT, ETRANGE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS Une bande son lente et dramatique avec des lignes douces de piano sur un design sonore pulsant et des cordes atmosphériques. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 199 tk001 johnny bernstein the subterfuge (a) wom 199 murder files west one music drama film score orchestral trailer sound elements atmospheres sound design main movies crime detective mystery movies espionage spy movies horror thriller movies human drama tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing eerie disturbing mysterious disturbing slow dramatic soundtrack with gentle piano lines over pulsing sound design and atmospheric strings. main delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="26366" name="Pressure Zone (a)" code="WOM 209 tk002" libraryid="6" albumid="565" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_209_Absolution/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Toby Y. Chu" comment="Tendu et menaçant avec des percussions fesant tic-tac et un piano suberbe. Progresse avec une batterie tribale et des cordes majestueuses." styleid="4" lengthseconds="144" time="2:24" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_209_Absolution/WOM209_trk002_PRESSURE_ZONE_(A)_Toby_Y._Chu_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), FORT, MAJESTUEUX, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, BATTERIE, CLAVIER, PIANO,, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETECTIVE, MYSTERE Tendu et menaçant avec des percussions fesant tic-tac et un piano suberbe. Progresse avec une batterie tribale et des cordes majestueuses. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 209 tk002 toby y. chu pressure zone (a) wom 209 absolution west one music film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) strong majestic serious serious disturbing mysterious disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense scary ominous movies action adventure movies crime detective mystery movies human drama movies horror thriller tense and ominous with ticking percussion and lush piano. builds with tribal drums and majestic strings. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="22355" name="Tinderbox" code="WOM 277 tk048" libraryid="6" albumid="479" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_277_Reconstruction_-_Textures/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Des arpèges élégants de cordes, avec des progressions dramatiques." styleid="12" lengthseconds="96" time="1:36" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_277_Reconstruction_-_Textures/WOM277_trk048_TINDERBOX_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="48" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, FORT, IMPLACABLE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, CHEVAUCHER, ÉQUESTRE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), STYLE VINTAGE, PERIODE, DETERMINE, ENERGIQUE, PERIODES, ELEGANT, EQUESTRE Des arpèges élégants de cordes, avec des progressions dramatiques. wom 277 tk048 david ashton tinderbox wom 277 reconstruction - textures west one music atmospheres film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral trailer main movies period historical costume drama strong determined strong energetic strong relentless movement rhythmic riding equestrian movement smooth elegant tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) vintage style elegant string arpeggios with dramatic builds. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="22397" name="Spyware (a)" code="WOM 279 tk006" libraryid="6" albumid="481" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_279_Action_Thriller_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Danny Mccarthy / Robert Leslie Bennett" comment="Unité sous couverture. Des sons de synthé hi-tech, des cordes épiques et des percussions brutales." styleid="2" lengthseconds="145" time="2:25" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_279_Action_Thriller_Trailers/WOM279_trk006_SPYWARE_(A)_Danny_Mccarthy_Robert_Leslie_Bennett_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="6" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, FORT, ÉPIQUE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), EPIQUE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE Unité sous couverture. Des sons de synthé hi-tech, des cordes épiques et des percussions brutales. wom 279 tk006 danny mccarthy robert leslie bennett spyware (a) wom 279 action thriller trailers west one music trailer film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral trailer main movies action adventure movies action drama movies crime detective mystery movies horror thriller trailers trailer track strong epic tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) the undercover unit. hi-tech synth sounds epic strings and brutal percussion. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="901" name="Runner (a)" code="FEM 019 tk001" libraryid="2" albumid="28" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_019_The_Game/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Udi Harpaz / Or Chausha" comment="Séquence action percutante, spectaculaire et plein d'adrénaline. Cordes à partir de 0:27 auxquelles se joignent des cuivres se développer en un final tout-puissant." styleid="2" lengthseconds="75" time="1:15" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_019_The_Game/FEM_019_trk001_RUNNER_(A)_Udi_Harpaz_Or_Chausha_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, CUIVRES, SECTION DE CUIVRES, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, PRINCIPAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, ORCHESTRAL HYBRIDE , TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, FORT, AVENTUREUX, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, ÉPIQUE, FORT, EXALTANT, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, IMPLACABLE, FORT, FORT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INSISTANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COURANT, EVOLUTIF, PERCUSSIF, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, JEUX VIDÉOS, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, ACTION, TRAILERS, TV, RADIO, SPORT, BATTERIE, TIMBALES, BATTERIE, TOMS, SERIEUX, JEUX VIDEOS, DETERMINE, EPIQUE, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Séquence action percutante, spectaculaire et plein d'adrénaline. Cordes à partir de 0:27 auxquelles se joignent des cuivres se développer en un final tout-puissant. fem 019 tk001 udi harpaz or chausha runner (a) fem 019 the game fired earth music trailer film score orchestral trailer brass brass section strings string section main film score orchestral orchestral hybrid disturbing tense dramatic intense serious determined serious serious strong adventurous strong confident strong determined strong epic strong exhilarating percussive action track with high drama and adrenaline. strings join from 0:27 and build with brass towards almighty backend. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
    <item id="20056" name="Straight to Hell (a)" code="WOM 228 tk010" libraryid="6" albumid="428" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_228_Apocalypse/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Gresby Race Nash" comment="Une ouverture gothique maussade, progresse avec des motifs répétitifs de piano et des cordes." styleid="14" lengthseconds="131" time="2:11" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_228_Apocalypse/WOM228_trk010_STRAIGHT_TO_HELL_(A)_Gresby_Race_Nash_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="10" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), TITRE POUR TRAILER, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, TROUBLANT, TENDU, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, TRAILERS, TV, RADIO, SPORT, SPORT,, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO) Une ouverture gothique maussade, progresse avec des motifs répétitifs de piano et des cordes. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 228 tk010 gresby race nash straight to hell (a) wom 228 apocalypse west one music drama film score orchestral trailer main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) trailer track strong prestigious disturbing tense movies action adventure movies human drama trailers tv radio sports sports brooding gothic opening builds with repeating piano patterns and strings. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="1382" name="Moscow (a)" code="FEM 015 tk004" libraryid="2" albumid="35" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_015_Zeitgeist/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Stephen Dean Hilton" comment="De l'indie-tronica sensible et tainté d'amour. Une section d'ouverture combine d'interessant et excentriques éléments de sound-design, percussions et cordes experimentales. Un thème rêveur et lamentant arrive à 1:18. L'intensité augmente au fur et à mesure à travers les percussions de 2:08 jusqu'à la fin." styleid="2" lengthseconds="166" time="2:46" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_015_Zeitgeist/FEM_015_trk004_MOSCOW_(A)_Stephen_Dean_Hilton_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, ORCHESTRAL HYBRIDE , ROCK, INDIE, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, SOUND DESIGN, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, CINÉMA FRANCAIS, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, FILMS INDÉPENDANTS, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, AGITÉ, TROUBLANT, TENDU, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, EVOLUTIF, GLITCHY, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), EUROPE, EUROPE DE L'OUEST, FRANCE, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, AGITE, CINEMA FRANCAIS, FILMS INDEPENDANTS, ELEMENTS, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION De l'indie-tronica sensible et tainté d'amour. Une section d'ouverture combine d'interessant et excentriques éléments de sound-design, percussions et cordes experimentales. Un thème rêveur et lamentant arrive à 1:18. L'intensité augmente au fur et à mesure à travers les percussions de 2:08 jusqu'à la fin. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede fem 015 tk004 stephen dean hilton moscow (a) fem 015 zeitgeist fired earth music trailer film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral orchestral hybrid rock indie sound elements atmospheres sound design main movies french cinema movies human drama movies indie films movies urban drama trailers trailer track disturbing restless disturbing tense peaceful emotive love-tinged indie-tronica. opening section combines interesting quirky sound design percussion and glitchy experimental strings. dreamy lamenting theme comes in from 1:18. building intensity through percussion from 2:08 to end. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
    <item id="26178" name="Dark Clouds (b)" code="WOM 098 tk017" libraryid="6" albumid="560" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_098_Emotive_Orchestral/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Bill Connor" comment="Des cordes et un chœur de grande envergure montant en crescendos, avec un sentiment anxieux de mouvement." styleid="4" lengthseconds="200" time="3:20" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_098_Emotive_Orchestral/WOM098_trk017_DARK_CLOUDS_(B)_Bill_Connor_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="17" tracktotal="" search="CLASSIQUE, CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIÈCLE, CLASSIQUE, STYLE MINIMALISTE, ALTERNATIF, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, TROUBLANT, ANXIEUX, TROUBLANT, AGITÉ, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT EN ÉMOTIONS, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CORDES, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, PERIODE, SERIEUX, FORT EN EMOTIONS, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIECLE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), AGITE, DETERMINE, EPIQUE, PERIODES, 20E SIECLE Des cordes et un chœur de grande envergure montant en crescendos, avec un sentiment anxieux de mouvement. wom 098 tk017 bill connor dark clouds (b) wom 098 emotive orchestral west one music film score orchestral classical classical 20th century classical style classical minimalist style alternate movies epic movies fantasy adventure movies human drama movies period historical costume drama disturbing anxious disturbing restless disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense scary ominous sweeping swelling strings with an anxious sense of motion. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="18231" name="Twisted Forces (a)" code="WOM 190 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="386" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_190_Urban_Thriller/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="John Shoto David Buckley" comment="Tendu et dramatique. Des beats électroniques croustillants avec des crescendos sombres de violon électrique et des percussions énormes de bandes-annonces." styleid="14" lengthseconds="161" time="2:41" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_190_Urban_Thriller/WOM190_trk001_TWISTED_FORCES_(A)_John_Shoto_David_Buckley_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, GUERRE, MILITAIRE, HISTORIQUE, GUERRE MODERNE, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, FILMS, GUERRE, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, CRAINTIF, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SURNATUREL, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, DANGEUREUX, EFFRAYANT, HORREUR, EFFRAYANT, MENAÇANT, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CORDES, HARPE, CORDES, VIOLON , PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, PERIODE, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), INQUIETANT, MENACANT, 20E SIECLE Tendu et dramatique. Des beats électroniques croustillants avec des crescendos sombres de violon électrique et des percussions énormes de bandes-annonces. wom 190 tk001 john shoto david buckley twisted forces (a) wom 190 urban thriller west one music drama film score orchestral trailer main activities settings war military historical modern warfare movies horror thriller movies urban drama movies war tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama trailer track disturbing dark disturbing eerie disturbing fearful disturbing tense and dramatic. crunchy electronic beats with dark electric violin sweeps string swells and huge trailer-style percussion. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="26368" name="Absolution (a)" code="WOM 209 tk004" libraryid="6" albumid="565" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_209_Absolution/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Toby Y. Chu" comment="Des sons atmosphériques profonds et flottants progressent, avec des cordes sombres de mauvaise augure et des beats, vers un climax épique." styleid="4" lengthseconds="205" time="3:25" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_209_Absolution/WOM209_trk004_ABSOLUTION_(A)_Toby_Y._Chu_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRAGIQUE, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, FORT, ÉPIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, EVOLUTIF, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), SERIEUX, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), DEPRIMANT, DETERMINE, EPIQUE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Des sons atmosphériques profonds et flottants progressent, avec des cordes sombres de mauvaise augure et des beats, vers un climax épique. wom 209 tk004 toby y. chu absolution (a) wom 209 absolution west one music film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer main movies crime detective mystery movies espionage spy movies human drama nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife trailers trailer track disturbing dark disturbing mysterious disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense peaceful deep drifting atmospherics building with dark foreboding strings and beats to an epic climax. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="26994" name="Young and Sprightly (a)" code="WOM 350A tk003" libraryid="6" albumid="579" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_350A_British_Drama/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Michael Price, Nicholas Hill" comment="Pizzicato de cordes et piano joyeux accompagnent un thème de cordes réconfortant." styleid="14" lengthseconds="110" time="1:50" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_350A_British_Drama/WOM_350A_trk003_YOUNG_AND_SPRIGHTLY_(A)_Michael_Price,_Nicholas_Hill_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, FAMILIAL, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, PERIODE, PERIODES, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, ELEMENTS, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, ART, ANTIQUITÉS, ANTIQUITES, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, DRAME TV, HEUREUX, JOYEUX, SÉRIEUX, ÉMOUVANT, SERIEUX, EMOUVANT, SÉRIEUX, ATTENTIONNÉ, SERIEUX, ATTENTIONNE, TENDRE, GRACIEUX, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, BEAU, MAGIQUE, PIZZICATO, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT, ELEGANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, BOIS, SECTION DE BOIS, CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, HARPE, CORDES, CORDES PIZZICATO, CORDES, VIOLON, BOIS, CLARINETTE, BOIS, FLUTE, BOIS, HAUTBOIS, HAUTBOIS, COR ANGLAIS, DRAME, BRITANNIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL Pizzicato de cordes et piano joyeux accompagnent un thème de cordes réconfortant. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 350a tk003 michael price nicholas hill young and sprightly (a) wom 350a british drama west one music drama film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral pastoral main movies children storytelling movies family movies human drama movies period historical costume drama movies romance nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral tv radio leisure lifestyle cheerful piano and pizzicato strings accompany a heartwarming string theme. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="7400" name="Situation Critical (a)" code="TSH 059 tk020" libraryid="5" albumid="168" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_059_Orchestral_Fantasia/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Arthur Rhodes" comment="Allusions dramatiques, soutenues." styleid="4" lengthseconds="68" time="1:08" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_059_Orchestral_Fantasia/TSH_059_trk020_SITUATION_CRITICAL_(A)_Simon_Arthur_Rhodes_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="20" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, TROUBLANT, AGITÉ, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, POURSUITE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE,, SERIEUX, AGITE, DETERMINE, ACCELERE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE Allusions dramatiques, soutenues. tsh 059 tk020 simon arthur rhodes situation critical (a) tsh 059 orchestral fantasia the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer main serious determined disturbing restless disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense movement rhythmic chase movement rhythmic clock like movement rhythmic speeded up time lapse movies action adventure movies action drama movies crime sustained dramatic undercurrents. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="587" name="Calliope (a)" code="FEM 004 tk005" libraryid="2" albumid="18" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_004_Bellitas/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Robert Leslie Bennett" comment="Un drame élégant, mystérieux et pénétrant." styleid="2" lengthseconds="106" time="1:46" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_004_Bellitas/FEM004_trk005_CALLIOPE_(A)_Robert_Leslie_Bennett_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ART ET ESSAI, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, CRAINTIF, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, DRAMATIQUE, DANGEUREUX, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, EFFRAYANT, MENAÇANT, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), STYLE VINTAGE, SERIEUX, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), DEPRIMANT, MENACANT, ELEGANT, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE Un drame élégant, mystérieux et pénétrant. fem 004 tk005 robert leslie bennett calliope (a) fem 004 bellitas fired earth music trailer film score orchestral trailer main movies art house movies crime detective mystery movies espionage spy movies human drama trailers trailer track disturbing fearful disturbing mysterious dramatic dangerous sad depressing sad scary menacing scary ominous serious serious elegant mystery drama and searching. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
    <item id="26483" name="Feeling the Pressure (a)" code="WOM 304 tk009" libraryid="6" albumid="568" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_304_Emotive_Minimalism/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Une atmosphère chargée d'anticipation: motifs tendus de cordes et piano réverberant. Tension dramatique à 1:04." styleid="4" lengthseconds="164" time="2:44" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_304_Emotive_Minimalism/WOM304_trk009_FEELING_THE_PRESSURE_(A)_Richard_Allen_Harvey_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, TROUBLANT, TENDU, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INSISTANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, RÉPÉTITIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA,, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), REPETITIF, ACCELERE, ELEMENTS Une atmosphère chargée d'anticipation: motifs tendus de cordes et piano réverberant. Tension dramatique à 1:04. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 304 tk009 richard allen harvey feeling the pressure (a) wom 304 emotive minimalism west one music film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer classical and semi classical symphony orchestra main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic disturbing tense movement rhythmic insistent movement rhythmic repetitive movement rhythmic tense string patterns and reverberant piano build an atmosphere of anticipation. dramatic tension builds at 1:04. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="1384" name="Dying is Easy (a)" code="FEM 015 tk006" libraryid="2" albumid="35" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_015_Zeitgeist/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Stephen Dean Hilton" comment="L'ultime combination de cordes sensibles et rythmes. Un thème de cordes déchirant se répète encore et encore, grandissant en émotions à travers la piste pendant que les rhytmes éléctroniques et le sound-design apparaissent. Le rythme s'intensifie à 2:15 puis s'éfface pour ne laisser que le thème de cordes déchirant et le piano." styleid="2" lengthseconds="167" time="2:47" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_015_Zeitgeist/FEM_015_trk006_DYING_IS_EASY_(A)_Stephen_Dean_Hilton_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="6" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, ORCHESTRAL HYBRIDE , ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, SOUND DESIGN, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, FILMS INDÉPENDANTS, FILMS, GUERRE, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, SÉRIEUX, ÉMOUVANT, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, ATTENTIONNÉ, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, FORT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), ELEMENTS SONORES, SERIEUX, ATMOSPHERES, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), EMOUVANT, ATTENTIONNE, FILMS INDEPENDANTS, ELEMENTS L'ultime combination de cordes sensibles et rythmes. Un thème de cordes déchirant se répète encore et encore, grandissant en émotions à travers la piste pendant que les rhytmes éléctroniques et le sound-design apparaissent. Le rythme s'intensifie à 2:15 puis s'éfface pour ne laisser que le thème de cordes déchirant et le piano. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live fem 015 tk006 stephen dean hilton dying is easy (a) fem 015 zeitgeist fired earth music trailer film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral orchestral hybrid sound elements atmospheres sound design main movies action drama movies human drama movies indie films movies war trailers trailer track serious emotional serious serious serious thoughtful strong the ultimate emotive strings and beats combination. a heartbreaking string theme repeats over and over growing in emotion throughout the track as electronic beats and sound design layer in. beats build to 2:15 then drop out leaving the lamenting strings and piano. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
    <item id="609" name="Burning Dawn (a)" code="FEM 023 tk004" libraryid="2" albumid="19" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_023_Unbreakable/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Christopher Wray / Daniel Heath" comment="Pop pour trailer puissant parfaite pour génériques crime, action, thriller et romantique. Introduction obsédante au piano, avec sound design cool mais dur à partir de 0:23. Hits de sound design, cool et inquiétants, précèdent des séries de deux claquements et montée électronique sci-fi inquiétante répétée trois fois. Cela est suivi d'une section spectaculaire, épique et intense avec beats, choeur et cordes pleines de caractère à 2:10, où un grésillement électronique amène une sinistre outro de piano." styleid="2" lengthseconds="157" time="2:37" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_023_Unbreakable/FEM_023_trk004_BURNING_DAWN_(A)_Christopher_Wray_Daniel_Heath_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, ORCHESTRAL HYBRIDE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, POP, POP, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, SOUND DESIGN, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, BACK END, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, EPIQUE, FILMS, MODERNE, FILMS, SCIENCE FICTION, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, FILMS, GUERRE, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, MÉLANCOLIE, DEPRIMANT, MELANCOLIE, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, SÉRIEUX, ÉMOUVANT, SERIEUX, EMOUVANT, SÉRIEUX, ATTENTIONNÉ, SERIEUX, ATTENTIONNE, SEXY, SÉDUISANT, SEDUISANT, SEXY, SEXY, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, DETERMINE, FORT, ÉPIQUE, EPIQUE, FORT, MAJESTUEUX, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, FORT, EVOLUTIF, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, CUIVRES, SECTION DE CUIVRES, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, GROUPES VOCAUX, CHOEUR, CHOEURS MIXTES, BATTERIE, BATTERIE, BATTERIE, TIMBALES, BATTERIE, TOMS, CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE Pop pour trailer puissant parfaite pour génériques crime, action, thriller et romantique. Introduction obsédante au piano, avec sound design cool mais dur à partir de 0:23. Hits de sound design, cool et inquiétants, précèdent des séries de deux claquements et montée électronique sci-fi inquiétante répétée trois fois. Cela est suivi d'une section spectaculaire, épique et intense avec beats, choeur et cordes pleines de caractère à 2:10, où un grésillement électronique amène une sinistre outro de piano. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live fem 023 tk004 christopher wray daniel heath burning dawn (a) fem 023 unbreakable fired earth music trailer film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral orchestral hybrid film score orchestral panoramic pop sound elements atmospheres sound design main movies action drama movies back end movies epic movies modern movies science fiction movies urban drama movies war modern pop trailer track for thriller romance crime or action titles. haunting piano intro with cool tough sound design from 0:23. cool eerie sound design hits precede series of two slams and eerie sci-fi electronic rise repeated three times. into tough epic dramatic section featuring beats choir and strings dripping in attitude to 2:10 where an electronic sizzle leads into eerie piano outro. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215288"/>
    <item id="22393" name="Stealth Mission (a)" code="WOM 279 tk002" libraryid="6" albumid="481" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_279_Action_Thriller_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Tobias Enhus / Robert Leslie Bennett" comment="Une introduction atmosphérique et menaçante évolue vers un final euphorisant et puissant." styleid="2" lengthseconds="128" time="2:08" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_279_Action_Thriller_Trailers/WOM279_trk002_STEALTH_MISSION_(A)_Tobias_Enhus_Robert_Leslie_Bennett_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, TRAILERS, TV, RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, TENDU, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, FORT, PUISSANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EVOLUTIF, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETECTIVE, TELE REALITE, MYSTERE, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Une introduction atmosphérique et menaçante évolue vers un final euphorisant et puissant. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 279 tk002 tobias enhus robert leslie bennett stealth mission (a) wom 279 action thriller trailers west one music trailer film score orchestral trailer main movies action drama movies crime detective mystery movies espionage spy trailers tv radio reality tv trailer track disturbing tense scary ominous strong powerful uplifting uplifting building tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) ominous atmospheric introduction evolves to uplifting powerful finale. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
  </items>
</librarycollection>
