<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<librarycollection>
  <items>
    <item id="22447" name="The Afterlife" code="WOM 280 tk012" libraryid="6" albumid="482" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_280_Cinematic_Indie/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Timothy Stephen Pierce / Brett Carr Boyett" comment="Une introduction optimiste entame une progression épique à 2:18. Inspirant et cinématographique." styleid="34" lengthseconds="282" time="4:42" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_280_Cinematic_Indie/WOM280_trk012_THE_AFTERLIFE_Timothy_Stephen_Pierce_Brett_Carr_Boyett_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, ENFANTS, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), ROCK, ROCK ALTERNATIF, ROCK, INDIE, FORT, ÉPIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE,, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), EPIQUE Une introduction optimiste entame une progression épique à 2:18. Inspirant et cinématographique. wom 280 tk012 timothy stephen pierce brett carr boyett the afterlife wom 280 cinematic indie west one music indie children main tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) rock alternative rock rock indie strong epic uplifting optimistic movies epic tv radio children youth tv optimistic introduction starts epic build at 2:18. inspiring and cinematic. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="23530" name="Turning the Tide (a)" code="WOM 305 tk008" libraryid="6" albumid="510" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_305_Inspiring_Indie/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Matthew James Robertson / Mike Reed / Tom Howe" comment="Une introduction menée au piano mène à un hymne indie qui ne cesse de grandir." styleid="34" lengthseconds="153" time="2:33" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_305_Inspiring_Indie/WOM_305_trk008_TURNING_THE_TIDE_(A)_Matthew_James_Robertson_Mike_Reed_Tom_Howe_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="8" tracktotal="" search="TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, ROCK, INDIE, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, RALENTI, EVOLUTIF, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, SPORT, JEUX OLYMPIQUES,, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), REVELER, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Une introduction menée au piano mène à un hymne indie qui ne cesse de grandir. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 305 tk008 matthew james robertson mike reed tom howe turning the tide (a) wom 305 inspiring indie west one music indie business corporate reveal launch main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) business corporate motivational business corporate reveal launch rock indie strong prestigious uplifting motivational movement smooth slow motion building business corporate tv radio sports sports piano-based introduction leads to ever-growing indie anthem. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="24401" name="Lovers’ Requiem (a)" code="WOM 322 tk005" libraryid="6" albumid="526" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_322_Cinematic_Drama/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Martin Tillmann" comment="Des lignes de piano à la beauté troublante entremelées avec des cordes enveloppantes, émouvantes." styleid="14" lengthseconds="151" time="2:31" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_322_Cinematic_Drama/WOM322_trk005_LOVERS_REQUIEM_(A)_Martin_Tillmann_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, MODERNE, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, DRAME FAMILIAL, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, DRAME HOSPITALIER, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, ANXIEUX, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, PASSIONNÉ, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, MÉLANCOLIE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, SÉRIEUX, INQUIET, SÉRIEUX, ÉMOUVANT, SÉRIEUX, SOLENNEL, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, CLAVIER, PIANO, FORMATIONS GENERALES, SERIEUX, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, PASSIONNE, DEPRIMANT, EMOUVANT, MELANCOLIE, ELEGANT Des lignes de piano à la beauté troublante entremelées avec des cordes enveloppantes, émouvantes. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 322 tk005 martin tillmann lovers’ requiem (a) wom 322 cinematic drama west one music drama film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral documentary main movies human drama movies modern tv radio tv drama family drama tv radio tv drama medical drama tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing anxious disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense hauntingly beautiful piano lines intertwined with rich emotive strings. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="23734" name="First Flight (b)" code="WOM 309 tk013" libraryid="6" albumid="514" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_309_Indie_Organica/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="John-Paul Jones" comment="Piano simple par dessus des break de luxuriantes textures vers une magnifique et édifiante section finale à 1:25." styleid="34" lengthseconds="142" time="2:22" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_309_Indie_Organica/WOM_309_trk013_FIRST_FLIGHT_(B)_John-Paul_Jones_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="13" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, POP CORPORATE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, ROCK, INDIE, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SPORT, TV, RADIO, SPORT, ABSTRAIT, SIMPLE, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, BEAU, EVOLUTIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETERMINE, AERIEN, REVELER, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Piano simple par dessus des break de luxuriantes textures vers une magnifique et édifiante section finale à 1:25. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 309 tk013 john-paul jones first flight (b) wom 309 indie organica west one music indie business corporate beds business corporate corporate pop business corporate motivational business corporate reveal launch rock indie main business corporate sports tv radio sports abstract simple serious determined strong prestigious uplifting motivational uplifting simple piano over lush textures breaks to a beautiful uplifting end section at 1:25. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="6292" name="Life Journeys" code="TSH 065A tk024" libraryid="5" albumid="148" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_065A_The_Piano_Book/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Ostinati fluides, expressifs." styleid="25" lengthseconds="185" time="3:05" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_065A_The_Piano_Book/TSH065A_trk024_LIFE_JOURNEYS_Richard_Allen_Harvey_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="24" tracktotal="" search="CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIÈCLE, PRINCIPAL, ENFANTS, CONTES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, INNOCENT, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, BEAU, MÉLODIQUE, LYRIQUE, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, CLAVIER, PIANO, SOLO, MELODIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIECLE, DEPRIMANT, 20E SIECLE, ELEMENTS Ostinati fluides, expressifs. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 065a tk024 richard allen harvey life journeys tsh 065a the piano book the scoring house classical opera classical 20th century classical style main children storytelling film score orchestral documentary film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral pastoral peaceful peaceful sad depressing poignant sad depressing sad tender hopeful tender innocent tender intimate expressive flowing ostinati. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="26493" name="Journey to the Light (b)" code="WOM 304 tk019" libraryid="6" albumid="568" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_304_Emotive_Minimalism/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Réconfortant et qui suscite l'inspiration. Évolue tout du long." styleid="4" lengthseconds="237" time="3:57" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_304_Emotive_Minimalism/WOM304_trk019_JOURNEY_TO_THE_LIGHT_(B)_Richard_Allen_Harvey_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="19" tracktotal="" search="CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE, CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, ALTERNATIF, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MER, PAYSAGE MARIN, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EVOLUTIF, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, ANGLETERRE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), AERIEN, ELEMENTS, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Réconfortant et qui suscite l'inspiration. Évolue tout du long. wom 304 tk019 richard allen harvey journey to the light (b) wom 304 emotive minimalism west one music film score orchestral classical classical styling classical classical styling film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic film score orchestral pastoral alternate documentary biographical historical the arts movies romance nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama inspirational and heartwarming gently building throughout. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="24397" name="Deliverance (a)" code="WOM 322 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="526" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_322_Cinematic_Drama/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Martin Tillmann" comment="Une introduction chatoyante amène des cordes puissantes et spectaculaires. Un voyage émouvant." styleid="14" lengthseconds="168" time="2:48" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_322_Cinematic_Drama/WOM322_trk001_DELIVERANCE_(A)_Martin_Tillmann_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, MODERNE, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, TROUBLANT, ANXIEUX, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, PASSIONNÉ, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, MÉLANCOLIE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, SÉRIEUX, INQUIET, SÉRIEUX, ÉMOUVANT, SÉRIEUX, SOLENNEL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, CLAVIER, PIANO, FORMATIONS GENERALES, SERIEUX, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, PASSIONNE, DEPRIMANT, EMOUVANT, MELANCOLIE, ELEGANT, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE Une introduction chatoyante amène des cordes puissantes et spectaculaires. Un voyage émouvant. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 322 tk001 martin tillmann deliverance (a) wom 322 cinematic drama west one music drama film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral documentary main movies crime detective mystery movies espionage spy movies human drama movies modern tv radio tv drama disturbing anxious disturbing mysterious disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense dramatic shimmering introduction leads to powerful cinematic strings and an emotive journey. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="3439" name="Wishes in the Wind" code="TSH 013 tk012" libraryid="5" albumid="103" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_013_It's_My_Life/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Ian Paul Livingstone" comment="Des espérances silencieuses et secrètes." styleid="10" lengthseconds="111" time="1:51" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_013_It's_My_Life/TSH013_trk012_WISHES_IN_THE_WIND_Ian_Paul_Livingstone_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, TROUBLANT, DROLE, MÉLODRAMATIQUE, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, INTROSPECTIF, PAISIBLE, DOUX, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, SÉRIEUX, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLAVIER, PIANO, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), MELODRAMATIQUE, DEPRIMANT, ELEMENTS Des espérances silencieuses et secrètes. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 013 tk012 ian paul livingstone wishes in the wind tsh 013 it's my life the scoring house documentary film score orchestral pastoral main documentary movies human drama nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife disturbing funny melodramatic peaceful dreamy peaceful introspective peaceful quiet sad depressing lonely sad depressing poignant sad depressing sad quiet introspective hopes. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="21262" name="The Breakthrough (a)" code="WOM 254A tk004" libraryid="6" albumid="456" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_254A_Supercharger_-_Indie/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Tyler Van Den Berg" comment="Des guitares stridentes et des refrains épiques qui célèbrent la vie." styleid="34" lengthseconds="124" time="2:04" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_254A_Supercharger_-_Indie/WOM254A_trk004_THE_BREAKTHROUGH_(A)_Tyler_Van_Den_Berg_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, INDIE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 90, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ROCK, ROCK DE STADE, FORT, ÉPIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, SPORT, SPORTS EXTREMES,, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), EPIQUE, ANNEES 2000, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 20, ANNEES 90 Des guitares stridentes et des refrains épiques qui célèbrent la vie. wom 254a tk004 tyler van den berg the breakthrough (a) wom 254a supercharger - indie west one music indie rock indie time period modern era 20th century 1990s time period modern era 2000s main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) rock stadium rock strong epic movement rhythmic driving movement rhythmic rugged movies epic tv radio sports sports extreme sports jangling guitars and epic life affirming choruses. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="4672" name="Dream the Moment (b)" code="TSH 035 tk068" libraryid="5" albumid="125" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_035_A_Winner_is_Born/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Mark Lasker" comment="Un thème visionnaire et sincère." styleid="22" lengthseconds="141" time="2:21" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_035_A_Winner_is_Born/TSH035_trk068_DREAM_THE_MOMENT_(B)_Mark_Lasker_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="68" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, ALTERNATIF, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, PRINTEMPS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, DIVIN, CÉLESTE, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, PATRIOTIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EVOLUTIF, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, MONTÉE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, RALENTI, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, MONTEE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, ACCELERE, AERIEN, REVELER, ELEMENTS, CELESTE, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Un thème visionnaire et sincère. tsh 035 tk068 mark lasker dream the moment (b) tsh 035 a winner is born the scoring house sport children storytelling business corporate luxury business corporate motivational business corporate reveal launch film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic alternate movies children storytelling nature wildlife the elements seasons time spring nature visionary heartfelt theme. alternative" waveformpath="" version="Alternative" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="26635" name="Beyond the Stratosphere (a)" code="WOM 257 tk002" libraryid="6" albumid="571" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_257_Cinematic_Soundscapes/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Daniel Law Heath / James Brian Brasher" comment="Des cordes planantes et somptueuses, des flûtes etniques rêveuses, et des motifs de piano magnifiques et évocateurs." styleid="4" lengthseconds="167" time="2:47" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_257_Cinematic_Soundscapes/WOM257_trk002_BEYOND_THE_STRATOSPHERE_(A)_Daniel_Law_Heath_James_Brian_Brasher_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, JAILLIR, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, SÉRIEUX, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, DOCUMENTAIRE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, MÉDICAL, SCIENCES DE LA VIE,, SERIEUX, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, MEDICAL Des cordes planantes et somptueuses, des flûtes etniques rêveuses, et des motifs de piano magnifiques et évocateurs. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 257 tk002 daniel law heath james brian brasher beyond the stratosphere (a) wom 257 cinematic soundscapes west one music film score orchestral business corporate science technology main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) uplifting soaring peaceful dreamy peaceful peaceful tender reflective serious movement smooth aerial flying business corporate documentary nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife nature soaring sumptuous strings dreamy ethnic flutes and gorgeous evocative piano patterns. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="1414" name="Freefall (a)" code="FEM 017 tk001" libraryid="2" albumid="36" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_017_Jesper_Kyd_Legacy/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jesper Kyd" comment="Épopée orchestrale grandiose et émouvante, avec percussion, choeur toute-puissante et un grand thème de cordes. Introduction jusqu'à 0:35, développement de la partie centrale jusqu'à 1:15. Continue jusqu'à 2:05 avec la reprise des cordes." styleid="2" lengthseconds="153" time="2:33" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_017_Jesper_Kyd_Legacy/FEM_017_trk001_FREEFALL_(A)_Jesper_Kyd_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, TRAILERS, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, DRAMATIQUE, PASSIONNÉ, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, SÉRIEUX, DIGNE, SÉRIEUX, ÉMOUVANT, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, COURAGEUX, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, ÉPIQUE, FORT, HÉROIQUE, FORT, MAJESTUEUX, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, FORT, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE DE CHAMBRE, PETIT ORCHESTRE, GROUPES VOCAUX, CHOEUR, CHOEURS MIXTES, PERIODE, SERIEUX, PASSIONNE, DETERMINE, EMOUVANT, EPIQUE, HEROIQUE, PERIODES, ELEMENTS Épopée orchestrale grandiose et émouvante, avec percussion, choeur toute-puissante et un grand thème de cordes. Introduction jusqu'à 0:35, développement de la partie centrale jusqu'à 1:15. Continue jusqu'à 2:05 avec la reprise des cordes. fem 017 tk001 jesper kyd freefall (a) fem 017 jesper kyd's legacy fired earth music trailer film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic main movies action drama movies epic movies period historical costume drama nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama trailers dramatic intense dramatic passionate serious determined serious huge emotive orchestral epic featuring percussion sweeping string theme and almighty choir. intro to 0:35 building mid-section to 1:15 then driving through to 2:05 with string reprise. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
    <item id="3437" name="Walking Away" code="TSH 013 tk010" libraryid="5" albumid="103" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_013_It's_My_Life/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Ian Paul Livingstone" comment="Un thème profond et émotionnel." styleid="10" lengthseconds="95" time="1:35" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_013_It's_My_Life/TSH013_trk010_WALKING_AWAY_Ian_Paul_Livingstone_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="10" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, TROUBLANT, DROLE, MÉLODRAMATIQUE, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, SÉRIEUX, ÉMOUVANT, SÉRIEUX, ATTENTIONNÉ, TENDRE, INNOCENT, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EVOLUTIF, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, MUSIQUE DE CHAMBRE, ENSEMBLE CLASSIQUE, STYLE VINTAGE, PERIODE, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), MELODRAMATIQUE, DEPRIMANT, EMOUVANT, ATTENTIONNE, PERIODES, ELEMENTS, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Un thème profond et émotionnel. tsh 013 tk010 ian paul livingstone walking away tsh 013 it's my life the scoring house documentary children business corporate luxury film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral pastoral main movies human drama movies period historical costume drama movies romance nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral nature wildlife the elements thoughtful emotional theme. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="466" name="Aphelion (b)" code="FEM 007 tk013" libraryid="2" albumid="14" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_007_Ultimatum/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jesper Kyd" comment="Un morceau orchestral épique et héroïque avec des percussions live." styleid="2" lengthseconds="148" time="2:28" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_007_Ultimatum/FEM007_trk013_APHELION_(B)_Jesper_Kyd_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="13" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, RELIGIEUX, WORLD BEAT, STYLES ETHNIQUES, GLOBAL, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, BACK END, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, SÉRIEUX, FORT, ÉPIQUE, FORT, FORT, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EVOLUTIF, COOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, MONTÉE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, RALENTI, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), SERIEUX, MONTEE, DEPRIMANT, EPIQUE, AERIEN, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Un morceau orchestral épique et héroïque avec des percussions live. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live fem 007 tk013 jesper kyd aphelion (b) fem 007 ultimatum fired earth music trailer film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic religious world beat ethnic stylings global main movies action drama movies back end movies epic movies fantasy adventure trailers trailer track peaceful dreamy peaceful peaceful sad depressing poignant sad epic orchestral cue that builds heroically with live percussion. without vocal knees up, mess piano, cockney, east london, singalong, pub joanna, piano bar, piano-bar, live" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
    <item id="1385" name="Night (a)" code="FEM 015 tk007" libraryid="2" albumid="35" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_015_Zeitgeist/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Stephen Dean Hilton" comment="Des batteries entrainantes, une guitare morne et des vocaux voilés créent cette piste pour bande annonce cool, moderne et énergique." styleid="2" lengthseconds="144" time="2:24" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_015_Zeitgeist/FEM_015_trk007_NIGHT_(A)_Stephen_Dean_Hilton_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ROCK, INDIE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, FILMS INDÉPENDANTS, FILMS, ROAD MOVIE, SPORT, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, FORT, PUISSANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, POURSUITE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COURANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ENERGIQUE, FILMS INDEPENDANTS Des batteries entrainantes, une guitare morne et des vocaux voilés créent cette piste pour bande annonce cool, moderne et énergique. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz fem 015 tk007 stephen dean hilton night (a) fem 015 zeitgeist fired earth music trailer film score orchestral trailer rock indie main movies action adventure movies indie films movies road movie sports trailers trailer track strong energetic strong powerful uplifting inspirational uplifting motivational uplifting positive uplifting uplifting movement driving drums moody guitar and warped vocals create a cool and energetic modern trailer track. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
    <item id="799" name="Infinite, Immortal (a)" code="FEM 014 tk003" libraryid="2" albumid="25" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_014_Heroes/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Mark John Petrie" comment="Ouverture à suspense, couveuse et pleine d'anticipation avec un thème de corde cahin-caha à partir de 00:48 se transforme en une piste héroïque toute puissante avec une fin magistrale accompagnée d'un synthé et un chœur d'hommes." styleid="2" lengthseconds="151" time="2:31" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_014_Heroes/FEM014_trk003_INFINITE,_IMMORTAL_(A)_Mark_John_Petrie_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, BACK END, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, SCIENCE FICTION, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, TENDU, FORT, ÉPIQUE, FORT, HÉROIQUE, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, FORT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, DÉFILÉ, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, PERIODE, EPIQUE, HEROIQUE, 20E SIECLE, DEFILE Ouverture à suspense, couveuse et pleine d'anticipation avec un thème de corde cahin-caha à partir de 00:48 se transforme en une piste héroïque toute puissante avec une fin magistrale accompagnée d'un synthé et un chœur d'hommes. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede fem 014 tk003 mark john petrie infinite immortal (a) fem 014 heroes fired earth music trailer film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic main movies action adventure movies back end movies epic movies science fiction trailers trailer track disturbing tense strong epic strong heroic strong powerful strong strong movement rhythmic driving brooding thriller opening full of anticipation with chugging string theme from 00:48 evolves into an almighty heroic epic at 01:08 with huge backend featuring synth and male choir. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
    <item id="23653" name="Titans of War (b)" code="WOM 307 tk017" libraryid="6" albumid="512" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_307_Epic_World_/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Daniel Law Heath" comment="Action rapide et furieuse, grondements de basse dramatiques et percussions tribales épiques." styleid="2" lengthseconds="138" time="2:18" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_307_Epic_World_/WOM_307_trk017_TITANS_OF_WAR_(B)_Daniel_Law_Heath_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="17" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, UNDERSCORE, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, FILMS, GUERRE, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, FORT, ÉPIQUE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), EPIQUE Action rapide et furieuse, grondements de basse dramatiques et percussions tribales épiques. wom 307 tk017 daniel law heath titans of war (b) wom 307 epic world west one music trailer film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral trailer underscore movies action adventure movies epic movies fantasy adventure movies war trailers trailer track strong epic tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) fast and furious action cue dramatic brass swells epic tribal percussion. underscore" waveformpath="" version="Underscore" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="1387" name="This is a Warning Sign (a)" code="FEM 015 tk009" libraryid="2" albumid="35" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_015_Zeitgeist/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Stephen Dean Hilton" comment="Un rythme de dance entrainant accompagné d'iconiques vocal masculins, cordes, guitare et rythme. &quot;This is a warning sign. I'm coming between the lines. This is the word to wake the dead. I'm coming look out ahead.&quot; Retombée à 0:47 vers un énergique vocal &quot;Look out ahead!&quot; annoncant le chorus entrainant et le thème de cordes. Une intense scène d'hommes courants sous la pluie au milieu de la nuit." styleid="2" lengthseconds="130" time="2:10" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_015_Zeitgeist/FEM_015_trk009_THIS_IS_A_WARNING_SIGN_(A)_Stephen_Dean_Hilton_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BIG BEAT, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, ORCHESTRAL HYBRIDE , BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, POP, ROCK, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, FILMS INDÉPENDANTS, FILMS, ROAD MOVIE, TRAILERS, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TITRE POUR TRAILER, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, JAILLIR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COURANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CHOEUR, CHOEUR MASCULIN, VOCAL, MASCULIN, VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, VOIX TRAITÉES, MODIFIÉES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ENERGIQUE, FILMS INDEPENDANTS, VOIX TRAITEES, MODIFIEES Un rythme de dance entrainant accompagné d'iconiques vocal masculins, cordes, guitare et rythme. &quot;This is a warning sign. I'm coming between the lines. This is the word to wake the dead. I'm coming look out ahead.&quot; Retombée à 0:47 vers un énergique vocal &quot;Look out ahead!&quot; annoncant le chorus entrainant et le thème de cordes. Une intense scène d'hommes courants sous la pluie au milieu de la nuit. fem 015 tk009 stephen dean hilton this is a warning sign (a) fem 015 zeitgeist fired earth music trailer film score orchestral trailer club electronica big beat film score orchestral orchestral hybrid film score orchestral panoramic pop rock main movies human drama movies indie films movies road movie trailers tv radio sports trailer track strong energetic strong powerful driving dance beat featuring iconic male vocal strings guitar and beats. &quot;this is a warning sign. i'm coming between the lines. this is the word to wake the dead. i'm coming look out ahead.&quot; drop out at 0:47 into energetic &quot;look out ahead!&quot; vocal announcing the catchy male chorus and string theme. think heart-pounding night scene with men running in the rain. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
    <item id="835" name="Raising Hell (a)" code="FEM 016 tk003" libraryid="2" albumid="26" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_016_Amplified/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Brent Woods / Enrico Cacace" comment="A toute allure! Action rock pour trailers. Idéal pour les scènes de poursuite en voiture et les promos de sport." styleid="2" lengthseconds="111" time="1:51" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_016_Amplified/FEM_016_trk003_RAISING_HELL_(A)_Brent_Woods_Enrico_Cacace_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, ROCK ALTERNATIF, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ROCK, GARAGE ROCK, ROCK, HARD ROCK, ROCK, HEAVY METAL, TITRE POUR TRAILER, DRAMATIQUE, DANGEUREUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, POURSUITE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, TRAILERS, TV, RADIO, SPORT, SPORT, SPORTS EXTREMES, A toute allure! Action rock pour trailers. Idéal pour les scènes de poursuite en voiture et les promos de sport. fem 016 tk003 brent woods enrico cacace raising hell (a) fem 016 amplified fired earth music trailer rock alternative rock main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) film score orchestral trailer rock garage rock rock hard rock rock heavy metal trailer track dramatic dangerous movement rhythmic chase movement rhythmic driving movement rhythmic rugged movies action adventure full throttle rock action trailer cue. perfect for explosive car chase scenes or sports promos. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
    <item id="28931" name="Riding Giants" code="WOMG 020A tk008" libraryid="7" albumid="621" albumartpath="Music/West One Music Group/WOMG_020A_This_is_Epic/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Ryan Amon" comment="Morceau sombre mais héroique avec un sens de l'expectative dans l'ouverture. Un thème de percussions et cuivres à partir de 0:22, et une mélodie héroique de cordes à partir de 0:46 se répètent tout au long du morceau jusqu'à la fin, avec un sens du drame grandissant." styleid="2" lengthseconds="123" time="2:03" samplefile="Music/West One Music Group/WOMG_020A_This_is_Epic/WOMG020A_trk008_RIDING_GIANTS_Ryan_Amon_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="8" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, FILMS, GUERRE, TRAILERS, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, DRAMATIQUE, PASSIONNÉ, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, FORT, AVENTUREUX, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, ÉPIQUE, FORT, HÉROIQUE, FORT, FORT, CUIVRES, SECTION DE CUIVRES, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, GROUPES VOCAUX, CHOEUR, CHOEURS MIXTES, BATTERIE, TIMBALES, SERIEUX, PASSIONNE, DETERMINE, EPIQUE, HEROIQUE Morceau sombre mais héroique avec un sens de l'expectative dans l'ouverture. Un thème de percussions et cuivres à partir de 0:22, et une mélodie héroique de cordes à partir de 0:46 se répètent tout au long du morceau jusqu'à la fin, avec un sens du drame grandissant. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede womg 020a tk008 ryan amon riding giants womg 020a this is epic west one music group trailer film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic main movies action adventure movies epic movies fantasy adventure movies war trailers dramatic intense dramatic passionate serious determined serious serious strong adventurous strong confident strong dark yet heroic trailer track with sense of anticipation in the opening. percussion and brass theme from 0:22 and a heroic string melody from 0:46 repeats throughout to ending with building drama and massive back end. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
    <item id="876" name="Tacitus (a)" code="FEM 018 tk006" libraryid="2" albumid="27" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_018_Vesuvius/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Daniel Law Heath" comment="Aventure fantastique, sombre et pleine d'appréhension avec des éléments de modernité. Un rythme cogneur, des accents de cuivres, un choeur et des cordes créent l'attente à 1:08. À 1:23, une section pleine d'obscurité, de pessimisme et d'énergie." styleid="2" lengthseconds="132" time="2:12" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_018_Vesuvius/FEM018_trk006_TACITUS_(A)_Daniel_Law_Heath_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="6" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, CUIVRES, SECTION DE CUIVRES, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, GROUPES VOCAUX, CHOEUR, CHOEURS MIXTES, PRINCIPAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, ORCHESTRAL HYBRIDE , BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, DRAMATIQUE, PASSIONNÉ, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, FORT, AVENTUREUX, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, FORT, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, BACK END, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, FILMS, SCIENCE FICTION, FILMS, GUERRE, TRAILERS, BATTERIE, TIMBALES, SERIEUX, PASSIONNE, DETERMINE, EPIQUE Aventure fantastique, sombre et pleine d'appréhension avec des éléments de modernité. Un rythme cogneur, des accents de cuivres, un choeur et des cordes créent l'attente à 1:08. À 1:23, une section pleine d'obscurité, de pessimisme et d'énergie. fem 018 tk006 daniel law heath tacitus (a) fem 018 vesuvius fired earth music trailer film score orchestral trailer brass brass section strings string section vocal groupings chorus mixed chorus main film score orchestral orchestral hybrid film score orchestral panoramic dramatic intense dramatic passionate serious determined serious serious strong dark foreboding fantasy adventure cue with modern elements. pounding rhythm brass stabs strings and choir build anticipation to 1:08. drop down and electronic set up and rise to 1:23 leads into dark end section of doom energy and almighty back end featuring massive stabs and rise. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
    <item id="3378" name="Mad Ferret" code="TSH 012 tk003" libraryid="5" albumid="102" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_012_Welcome_to_Rockford/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="James Robert Nisbet / James Roger Graydon" comment="Du rock accrocheur avec un bon feeling." styleid="6" lengthseconds="200" time="3:20" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_012_Welcome_to_Rockford/TSH012_trk003_MAD_FERRET_James_Robert_Nisbet_James_Roger_Graydon_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="POP, BRITPOP, ROCK, PRINCIPAL, SPORT, TV, RADIO, SPORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO) Du rock accrocheur avec un bon feeling. tsh 012 tk003 james robert nisbet james roger graydon mad ferret tsh 012 welcome to rockford the scoring house rock pop britpop rock main sports tv radio sports uplifting positive movement rhythmic driving movement rhythmic rugged tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) hooky feelgood rock. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="22724" name="Rage Racer (a)" code="WOM 287 tk005" libraryid="6" albumid="491" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_287_Rock_Action_Hybrid/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="George Francis" comment="Une basse grondante et crasseuse et des guitares rencontrent un mélange musclé de batterie rock et synthés." styleid="6" lengthseconds="200" time="3:20" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_287_Rock_Action_Hybrid/WOM_287_trk005_RAGE_RACER_(A)_George_Francis_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), ROCK, ROCK ALTERNATIF, ROCK, NU METAL, TITRE POUR TRAILER, DRAMATIQUE, DANGEUREUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FRÉNÉSIE, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, ACTION, TRAILERS, TV, RADIO, SPORT, SPORT, SPORTS EXTREMES,, FRENESIE Une basse grondante et crasseuse et des guitares rencontrent un mélange musclé de batterie rock et synthés. wom 287 tk005 george francis rage racer (a) wom 287 rock action hybrid west one music rock film score orchestral trailer main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) rock alternative rock rock nu metal trailer track dramatic dangerous movement rhythmic frenzy movies action adventure movies action drama trailers tv radio sports sports extreme sports growling dirty bass and guitars meet smashed-up amped-up rock drums and synth leads. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="22358" name="Starting Gun (a)" code="WOM 278 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="480" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_278_Drums_Rule_the_World/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Emre Ramazanoglu / Geoffrey James Pidcock Holroyde" comment="La partie peut commencer ! Des percussions épiques de bande-annonce et des immenses accords de rock power." styleid="22" lengthseconds="143" time="2:23" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_278_Drums_Rule_the_World/WOM278_trk001_STARTING_GUN_(A)_Emre_Ramazanoglu_Geoffrey_James_Pidcock_Holroyde_West_One_Music_Limi.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, SPORT, SPORTS EXTREMES, TV, RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TV, RADIO, SPORT, FORT, ÉPIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, POURSUITE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COURANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BATTERIE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), EPIQUE, TELE REALITE La partie peut commencer ! Des percussions épiques de bande-annonce et des immenses accords de rock power. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede wom 278 tk001 emre ramazanoglu geoffrey james pidcock holroyde starting gun (a) wom 278 drums rule the world west one music sport film score orchestral trailer main movies action drama movies epic sports extreme sports tv radio reality tv tv radio sports strong epic movement rhythmic chase movement rhythmic driving movement rhythmic rugged movement rhythmic running tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) let the games begin! epic trailer-style percussion and big rock power chords. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="1345" name="Seeker of the Prophecy" code="FEM 012 tk001" libraryid="2" albumid="34" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_012_Dark_Urban_Epics/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Enrico Cacace" comment="Sound design et coups de cuivres osés ouvrent cette piste urbaine épique et sombre pour bande-annonce. Les percussions toutes-puissantes et un thème de cuivres implacables sont au centre de cette piste héroïque." styleid="2" lengthseconds="99" time="1:39" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_012_Dark_Urban_Epics/FEM_012_trk001_SEEKER_OF_THE_PROPHECY_Enrico_Cacace_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, SOUND DESIGN, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, BACK END, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, MODERNE, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, AGRESSIF, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, FORT, ÉPIQUE, FORT, HÉROIQUE, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, FORT, IMPLACABLE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, DÉFILÉ, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ELEMENTS SONORES, PERIODE, SERIEUX, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETERMINE, EPIQUE, HEROIQUE, 20E SIECLE, DEFILE, ELEMENTS Sound design et coups de cuivres osés ouvrent cette piste urbaine épique et sombre pour bande-annonce. Les percussions toutes-puissantes et un thème de cuivres implacables sont au centre de cette piste héroïque. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede fem 012 tk001 enrico cacace seeker of the prophecy fem 012 dark urban epics fired earth music trailer film score orchestral trailer sound elements atmospheres sound design main movies action drama movies back end movies epic movies modern trailers trailer track disturbing dark disturbing tense dramatic aggressive scary ominous serious determined serious serious strong sound design and bold brass stabs open this dark urban epic trailer cue. almighty percussion and a relentless brass theme form the backbone to this heroic trailer track. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
    <item id="655" name="Fire of Zeus (a)" code="FEM 009 tk001" libraryid="2" albumid="21" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_009_Immortality/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Ryan Amon" comment="Une ouverture dramatique de percussions évolue vers la moitié du morceau et laisse présager un final puissant et dark." styleid="2" lengthseconds="122" time="2:02" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_009_Immortality/FEM009_trk001_FIRE_OF_ZEUS_(A)_Ryan_Amon_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, BACK END, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, TENDU, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, PATRIOTIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, PERCUSSIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, DÉFILÉ, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, CHEVAUCHER, ÉQUESTRE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COURANT, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, CHOEUR, PÉRIODE, CIVILISATIONS ANCIENNES, ROME ANTIQUE (500 AV. J-C - 476 AP. J-C), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, PERIODE, SERIEUX, DETERMINE, EPIQUE, PERIODES, 20E SIECLE, DEFILE, EQUESTRE Une ouverture dramatique de percussions évolue vers la moitié du morceau et laisse présager un final puissant et dark. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede fem 009 tk001 ryan amon fire of zeus (a) fem 009 immortality fired earth music trailer film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic main movies action adventure movies back end movies epic movies period historical costume drama trailers trailer track disturbing dark disturbing tense scary ominous serious determined serious serious strong dramatic percussive opening evolves into foreboding mid-section and powerful dark build to huge back end. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
    <item id="28067" name="Precession" code="WOMG 001A tk001" libraryid="7" albumid="600" albumartpath="Music/West One Music Group/WOMG_001A_This_Is_Sport/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jesper Kyd (BMI)" comment="Morceau pour trailer épique. Des cordes sombres préparent le terrain pour une grande séquence de percussions avec montées de cuivres et choeur sinistre et profond." styleid="22" lengthseconds="114" time="1:54" samplefile="Music/West One Music Group/WOMG_001A_This_Is_Sport/WOMG_001A_trk001_PRECESSION_Jesper_Kyd_(BMI)_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, CHOEUR, CHOEUR MASCULIN, PÉRIODE, CIVILISATIONS ANCIENNES, ROME ANTIQUE (500 AV. J-C - 476 AP. J-C), PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, AGRESSIF, DRAMATIQUE, DANGEUREUX, DRAMATIQUE, VIOLENT, EFFRAYANT, MENAÇANT, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, ÉPIQUE, EVOLUTIF, PERCUSSIF, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, BACK END, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, PERIODE, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), MENACANT, DETERMINE, EPIQUE, PERIODES, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Morceau pour trailer épique. Des cordes sombres préparent le terrain pour une grande séquence de percussions avec montées de cuivres et choeur sinistre et profond. womg 001a tk001 jesper kyd (bmi) precession womg 001a this is sport west one music group sport sport promo action epic drama emotive orchestral indie rock dance urban inspiring adventure action sport extreme sport commercials advertising epic trailer cue. dark strings set up for giant percussive cue with brass swells and deep sinister choir. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
    <item id="1454" name="Man of Steel Dirty Dubstep Remix" code="FEM 006 tk001" libraryid="2" albumid="37" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_006_Man_of_Steel_-_Remixed_EP/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Troels Brun Folmann" comment="Une orchestration épique mélangée à du dubstep battant pour des bandes-annonces chargées en adrénaline." styleid="2" lengthseconds="168" time="2:48" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_006_Man_of_Steel_-_Remixed_EP/FEM006_trk001_MAN_OF_STEEL_DIRTY_DUBSTEP_REMIX_Troels_Brun_Folmann_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, ORCHESTRAL HYBRIDE , CLUB, ELECTRONICA, DUB, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, DUBSTEP, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRO, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, REMIXES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, MODERNE, SPORT, SPORTS EXTREMES, TRAILERS, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, TENDU, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, ÉPIQUE, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, MÉCANIQUE, ROBOTIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, VOIX TRAITÉES, MODIFIÉES, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PERIODE, SERIEUX, MECANIQUE, DETERMINE, EPIQUE, ANNEES 2000, VOIX TRAITEES, ANNEES 20, MODIFIEES Une orchestration épique mélangée à du dubstep battant pour des bandes-annonces chargées en adrénaline. fem 006 tk001 troels brun folmann man of steel dirty dubstep remix fem 006 man of steel - remixed ep fired earth music trailer film score orchestral orchestral hybrid club electronica dub club electronica dubstep club electronica electro club electronica remixes film score orchestral trailer main movies action drama movies modern sports extreme sports trailers tv radio sports trailer track epic orchestral smashed together with pounding dupstep for high-adrenaline trailers. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
    <item id="21120" name="Shattered and Battered" code="WOM 251A tk007" libraryid="6" albumid="452" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_251A_Breakbeat_Deluxe/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Russell Mcnamara" comment="Des breaks trash et fracassants avec des samples jazzy et des sons atmosphériques sombres." styleid="1" lengthseconds="256" time="4:16" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_251A_Breakbeat_Deluxe/WOM251A_trk007_SHATTERED_AND_BATTERED_Russell_Mcnamara_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, MÉLODRAMATIQUE, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, DONNE LA CHAIR DE POULE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE,, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), MELODRAMATIQUE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE Des breaks trash et fracassants avec des samples jazzy et des sons atmosphériques sombres. wom 251a tk007 russell mcnamara shattered and battered wom 251a breakbeat deluxe west one music dance electro club electronica breakbeat main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) film score orchestral trailer funny comedic funny melodramatic disturbing dark disturbing spooky movies crime detective mystery movies espionage spy tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle trashy smashed-up breaks with jazzy samples and dark atmospherics. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="797" name="Black Angels Rise (a)" code="FEM 014 tk001" libraryid="2" albumid="25" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_014_Heroes/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Mark John Petrie" comment="Thème délicat au piano, pulsation délicate et subtile et cordes élegantes ouvrent ce track épique et sensible, qui se developpe ensuite en un thème magistral à partir de 0:34 avec pour accompagnement des batteries et un chœur retentissant. Énorme construction à 1:30, puis retour vers une intimidante outro d'après-coup reflétant l'intro." styleid="2" lengthseconds="113" time="1:53" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_014_Heroes/FEM014_trk001_BLACK_ANGELS_RISE_(A)_Mark_John_Petrie_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, BACK END, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, SCIENCE FICTION, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, TENDU, FORT, ÉPIQUE, TENDRE, DÉLICAT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), EPIQUE, DELICAT, ELEGANT Thème délicat au piano, pulsation délicate et subtile et cordes élegantes ouvrent ce track épique et sensible, qui se developpe ensuite en un thème magistral à partir de 0:34 avec pour accompagnement des batteries et un chœur retentissant. Énorme construction à 1:30, puis retour vers une intimidante outro d'après-coup reflétant l'intro. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live fem 014 tk001 mark john petrie black angels rise (a) fem 014 heroes fired earth music trailer film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic main movies action adventure movies back end movies epic movies science fiction trailers trailer track disturbing tense strong epic tender delicate movement rhythmic driving movement rhythmic rugged movement delicate piano theme deep pulse and subtle elegant strings open this emotive evolving epic which develops into a huge theme from 0:34 featuring pounding drums and chorus. enormous build to 1:30 then returning to a daunting aftermath outro reflecting the opening. main delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
  </items>
</librarycollection>
