<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<librarycollection>
  <items>
    <item id="27007" name="Life on Earth (b)" code="WOM 350A tk016" libraryid="6" albumid="579" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_350A_British_Drama/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Joseph Rubel, Michael Price" comment="Cordes en pizzicato pleines de caractère et percussions joueuses." styleid="14" lengthseconds="84" time="1:24" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_350A_British_Drama/WOM_350A_trk016_LIFE_ON_EARTH_(B)_Joseph_Rubel,_Michael_Price_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="16" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, UNDERSCORE, FILMS, ANIMATION, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, FAMILIAL, FILMS, COMÉDIE ROMANTIQUE, COMEDIE, COMEDIE ROMANTIQUE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, DRAME TV, HEUREUX, BONDISSANT, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, JOYEUX, HEUREUX, FUN, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, ENJOUÉ, ENJOUE, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, TENDRE, INNOCENT, TENDRE, LÉGER, LEGER, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, PIZZICATO, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, BONDISSANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, DÉFILÉ, DEFILE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, BOIS, SECTION DE BOIS, BATTERIE, CAISSE CLAIRE, BATTERIE, TIMBALES, CORDES, CORDES PIZZICATO, CORDES, VIOLON, BOIS, BASSON, DRAME, BRITANNIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL Cordes en pizzicato pleines de caractère et percussions joueuses. wom 350a tk016 joseph rubel michael price life on earth (b) wom 350a british drama west one music drama film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral documentary underscore movies animation movies children storytelling movies family movies romantic comedy tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden tv radio reality tv tv radio tv drama happy bouncy happy characterful pizzicato strings with playful percussion. dramedy. underscore" waveformpath="" version="Underscore" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="8111" name="The Puzzle (a)" code="TSH 050 tk020" libraryid="5" albumid="176" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_050_A_Curious_Mind/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Andrew Clark" comment="Échange curieux et interrogatif." styleid="10" lengthseconds="105" time="1:45" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_050_A_Curious_Mind/TSH050_trk020_THE_PUZZLE_(A)_Simon_Andrew_Clark_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="20" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ANIMATION, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, TV, RADIO, DESSINS ANIMÉS, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, HUMORISTIQUE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, DROLE, IRONIQUE, PIZZICATO, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, EXCENTRIQUE, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), CORDES, CORDES PIZZICATO, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), DECALE, IRREGULIER, DESSINS ANIMES, ELEMENTS Échange curieux et interrogatif. tsh 050 tk020 simon andrew clark the puzzle (a) tsh 050 a curious mind the scoring house documentary film score orchestral trailer main movies animation nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife tv radio cartoons funny comedic funny eccentric funny humorous funny quirky funny wry pizzicato movement irregular eccentric tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) curious questioning interplay. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="1584" name="Spores Take Flight (b)" code="NRF 011 tk016" libraryid="3" albumid="41" albumartpath="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_011_Majestic/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Christian Telford / Nigel William Graham / Kenneth E. Belcher" comment="Bed décalé de pizzicato gai. Des couches de percussions bizzarres arrivent peu à peu, créant un sentiment joueur et énergique. Dramedy." styleid="4" lengthseconds="120" time="2:00" samplefile="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_011_Majestic/NRF_011_trk016_SPORES_TAKE_FLIGHT_(B)_Christian_Telford_Nigel_William_Graham_Kenneth_E._Belcher_Noise_Refinery.mp3" track="16" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, UNDERSCORE, FILMS, ANIMATION, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, FAMILIAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, CHAUD, DÉSERT, DESERT, ELEMENTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, ELEMENTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, ELEMENTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ELEMENTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, ELEMENTS, ABSTRAIT, ANGULEUX, DÉCOUSU, DECOUSU, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, ESPIEGLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, DECALE, HEUREUX, FUN, HEUREUX, ENJOUÉ, ENJOUE, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, ENERGIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EVOLUTIF, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION, PINCÉ, PINCE, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, EXCENTRIQUE, IRREGULIER, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, SYNCOPÉ, IRREGULIER, SYNCOPE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, BONDISSANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, RÉPÉTITIF, REPETITIF, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, PERCUSSION Bed décalé de pizzicato gai. Des couches de percussions bizzarres arrivent peu à peu, créant un sentiment joueur et énergique. Dramedy. nrf 011 tk016 christian telford nigel william graham kenneth e. belcher spores take flight (b) nrf 011 majestic noise refinery film score orchestral film score orchestral documentary film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic film score orchestral pastoral underscore movies animation movies children storytelling movies family nature wildlife the elements land hot desert nature wildlife the elements quirky light-hearted pizzicato bed. layers of odd percussion gradually enter creating a sense of playful energy. dramedy. underscore" waveformpath="" version="Underscore" publisher="Noise Refinery" cae="00719510644"/>
    <item id="16914" name="Hit the Strip (b)" code="WOM 359 tk031" libraryid="6" albumid="356" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_359_Modern_Dramedy/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Thomas Greenberg (PRS)" comment="Positif et entrainant: sexy et sur de soi avec guitares et percussions légères. Pour dramedy." styleid="16" lengthseconds="78" time="1:18" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_359_Modern_Dramedy/WOM_359_trk031_HIT_THE_STRIP_(B)_Thomas_Greenberg_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="31" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, INDIE, HIP HOP, URBAIN, HIP HOP, UNDERSCORE, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, DOCUMENTAIRE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TƒLƒ RƒALITƒ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SITCOM, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SOAP OPERA, TELENOVELA, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, SEXY, COOL, SEXY, SEXY, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DƒTERMINƒ, DETERMINE, FORT, ƒNERGIQUE, ENERGIQUE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MACHO, ARROGANCE, BATTERIE, BOITE Ë RYTHMES, BATTERIE ƒLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ƒLECTRONIQUES, ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ELECTRONIQUES, CORDES, GUITARE, ƒLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE Positif et entrainant: sexy et sur de soi avec guitares et percussions légères. Pour dramedy. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 359 tk031 thomas greenberg (prs) hit the strip (b) wom 359 modern dramedy west one music quirky rock indie hip hop urban hip hop underscore activities settings city urban human environment activities settings showbiz documentary tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio reality tv tv radio sitcom tv radio soap opera telenovela happy upbeat sexy cool positive &amp; upbeat: sexy and confident with guitars and light percussion. dramedy. underscore" waveformpath="" version="Underscore" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="428434750"/>
    <item id="29118" name="Strange Goings On" code="WOMG 021 tk012" libraryid="7" albumid="625" albumartpath="Music/West One Music Group/WOMG_021_This_Is_Oddball_Orchestral/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Philip Hochstrate / Bill Connor" comment="Bois mystérieux, cordes pizzicato tendues." styleid="16" lengthseconds="146" time="2:26" samplefile="Music/West One Music Group/WOMG_021_This_Is_Oddball_Orchestral/WOMG_021_trk012_STRANGE_GOINGS_ON_Philip_Hochstrate_Bill_Connor_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, SEXY, GRIVOIS, PIZZICATO, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, COMÉDIE, FILMS, COMÉDIE ROMANTIQUE, TV, RADIO, SITCOM, CORDES, CORDES PIZZICATO, BOIS, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), ESPIEGLE, DECALE, COMEDIE, COMEDIE ROMANTIQUE Bois mystérieux, cordes pizzicato tendues. womg 021 tk012 philip hochstrate bill connor strange goings on womg 021 this is oddball orchestral west one music group quirky film score orchestral trailer main tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) disturbing mysterious disturbing tense funny comedic funny mischievous funny quirky happy playful sexy saucy pizzicato movies children storytelling movies comedy movies romantic comedy tv radio mysterious woodwinds tense pizzicato strings. dramedy. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="0428434750"/>
    <item id="16906" name="Trouble in Paradise (b)" code="WOM 359 tk023" libraryid="6" albumid="356" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_359_Modern_Dramedy/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Thomas Greenberg (PRS)" comment="Excentrique et malicieux: guitares décalées avec percussions bizzarres et piano. Pour dramedy." styleid="16" lengthseconds="106" time="1:46" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_359_Modern_Dramedy/WOM_359_trk023_TROUBLE_IN_PARADISE_(B)_Thomas_Greenberg_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="23" tracktotal="" search="HIP HOP, URBAIN, UNDERSCORE, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, DOCUMENTAIRE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TƒLƒ RƒALITƒ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SITCOM, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SOAP OPERA, TELENOVELA, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, ESPIéGLE, ESPIEGLE, DROLE, DƒCALƒ, DECALE, HEUREUX, ENJOUƒ, ENJOUE, HEUREUX, GUILLERET, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, SEXY, COOL, SEXY, CHARMEUR, SEXY, SEXY, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, FORT, COOL, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, PIZZICATO, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, BATTERIE, BOITE Ë RYTHMES, BATTERIE ƒLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, CLAVIER, PIANO, AUTRE, INHABITUEL, PERCUSSION CORPORELLE, CORDES, GUITARE, ƒLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE Excentrique et malicieux: guitares décalées avec percussions bizzarres et piano. Pour dramedy. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 359 tk023 thomas greenberg (prs) trouble in paradise (b) wom 359 modern dramedy west one music quirky hip hop urban underscore activities settings city urban human environment activities settings showbiz documentary tv radio reality tv tv radio sitcom tv radio soap opera telenovela funny comedic funny eccentric funny mischievous funny quirky happy lighthearted happy mischievous &amp; oddball: off-the-wall guitars meet quirky percussion and piano. dramedy. underscore" waveformpath="" version="Underscore" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="428434750"/>
    <item id="26884" name="Snooping Around (a)" code="WOM 317 tk008" libraryid="6" albumid="577" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_317_Weird_and_Wonderful/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Bill Connor" comment="Le monde secret de l'étrange et du merveilleux." styleid="16" lengthseconds="149" time="2:29" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_317_Weird_and_Wonderful/WOM_317_trk008_SNOOPING_AROUND_(A)_Bill_Connor_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="8" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, ENFANTS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, ANIMATION, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, COMÉDIE, FILMS, FAMILIAL, TROUBLANT, AGITÉ, TROUBLANT, BIZARRE, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, HUMORISTIQUE, DROLE, MÉLODRAMATIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, PIZZICATO, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, EXCENTRIQUE, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, INSECTE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, CORDES, CORDES PIZZICATO, AGITE, MELODRAMATIQUE, ESPIEGLE, DECALE, IRREGULIER, COMEDIE, ELEGANT Le monde secret de l'étrange et du merveilleux. wom 317 tk008 bill connor snooping around (a) wom 317 weird and wonderful west one music quirky children storytelling children film score orchestral trailer main documentary movies animation movies children storytelling movies comedy movies family disturbing restless disturbing weird funny comedic funny eccentric funny humorous funny melodramatic funny mischievous the secret world of the weird and wonderful. dramedy. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="8283" name="The Slippery Path (a)" code="TSH 061 tk017" libraryid="5" albumid="178" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_061_Life_Little_Whimsies/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Alexander Rudd / Zach Lemmon Lemmon" comment="Grande hésitation." styleid="16" lengthseconds="130" time="2:10" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_061_Life_Little_Whimsies/TSH061_trk017_THE_SLIPPERY_PATH_(A)_Alexander_Rudd_Zach_Lemmon_Lemmon_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="17" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, BOIS, SECTION DE BOIS, PRINCIPAL, ENFANTS, CONTES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, DROLE, IRONIQUE, HEUREUX, ENJOUÉ, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, EXCENTRIQUE, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, SYNCOPÉ, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, PINCÉ, PIZZICATO, FILMS, COMÉDIE, PARODIE, SATIRE, FILMS, COMÉDIE, DISCRÉTION, BASSESSE, FILMS, COMÉDIE ROMANTIQUE, TV, RADIO, SITCOM, CLAVIER, PIANO, FORMATIONS GENERALES, PINCE, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, ESPIEGLE, DECALE, ENJOUE, IRREGULIER, COMEDIE, COMEDIE ROMANTIQUE, SYNCOPE, DISCRETION Grande hésitation. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 061 tk017 alexander rudd zach lemmon lemmon the slippery path (a) tsh 061 life's little whimsies the scoring house quirky film score orchestral documentary general lineups electronic and acoustic strings string section woodwind woodwind section main children storytelling film score orchestral trailer funny mischievous funny quirky funny wry happy lighthearted happy playful movement irregular uncertain hesitancy. dramedy. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="26791" name="The Sunshine State (a)" code="WOM 248 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="575" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_248_Dramedy/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Philip Hochstrate / Bill Connor" comment="Un morceau au parfum latino, enjoué et fun." styleid="14" lengthseconds="158" time="2:38" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_248_Dramedy/WOM248_trk001_THE_SUNSHINE_STATE_(A)_Philip_Hochstrate_Bill_Connor_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, COMÉDIE, FILMS, COMÉDIE ROMANTIQUE, TV, RADIO, SITCOM, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, DROLE, IRONIQUE, HEUREUX, FUN, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, SEXY, GRIVOIS, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), AMÉRIQUE LATINE, AMÉRIQUE DU SUD, AMERIQUE LATINE, AMERIQUE DU SUD, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ESPIEGLE, DECALE, COMEDIE, COMEDIE ROMANTIQUE, JOURNEE Un morceau au parfum latino, enjoué et fun. wom 248 tk001 philip hochstrate bill connor the sunshine state (a) wom 248 dramedy west one music drama film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral trailer main movies comedy movies romantic comedy tv radio sitcom tv radio talkshow entertainment daytime funny comedic funny mischievous funny quirky funny wry happy fun happy playful happy upbeat sexy saucy latin flavoured upbeat and fun. dramedy. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="16909" name="A Little Mischief (b)" code="WOM 359 tk026" libraryid="6" albumid="356" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_359_Modern_Dramedy/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Thomas Greenberg (PRS)" comment="Excentrique et malicieux: espiègle et loufoque, avec guitares, xylophone et percussions décalées. Pour dramedy." styleid="16" lengthseconds="96" time="1:36" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_359_Modern_Dramedy/WOM_359_trk026_A_LITTLE_MISCHIEF_(B)_Thomas_Greenberg_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="26" tracktotal="" search="HIP HOP, URBAIN, UNDERSCORE, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, DOCUMENTAIRE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TƒLƒ RƒALITƒ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SITCOM, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SOAP OPERA, TELENOVELA, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, INSENSƒ, INSENSE, DROLE, ESPIéGLE, ESPIEGLE, DROLE, DƒCALƒ, DECALE, DROLE, IDIOT, DROLE, FANTASQUE, HEUREUX, ENJOUƒ, ENJOUE, HEUREUX, GUILLERET, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, SEXY, CHARMEUR, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, PIZZICATO, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, BATTERIE, BOITE Ë RYTHMES, BATTERIE ƒLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, CLAVIER, PIANO, PERCUSSION, XYLOPHONE, GLOCKENSPIEL, CORDES, GUITARE, ƒLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE Excentrique et malicieux: espiègle et loufoque, avec guitares, xylophone et percussions décalées. Pour dramedy. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 359 tk026 thomas greenberg (prs) a little mischief (b) wom 359 modern dramedy west one music quirky hip hop urban underscore activities settings city urban human environment activities settings showbiz documentary tv radio reality tv tv radio sitcom tv radio soap opera telenovela funny comedic funny eccentric funny madcap funny mischievous funny quirky funny silly mischievous &amp; oddball: playful and kooky with guitars xylophone and quirky percussion. dramedy. underscore" waveformpath="" version="Underscore" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="428434750"/>
    <item id="29135" name="Secret Liaisons" code="WOMG 021 tk029" libraryid="7" albumid="625" albumartpath="Music/West One Music Group/WOMG_021_This_Is_Oddball_Orchestral/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Philip Hochstrate / Bill Connor" comment="Le mystère s'épaissit. Activités undercover et plans secrets. Avec marimba, cordes pizzicato, bois et percussions." styleid="16" lengthseconds="128" time="2:08" samplefile="Music/West One Music Group/WOMG_021_This_Is_Oddball_Orchestral/WOMG_021_trk029_SECRET_LIAISONS_Philip_Hochstrate_Bill_Connor_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="29" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, UNDERSCORE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ENFANTS, CONTES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, HUMORISTIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, SEXY, GRIVOIS, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, COMÉDIE, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, FILMS, COMÉDIE ROMANTIQUE, TV, RADIO, SITCOM, ETHNIQUE, PERCUSSION, MARIMBA, CORDES, CORDES PIZZICATO, BOIS, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ESPIEGLE, DECALE, COMEDIE, COMEDIE ROMANTIQUE Le mystère s'épaissit. Activités undercover et plans secrets. Avec marimba, cordes pizzicato, bois et percussions. womg 021 tk029 philip hochstrate bill connor secret liaisons womg 021 this is oddball orchestral west one music group quirky children storytelling underscore tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) children storytelling film score orchestral trailer funny comedic funny eccentric funny humorous funny mischievous funny quirky happy playful sexy saucy movement rhythmic stealthy movies children the plot thickens... undercover dealings covert plans. featuring marimba pizzicato strings woodwind and percussion. dramedy. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="0428434750"/>
    <item id="8275" name="One Slip at a Time (a)" code="TSH 061 tk009" libraryid="5" albumid="178" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_061_Life_Little_Whimsies/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Alexander Rudd / Zach Lemmon Lemmon" comment="Prudente maladresse." styleid="16" lengthseconds="90" time="1:30" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_061_Life_Little_Whimsies/TSH061_trk009_ONE_SLIP_AT_A_TIME_(A)_Alexander_Rudd_Zach_Lemmon_Lemmon_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, BOIS, SECTION DE BOIS, PRINCIPAL, ENFANTS, CONTES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, DROLE, IRONIQUE, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, EXCENTRIQUE, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, INSECTE, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, SYNCOPÉ, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, FILMS, COMÉDIE, PARODIE, SATIRE, FILMS, COMÉDIE, DISCRÉTION, BASSESSE, FILMS, COMÉDIE ROMANTIQUE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, CLAVIER, PIANO, FORMATIONS GENERALES, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, ESPIEGLE, DECALE, IRREGULIER, COMEDIE, COMEDIE ROMANTIQUE, SYNCOPE, DISCRETION, ELEMENTS Prudente maladresse. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 061 tk009 alexander rudd zach lemmon lemmon one slip at a time (a) tsh 061 life's little whimsies the scoring house quirky film score orchestral trailer general lineups electronic and acoustic strings string section woodwind woodwind section main children storytelling film score orchestral documentary funny mischievous funny quirky funny wry movement irregular eccentric movement irregular cautious incompetence. dramedy. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="26879" name="Oddball Tango (a)" code="WOM 317 tk003" libraryid="6" albumid="577" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_317_Weird_and_Wonderful/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Bill Connor" comment="Le tango de l'étrange: de merveilleuses cordes pizzicato, un piano et un lead de marimba." styleid="16" lengthseconds="148" time="2:28" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_317_Weird_and_Wonderful/WOM_317_trk003_ODDBALL_TANGO_(A)_Bill_Connor_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, ENFANTS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, KITSCH, RETRO, CHEESY, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, COMÉDIE, FILMS, FAMILIAL, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TROUBLANT, ÉTRANGE , DROLE, MANIÉRÉ, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, HUMORISTIQUE, DROLE, MÉLODRAMATIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, HEUREUX, ENJOUÉ, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, PIZZICATO, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, EXCENTRIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, PERCUSSION, MARIMBA, CORDES, CORDES PIZZICATO, ETRANGE, MANIERE, MELODRAMATIQUE, ESPIEGLE, DECALE, ENJOUE, IRREGULIER, COMEDIE, ELEGANT Le tango de l'étrange: de merveilleuses cordes pizzicato, un piano et un lead de marimba. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 317 tk003 bill connor oddball tango (a) wom 317 weird and wonderful west one music quirky children storytelling children film score orchestral trailer kitsch retro cheesy main documentary movies children storytelling movies comedy movies family tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden disturbing strange funny campy funny comedic funny eccentric tango of the strange. wonderful pizzicato strings and piano backing with marimba lead. dramedy. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="26800" name="No Time to Waste (a)" code="WOM 248 tk010" libraryid="6" albumid="575" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_248_Dramedy/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Philip Hochstrate / Bill Connor" comment="De l'action qui évolue rapidement. Des percussions légères et agitées avec des cordes pizzicati entraînantes et des bois séduisants." styleid="14" lengthseconds="153" time="2:33" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_248_Dramedy/WOM248_trk010_NO_TIME_TO_WASTE_(A)_Philip_Hochstrate_Bill_Connor_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="10" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ANIMATION, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, COMÉDIE, FILMS, COMÉDIE ROMANTIQUE, TV, RADIO, SITCOM, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, SEXY, GRIVOIS, TENDRE, LÉGER, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, OCCUPÉ, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CORDES, CORDES PIZZICATO, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ESPIEGLE, DECALE, LEGER, COMEDIE, COMEDIE ROMANTIQUE, OCCUPE De l'action qui évolue rapidement. Des percussions légères et agitées avec des cordes pizzicati entraînantes et des bois séduisants. wom 248 tk010 philip hochstrate bill connor no time to waste (a) wom 248 dramedy west one music drama film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral trailer main movies animation movies children storytelling movies comedy movies romantic comedy tv radio sitcom funny comedic funny mischievous funny quirky happy playful sexy saucy tender light movement rhythmic fast moving action. busy light percussion with driving pizzicato strings and enticing woodwinds. dramedy. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="26878" name="Wotsedoin (a)" code="WOM 317 tk002" libraryid="6" albumid="577" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_317_Weird_and_Wonderful/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Bill Connor" comment="Pizzicati de cordes doux, curieux avec mélodies de marimba, xylophone et basson." styleid="16" lengthseconds="119" time="1:59" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_317_Weird_and_Wonderful/WOM_317_trk002_WOTSEDOIN_(A)_Bill_Connor_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, ENFANTS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, ANIMATION, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, FAMILIAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, HUMORISTIQUE, DROLE, INSENSÉ, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, DROLE, IDIOT, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, ENJOUÉ, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, PIZZICATO, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, EXCENTRIQUE, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, INSECTE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, POURSUITE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, PERCUSSION, MARIMBA, PERCUSSION, XYLOPHONE, GLOCKENSPIEL, CORDES, CORDES PIZZICATO, BOIS, BASSON, INSENSE, DECALE, ENJOUE, IRREGULIER, ELEGANT, ELEMENTS Pizzicati de cordes doux, curieux avec mélodies de marimba, xylophone et basson. wom 317 tk002 bill connor wotsedoin (a) wom 317 weird and wonderful west one music quirky children storytelling children film score orchestral trailer main documentary movies animation movies children storytelling movies family nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife funny comedic funny eccentric funny humorous funny madcap funny quirky funny gentle curious pizzicato strings with marimba xylophone and bassoon melodies. dramedy. main delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="27009" name="Young and Sprightly (b)" code="WOM 350A tk018" libraryid="6" albumid="579" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_350A_British_Drama/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Michael Price, Nicholas Hill" comment="Pizzicato de cordes et piano joyeux." styleid="14" lengthseconds="109" time="1:49" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_350A_British_Drama/WOM_350A_trk018_YOUNG_AND_SPRIGHTLY_(B)_Michael_Price,_Nicholas_Hill_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="18" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, UNDERSCORE, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, FAMILIAL, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, PERIODE, PERIODES, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, ELEMENTS, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, DRAME TV, HEUREUX, JOYEUX, SÉRIEUX, ÉMOUVANT, SERIEUX, EMOUVANT, SÉRIEUX, ATTENTIONNÉ, SERIEUX, ATTENTIONNE, TENDRE, GRACIEUX, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, BEAU, MAGIQUE, PIZZICATO, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT, ELEGANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, CORDES PIZZICATO, CORDES, VIOLON, DRAME, BRITANNIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL Pizzicato de cordes et piano joyeux. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 350a tk018 michael price nicholas hill young and sprightly (b) wom 350a british drama west one music drama film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral pastoral underscore movies children storytelling movies family movies human drama movies period historical costume drama movies romance nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral tv radio reality tv cheerful piano and pizzicato strings. underscore" waveformpath="" version="Underscore" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="16916" name="Optimistic Adventures (b)" code="WOM 359 tk033" libraryid="6" albumid="356" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_359_Modern_Dramedy/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Thomas Greenberg (PRS)" comment="Positif et entrainant: de grands espoirs. Un celesta délicat est rejoint par des percussions, une guitare et un piano nostalgique. Pour dramedy." styleid="16" lengthseconds="122" time="2:02" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_359_Modern_Dramedy/WOM_359_trk033_OPTIMISTIC_ADVENTURES_(B)_Thomas_Greenberg_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="33" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, INDIE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RƒVƒLER, LANCEMENT, REVELER, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FORMATION, INFORMATION, POP, POP, UNDERSCORE, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, DOCUMENTAIRE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, SANTƒ, BIEN-æTRE, BIEN-ETRE, SANTE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TƒLƒ RƒALITƒ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SITCOM, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SOAP OPERA, TELENOVELA, DROLE, DƒCALƒ, DECALE, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, FESTIF, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, ENJOUƒ, ENJOUE, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, SEXY, COOL, SEXY, SEXY, FORT, AVENTUREUX, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, INNOCENT, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, BATTERIE, BOITE Ë RYTHMES, BATTERIE ƒLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ƒLECTRONIQUES, ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ELECTRONIQUES, CLAVIER, CELESTE, CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, GUITARE, ƒLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE Positif et entrainant: de grands espoirs. Un celesta délicat est rejoint par des percussions, une guitare et un piano nostalgique. Pour dramedy. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 359 tk033 thomas greenberg (prs) optimistic adventures (b) wom 359 modern dramedy west one music quirky rock indie business corporate bright optimistic business corporate luxury business corporate motivational business corporate reveal launch business corporate science technology business corporate training information pop underscore activities settings city urban positive &amp; upbeat: high hopes. ethereal celeste joins with percussion guitar and nostalgic piano. dramedy. underscore" waveformpath="" version="Underscore" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="428434750"/>
    <item id="26792" name="On Tip Toes (a)" code="WOM 248 tk002" libraryid="6" albumid="575" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_248_Dramedy/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Philip Hochstrate / Bill Connor" comment="Léger, délicat et espiègle." styleid="14" lengthseconds="134" time="2:14" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_248_Dramedy/WOM248_trk002_ON_TIP_TOES_(A)_Philip_Hochstrate_Bill_Connor_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, COMÉDIE, FILMS, COMÉDIE ROMANTIQUE, TV, RADIO, SITCOM, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, HUMORISTIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, SEXY, GRIVOIS, TENDRE, DÉLICAT, TENDRE, LÉGER, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ESPIEGLE, DECALE, DELICAT, LEGER, COMEDIE, COMEDIE ROMANTIQUE Léger, délicat et espiègle. wom 248 tk002 philip hochstrate bill connor on tip toes (a) wom 248 dramedy west one music drama film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral trailer main movies comedy movies romantic comedy tv radio sitcom funny comedic funny eccentric funny humorous funny mischievous funny quirky happy playful sexy saucy tender delicate tender light movement rhythmic light delicate and playful. dramedy. main delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="29128" name="Beneath the Surface" code="WOMG 021 tk022" libraryid="7" albumid="625" albumartpath="Music/West One Music Group/WOMG_021_This_Is_Oddball_Orchestral/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Bill Connor" comment="Musique simple et répétitive, pleine d'intrigue et de curiosité. Avec celeste et cordes pizzicato." styleid="16" lengthseconds="126" time="2:06" samplefile="Music/West One Music Group/WOMG_021_This_Is_Oddball_Orchestral/WOMG_021_trk022_BENEATH_THE_SURFACE_Bill_Connor_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="22" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, ENFANTS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, ANIMATION, FILMS, COMÉDIE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, COMÉDIE ROMANTIQUE, ABSTRAIT, SIMPLE, TROUBLANT, CRAINTIF, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, HUMORISTIQUE, DROLE, MÉLODRAMATIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, PIZZICATO, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, EXCENTRIQUE, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, INSECTE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, CORDES, CORDES PIZZICATO, MELODRAMATIQUE, ESPIEGLE, DECALE, IRREGULIER, COMEDIE, COMEDIE ROMANTIQUE, ELEGANT Musique simple et répétitive, pleine d'intrigue et de curiosité. Avec celeste et cordes pizzicato. womg 021 tk022 bill connor beneath the surface womg 021 this is oddball orchestral west one music group quirky children storytelling children film score orchestral trailer main documentary movies animation movies comedy movies human drama movies romantic comedy abstract simple disturbing fearful funny comedic funny eccentric funny humorous funny melodramatic funny mischievous a simple repeating soundtrack full of intrigue and curiosity. featuring celeste and pizzicato strings. dramedy. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="0428434750"/>
    <item id="26795" name="Feeling Curious (a)" code="WOM 248 tk005" libraryid="6" albumid="575" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_248_Dramedy/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Philip Hochstrate / Bill Connor" comment="Des cordes pizzicati espiègles et des mélodies de bois excentriques." styleid="14" lengthseconds="139" time="2:19" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_248_Dramedy/WOM248_trk005_FEELING_CURIOUS_(A)_Philip_Hochstrate_Bill_Connor_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ANIMATION, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, COMÉDIE, FILMS, COMÉDIE ROMANTIQUE, TV, RADIO, SITCOM, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CORDES, CORDES PIZZICATO, ESPIEGLE, COMEDIE, COMEDIE ROMANTIQUE Des cordes pizzicati espiègles et des mélodies de bois excentriques. wom 248 tk005 philip hochstrate bill connor feeling curious (a) wom 248 dramedy west one music drama children storytelling film score orchestral trailer main movies animation movies children storytelling movies comedy movies romantic comedy tv radio sitcom funny comedic funny mischievous happy playful movement rhythmic stealthy tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) strings playful pizzicato strings and kooky woodwind melodies. dramedy. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="16905" name="Life in the Hills (b)" code="WOM 359 tk022" libraryid="6" albumid="356" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_359_Modern_Dramedy/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Thomas Greenberg (PRS)" comment="Excentrique et malicieux: sur de soi et provocateur, avec carillons et guitares en picking. Pour dramedy." styleid="16" lengthseconds="84" time="1:24" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_359_Modern_Dramedy/WOM_359_trk022_LIFE_IN_THE_HILLS_(B)_Thomas_Greenberg_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="22" tracktotal="" search="HIP HOP, URBAIN, HIP HOP, URBAIN, HIP HOP, UNDERSCORE, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, DOCUMENTAIRE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TƒLƒ RƒALITƒ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SITCOM, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SOAP OPERA, TELENOVELA, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, ESPIéGLE, ESPIEGLE, SEXY, COOL, SEXY, CHARMEUR, SEXY, SƒDUISANT, SEDUISANT, SEXY, SEXY, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, FORT, COOL, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MACHO, ARROGANCE, PIZZICATO, CLOCHES, CARILLONS, CLOCHES D'ƒGLISE, CARILLONS, CLOCHES D'EGLISE, BATTERIE, BOITE Ë RYTHMES, BATTERIE ƒLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, CLAVIER, PIANO, PERCUSSION, MARIMBA, CORDES, GUITARE, ƒLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE, CORDES, CORDES PIZZICATO Excentrique et malicieux: sur de soi et provocateur, avec carillons et guitares en picking. Pour dramedy. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 359 tk022 thomas greenberg (prs) life in the hills (b) wom 359 modern dramedy west one music quirky hip hop urban hip hop urban hip hop underscore activities settings city urban human environment activities settings showbiz documentary tv radio reality tv tv radio sitcom tv radio soap opera telenovela funny comedic funny eccentric funny mischievous sexy cool sexy mischievous &amp; oddball: confident and provocative with tubular bells and picked guitars. dramedy. underscore" waveformpath="" version="Underscore" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="428434750"/>
    <item id="29127" name="Lovers' Tryst" code="WOMG 021 tk021" libraryid="7" albumid="625" albumartpath="Music/West One Music Group/WOMG_021_This_Is_Oddball_Orchestral/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Philip Hochstrate / Bill Connor" comment="Tango cool et décalé avec bois, piano, cordes et caisse claire." styleid="16" lengthseconds="159" time="2:39" samplefile="Music/West One Music Group/WOMG_021_This_Is_Oddball_Orchestral/WOMG_021_trk021_LOVERS'_TRYST_Philip_Hochstrate_Bill_Connor_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="21" tracktotal="" search="STYLES DE DANSE TRADITIONNEL, AMÉRIQUE LATINE, AMÉRIQUE DU SUD, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, LATIN, STYLES DE DANSE LATINE, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, HUMORISTIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, SEXY, GRIVOIS, DANSE DE SALON, TANGO, FILMS, COMÉDIE, FILMS, COMÉDIE ROMANTIQUE, TV, RADIO, SITCOM, CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, BOIS, AMERIQUE LATINE, AMERIQUE DU SUD, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), ESPIEGLE, DECALE, COMEDIE, COMEDIE ROMANTIQUE Tango cool et décalé avec bois, piano, cordes et caisse claire. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live womg 021 tk021 philip hochstrate bill connor lovers' tryst womg 021 this is oddball orchestral west one music group quirky traditional dance styles latin america south america main tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) film score orchestral trailer latin latin dance styles funny comedic funny eccentric funny humorous funny mischievous funny quirky happy playful sexy saucy ballroom dance tango a cool quirky tango featuring woodwind piano strings and snare. dramedy. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="0428434750"/>
  </items>
</librarycollection>
