<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<librarycollection>
  <items>
    <item id="6870" name="For Better Forever" code="TSH 073 tk008" libraryid="5" albumid="157" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_073_Travelogue_Diaries/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Robert Henry Peter White, Alexander Stephen Gray" comment="Optimiste, tourné vers l'avenir." styleid="10" lengthseconds="102" time="1:42" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_073_Travelogue_Diaries/TSH_073_trk008_FOR_BETTER_FOREVER_Robert_Henry_Peter_White,_Alexander_Stephen_Gray_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="8" tracktotal="" search="DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS INDÉPENDANTS, ROAD MOVIEBUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FORMATION, INFORMATION, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, ROAD TRIP, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FILMS, FILMS INDÉPENDANTS, FILMS, ROAD MOVIE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, NEUTRE, FORT, CONFIANT, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INSISTANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, RÉPÉTITIF, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, MENÉ PAR L'ARTISTE, FORMATIONS GENERALES, MENE PAR L'ARTISTE, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, FILMS INDEPENDANTS, REPETITIF Optimiste, tourné vers l'avenir. tsh 073 tk008 robert henry peter white alexander stephen gray for better forever tsh 073 travelogue diaries the scoring house documentary film score orchestral documentary business corporate beds business corporate training information main activities settings road trip business corporate movies indie films movies road movie tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden happy feel good neutral optimistic forward-looking. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="8046" name="Time to Build" code="TSH 039 tk020" libraryid="5" albumid="175" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_039_Life_in_Colour/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Alexander Paul Rudd / Zach Lemmon Lemmon" comment="Un fond sonore léger et résolu." styleid="20" lengthseconds="212" time="3:32" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_039_Life_in_Colour/TSH039_trk020_TIME_TO_BUILD_Alexander_Paul_Rudd_Zach_Lemmon_Lemmon_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="20" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FORMATION, INFORMATION, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, TENDRE, LÉGER, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, RÉPÉTITIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UN TRAIN, EVOLUTIF, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, NOUVELLES LÉGÈRES, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE,, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), LEGER, REPETITIF, ACTUALITES, REVELER, NOUVELLES LEGERES, JOURNEE, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Un fond sonore léger et résolu. tsh 039 tk020 alexander paul rudd zach lemmon lemmon time to build tsh 039 life in colour the scoring house children children main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) business corporate beds business corporate bright optimistic business corporate reveal launch business corporate training information happy feel good tender light movement rhythmic driving movement rhythmic repetitive movement light purposeful bed. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="25188" name="Live Free (a)" code="WOM 336A tk017" libraryid="6" albumid="541" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_336A_Supercharger_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Dean Saban" comment="Indie chantonnante qui donne la peche." styleid="34" lengthseconds="127" time="2:07" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_336A_Supercharger_2/WOM_336A_trk017_LIVE_FREE_(A)_Dean_Saban_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="17" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, GROUPE DE ROCK, PRINCIPAL, ROCK, INDIE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, BONDISSANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, ROAD TRIP, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TELE REALITE Indie chantonnante qui donne la peche. wom 336a tk017 dean saban live free (a) wom 336a supercharger 2 west one music indie rock rock band main rock indie happy feel good happy upbeat uplifting inspirational uplifting motivational uplifting positive uplifting uplifting movement rhythmic bouncy movement rhythmic driving activities settings road trip tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure lilting feelgood indie. main knees up, mess piano, cockney, east london, singalong, pub joanna, piano bar, piano-bar, live" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="26493" name="Journey to the Light (b)" code="WOM 304 tk019" libraryid="6" albumid="568" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_304_Emotive_Minimalism/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Réconfortant et qui suscite l'inspiration. Évolue tout du long." styleid="4" lengthseconds="237" time="3:57" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_304_Emotive_Minimalism/WOM304_trk019_JOURNEY_TO_THE_LIGHT_(B)_Richard_Allen_Harvey_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="19" tracktotal="" search="CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE, CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, ALTERNATIF, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MER, PAYSAGE MARIN, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EVOLUTIF, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, ANGLETERRE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), AERIEN, ELEMENTS, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Réconfortant et qui suscite l'inspiration. Évolue tout du long. wom 304 tk019 richard allen harvey journey to the light (b) wom 304 emotive minimalism west one music film score orchestral classical classical styling classical classical styling film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic film score orchestral pastoral alternate documentary biographical historical the arts movies romance nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama inspirational and heartwarming gently building throughout. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="4253" name="Paths of Progress (a)" code="TSH 030 tk013" libraryid="5" albumid="119" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_030_Outlook_Sunny/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Peter Simon Beckmann" comment="Une progression à l'évolution régulière." styleid="11" lengthseconds="138" time="2:18" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_030_Outlook_Sunny/TSH030_trk013_PATHS_OF_PROGRESS_(A)_Peter_Simon_Beckmann_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="13" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, CLASSIQUE, STYLE MINIMALISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, COMMUNICATION, ACTUALITÉS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FORMATION, INFORMATION, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, AUTOMATISATION, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, HI TECH, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, PAISIBLE, TRANQUILLE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, RÉPÉTITIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), REPETITIF, ACCELERE, ACTUALITES, ELEMENTS Une progression à l'évolution régulière. tsh 030 tk013 peter simon beckmann paths of progress (a) tsh 030 outlook sunny the scoring house corporate business business corporate beds classical minimalist style business corporate communication news business corporate science technology business corporate training information film score orchestral trailer main nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife science technology evolving steady progression. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="25189" name="Keep on Going (a)" code="WOM 336A tk018" libraryid="6" albumid="541" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_336A_Supercharger_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jay Price" comment="Guitares punk anguleuses et synthés loufoques avec un chant sans paroles accrocheur." styleid="34" lengthseconds="101" time="1:41" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_336A_Supercharger_2/WOM_336A_trk018_KEEP_ON_GOING_(A)_Jay_Price_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="18" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, GROUPE DE ROCK, PRINCIPAL, POP, POP POUR ENFANTS, POP, ROCK, INDIE, HEUREUX, BONDISSANT, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, ROAD TRIP, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TV, RADIO, SPORT, VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, PHRASE VOCALE, CRI, APPEL, ENERGIQUE, TELE REALITE Guitares punk anguleuses et synthés loufoques avec un chant sans paroles accrocheur. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 336a tk018 jay price keep on going (a) wom 336a supercharger 2 west one music indie rock rock band main pop kiddie pop pop rock indie happy bouncy happy bright happy feel good happy happy happy upbeat strong energetic uplifting positive uplifting uplifting movement rhythmic driving activities settings road trip tv radio leisure lifestyle food angular punky guitars with kooky synths and catchy non-lyric vocals. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="15304" name="A World of Wonder (a)" code="WOM 124 tk010" libraryid="6" albumid="318" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_124_Life_in_Motion/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Paul Reeves (Gb 2)" comment="Un piano lumineux et un fond de cordes, progressant lentement." styleid="26" lengthseconds="145" time="2:25" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_124_Life_in_Motion/WOM124_trk010_A_WORLD_OF_WONDER_(A)_Paul_Reeves_(Gb_2)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="10" tracktotal="" search="CLASSIQUE, CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIÈCLE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, EVOLUTIF, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ACCOMPAGNEMENT AU PIANO, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, PERIODE, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIECLE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, 20E SIECLE, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Un piano lumineux et un fond de cordes, progressant lentement. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 124 tk010 paul reeves (gb 2) a world of wonder (a) wom 124 life in motion west one music nature wildlife classical classical 20th century classical style film score orchestral panoramic film score orchestral pastoral main movies human drama nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral nature wildlife luminous piano and strings backdrop gently building. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="26538" name="Colourful Future (a)" code="WOM 335 tk005" libraryid="6" albumid="569" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_335_Inspiring_Minimalism/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="jono Buchanan" comment="Thème au piano léger, percutant et positif avec pizzicati de cordes, guitare acoustique et claquements de mains." styleid="4" lengthseconds="112" time="1:52" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_335_Inspiring_Minimalism/WOM_335_trk005_COLOURFUL_FUTURE_(A)_jono_Buchanan_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, COMMUNICATION, ACTUALITÉS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, HEUREUX, BONDISSANT, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, JOYEUX, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, FUN, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, GUILLERET, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, BONDISSANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, SAUTER, ACOUSTIQUE, ENFANTIN, PIZZICATO, ÉTINCELANT, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, ENFANTS, MATERNELLE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, AMBIANCES ET FONDS SONORES POUR PROJETS, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, MATERNELLE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, CLAVIER, CELESTE, CLAVIER, PIANO, JOUET, INHABITUEL, PERCUSSION CORPORELLE, PERCUSSION, MARIMBA, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN NYLON, ETINCELANT, ACTUALITES Thème au piano léger, percutant et positif avec pizzicati de cordes, guitare acoustique et claquements de mains. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 335 tk005 jono buchanan colourful future (a) wom 335 inspiring minimalism west one music film score orchestral business corporate bright optimistic strings string section main business corporate beds business corporate communication news film score orchestral documentary happy bouncy happy bright happy cheerful happy feel good happy fun happy happy happy perky happy playful light percussive and positive piano-led theme with pizzicato strings acoustic guitar and handclaps. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="8036" name="Stretching Time (a)" code="TSH 039 tk010" libraryid="5" albumid="175" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_039_Life_in_Colour/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Alexander Paul Rudd / Zach Lemmon Lemmon" comment="Un fond sonore hypnotique et agité." styleid="20" lengthseconds="99" time="1:39" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_039_Life_in_Colour/TSH039_trk010_STRETCHING_TIME_(A)_Alexander_Paul_Rudd_Zach_Lemmon_Lemmon_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="10" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, COMMUNICATION, ACTUALITÉS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, PUISSANCE, ÉNERGIE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FORMATION, INFORMATION, FORT, PUISSANT, TROUBLANT, AGITÉ, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INDUSTRIE, MACHINES, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UN TRAIN, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, BEDS POUR ACTUALITÉS, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, AUTOMATISATION, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, HI TECH,, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), AGITE, ACCELERE, ACTUALITES, BEDS POUR ACTUALITES, ENERGIE Un fond sonore hypnotique et agité. tsh 039 tk010 alexander paul rudd zach lemmon lemmon stretching time (a) tsh 039 life in colour the scoring house children business corporate beds main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) business corporate communication news business corporate power energy business corporate science technology business corporate training information strong powerful disturbing restless movement rhythmic driving hypnotic restless bed. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="17573" name="The Right Path (a)" code="WOM 174 tk009" libraryid="6" albumid="370" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_174_Age_of_Innocence/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Thomas Greenberg" comment="Un thème positif et émouvant, avec des arpèges de piano hypnotiques, des cordes chaleureuses et une guitare acoustique douce." styleid="10" lengthseconds="148" time="2:28" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_174_Age_of_Innocence/WOM174_trk009_THE_RIGHT_PATH_(A)_Thomas_Greenberg_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, ENFANTS, CLASSIQUE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, COMMUNICATION, ACTUALITÉS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, NOËL, ENFANTS, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, FAMILIAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, NEIGE, GLACE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TENDRE, INNOCENT, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, ACOUSTIQUE, EVOLUTIF, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, CLAVIER, CELESTE, CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN NYLON, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN MÉTAL, CORDES, VIOLON, FORMATIONS GENERALES, NOEL, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ACTUALITES, ELEMENTS, CORDES EN METAL, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Un thème positif et émouvant, avec des arpèges de piano hypnotiques, des cordes chaleureuses et une guitare acoustique douce. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 174 tk009 thomas greenberg the right path (a) wom 174 age of innocence west one music documentary children storytelling children classical business corporate beds business corporate communication news film score orchestral trailer main business corporate christmas children movies children storytelling movies family nature wildlife the elements land snow ice happy a positive and emotive theme featuring mesmeric piano arpeggios warm strings and gentle acoustic guitar. main delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="18898" name="Leave it all Behind (a)" code="WOM 201 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="400" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_201_Travelling_On/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Thomas Richard Peter Howe / Nikolas Joseph Ammar" comment="Une introduction intime mène à des refrains expansifs et inspirants." styleid="18" lengthseconds="145" time="2:25" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_201_Travelling_On/WOM201_trk001_LEAVE_IT_ALL_BEHIND_(A)_Thomas_Richard_Peter_Howe_Nikolas_Joseph_Ammar_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, COUCHER DE SOLEIL, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, DÉTENDU, TENDRE, INNOCENT, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), AFRIQUE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETENDU, ELEMENTS, JOURNEE Une introduction intime mène à des refrains expansifs et inspirants. wom 201 tk001 thomas richard peter howe nikolas joseph ammar leave it all behind (a) wom 201 travelling on west one music world business corporate bright optimistic business corporate luxury business corporate motivational main business corporate nature wildlife the elements land sun tropical seaside nature wildlife the elements seasons time sunset tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio intimate introduction leads to expansive inspiring choruses. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="4605" name="New Light" code="TSH 035 tk001" libraryid="5" albumid="125" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_035_A_Winner_is_Born/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Mark Lasker" comment="Des textures délicates et frémissantes." styleid="22" lengthseconds="71" time="1:11" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_035_A_Winner_is_Born/TSH035_trk001_NEW_LIGHT_Mark_Lasker_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FORMATION, INFORMATION, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, SOLEIL, CHALEUR, SPORT, JEUX OLYMPIQUES, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, NOUVELLES LÉGÈRES, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, BEDS POUR ACTUALITÉS, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, TENDRE, DÉLICAT, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, RALENTI, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DELICAT, ACTUALITES, ELEMENTS, NOUVELLES LEGERES, BEDS POUR ACTUALITES, METEO, ETE Des textures délicates et frémissantes. tsh 035 tk001 mark lasker new light tsh 035 a winner is born the scoring house sport business corporate beds business corporate bright optimistic business corporate luxury business corporate motivational business corporate training information main documentary nature wildlife the elements weather sun heat sports olympics tv radio news and current affairs shimmering delicate textures. main delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="22447" name="The Afterlife" code="WOM 280 tk012" libraryid="6" albumid="482" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_280_Cinematic_Indie/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Timothy Stephen Pierce / Brett Carr Boyett" comment="Une introduction optimiste entame une progression épique à 2:18. Inspirant et cinématographique." styleid="34" lengthseconds="282" time="4:42" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_280_Cinematic_Indie/WOM280_trk012_THE_AFTERLIFE_Timothy_Stephen_Pierce_Brett_Carr_Boyett_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, ENFANTS, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), ROCK, ROCK ALTERNATIF, ROCK, INDIE, FORT, ÉPIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE,, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), EPIQUE Une introduction optimiste entame une progression épique à 2:18. Inspirant et cinématographique. wom 280 tk012 timothy stephen pierce brett carr boyett the afterlife wom 280 cinematic indie west one music indie children main tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) rock alternative rock rock indie strong epic uplifting optimistic movies epic tv radio children youth tv optimistic introduction starts epic build at 2:18. inspiring and cinematic. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="7384" name="Big Blue Sky (a)" code="TSH 059 tk004" libraryid="5" albumid="168" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_059_Orchestral_Fantasia/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Arthur Rhodes" comment="Panoramas chauds et dérivants." styleid="4" lengthseconds="266" time="4:26" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_059_Orchestral_Fantasia/TSH_059_trk004_BIG_BLUE_SKY_(A)_Simon_Arthur_Rhodes_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, PRINCIPAL, CLASSIQUE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN NYLON, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN MÉTAL,, PERIODE, 20E SIECLE, AERIEN, ELEGANT, ELEMENTS, CORDES EN METAL Panoramas chauds et dérivants. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 059 tk004 simon arthur rhodes big blue sky (a) tsh 059 orchestral fantasia the scoring house film score orchestral classical classical styling classical and semi classical symphony orchestra time period modern era 20th century main classical business corporate luxury film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic tender intimate tender nostalgic tender romantic tender warm warm drifting panoramas. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="23052" name="Shape the Future (a)" code="WOM 293 tk002" libraryid="6" albumid="498" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_293_The_Acoustic_Boutique/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Dan Cassady" comment="Inspirant et édifiant. Construction du petit commencement jusqu'à l'énorme climax." styleid="13" lengthseconds="175" time="2:55" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_293_The_Acoustic_Boutique/WOM_293_trk002_SHAPE_THE_FUTURE_(A)_Dan_Cassady_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, PRESTIGE , BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FORMATION, INFORMATION, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SPORT, EXERCICE, FITNESS, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EVOLUTIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UN TRAIN, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), REVELER, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Inspirant et édifiant. Construction du petit commencement jusqu'à l'énorme climax. wom 293 tk002 dan cassady shape the future (a) wom 293 the acoustic boutique west one music acoustic business corporate reveal launch business corporate motivational business corporate prestige business corporate training information main business corporate sports exercise fitness tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio sports strong prestigious uplifting inspiring and uplifting. building from small beginnings to a rousing climax. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="6479" name="Reach for the Skies" code="TSH 067 tk031" libraryid="5" albumid="151" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_067_Inspiring_Innovation/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Everard Lawrence Wells / Robert John Foster" comment="Imagerie ambitieuse et évolutive." styleid="11" lengthseconds="181" time="3:01" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_067_Inspiring_Innovation/TSH067_trk031_REACH_FOR_THE_SKIES_Richard_Everard_Lawrence_Wells_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="31" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, PRESTIGE , FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, PRINCIPAL, CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIÈCLE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, FORT, PUISSANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, JAILLIR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MÉLODIQUE, LYRIQUE, SOPHISTIQUÉ, CLASSE, ÉTINCELANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, CLAVIER, PIANO, FORMATIONS GENERALES, SERIEUX, MELODIQUE, SOPHISTIQUE, ETINCELANT, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIECLE, 20E SIECLE, AERIEN, ELEGANT Imagerie ambitieuse et évolutive. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 067 tk031 richard everard lawrence wells robert john foster reach for the skies tsh 067 inspiring innovation the scoring house corporate business business corporate prestige general lineups acoustic strings string section main classical 20th century classical style business corporate luxury serious serious strong powerful uplifting inspirational uplifting soaring uplifting uplifting movement smooth aerial flying aspirational evolving imagery. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="23736" name="Dawn of a Dream (b)" code="WOM 309 tk015" libraryid="6" albumid="514" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_309_Indie_Organica/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="John-Paul Jones" comment="Introduction simple et chaleureuse vers un final édifiant et inspirant à 1:28." styleid="34" lengthseconds="152" time="2:32" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_309_Indie_Organica/WOM_309_trk015_DAWN_OF_A_DREAM_(B)_John-Paul_Jones_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="15" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, POP CORPORATE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, ROCK, INDIE, WORLD BEAT, STYLES ETHNIQUES, GLOBAL, ALTERNATIF, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, SPORT, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, ABSTRAIT, SIMPLE, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), ELEMENTS Introduction simple et chaleureuse vers un final édifiant et inspirant à 1:28. wom 309 tk015 john-paul jones dawn of a dream (b) wom 309 indie organica west one music indie business corporate beds business corporate corporate pop business corporate motivational rock indie world beat ethnic stylings global alternate business corporate nature wildlife the elements land sun tropical seaside sports tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio simple and heartwarming introduction leads to an uplifting and inspiring outro at 1:28. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="26535" name="Life’s Wonder (a)" code="WOM 335 tk002" libraryid="6" albumid="569" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_335_Inspiring_Minimalism/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Steven Gutheinz" comment="Morceau émouvant et au bon coeur pour piano solo. Avec accompagnement de cordes expressives." styleid="4" lengthseconds="173" time="2:53" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_335_Inspiring_Minimalism/WOM_335_trk002_LIFES_WONDER_(A)_Steven_Gutheinz_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, PRINCIPAL, CLASSIQUE, STYLE MINIMALISTE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, SÉRIEUX, ÉMOUVANT, SÉRIEUX, ATTENTIONNÉ, TENDRE, INNOCENT, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TENDRE, TENDRE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, BEAU, EVOLUTIF, DIVIN, MÉLODIQUE, LYRIQUE, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, HIVER, CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, VIOLONCELLE, SERIEUX, MELODIQUE, EMOUVANT, ATTENTIONNE, ELEGANT, ELEMENTS, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Morceau émouvant et au bon coeur pour piano solo. Avec accompagnement de cordes expressives. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 335 tk002 steven gutheinz life’s wonder (a) wom 335 inspiring minimalism west one music film score orchestral film score orchestral documentary strings string section main classical minimalist style film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic serious emotional serious thoughtful tender innocent tender nostalgic tender reflective tender romantic tender sentimental emotional tender-hearted solo piano with expressive string accompaniment. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="8039" name="Realise the Dream" code="TSH 039 tk013" libraryid="5" albumid="175" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_039_Life_in_Colour/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Alexander Paul Rudd / Zach Lemmon Lemmon" comment="Un motif festif de progression." styleid="20" lengthseconds="107" time="1:47" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_039_Life_in_Colour/TSH039_trk013_REALISE_THE_DREAM_Alexander_Paul_Rudd_Zach_Lemmon_Lemmon_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="13" tracktotal="" search="POP, POP POUR ENFANTS, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ENFANTS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, COMMUNICATION, ACTUALITÉS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, POP, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, HEUREUX, FESTIF, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, EVOLUTIF, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE,, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ACTUALITES, JOURNEE, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Un motif festif de progression. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede tsh 039 tk013 alexander paul rudd zach lemmon lemmon realise the dream tsh 039 life in colour the scoring house children pop kiddie pop main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) children business corporate bright optimistic business corporate communication news business corporate motivational pop uplifting motivational uplifting uplifting happy celebratory happy feel good happy happy building building celebratory motif. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="23886" name="Loud and Proud (a)" code="WOM 312 tk010" libraryid="6" albumid="517" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_312_Xcelerator/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Tristan Ivemy" comment="Indie rock inspirant, entrainant et excitant." styleid="6" lengthseconds="148" time="2:28" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_312_Xcelerator/WOM_312_trk010_LOUD_AND_PROUD_(A)_Tristan_Ivemy_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="10" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, POP CORPORATE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ROCK, ROCK ALTERNATIF, ROCK, INDIE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UN TRAIN, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, SPORT,, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO) Indie rock inspirant, entrainant et excitant. wom 312 tk010 tristan ivemy loud and proud (a) wom 312 xcelerator west one music rock business corporate corporate pop main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) rock alternative rock rock indie strong exciting strong prestigious uplifting uplifting movement rhythmic driving movement rhythmic rugged movement rhythmic train like business corporate tv radio inspiring uplifting and exciting indie rock. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="20401" name="Song to the Sun (a)" code="WOM 233 tk013" libraryid="6" albumid="434" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_233_Atmospheric_Indie/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Matthew James Robertson / Mike Reed / Tom Howe" comment="Des couplets tourbillonnants et pensifs débouchent sur des refrains radieux et entraînants." styleid="34" lengthseconds="202" time="3:22" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_233_Atmospheric_Indie/WOM233_trk013_SONG_TO_THE_SUN_(A)_Matthew_James_Robertson_Mike_Reed_Tom_Howe_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="13" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, INDIE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, HEUREUX, VIF, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, SPORT, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, SOLEIL, CHALEUR, VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, TEXTURE VOCALE,, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ANNEES 2000, AERIEN, ANNEES 20, ELEMENTS, METEO, ETE Des couplets tourbillonnants et pensifs débouchent sur des refrains radieux et entraînants. wom 233 tk013 matthew james robertson mike reed tom howe song to the sun (a) wom 233 atmospheric indie west one music indie rock indie time period modern era 2000s main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) strong prestigious uplifting uplifting happy bright movement smooth aerial flying tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio sports sports nature wildlife the elements land sun tropical swirling pensive verses break to bright catchy choruses. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="21259" name="Sunshine Skyway (a)" code="WOM 254A tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="456" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_254A_Supercharger_-_Indie/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Tyler Van Den Berg" comment="Du rock indé stadium euphorique." styleid="34" lengthseconds="119" time="1:59" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_254A_Supercharger_-_Indie/WOM254A_trk001_SUNSHINE_SKYWAY_(A)_Tyler_Van_Den_Berg_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, INDIE, ROCK, ROCK DE STADE, PRINCIPAL, SPORT, SPORTS EXTREMES, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), GROUPE DE ROCK, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 90, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ANNEES 2000, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 20, ANNEES 90 Du rock indé stadium euphorique. wom 254a tk001 tyler van den berg sunshine skyway (a) wom 254a supercharger - indie west one music indie rock indie rock stadium rock main sports extreme sports tv radio children youth tv tv radio sports uplifting euphoric movement rhythmic driving movement rhythmic rugged tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) rock band time period modern era 2000s time period modern era euphoric stadium indie. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="18570" name="An Amazing Day (a)" code="WOM 197 tk003" libraryid="6" albumid="393" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_197_Piano_Pop_Rock/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Dan Graham / Andrew Robert Flett" comment="Une célébration joyeuse avec des refrains euphoriques et toniques." styleid="7" lengthseconds="128" time="2:08" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_197_Piano_Pop_Rock/WOM197_trk003_AN_AMAZING_DAY_(A)_Dan_Graham_Andrew_Robert_Flett_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, COMMUNICATION, ACTUALITÉS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, POP CORPORATE, POP, ROCK, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, SPORT, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EVOLUTIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BATTERIE, CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, BASSE, BASSE ÉLECTRIQUE, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, CORDES, VIOLON , PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, AIR CONNU, PERIODE, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETERMINE, ANNEES 2000, ACTUALITES, ELECTRIQUE, BASSE ELECTRIQUE, ANNEES 20, ELEMENTS, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Une célébration joyeuse avec des refrains euphoriques et toniques. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 197 tk003 dan graham andrew robert flett an amazing day (a) wom 197 piano pop rock west one music pop business corporate bright optimistic business corporate communication news business corporate corporate pop pop rock main business corporate nature wildlife the elements land sun tropical seaside sports tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio sports happy a joyful celebration with euphoric uplifting choruses. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="23497" name="The Time is Now (b)" code="WOM 303 tk014" libraryid="6" albumid="509" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_303_Commercial_Dance/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Charlie Tenku / Jamie Paul Reddington / Emre Ramazanoglu / Sara Jane Novak" comment="Un morceau club emblématique, positif et réjouissant." styleid="1" lengthseconds="189" time="3:09" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_303_Commercial_Dance/WOM303_trk014_THE_TIME_IS_NOW_(B)_Charlie_Tenku_Jamie_Paul_Reddington_Emre_Ramazanoglu_Sara_Jane_Novak_.mp3" track="14" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRO, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRO, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HOUSE, POP, UNDERSCORE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, SPORT, EXERCICE, FITNESS, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), VOCAL, FÉMININ, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEFILE DE MODE, FEMININ, DEFILE Un morceau club emblématique, positif et réjouissant. wom 303 tk014 charlie tenku jamie paul reddington emre ramazanoglu sara jane novak the time is now (b) wom 303 commercial dance west one music dance electro club electronica electro club electronica electro club electronica house pop underscore activities settings fashion show sports exercise fitness tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio sports uplifting euphoric tempo a spine-tingling life affirming club anthem. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="23534" name="Final Triumph (a)" code="WOM 305 tk012" libraryid="6" albumid="510" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_305_Inspiring_Indie/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Matthew James Robertson / Mike Reed / Tom Howe" comment="Vaste indie cinématique. Entrainant et emblématique." styleid="34" lengthseconds="178" time="2:58" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_305_Inspiring_Indie/WOM_305_trk012_FINAL_TRIUMPH_(A)_Matthew_James_Robertson_Mike_Reed_Tom_Howe_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, PRESTIGE , BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, ROCK, INDIE, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EMBLÉMATIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, RALENTI, EVOLUTIF, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, SPORT, JEUX OLYMPIQUES,, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), EMBLEMATIQUE, REVELER, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Vaste indie cinématique. Entrainant et emblématique. wom 305 tk012 matthew james robertson mike reed tom howe final triumph (a) wom 305 inspiring indie west one music indie business corporate reveal launch main tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) business corporate motivational business corporate prestige business corporate reveal launch rock indie strong prestigious uplifting anthemic uplifting motivational uplifting uplifting movement broad cinematic indie. uplifting and anthemic. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="21841" name="The Winner (a)" code="WOM 265 tk012" libraryid="6" albumid="468" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_265_Pressure_Point/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Matthew James Robertson / Mike Reed / Tom Howe" comment="Le gagnant remporte tout. Une victoire euphorisante infusée au son indé." styleid="14" lengthseconds="160" time="2:40" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_265_Pressure_Point/WOM265_trk012_THE_WINNER_(A)_Matthew_James_Robertson_Mike_Reed_Tom_Howe_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, PRESTIGE , BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FORMATION, INFORMATION, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, SPORT,, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO) Le gagnant remporte tout. Une victoire euphorisante infusée au son indé. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede wom 265 tk012 matthew james robertson mike reed tom howe the winner (a) wom 265 pressure point west one music drama business corporate bright optimistic main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) business corporate motivational business corporate prestige business corporate training information strong prestigious uplifting motivational uplifting uplifting happy feel good business corporate tv the winner takes it all. an uplifting indie-infused celebration. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="25690" name="Get Me Up (b)" code="WOM 345 tk014" libraryid="6" albumid="550" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_345_Electro_Indie_Alternative/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Philip Hochstrate" comment="Indie electro pleine de confiance et d'espoir, avec des synthétiseurs vifs." styleid="34" lengthseconds="172" time="2:52" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_345_Electro_Indie_Alternative/WOM_345_trk014_GET_ME_UP_(B)_Philip_Hochstrate_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="14" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, INDIE, POP, ELECTRO POP, UNDERSCORE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EMBLÉMATIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, COOL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, GROUPE DE ROCK, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, VOCAL, MASCULIN, MASCULIN, FORMATIONS GENERALES, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, EMBLEMATIQUE, ELECTRIQUE Indie electro pleine de confiance et d'espoir, avec des synthétiseurs vifs. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 345 tk014 philip hochstrate get me up (b) wom 345 electro indie alternative west one music indie rock indie pop electro pop underscore activities settings city urban human environment tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio sports happy bright happy feel good uplifting anthemic uplifting confident and life-affirming electro indie with bold synths. underscore" waveformpath="" version="Underscore" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="21262" name="The Breakthrough (a)" code="WOM 254A tk004" libraryid="6" albumid="456" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_254A_Supercharger_-_Indie/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Tyler Van Den Berg" comment="Des guitares stridentes et des refrains épiques qui célèbrent la vie." styleid="34" lengthseconds="124" time="2:04" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_254A_Supercharger_-_Indie/WOM254A_trk004_THE_BREAKTHROUGH_(A)_Tyler_Van_Den_Berg_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, INDIE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 90, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ROCK, ROCK DE STADE, FORT, ÉPIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, SPORT, SPORTS EXTREMES,, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), EPIQUE, ANNEES 2000, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 20, ANNEES 90 Des guitares stridentes et des refrains épiques qui célèbrent la vie. wom 254a tk004 tyler van den berg the breakthrough (a) wom 254a supercharger - indie west one music indie rock indie time period modern era 20th century 1990s time period modern era 2000s main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) rock stadium rock strong epic movement rhythmic driving movement rhythmic rugged movies epic tv radio sports sports extreme sports jangling guitars and epic life affirming choruses. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="25200" name="Bourbon and Beer (b)" code="WOM 336A tk029" libraryid="6" albumid="541" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_336A_Supercharger_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="John-Paul Jones / Dean Saban" comment="Folk indé palpitante et contagieuse." styleid="34" lengthseconds="114" time="1:54" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_336A_Supercharger_2/WOM_336A_trk029_BOURBON_AND_BEER_(B)_John-Paul_Jones_Dean_Saban_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="29" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, GROUPE DE ROCK, ALTERNATIF, ENFANTS, ROCK, INDIE, HEUREUX, BONDISSANT, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, BONDISSANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, ROAD TRIP, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TELE REALITE Folk indé palpitante et contagieuse. wom 336a tk029 john-paul jones dean saban bourbon and beer (b) wom 336a supercharger 2 west one music indie rock rock band alternate children rock indie happy bouncy happy bright happy feel good happy happy happy upbeat uplifting motivational uplifting positive uplifting uplifting movement rhythmic bouncy movement rhythmic driving activities settings road trip tv radio infectious uplifting indie folk. no vocal" waveformpath="" version="No Vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="23725" name="Something Good (a)" code="WOM 309 tk004" libraryid="6" albumid="514" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_309_Indie_Organica/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="John-Paul Jones" comment="Audacieuse guitare infusée de soleil et batteries entrainantes. Édifiant et inspirant." styleid="34" lengthseconds="145" time="2:25" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_309_Indie_Organica/WOM_309_trk004_SOMETHING_GOOD_(A)_John-Paul_Jones_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, POP CORPORATE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, ROCK, INDIE, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, SPORT, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ELECTRIQUE, ELEMENTS Audacieuse guitare infusée de soleil et batteries entrainantes. Édifiant et inspirant. wom 309 tk004 john-paul jones something good (a) wom 309 indie organica west one music indie business corporate corporate pop business corporate motivational rock indie main business corporate nature wildlife the elements land sun tropical seaside sports tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio sports strong prestigious uplifting motivational uplifting bold sunshine-soaked guitars and driving drums. uplifting and inspiring. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="21181" name="Blaze of Glory (a)" code="WOM 252 tk004" libraryid="6" albumid="454" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_252_Indie_Folk/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Charlie Taylor / Jake Jarvis" comment="Enthousiasmant et épique. Des couplets punchy basculent vers des refrains puissants et euphorisants." styleid="23" lengthseconds="170" time="2:50" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_252_Indie_Folk/WOM252_trk004_BLAZE_OF_GLORY_(A)_Charlie_Taylor_Jake_Jarvis_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), FOLK CONTEMPORAINE, COUNTRY, WESTERN, FOLK ETHNIQUE TRADITIONNEL, FOLK AMÉRICAIN TRADITIONNEL, ETHNIQUE, FORT, ÉPIQUE, FORT, PUISSANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, CORDES, BANJO, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN NYLON, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN MÉTAL,, AMERIQUE DU NORD, FOLK AMERICAIN TRADITIONNEL, ETATS-UNIS, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), EPIQUE, CORDES EN METAL Enthousiasmant et épique. Des couplets punchy basculent vers des refrains puissants et euphorisants. wom 252 tk004 charlie taylor jake jarvis blaze of glory (a) wom 252 indie folk west one music country folk children north america usa main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) contemporary folk country western traditional ethnic folk traditional american folk ethnic strong epic strong powerful uplifting uplifting happy feel good movies epic tv radio leisure lifestyle travel strings rousing and epic. punchy verses break to powerful uplifting choruses. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="20395" name="Making Waves (a)" code="WOM 233 tk007" libraryid="6" albumid="434" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_233_Atmospheric_Indie/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Matthew James Robertson / Mike Reed / Tom Howe" comment="Une batterie battante et tonique et un piano progressent vers un final anthémique." styleid="34" lengthseconds="168" time="2:48" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_233_Atmospheric_Indie/WOM233_trk007_MAKING_WAVES_(A)_Matthew_James_Robertson_Mike_Reed_Tom_Howe_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, ROCK, INDIE, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, SOLEIL, CHALEUR, SPORT, JEUX OLYMPIQUES, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EMBLÉMATIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EVOLUTIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), GROUPE DE ROCK, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), EMBLEMATIQUE, REVELER, ELEMENTS, METEO, ETE, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Une batterie battante et tonique et un piano progressent vers un final anthémique. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 233 tk007 matthew james robertson mike reed tom howe making waves (a) wom 233 atmospheric indie west one music indie business corporate bright optimistic business corporate motivational business corporate reveal launch rock indie main business corporate nature wildlife the elements weather sun heat sports olympics tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio sports happy feel good pounding uplifting drums and piano building to anthemic finale. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="1383" name="Sky (a)" code="FEM 015 tk005" libraryid="2" albumid="35" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_015_Zeitgeist/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Stephen Dean Hilton" comment="Une piste pour bande-annonce contemporaine optimise et positive, idéale pour les films art-house et romantiques. Un piano rapide et un thème de cordes se combinent avec les batteries pour créer un effet des plus édifiants." styleid="2" lengthseconds="172" time="2:52" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_015_Zeitgeist/FEM_015_trk005_SKY_(A)_Stephen_Dean_Hilton_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, POP CORPORATE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, PRESTIGE , BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ROCK, INDIE, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, EVOLUTIF, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FILMS, ROAD MOVIE, FILMS, IDYLLE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, SPORT, JEUX OLYMPIQUES,, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), REVELER, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Une piste pour bande-annonce contemporaine optimise et positive, idéale pour les films art-house et romantiques. Un piano rapide et un thème de cordes se combinent avec les batteries pour créer un effet des plus édifiants. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live fem 015 tk005 stephen dean hilton sky (a) fem 015 zeitgeist fired earth music trailer business corporate reveal launch main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) business corporate corporate pop business corporate prestige business corporate reveal launch film score orchestral trailer rock indie strong prestigious uplifting optimistic uplifting positive happy positive optimistic contemporary trailer track for art-house and romantic movies. an upbeat piano and string theme combines with drums to create the most heart-lifting track. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
    <item id="2009" name="Celestial Ascension (a)" code="NRF 008 tk001" libraryid="3" albumid="52" albumartpath="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_008_Lumos/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Christian Telford, Koichi C. Sanchez-Imahashi, Shinnosuke Miyazawa, Kenneth E. Belcher" comment="Des rythmes énergiques de piano et guitare évoluent en un ostinato stimulant. Glorieux et plein d'espoir. Conclusion paroxystique une envolée de cuivres et violons." styleid="4" lengthseconds="171" time="2:51" samplefile="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_008_Lumos/NRF_008_trk001_CELESTIAL_ASCENSION_(A)_Christian_Telford,_Koichi_C._Sanchez-Imahashi,_Shinnosuke_Miyazawa,_Kenneth_E._Bel.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, ORCHESTRAL HYBRIDE , BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ART ET ESSAI, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, FAMILIAL, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, FILMS INDÉPENDANTS, FILMS, IDYLLE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, DRAME FAMILIAL, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EMBLÉMATIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, BEAU, EVOLUTIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, CLAVIER, PIANO, FORMATIONS GENERALES, ENERGIQUE, FILMS INDEPENDANTS, EMBLEMATIQUE, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Des rythmes énergiques de piano et guitare évoluent en un ostinato stimulant. Glorieux et plein d'espoir. Conclusion paroxystique une envolée de cuivres et violons. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live nrf 008 tk001 christian telford koichi c. sanchez-imahashi shinnosuke miyazawa kenneth e. belcher celestial ascension (a) nrf 008 lumos noise refinery film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral documentary film score orchestral orchestral hybrid film score orchestral panoramic main movies art house movies children storytelling movies family movies human drama movies indie films movies romance tv radio sports tv energetic piano and guitar rhythms grow to an inspirational ostinato. hopeful and glorious. climactic conclusion with soaring violins and horns. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Noise Refinery" cae="00719510644"/>
    <item id="4625" name="Personal Reflections" code="TSH 035 tk021" libraryid="5" albumid="125" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_035_A_Winner_is_Born/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Mark Lasker" comment="Une atmosphère d'introspection évoluant lentement." styleid="22" lengthseconds="133" time="2:13" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_035_A_Winner_is_Born/TSH035_trk021_PERSONAL_REFLECTIONS_Mark_Lasker_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="21" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, NEIGE, GLACE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MER, SOUS-MARIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, TROUBLANT, STÉRILE, TROUBLANT, FROID , TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, ÉTRANGE , TROUBLANT, BIZARRE, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, INTROSPECTIF, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRAGIQUE, SÉRIEUX, TENDRE, SONGEUR, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), ELEMENTS SONORES, SERIEUX, ATMOSPHERES, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), STERILE, INQUIETANT, ETRANGE, DEPRIMANT, AERIEN, ELEMENTS Une atmosphère d'introspection évoluant lentement. tsh 035 tk021 mark lasker personal reflections tsh 035 a winner is born the scoring house sport sound elements atmospheres main movies human drama nature wildlife the elements land snow ice nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife nature wildlife the elements sea underwater nature wildlife the elements sky aerial clouds disturbing barren disturbing cold introspective slowly evolving atmosphere. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="5155" name="Chapter's End (a)" code="TSH 048 tk002" libraryid="5" albumid="134" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_048_Storyboards/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Robert Henry Peter White" comment="Thème pensif et réflechi." styleid="10" lengthseconds="111" time="1:51" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_048_Storyboards/TSH_048_trk002_CHAPTER'S_END_(A)_Robert_Henry_Peter_White_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, NUIT, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, SÉRIEUX, ATTENTIONNÉ, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), SERIEUX, DEPRIMANT, ATTENTIONNE Thème pensif et réflechi. tsh 048 tk002 robert henry peter white chapter's end (a) tsh 048 storyboards the scoring house documentary film score orchestral documentary main documentary movies human drama movies urban drama tv radio talkshow entertainment late night tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama sad depressing poignant sad depressing sad serious thoughtful tender nostalgic tender thoughtful reflective theme. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="24013" name="Keepsake (a)" code="WOM 315 tk008" libraryid="6" albumid="520" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_315_Piano_Evolutions/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Clifford Eric Haywood" comment="Sincère et pensif. Se construit tout du long." styleid="14" lengthseconds="127" time="2:07" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_315_Piano_Evolutions/WOM_315_trk008_KEEPSAKE_(A)_Clifford_Eric_Haywood_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="8" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, SOLO, DROLE, MÉLODRAMATIQUE, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, EVOLUTIF, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, FILM NOIR, DOCUMENTAIRE, CLAVIER, PIANO,, MELODRAMATIQUE, DEPRIMANT, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Sincère et pensif. Se construit tout du long. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 315 tk008 clifford eric haywood keepsake (a) wom 315 piano evolutions west one music drama film score orchestral trailer main solo funny melodramatic tender nostalgic tender reflective tender romantic tender sentimental sad depressing lonely sad depressing poignant sad depressing sad building movies human drama movies film noir documentary keyboard piano sincere and wistful building throughout. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="26332" name="Stratosphere (a)" code="WOM 207 tk010" libraryid="6" albumid="564" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_207_Enlightenment/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Christian Telford / Nigel William Graham" comment="Une atmosphère sonore de tranquilité, d’élégance et de beauté. Des cordes superbes planent sur de l’electronica aérienne." styleid="4" lengthseconds="149" time="2:29" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_207_Enlightenment/WOM207_trk010_STRATOSPHERE_(A)_Christian_Telford_Nigel_William_Graham_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="10" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, JAILLIR, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), AERIEN, ELEMENTS Une atmosphère sonore de tranquilité, d’élégance et de beauté. Des cordes superbes planent sur de l’electronica aérienne. wom 207 tk010 christian telford nigel william graham stratosphere (a) wom 207 enlightenment west one music film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer club electronica club electronica club electronica film score orchestral panoramic main movies action adventure movies fantasy adventure nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama trailers trailer track uplifting soaring movement soundscape of tranquillity elegance and beauty. lush strings soar over airy electronica. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="20871" name="Never Again (a)" code="WOM 245 tk010" libraryid="6" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_245_Night_Music/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Caspar John Valentine Kedros / Scott Doran" comment="Des vagues tournantes d'electronica chaleureuse évoluant." styleid="34" lengthseconds="192" time="3:12" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_245_Night_Music/WOM245_trk010_NEVER_AGAIN_(A)_Caspar_John_Valentine_Kedros_Scott_Doran_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="10" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CLUB, ELECTRONICA, AMBIENT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, RALENTI, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, SPORT, DOCUMENTAIRE,, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, DEPRIMANT, ACCELERE, AERIEN, ELEMENTS Des vagues tournantes d'electronica chaleureuse évoluant. wom 245 tk010 caspar john valentine kedros scott doran never again (a) wom 245 night music west one music indie sound elements atmospheres main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) club electronica ambient club electronica club electronica club electronica peaceful dreamy tender warm sad depressing lonely movement rhythmic speeded up time lapse movement smooth aerial floating movement revolving and evolving waves of warm electronica. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="4672" name="Dream the Moment (b)" code="TSH 035 tk068" libraryid="5" albumid="125" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_035_A_Winner_is_Born/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Mark Lasker" comment="Un thème visionnaire et sincère." styleid="22" lengthseconds="141" time="2:21" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_035_A_Winner_is_Born/TSH035_trk068_DREAM_THE_MOMENT_(B)_Mark_Lasker_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="68" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, ALTERNATIF, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, PRINTEMPS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, DIVIN, CÉLESTE, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, PATRIOTIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EVOLUTIF, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, MONTÉE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, RALENTI, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, MONTEE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, ACCELERE, AERIEN, REVELER, ELEMENTS, CELESTE, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Un thème visionnaire et sincère. tsh 035 tk068 mark lasker dream the moment (b) tsh 035 a winner is born the scoring house sport children storytelling business corporate luxury business corporate motivational business corporate reveal launch film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic alternate movies children storytelling nature wildlife the elements seasons time spring nature visionary heartfelt theme. alternative" waveformpath="" version="Alternative" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="25693" name="Walk Into the Light (b)" code="WOM 345 tk017" libraryid="6" albumid="550" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_345_Electro_Indie_Alternative/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Philip Hochstrate" comment="Electro indie expansive et éthérée, avec de gros synthétiseurs et une batterie jouant un rythme de half time shuffle." styleid="34" lengthseconds="184" time="3:04" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_345_Electro_Indie_Alternative/WOM_345_trk017_WALK_INTO_THE_LIGHT_(B)_Philip_Hochstrate_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="17" tracktotal="" search="TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, ROCK, INDIE, POP, ELECTRO POP, UNDERSCORE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, HEUREUX, FESTIF, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EMBLÉMATIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EVOLUTIF, COOL, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, GROUPE DE ROCK, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, FORMATIONS GENERALES, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, DETERMINE, EMBLEMATIQUE, ELECTRIQUE, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Electro indie expansive et éthérée, avec de gros synthétiseurs et une batterie jouant un rythme de half time shuffle. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 345 tk017 philip hochstrate walk into the light (b) wom 345 electro indie alternative west one music indie rock indie pop electro pop underscore activities settings city urban human environment tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio sports happy celebratory happy feel good strong determined strong expansive and ethereal indie electro with big synths and half time drums. underscore" waveformpath="" version="Underscore" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="2769" name="Pure Release (a)" code="TSH 002 tk021" libraryid="5" albumid="93" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_002_Evolutions/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Robert Henry Peter White" comment="Une ascension émouvante vers une fin triomphante." styleid="11" lengthseconds="129" time="2:09" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_002_Evolutions/TSH002_trk021_PURE_RELEASE_(A)_Robert_Henry_Peter_White_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="21" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, POP CORPORATE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, PRESTIGE , BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FORMATION, INFORMATION, EASY LISTENING, MIDDLE OF THE ROAD, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SPORT, JEUX OLYMPIQUES, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, SÉRIEUX, ÉMOUVANT, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, FORT, TRIOMPHAL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EVOLUTIF, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, RALENTI, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), SERIEUX, EMOUVANT, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Une ascension émouvante vers une fin triomphante. tsh 002 tk021 robert henry peter white pure release (a) tsh 002 evolutions the scoring house corporate business business corporate bright optimistic business corporate corporate pop business corporate motivational business corporate prestige business corporate training information easy listening middle of the road main business corporate sports olympics tv radio leisure lifestyle emotional ascent to triumphant end. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="4618" name="Beauty in Motion" code="TSH 035 tk014" libraryid="5" albumid="125" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_035_A_Winner_is_Born/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Mark Lasker" comment="Des images descriptives et émotionnelles avec un ensemble violoncelle." styleid="22" lengthseconds="118" time="1:58" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_035_A_Winner_is_Born/TSH035_trk014_BEAUTY_IN_MOTION_Mark_Lasker_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="14" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, SÉRIEUX, ÉMOUVANT, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, CORDES, VIOLONCELLE, STYLE VINTAGE, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, EMOUVANT, ELEMENTS Des images descriptives et émotionnelles avec un ensemble violoncelle. tsh 035 tk014 mark lasker beauty in motion tsh 035 a winner is born the scoring house sport film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral pastoral main documentary movies human drama movies romance nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral peaceful dreamy peaceful peaceful sad emotional descriptive imagery featuring cello ensemble. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="7390" name="Our Heritage (a)" code="TSH 059 tk010" libraryid="5" albumid="168" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_059_Orchestral_Fantasia/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Arthur Rhodes" comment="Thème plein d'attention et de dignité." styleid="4" lengthseconds="149" time="2:29" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_059_Orchestral_Fantasia/TSH_059_trk010_OUR_HERITAGE_(A)_Simon_Arthur_Rhodes_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="10" tracktotal="" search="CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE, CLASSIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, SÉRIEUX, DIGNE, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, ATTENTIONNÉ, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, PATRIOTIQUE, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, CLAVIER, PIANO, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, PÉRIODE, PRÉ-20E SIÈCLE, 19E SIÈCLE, AMERIQUE DU NORD, PERIODE, SERIEUX, ETATS-UNIS, PRE-20E SIECLE, ATTENTIONNE, PERIODES, 20E SIECLE, 19E SIECLE, ELEMENTS Thème plein d'attention et de dignité. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 059 tk010 simon arthur rhodes our heritage (a) tsh 059 orchestral fantasia the scoring house film score orchestral classical classical styling classical film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic film score orchestral pastoral main documentary biographical historical the arts movies period historical costume drama nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama thoughtful dignified theme. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="20904" name="Stars Like Dust (a)" code="WOM 246 tk006" libraryid="6" albumid="447" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_246_Atmospheric_Guitar/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Dan Cassady" comment="Une introduction sombre et maussade se change en une beauté impressionnante à 1:52." styleid="12" lengthseconds="236" time="3:56" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_246_Atmospheric_Guitar/WOM246_trk006_STARS_LIKE_DUST_(A)_Dan_Cassady_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="6" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, PAISIBLE, DÉTENDU, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, ELEMENTS SONORES, AMERIQUE DU NORD, ATMOSPHERES, ETATS-UNIS, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETENDU, ELECTRIQUE, ELEMENTS Une introduction sombre et maussade se change en une beauté impressionnante à 1:52. wom 246 tk006 dan cassady stars like dust (a) wom 246 atmospheric guitar west one music atmospheres sound elements atmospheres main documentary nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama disturbing dark peaceful relaxed tender reflective tender sentimental tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) strings guitar electric north america usa dark and brooding introduction changes to awe-inspiring beauty at 1:52. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="24401" name="Lovers’ Requiem (a)" code="WOM 322 tk005" libraryid="6" albumid="526" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_322_Cinematic_Drama/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Martin Tillmann" comment="Des lignes de piano à la beauté troublante entremelées avec des cordes enveloppantes, émouvantes." styleid="14" lengthseconds="151" time="2:31" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_322_Cinematic_Drama/WOM322_trk005_LOVERS_REQUIEM_(A)_Martin_Tillmann_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, MODERNE, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, DRAME FAMILIAL, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, DRAME HOSPITALIER, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, ANXIEUX, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, PASSIONNÉ, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, MÉLANCOLIE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, SÉRIEUX, INQUIET, SÉRIEUX, ÉMOUVANT, SÉRIEUX, SOLENNEL, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, CLAVIER, PIANO, FORMATIONS GENERALES, SERIEUX, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, PASSIONNE, DEPRIMANT, EMOUVANT, MELANCOLIE, ELEGANT Des lignes de piano à la beauté troublante entremelées avec des cordes enveloppantes, émouvantes. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 322 tk005 martin tillmann lovers’ requiem (a) wom 322 cinematic drama west one music drama film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral documentary main movies human drama movies modern tv radio tv drama family drama tv radio tv drama medical drama tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing anxious disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense hauntingly beautiful piano lines intertwined with rich emotive strings. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="20397" name="Waves of Light (a)" code="WOM 233 tk009" libraryid="6" albumid="434" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_233_Atmospheric_Indie/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Matthew James Robertson / Mike Reed / Tom Howe" comment="Des atmosphères sonores riches et expansives avec des motifs de piano éblouissants. Progression dès 1:45." styleid="34" lengthseconds="209" time="3:29" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_233_Atmospheric_Indie/WOM233_trk009_WAVES_OF_LIGHT_(A)_Matthew_James_Robertson_Mike_Reed_Tom_Howe_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, ROCK, INDIE, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, MÉDICAL, SCIENCES DE LA VIE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, EVOLUTIF, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), SOUND DESIGN, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), AERIEN, ELEMENTS, MEDICAL, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Des atmosphères sonores riches et expansives avec des motifs de piano éblouissants. Progression dès 1:45. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 233 tk009 matthew james robertson mike reed tom howe waves of light (a) wom 233 atmospheric indie west one music indie business corporate science technology business corporate luxury rock indie main business corporate nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife science technology industry medical life science tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden tv radio leisure rich expansive soundscapes with stunning piano patterns. building from 1:45. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="7122" name="Nirvana (a)" code="TSH 029 tk004" libraryid="5" albumid="164" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_029_Symphonic_Fantasia/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Arthur Rhodes" comment="Serein, enveloppant, flottant." styleid="4" lengthseconds="199" time="3:19" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_029_Symphonic_Fantasia/TSH029_trk004_NIRVANA_(A)_Simon_Arthur_Rhodes_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, ESPACE, INTERSIDÉRAL, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, SEREIN, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, RALENTI, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, CLAVIER, PIANO, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, DEPRIMANT, ACCELERE, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, INTERSIDERAL Serein, enveloppant, flottant. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 029 tk004 simon arthur rhodes nirvana (a) tsh 029 symphonic fantasia the scoring house film score orchestral sound elements atmospheres film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic main movies romance nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife nature wildlife the elements sky aerial clouds nature serene immersive drifting. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="19169" name="Mercury Falls (a)" code="WOM 208 tk003" libraryid="6" albumid="406" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_208_Lost_Highways/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Patrick Robert Murdoch" comment="Nostalgique et mélancolique avec une batterie live réverbérante, des ondes généreuses de slide guitare et une guitare lead lyrique." styleid="6" lengthseconds="190" time="3:10" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_208_Lost_Highways/WOM208_trk003_MERCURY_FALLS_(A)_Patrick_Robert_Murdoch_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 70, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), COUNTRY, COUNTRY ROCK, EASY LISTENING, AOR, PAISIBLE, LYRIQUE, MÉLODIQUE, LYRIQUE, FILMS, ROAD MOVIE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, CORDES, GUITARE, BOTTLENECK, SLIDE, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE,, AMERIQUE DU NORD, PERIODE, MELODIQUE, ETATS-UNIS, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), 20E SIECLE, ELECTRIQUE, ANNEES 70 Nostalgique et mélancolique avec une batterie live réverbérante, des ondes généreuses de slide guitare et une guitare lead lyrique. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 208 tk003 patrick robert murdoch mercury falls (a) wom 208 lost highways west one music rock film score orchestral trailer north america usa time period modern era 20th century 1970s main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) country country rock easy listening aor peaceful lyrical melodic lyrical movies road movie tv radio leisure lifestyle travel strings guitar wistful and melancholic with reverberant live drums waves of rich slide guitar and lyrical lead guitar. main knees up, mess piano, cockney, east london, singalong, pub joanna, piano bar, piano-bar, live" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="26367" name="Inner World (a)" code="WOM 209 tk003" libraryid="6" albumid="565" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_209_Absolution/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Toby Y. Chu" comment="Une belle et délicate introduction progresse graduellement vers un climax mené par des cordes à 1:54. Avec un gamelan et des guitares électriques." styleid="4" lengthseconds="142" time="2:22" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_209_Absolution/WOM209_trk003_INNER_WORLD_(A)_Toby_Y._Chu_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, CLASSIQUE, STYLE MINIMALISTE, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, ART ET ESSAI, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, DÉTENDU, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, SÉRIEUX, TENDRE, DÉLICAT, TENDRE, SONGEUR, BEAU, CHUTE, DESCENTE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ETHNIQUE, PERCUSSION, GAMELAN, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETENDU, DEPRIMANT, DELICAT, ACCELERE, AERIEN, ELECTRIQUE, ELEMENTS Une belle et délicate introduction progresse graduellement vers un climax mené par des cordes à 1:54. Avec un gamelan et des guitares électriques. wom 209 tk003 toby y. chu inner world (a) wom 209 absolution west one music film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer classical minimalist style main documentary movies art house movies human drama nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife trailer track disturbing mysterious peaceful contented beautiful delicate introduction gradually builds to stunning string-led climax at 1:54. featuring gamelan and electric guitars. main delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="18029" name="Pure and Simple (a)" code="WOM 185 tk008" libraryid="6" albumid="381" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_185_Indie_Rock_&amp;_Pop_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jared Nathan Sweetman / Paul James Borg" comment="Une beauté maussade et chatoyante. Des couplets calmes et tendres basculent vers des refrains massifs et expansifs." styleid="6" lengthseconds="169" time="2:49" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_185_Indie_Rock_&amp;_Pop_2/WOM185_trk008_PURE_AND_SIMPLE_(A)_Jared_Nathan_Sweetman_Paul_James_Borg_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="8" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, PRESTIGE , BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, ROCK, INDIE, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SPORT, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, DOUX, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, TENDRE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EVOLUTIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UN TRAIN, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), BATTERIE, CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, BASSE, BASSE ÉLECTRIQUE, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN NYLON, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN MÉTAL, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, CORDES, VIOLON , PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PERIODE, SERIEUX, DETERMINE, DEFILE DE MODE, ANNEES 2000, DEFILE, ELECTRIQUE, BASSE ELECTRIQUE, REVELER, ANNEES 20, CORDES EN METAL, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Une beauté maussade et chatoyante. Des couplets calmes et tendres basculent vers des refrains massifs et expansifs. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 185 tk008 jared nathan sweetman paul james borg pure and simple (a) wom 185 indie rock &amp; pop 2 west one music rock business corporate business corporate motivational business corporate prestige business corporate reveal launch rock indie main activities settings fashion show business corporate sports tv radio children youth tv tv radio sports peaceful contented peaceful dreamy bleak shimmering beauty. quiet tender verses break to big expansive choruses. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="6292" name="Life Journeys" code="TSH 065A tk024" libraryid="5" albumid="148" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_065A_The_Piano_Book/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Ostinati fluides, expressifs." styleid="25" lengthseconds="185" time="3:05" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_065A_The_Piano_Book/TSH065A_trk024_LIFE_JOURNEYS_Richard_Allen_Harvey_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="24" tracktotal="" search="CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIÈCLE, PRINCIPAL, ENFANTS, CONTES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, INNOCENT, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, BEAU, MÉLODIQUE, LYRIQUE, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, CLAVIER, PIANO, SOLO, MELODIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIECLE, DEPRIMANT, 20E SIECLE, ELEMENTS Ostinati fluides, expressifs. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 065a tk024 richard allen harvey life journeys tsh 065a the piano book the scoring house classical opera classical 20th century classical style main children storytelling film score orchestral documentary film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral pastoral peaceful peaceful sad depressing poignant sad depressing sad tender hopeful tender innocent tender intimate expressive flowing ostinati. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="23745" name="Walking the Ghost (b)" code="WOM 309 tk024" libraryid="6" albumid="514" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_309_Indie_Organica/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="John-Paul Jones" comment="Sensible et nostalgique. Motifs de guitare réverbérants accompagné d'un piano distant et de cordes simples." styleid="34" lengthseconds="124" time="2:04" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_309_Indie_Organica/WOM_309_trk024_WALKING_THE_GHOST_(B)_John-Paul_Jones_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="24" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, INDIE, ALTERNATIF, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, SOLEIL, CHALEUR, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, ABSTRAIT, SIMPLE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ELEMENTS, METEO, ETE Sensible et nostalgique. Motifs de guitare réverbérants accompagné d'un piano distant et de cordes simples. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 309 tk024 john-paul jones walking the ghost (b) wom 309 indie organica west one music indie rock indie alternate nature wildlife the elements land sun tropical seaside nature wildlife the elements weather sun heat tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio sports abstract simple tender warm tempo emotive and wistful. reverberant guitar patterns with distant piano and simple strings. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="20684" name="Back 'em Down (a)" code="WOM 240 tk004" libraryid="6" albumid="441" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_240_Hip_Hop_USA/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jerome Henry Spence / Jabula Taiwo Hudson / Antoine Jermaine Heard / Felisha Aileen Booker" comment="Vocales et gros beats seulement. Voix de rappeur." styleid="28" lengthseconds="133" time="2:13" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_240_Hip_Hop_USA/WOM240_trk004_BACK_'EM_DOWN_(A)_Jerome_Henry_Spence_Jabula_Taiwo_Hudson_Antoine_Jermaine_Heard_Felisha_Ailee.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HIP HOP, URBAIN, HIP HOP, HIP HOP, URBAIN, RAP, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, HOLLYWOOD, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, NUIT, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), VOCAL, ENERGIQUE Vocales et gros beats seulement. Voix de rappeur. wom 240 tk004 jerome henry spence jabula taiwo hudson antoine jermaine heard felisha aileen booker back 'em down (a) wom 240 hip hop usa west one music hip-hop urban club electronica hip hop urban hip hop hip hop urban rap main activities settings showbiz hollywood tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio talkshow entertainment late night strong energetic glamorous luxurious tempo just vocals and fat beats. male rap vocal. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="1454" name="Man of Steel Dirty Dubstep Remix" code="FEM 006 tk001" libraryid="2" albumid="37" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_006_Man_of_Steel_-_Remixed_EP/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Troels Brun Folmann" comment="Une orchestration épique mélangée à du dubstep battant pour des bandes-annonces chargées en adrénaline." styleid="2" lengthseconds="168" time="2:48" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_006_Man_of_Steel_-_Remixed_EP/FEM006_trk001_MAN_OF_STEEL_DIRTY_DUBSTEP_REMIX_Troels_Brun_Folmann_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, ORCHESTRAL HYBRIDE , CLUB, ELECTRONICA, DUB, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, DUBSTEP, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRO, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, REMIXES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, MODERNE, SPORT, SPORTS EXTREMES, TRAILERS, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, TENDU, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, ÉPIQUE, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, MÉCANIQUE, ROBOTIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, VOIX TRAITÉES, MODIFIÉES, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PERIODE, SERIEUX, MECANIQUE, DETERMINE, EPIQUE, ANNEES 2000, VOIX TRAITEES, ANNEES 20, MODIFIEES Une orchestration épique mélangée à du dubstep battant pour des bandes-annonces chargées en adrénaline. fem 006 tk001 troels brun folmann man of steel dirty dubstep remix fem 006 man of steel - remixed ep fired earth music trailer film score orchestral orchestral hybrid club electronica dub club electronica dubstep club electronica electro club electronica remixes film score orchestral trailer main movies action drama movies modern sports extreme sports trailers tv radio sports trailer track epic orchestral smashed together with pounding dupstep for high-adrenaline trailers. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
    <item id="4388" name="Adrenaline High (c)" code="TSH 032A tk009" libraryid="5" albumid="121" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_032A_Big_Bang_Percussion/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="John Gregory Knowles" comment="Un rythme extrême et puissant avec des éléments électroniques." styleid="2" lengthseconds="59" time="0:59" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_032A_Big_Bang_Percussion/TSH032A_trk009_ADRENALINE_HIGH_(C)_John_Gregory_Knowles_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ALTERNATIF, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, GUERRE, MILITAIRE, HISTORIQUE, GUERRE MODERNE, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, JUNGLE, TROPICAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, TEMPETES, TONNERRE, VENT, OURAGANS, SPORT, SPORTS EXTREMES, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, AGRESSIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, POURSUITE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FRÉNÉSIE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), 20E SIECLE, FRENESIE, ELEMENTS, METEO, ETE Un rythme extrême et puissant avec des éléments électroniques. tsh 032a tk009 john gregory knowles adrenaline high (c) tsh 032a big bang percussion the scoring house trailer film score orchestral trailer alternate activities settings war military historical modern warfare movies action adventure nature wildlife the elements land jungle tropical nature wildlife the elements weather storms thunder wind hurricanes sports extreme sports extreme rhythm workout with electronic elements. alternative" waveformpath="" version="Alternative" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="21080" name="Hammerhead" code="WOM 250 tk009" libraryid="6" albumid="451" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_250_Dubstep/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Steve Ruff" comment="Des synthés trance classiques avec des basses dubstep féroces et des breaks." styleid="28" lengthseconds="280" time="4:40" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_250_Dubstep/WOM250_trk009_HAMMERHEAD_Steve_Ruff_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, DUBSTEP, PRINCIPAL, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TROUBLANT, ÉTRANGE , TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ETRANGE, ANNEES 2000, ANNEES 20 Des synthés trance classiques avec des basses dubstep féroces et des breaks. wom 250 tk009 steve ruff hammerhead wom 250 dubstep west one music hip-hop urban club electronica club electronica dubstep main tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style disturbing strange tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) time period modern era 2000s classic trance synths with fierce dubstep bass and breaks. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="231" name="Devotion (a)" code="EDS 011 tk006" libraryid="1" albumid="7" albumartpath="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_011_Mainroom_House/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Huw Williams" comment="Titre ÉNORME pour club. Une intro accrocheuse au synthé se développe avec des chorus exaltants. Avec morceaux de voix." styleid="1" lengthseconds="193" time="3:13" samplefile="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_011_Mainroom_House/EDS_011_trk006_DEVOTION_(A)_Huw_Williams_Electronic_Dance_Series.mp3" track="6" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HOUSE, ELECTRO HOUSE, ÉLECTRONIQUE, PRINCIPAL, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EMBLÉMATIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INSISTANT, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, ELECTRONIQUE, ENERGIQUE, EMBLEMATIQUE, ELEMENTS Titre ÉNORME pour club. Une intro accrocheuse au synthé se développe avec des chorus exaltants. Avec morceaux de voix. eds 011 tk006 huw williams devotion (a) eds 011 mainroom house electronic dance series dance electro club electronica house electro house electronic main club electronica club electronica happy bright happy feel good strong energetic uplifting anthemic uplifting euphoric uplifting motivational uplifting positive uplifting uplifting movement rhythmic driving movement huge energetic club monster. catchy rising synth intro builds to uplifting choruses featuring vocal chops. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Electronic Dance Series" cae="00666407133"/>
    <item id="656" name="The Sword of Peleus (a)" code="FEM 009 tk002" libraryid="2" albumid="21" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_009_Immortality/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Ryan Amon" comment="Un morceau orchestral pour bande-annonce dark et héroïque, conduit à un thème mémorable à partir de 1:32 et jusqu'à la fin." styleid="2" lengthseconds="131" time="2:11" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_009_Immortality/FEM009_trk002_THE_SWORD_OF_PELEUS_(A)_Ryan_Amon_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, BACK END, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, AGRESSIF, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, HÉROIQUE, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, PATRIOTIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, DÉFILÉ, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, CHEVAUCHER, ÉQUESTRE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COURANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, CHOEUR, PÉRIODE, CIVILISATIONS ANCIENNES, ROME ANTIQUE (500 AV. J-C - 476 AP. J-C), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, PERIODE, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETERMINE, EPIQUE, HEROIQUE, PERIODES, 20E SIECLE, DEFILE, EQUESTRE Un morceau orchestral pour bande-annonce dark et héroïque, conduit à un thème mémorable à partir de 1:32 et jusqu'à la fin. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede fem 009 tk002 ryan amon the sword of peleus (a) fem 009 immortality fired earth music trailer film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic main movies action adventure movies back end movies epic movies period historical costume drama trailers trailer track disturbing dark disturbing tense dramatic aggressive scary ominous serious determined dark heroic orchestral trailer cue that builds to huge memorable theme from 1:32 to end. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
    <item id="3631" name="With Intent (a)" code="TSH 016 tk007" libraryid="5" albumid="107" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_016_A_Clearer_Vision/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Andrew Clark" comment="Une progression décidée et entraînante." styleid="11" lengthseconds="173" time="2:53" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_016_A_Clearer_Vision/TSH016_trk007_WITH_INTENT_(A)_Simon_Andrew_Clark_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, COMMUNICATION, ACTUALITÉS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FORMATION, INFORMATION, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, NOUVELLES BUSINESS, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, TROUBLANT, TENDU, EVOLUTIF, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, INSECTE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INDUSTRIE, MACHINES, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UN TRAIN, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), IRREGULIER, ACTUALITES, REVELER, JOURNEE, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Une progression décidée et entraînante. tsh 016 tk007 simon andrew clark with intent (a) tsh 016 a clearer vision the scoring house corporate business business corporate reveal launch business corporate communication news business corporate science technology business corporate training information main business corporate documentary science technology science technology industry tv radio news and current affairs purposeful driving build. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="758" name="Battlefied: Milky Way (a)" code="FEM 013 tk006" libraryid="2" albumid="24" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_013_Bad_Boy_Trailer/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Enrico Cacace" comment="Une introduction électronique brouillée avec un rythme entrainant ouvrent cette piste Sci-Fi épique. Cuivres sombres et courses de chordes entrent à 00:32 par dessus un lit électronique sexy fait d'effets de bataille spatiale, le tout pour developper une fin d'action magistrale avec frappes et accoups." styleid="2" lengthseconds="100" time="1:40" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_013_Bad_Boy_Trailer/FEM013_trk006_BATTLEFIED_MILKY_WAY_(A)_Enrico_Cacace_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="6" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, ORCHESTRAL HYBRIDE , ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, SOUND DESIGN, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, BACK END, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, DRAMATIQUE, AGRESSIF, SEXY, SEXY, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, ÉPIQUE, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, IMPLACABLE, FORT, FORT, GLITCHY, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, DETERMINE, EPIQUE, ELEMENTS Une introduction électronique brouillée avec un rythme entrainant ouvrent cette piste Sci-Fi épique. Cuivres sombres et courses de chordes entrent à 00:32 par dessus un lit électronique sexy fait d'effets de bataille spatiale, le tout pour developper une fin d'action magistrale avec frappes et accoups. fem 013 tk006 enrico cacace battlefied: milky way (a) fem 013 bad boy trailer fired earth music trailer film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral orchestral hybrid sound elements atmospheres sound design main movies action adventure movies back end movies epic movies urban drama trailers trailer track disturbing dark dramatic aggressive sexy sexy strong confident glitchy electronic intro with catchy beat opens this sci-fi epic. dark brass and string runs layer in at 00:32 over this sexy electronic bed with space-wars effects coming together to develop to a huge action backend with stabs and hits. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
    <item id="1812" name="Above The Law (a)" code="NRF 003 tk004" libraryid="3" albumid="47" albumartpath="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_003_Bring_The_Noise/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Fumitake Igarashi" comment="Electro mid-tempo classe avec des textures irrésisitibles de synthétiseur." styleid="1" lengthseconds="153" time="2:33" samplefile="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_003_Bring_The_Noise/NRF_003_trk004_ABOVE_THE_LAW_(A)_Fumitake_Igarashi_Noise_Refinery.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ÉLECTRONIQUE, PRINCIPAL, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INSISTANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, NERVEUX, QUI A DU CRAN, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, FETE, FÊTE GÉNÉRALE, SPORT, EXERCICE, FITNESS, SPORT, SPORTS EXTREMES, ELECTRONIQUE, ENERGIQUE, FETE GENERALE Electro mid-tempo classe avec des textures irrésisitibles de synthétiseur. nrf 003 tk004 fumitake igarashi above the law (a) nrf 003 bring the noise noise refinery dance electro club electronica electronic main club electronica breakbeat club electronica club electronica strong confident strong energetic strong powerful strong strong uplifting motivational uplifting positive uplifting uplifting movement rhythmic driving movement rhythmic medium tempo stylish electronica with compelling synth textures. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Noise Refinery" cae="00719510644"/>
    <item id="22362" name="Tribal Dance (a)" code="WOM 278 tk005" libraryid="6" albumid="480" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_278_Drums_Rule_the_World/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Emre Ramazanoglu / Geoffrey James Pidcock Holroyde" comment="Des beats énormes et palpitants, avec des touches de synthé." styleid="22" lengthseconds="174" time="2:54" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_278_Drums_Rule_the_World/WOM278_trk005_TRIBAL_DANCE_(A)_Emre_Ramazanoglu_Geoffrey_James_Pidcock_Holroyde_West_One_Music_Limi.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, FOLK ETHNIQUE TRADITIONNEL, INDIGÈNE, AUTHENTIQUE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, ACTION, SPORT, TV, RADIO, SPORT, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COURANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BATTERIE, AFRIQUE, INDIGENE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO) Des beats énormes et palpitants, avec des touches de synthé. wom 278 tk005 emre ramazanoglu geoffrey james pidcock holroyde tribal dance (a) wom 278 drums rule the world west one music sport film score orchestral trailer traditional ethnic folk authentic indigenous main movies action adventure movies action drama sports tv radio sports dramatic intense movement rhythmic driving movement rhythmic rugged movement rhythmic running tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) huge throbbing beats with synth touches. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="28819" name="Sandpaper" code="WOMG 022A tk003" libraryid="7" albumid="618" albumartpath="Music/West One Music Group/WOMG_022A_This_Is_Sport_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Stephen Dean Hilton" comment="Cordes époustouflantes, beats électroniques et sound design éclatants se développent constamment, avec émotion et dynamisme, jusqu'à la fin." styleid="22" lengthseconds="118" time="1:58" samplefile="Music/West One Music Group/WOMG_022A_This_Is_Sport_2/WOMG_022A_trk003_SANDPAPER_Stephen_Dean_Hilton_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, ORCHESTRAL HYBRIDE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, ROCK, INDIE, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, SOUND DESIGN, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, FILMS INDÉPENDANTS, FILMS INDEPENDANTS, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, SPORT, TRAILERS, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, TITRE POUR TRAILER, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, DRAMATIQUE, PASSIONNÉ, PASSIONNE, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, DETERMINE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, IMPLACABLE, FORT, FORT, EVOLUTIF, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, PIÉTINEMENT, PIETINEMENT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT, ELEGANT, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, BATTERIE, BOITE À RYTHMES, BATTERIE ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, FUTURISTE, PERIODE, SPORT, ACTION, TRAILER Cordes époustouflantes, beats électroniques et sound design éclatants se développent constamment, avec émotion et dynamisme, jusqu'à la fin. womg 022a tk003 stephen dean hilton sandpaper womg 022a this is sport 2 west one music group sport film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral orchestral hybrid film score orchestral panoramic rock indie sound elements atmospheres sound design main movies action drama movies indie films movies urban drama sports trailers tv radio sports trailer track dramatic stunning strings stomping electronic beats and sound design constantly building in emotion and drive to the end. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
    <item id="1456" name="Man of Steel Platinum Mix" code="FEM 006 tk003" libraryid="2" albumid="37" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_006_Man_of_Steel_-_Remixed_EP/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Troels Brun Folmann" comment="Un morceau épique de bande-annonce avec un thème colossal et des chœurs." styleid="2" lengthseconds="93" time="1:33" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_006_Man_of_Steel_-_Remixed_EP/FEM006_trk003_MAN_OF_STEEL_PLATINUM_MIX_Troels_Brun_Folmann_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, DUBSTEP, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, GUERRE, MILITAIRE, HISTORIQUE, ANCIEN, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, BACK END, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, AGRESSIF, DRAMATIQUE, DANGEUREUX, EFFRAYANT, MENAÇANT, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, ÉPIQUE, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EVOLUTIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, CHOEUR, VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, TEXTURE VOCALE, PÉRIODE, CIVILISATIONS ANCIENNES, ROME ANTIQUE (500 AV. J-C - 476 AP. J-C), PERIODE, SERIEUX, MENACANT, DETERMINE, EPIQUE, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Un morceau épique de bande-annonce avec un thème colossal et des chœurs. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede fem 006 tk003 troels brun folmann man of steel platinum mix fem 006 man of steel - remixed ep fired earth music trailer children club electronica dubstep film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic main activities settings war military historical ancient movies action adventure movies back end movies epic movies fantasy adventure trailers trailer track disturbing tense epic trailer music cue with colossal theme and choir. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
    <item id="21120" name="Shattered and Battered" code="WOM 251A tk007" libraryid="6" albumid="452" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_251A_Breakbeat_Deluxe/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Russell Mcnamara" comment="Des breaks trash et fracassants avec des samples jazzy et des sons atmosphériques sombres." styleid="1" lengthseconds="256" time="4:16" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_251A_Breakbeat_Deluxe/WOM251A_trk007_SHATTERED_AND_BATTERED_Russell_Mcnamara_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, MÉLODRAMATIQUE, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, DONNE LA CHAIR DE POULE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE,, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), MELODRAMATIQUE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE Des breaks trash et fracassants avec des samples jazzy et des sons atmosphériques sombres. wom 251a tk007 russell mcnamara shattered and battered wom 251a breakbeat deluxe west one music dance electro club electronica breakbeat main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) film score orchestral trailer funny comedic funny melodramatic disturbing dark disturbing spooky movies crime detective mystery movies espionage spy tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle trashy smashed-up breaks with jazzy samples and dark atmospherics. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="17848" name="The Championship" code="WOM 180A tk028" libraryid="6" albumid="376" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_180A_Livewire_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Lewis (Gb 3) (PRS)" comment="La course pour le prix commence !" styleid="1" lengthseconds="62" time="1:02" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_180A_Livewire_2/WOM_180A_trk028_THE_CHAMPIONSHIP_Richard_Lewis_(Gb_3)_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="28" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, AMBIENT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTROCLASH, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, GROOVES, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, SPORT, TV, RADIO, JEU, QUIZZ, SPECTACLE DE VARIÉTÉS, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TROUBLANT, TENDU, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, TENDRE, SONGEUR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, EVOLUTIF, COOL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, RALENTI, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ÉLECTRONIQUE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, AIR CONNU, ELEMENTS SONORES, ELECTRONIQUE, PERIODE, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEFILE DE MODE, ANNEES 2000, DEFILE, ANNEES 20, ELEMENTS, SPECTACLE DE VARIETES, ETE, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION La course pour le prix commence ! cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 180a tk028 richard lewis (gb 3) (prs) the championship wom 180a livewire 2 west one music dance electro sports football extreme sports promos youth streets olympics the race for the prize is on. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="278" name="Underpass (b)" code="EDS 005 tk015" libraryid="1" albumid="8" albumartpath="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_005_Nu_Skool_Breaks/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Gresby Race Nash" comment="Des breaks old school, des synthés colossaux et une ligne de basse grondante." styleid="1" lengthseconds="189" time="3:09" samplefile="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_005_Nu_Skool_Breaks/EDS005_trk015_UNDERPASS_(B)_Gresby_Race_Nash_Electronic_Dance_Series.mp3" track="15" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKS NU SCHOOL, POP, UNDERSCORE, SPORT, EXERCICE, FITNESS, SPORT, SPORTS EXTREMES, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, FORT, FORT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COURANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), VOCAL, MASCULIN, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETERMINE, ENERGIQUE, ANNEES 2000, ANNEES 20 Des breaks old school, des synthés colossaux et une ligne de basse grondante. eds 005 tk015 gresby race nash underpass (b) eds 005 nu skool breaks electronic dance series dance electro club electronica club electronica breakbeat club electronica nu school breaks pop underscore sports exercise fitness sports extreme sports tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio sports strong confident strong determined strong energetic strong strong old-skool breaks huge synths and a growling bassline. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="Electronic Dance Series" cae="00666407133"/>
    <item id="21260" name="Boom and Blast (a)" code="WOM 254A tk002" libraryid="6" albumid="456" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_254A_Supercharger_-_Indie/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Tyler Van Den Berg" comment="Explosif, implacable et entraînant." styleid="34" lengthseconds="118" time="1:58" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_254A_Supercharger_-_Indie/WOM254A_trk002_BOOM_AND_BLAST_(A)_Tyler_Van_Den_Berg_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, INDIE, ROCK, PRINCIPAL, SPORT, SPORTS EXTREMES, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, FORT, EXCITANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 90, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ANNEES 2000, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 20, ANNEES 90 Explosif, implacable et entraînant. wom 254a tk002 tyler van den berg boom and blast (a) wom 254a supercharger - indie west one music indie rock indie rock main sports extreme sports tv radio children youth tv tv radio sports strong exciting movement rhythmic driving movement rhythmic rugged tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) time period modern era 2000s time period modern era 20th century 1990s explosive hard-hitting and catchy. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="25195" name="Hey Yeah (b)" code="WOM 336A tk024" libraryid="6" albumid="541" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_336A_Supercharger_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jay Price" comment="Une intro au développement lent se heurte à 0:26 à un chorus épique et euphorique." styleid="34" lengthseconds="113" time="1:53" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_336A_Supercharger_2/WOM_336A_trk024_HEY_YEAH_(B)_Jay_Price_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="24" tracktotal="" search="TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, ROCK, GROUPE DE ROCK, ALTERNATIF, ROCK, INDIE, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, ROAD TRIP, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TELE REALITE Une intro au développement lent se heurte à 0:26 à un chorus épique et euphorique. wom 336a tk024 jay price hey yeah (b) wom 336a supercharger 2 west one music indie rock rock band alternate rock indie strong confident strong strong uplifting inspirational uplifting motivational uplifting positive uplifting uplifting movement rhythmic driving activities settings road trip tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden tv slowly building intro hits epic euphoric chorus at 0:26. no vocal" waveformpath="" version="No Vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="799" name="Infinite, Immortal (a)" code="FEM 014 tk003" libraryid="2" albumid="25" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_014_Heroes/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Mark John Petrie" comment="Ouverture à suspense, couveuse et pleine d'anticipation avec un thème de corde cahin-caha à partir de 00:48 se transforme en une piste héroïque toute puissante avec une fin magistrale accompagnée d'un synthé et un chœur d'hommes." styleid="2" lengthseconds="151" time="2:31" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_014_Heroes/FEM014_trk003_INFINITE,_IMMORTAL_(A)_Mark_John_Petrie_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, BACK END, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, SCIENCE FICTION, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, TENDU, FORT, ÉPIQUE, FORT, HÉROIQUE, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, FORT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, DÉFILÉ, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, PERIODE, EPIQUE, HEROIQUE, 20E SIECLE, DEFILE Ouverture à suspense, couveuse et pleine d'anticipation avec un thème de corde cahin-caha à partir de 00:48 se transforme en une piste héroïque toute puissante avec une fin magistrale accompagnée d'un synthé et un chœur d'hommes. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede fem 014 tk003 mark john petrie infinite immortal (a) fem 014 heroes fired earth music trailer film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic main movies action adventure movies back end movies epic movies science fiction trailers trailer track disturbing tense strong epic strong heroic strong powerful strong strong movement rhythmic driving brooding thriller opening full of anticipation with chugging string theme from 00:48 evolves into an almighty heroic epic at 01:08 with huge backend featuring synth and male choir. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
    <item id="117" name="Tidal Wave" code="EDS 008 tk010" libraryid="1" albumid="4" albumartpath="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_008_Extreme_Dubstep/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Samuel Rupert Cole Sutton / Alexander David Bachell" comment="Cette intro avec un ligne de synthé répetitive et nappe chaude évolue en une gigantesque ligne de basse." styleid="1" lengthseconds="173" time="2:53" samplefile="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_008_Extreme_Dubstep/EDS_008_trk010_TIDAL_WAVE_Samuel_Rupert_Cole_Sutton_Alexander_David_Bachell_Electronic_Dance_Series.mp3" track="10" tracktotal="" search="TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, DUBSTEP, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, HOLLYWOOD, SPORT, SPORTS EXTREMES, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, PUISSANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, NERVEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INDUSTRIE, MACHINES, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, ÉLECTRONIQUE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, ELECTRONIQUE, PERIODE, ANNEES 2000, ANNEES 20 Cette intro avec un ligne de synthé répetitive et nappe chaude évolue en une gigantesque ligne de basse. eds 008 tk010 samuel rupert cole sutton alexander david bachell tidal wave eds 008 extreme dubstep electronic dance series dance electro club electronica dubstep club electronica club electronica main activities settings city urban human environment activities settings showbiz hollywood sports extreme sports tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio sports strong confident strong exciting strong repetitive synth hook and warm pad intro evolves to a mammoth bassline drop. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Electronic Dance Series" cae="00666407133"/>
    <item id="22358" name="Starting Gun (a)" code="WOM 278 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="480" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_278_Drums_Rule_the_World/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Emre Ramazanoglu / Geoffrey James Pidcock Holroyde" comment="La partie peut commencer ! Des percussions épiques de bande-annonce et des immenses accords de rock power." styleid="22" lengthseconds="143" time="2:23" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_278_Drums_Rule_the_World/WOM278_trk001_STARTING_GUN_(A)_Emre_Ramazanoglu_Geoffrey_James_Pidcock_Holroyde_West_One_Music_Limi.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, SPORT, SPORTS EXTREMES, TV, RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TV, RADIO, SPORT, FORT, ÉPIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, POURSUITE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COURANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BATTERIE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), EPIQUE, TELE REALITE La partie peut commencer ! Des percussions épiques de bande-annonce et des immenses accords de rock power. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede wom 278 tk001 emre ramazanoglu geoffrey james pidcock holroyde starting gun (a) wom 278 drums rule the world west one music sport film score orchestral trailer main movies action drama movies epic sports extreme sports tv radio reality tv tv radio sports strong epic movement rhythmic chase movement rhythmic driving movement rhythmic rugged movement rhythmic running tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) let the games begin! epic trailer-style percussion and big rock power chords. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="21122" name="Highway Child" code="WOM 251A tk009" libraryid="6" albumid="452" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_251A_Breakbeat_Deluxe/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Patrick Robert Murdoch / David Edward Bloor" comment="Route dégagée et ciel azuré, un mix parfait de guitares rock et de beats trash." styleid="1" lengthseconds="171" time="2:51" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_251A_Breakbeat_Deluxe/WOM251A_trk009_HIGHWAY_CHILD_Patrick_Robert_Murdoch_David_Edward_Bloor_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, PUISSANCE, ÉNERGIE, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, PUISSANCE, ÉNERGIE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FORMATION, INFORMATION, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ROAD MOVIE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, INDUSTRIE LOURDE, SPORT, EXERCICE, FITNESS, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, CAFARD, FORT, PUISSANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, RÉPÉTITIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, AMERIQUE DU NORD, ETATS-UNIS, DEPRIMANT, REPETITIF, ENERGIE Route dégagée et ciel azuré, un mix parfait de guitares rock et de beats trash. wom 251a tk009 patrick robert murdoch david edward bloor highway child wom 251a breakbeat deluxe west one music dance electro business corporate power energy club electronica breakbeat business corporate power energy business corporate training information film score orchestral trailer main movies road movie science technology industry heavy industry sports exercise fitness tv radio children open roads and clear blue skies a perfect mix of rock guitars and trashy beats. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="1387" name="This is a Warning Sign (a)" code="FEM 015 tk009" libraryid="2" albumid="35" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_015_Zeitgeist/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Stephen Dean Hilton" comment="Un rythme de dance entrainant accompagné d'iconiques vocal masculins, cordes, guitare et rythme. &quot;This is a warning sign. I'm coming between the lines. This is the word to wake the dead. I'm coming look out ahead.&quot; Retombée à 0:47 vers un énergique vocal &quot;Look out ahead!&quot; annoncant le chorus entrainant et le thème de cordes. Une intense scène d'hommes courants sous la pluie au milieu de la nuit." styleid="2" lengthseconds="130" time="2:10" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_015_Zeitgeist/FEM_015_trk009_THIS_IS_A_WARNING_SIGN_(A)_Stephen_Dean_Hilton_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BIG BEAT, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, ORCHESTRAL HYBRIDE , BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, POP, ROCK, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, FILMS INDÉPENDANTS, FILMS, ROAD MOVIE, TRAILERS, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TITRE POUR TRAILER, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, JAILLIR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COURANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CHOEUR, CHOEUR MASCULIN, VOCAL, MASCULIN, VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, VOIX TRAITÉES, MODIFIÉES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ENERGIQUE, FILMS INDEPENDANTS, VOIX TRAITEES, MODIFIEES Un rythme de dance entrainant accompagné d'iconiques vocal masculins, cordes, guitare et rythme. &quot;This is a warning sign. I'm coming between the lines. This is the word to wake the dead. I'm coming look out ahead.&quot; Retombée à 0:47 vers un énergique vocal &quot;Look out ahead!&quot; annoncant le chorus entrainant et le thème de cordes. Une intense scène d'hommes courants sous la pluie au milieu de la nuit. fem 015 tk009 stephen dean hilton this is a warning sign (a) fem 015 zeitgeist fired earth music trailer film score orchestral trailer club electronica big beat film score orchestral orchestral hybrid film score orchestral panoramic pop rock main movies human drama movies indie films movies road movie trailers tv radio sports trailer track strong energetic strong powerful driving dance beat featuring iconic male vocal strings guitar and beats. &quot;this is a warning sign. i'm coming between the lines. this is the word to wake the dead. i'm coming look out ahead.&quot; drop out at 0:47 into energetic &quot;look out ahead!&quot; vocal announcing the catchy male chorus and string theme. think heart-pounding night scene with men running in the rain. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
    <item id="20389" name="Future Perfect (a)" code="WOM 233 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="434" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_233_Atmospheric_Indie/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Matthew James Robertson / Mike Reed / Tom Howe" comment="Des tourbillons de piano et de célesta sur une envolée de guitares et de batterie." styleid="34" lengthseconds="142" time="2:22" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_233_Atmospheric_Indie/WOM233_trk001_FUTURE_PERFECT_(A)_Matthew_James_Robertson_Mike_Reed_Tom_Howe_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, ROCK, INDIE, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, SPORT, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, JAILLIR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EVOLUTIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), GROUPE DE ROCK, CLAVIER, CELESTE, REVELER, ELEMENTS, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Des tourbillons de piano et de célesta sur une envolée de guitares et de batterie. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 233 tk001 matthew james robertson mike reed tom howe future perfect (a) wom 233 atmospheric indie west one music indie business corporate reveal launch business corporate motivational rock indie main business corporate nature wildlife the elements land sun tropical seaside sports tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio sports strong confident strong prestigious uplifting swirls of piano and celeste over soaring guitars and drums. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="23441" name="Total Wipe Out (a)" code="WOM 302 tk007" libraryid="6" albumid="508" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_302_Adrenalizer/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jay Price" comment="Batterie punk tribale, guitares glam-rock à paillettes." styleid="6" lengthseconds="127" time="2:07" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_302_Adrenalizer/WOM302_trk007_TOTAL_WIPE_OUT_(A)_Jay_Price_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, ROCK ALTERNATIF, ROCK, ROCK ALTERNATIF, ROCK, INDIE, PRINCIPAL, SPORT, SPORTS EXTREMES, TV, RADIO, SPORT, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, FORT, IMPLACABLE, FORT, FORT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PERIODE, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), ENERGIQUE, ANNEES 2000, ANNEES 20 Batterie punk tribale, guitares glam-rock à paillettes. wom 302 tk007 jay price total wipe out (a) wom 302 adrenalizer west one music rock rock alternative rock rock alternative rock rock indie main sports extreme sports tv radio sports strong energetic strong relentless strong strong movement rhythmic driving movement rhythmic rugged tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) time period modern era 2000s tribal punk drums glitzy glam-rock guitars. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="16593" name="Pure (a)" code="WOM 154 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="349" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_154_Inspired/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jay Price" comment="Une intro légère paradisiaque et atmosphérique se développe en un refrain indé inspirant et chargé en énergie avec des cordes planantes." styleid="11" lengthseconds="211" time="3:31" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_154_Inspired/WOM154_trk001_PURE_(A)_Jay_Price_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, POP CORPORATE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, POP, POP ORCHESTRALE, POP, ROCK, INDIE, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SPORT, JEUX OLYMPIQUES, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, LÉGER, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, JAILLIR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EVOLUTIF, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), GROUPE DE ROCK, CORDES, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PERIODE, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETERMINE, LEGER, ANNEES 2000, REVELER, ANNEES 20, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Une intro légère paradisiaque et atmosphérique se développe en un refrain indé inspirant et chargé en énergie avec des cordes planantes. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 154 tk001 jay price pure (a) wom 154 inspired west one music corporate business business corporate bright optimistic business corporate corporate pop business corporate reveal launch pop orchestral pop pop rock indie main business corporate sports olympics tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio sports happy feel good happy happy serious heavenly and atmospheric light intro develops into high energy inspiring indie chorus with soaring strings. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="13776" name="Driven (a)" code="WOM 088 tk002" libraryid="6" albumid="278" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_088_Forensic_Beats/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Tord Jungsten" comment="Du rock indé britannique atmosphérique et rythmé." styleid="14" lengthseconds="161" time="2:41" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_088_Forensic_Beats/WOM088_trk002_DRIVEN_(A)_Tord_Jungsten_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, INDIE, POP, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, COMÉDIE ROMANTIQUE, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), GROUPE DE ROCK, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), COMEDIE, COMEDIE ROMANTIQUE Du rock indé britannique atmosphérique et rythmé. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 088 tk002 tord jungsten driven (a) wom 088 forensic beats west one music drama rock indie pop main movies human drama movies romantic comedy tv radio children youth tv tv radio tv drama uplifting uplifting tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) rock band atmospheric pacey british indie rock. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="25174" name="Bright Young Things (a)" code="WOM 336A tk003" libraryid="6" albumid="541" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_336A_Supercharger_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jay Price" comment="Indie enthousiaste et exaltante." styleid="34" lengthseconds="130" time="2:10" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_336A_Supercharger_2/WOM_336A_trk003_BRIGHT_YOUNG_THINGS_(A)_Jay_Price_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, ROCK, GROUPE DE ROCK, PRINCIPAL, POP, ROCK, INDIE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, ROAD TRIP, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, SANTÉ, BIEN-ÊTRE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, SANTE, BIEN-ETRE Indie enthousiaste et exaltante. wom 336a tk003 jay price bright young things (a) wom 336a supercharger 2 west one music indie rock rock band main pop rock indie happy feel good happy happy uplifting inspirational uplifting motivational uplifting positive uplifting uplifting movement rhythmic driving activities settings road trip tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden tv radio vibrant and uplifting indie. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="22125" name="Against the Odds (a)" code="WOM 273 tk002" libraryid="6" albumid="475" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_273_Inspiring_Anthems_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jay Price" comment="Des crescendos de piano et de guitare électrique basculent sur de la pop indé dynamisante et entraînante." styleid="11" lengthseconds="174" time="2:54" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_273_Inspiring_Anthems_2/WOM273_trk002_AGAINST_THE_ODDS_(A)_Jay_Price_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, EVOLUTIF, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, SPORT, JEUX OLYMPIQUES,, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETERMINE, REVELER, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Des crescendos de piano et de guitare électrique basculent sur de la pop indé dynamisante et entraînante. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 273 tk002 jay price against the odds (a) wom 273 inspiring anthems 2 west one music corporate business business corporate bright optimistic main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) business corporate motivational business corporate reveal launch strong prestigious uplifting motivational uplifting uplifting happy feel good tender hopeful serious determined movement rhythmic swells of piano and electric guitar break to motivating driving indie. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="25695" name="Supersonic Light (b)" code="WOM 345 tk019" libraryid="6" albumid="550" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_345_Electro_Indie_Alternative/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Philip Hochstrate" comment="Indie electro énergique. Un riff de synthétiseur inoubliable et des guitares classes se développent en d'euphoriques chorus." styleid="34" lengthseconds="173" time="2:53" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_345_Electro_Indie_Alternative/WOM_345_trk019_SUPERSONIC_LIGHT_(B)_Philip_Hochstrate_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="19" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, INDIE, ROCK, ROCK ALTERNATIF, UNDERSCORE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EMBLÉMATIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EVOLUTIF, COOL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INSISTANT, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, GROUPE DE ROCK, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, FORMATIONS GENERALES, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, DETERMINE, ENERGIQUE, EMBLEMATIQUE, ELECTRIQUE, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Indie electro énergique. Un riff de synthétiseur inoubliable et des guitares classes se développent en d'euphoriques chorus. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 345 tk019 philip hochstrate supersonic light (b) wom 345 electro indie alternative west one music indie rock indie rock alternative rock underscore activities settings city urban human environment tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio sports happy bright happy feel good strong confident strong energetic electro indie. a memorable synth riff and stylish guitars build to euphoric choruses. underscore" waveformpath="" version="Underscore" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="25552" name="The Battle Begins (a)" code="WOM 342 tk003" libraryid="6" albumid="547" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_342_Urban_Strings_&amp;_Beats/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Christopher J. Harvey, Rupert F. C. Garvey" comment="Ouverture avec un thème de cordes héroique, suivie de cordes énergiques et de beats agressifs." styleid="2" lengthseconds="131" time="2:11" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_342_Urban_Strings_&amp;_Beats/WOM_342_trk003_THE_BATTLE_BEGINS_(A)_Christopher_J._Harvey,_Rupert_F._C._Garvey_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, ORCHESTRAL HYBRIDE , CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, PRINCIPAL, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BIG BEAT, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, HIP HOP, URBAIN, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, SOUND DESIGN, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, DRAMATIQUE, PASSIONNÉ, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, FORT, COURAGEUX, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, FORT, ÉPIQUE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, HÉROIQUE, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, FORT, FORT, TRIOMPHAL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, JAILLIR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, EVOLUTIF, QUI A DU CRAN, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, SPORT, TV, RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TV, RADIO, SPORT, BATTERIE, BOITE À RYTHMES, BATTERIE ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELEMENTS SONORES, ELECTRONIQUE, SERIEUX, ATMOSPHERES, PASSIONNE, DETERMINE, ENERGIQUE, EPIQUE, HEROIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, TELE REALITE, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, ELEMENTS, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Ouverture avec un thème de cordes héroique, suivie de cordes énergiques et de beats agressifs. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede wom 342 tk003 christopher j. harvey rupert f. c. garvey the battle begins (a) wom 342 urban strings &amp; beats west one music trailer film score orchestral orchestral hybrid strings string section main club electronica big beat film score orchestral trailer hip hop urban sound elements atmospheres sound design dramatic intense dramatic passionate serious determined serious serious strong courageous strong heroic opening string theme into energetic strings and aggressive beats. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="22132" name="Road to Joy" code="WOM 273 tk009" libraryid="6" albumid="475" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_273_Inspiring_Anthems_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jay Price" comment="Des guitares nerveuses et des cordes imposantes avec une batterie entraînante." styleid="11" lengthseconds="158" time="2:38" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_273_Inspiring_Anthems_2/WOM273_trk009_ROAD_TO_JOY_Jay_Price_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, POP CORPORATE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, EVOLUTIF, NERVEUX, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, SPORT,, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETERMINE, REVELER, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Des guitares nerveuses et des cordes imposantes avec une batterie entraînante. wom 273 tk009 jay price road to joy wom 273 inspiring anthems 2 west one music corporate business business corporate bright optimistic main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) business corporate corporate pop business corporate reveal launch strong prestigious uplifting uplifting happy feel good tender hopeful serious determined movement rhythmic driving building edgy edgy guitars and stately strings with driving drums. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="20687" name="This Is My Year (a)" code="WOM 240 tk007" libraryid="6" albumid="441" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_240_Hip_Hop_USA/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jerome Henry Spence / Sylvester Maurice Manning / Rudy Michael Jr. Covington / Felisha Aileen Booker / Ronald Agee" comment="Un piano qui claque, des riffs de guitare, et des vocales par un rappeur acharné et fougueux." styleid="28" lengthseconds="184" time="3:04" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_240_Hip_Hop_USA/WOM240_trk007_THIS_IS_MY_YEAR_(A)_Jerome_Henry_Spence_Sylvester_Maurice_Manning_Rudy_Michael_Jr._Covington_F.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), HIP HOP, URBAIN, HIP HOP, HIP HOP, URBAIN, RAP, FORT, IMPLACABLE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, HOLLYWOOD, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, VOCAL, Un piano qui claque, des riffs de guitare, et des vocales par un rappeur acharné et fougueux. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 240 tk007 jerome henry spence sylvester maurice manning rudy michael jr. covington felisha aileen booker ronald agee this is my year (a) wom 240 hip hop usa west one music hip-hop urban club electronica main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) hip hop urban hip hop hip hop urban rap strong relentless activities settings showbiz hollywood tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style vocals slamming piano and guitar riffs and relentless gutsy male rap vocals. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="14239" name="Imagination" code="WOM 099 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="289" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_099_Organica/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Olivier Foubert" comment="Art rock anthémique et émouvant." styleid="26" lengthseconds="229" time="3:49" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_099_Organica/WOM099_trk001_IMAGINATION_Olivier_Foubert_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="FOLK CONTEMPORAINE, FOLK ROCK, FOLK CONTEMPORAINE, ACOUSTIQUE NOUVELLE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, IDYLLE, FILMS, COMÉDIE ROMANTIQUE, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EMBLÉMATIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), GROUPE DE ROCK, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), COMEDIE, COMEDIE ROMANTIQUE, ANNEES 2000, EMBLEMATIQUE, ANNEES 20 Art rock anthémique et émouvant. wom 099 tk001 olivier foubert imagination wom 099 organica west one music nature wildlife contemporary folk folk rock contemporary folk new acoustic main movies human drama movies romance movies romantic comedy tv radio tv drama uplifting anthemic uplifting euphoric tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) rock band time period modern era 2000s anthemic and emotive art rock. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="21181" name="Blaze of Glory (a)" code="WOM 252 tk004" libraryid="6" albumid="454" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_252_Indie_Folk/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Charlie Taylor / Jake Jarvis" comment="Enthousiasmant et épique. Des couplets punchy basculent vers des refrains puissants et euphorisants." styleid="23" lengthseconds="170" time="2:50" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_252_Indie_Folk/WOM252_trk004_BLAZE_OF_GLORY_(A)_Charlie_Taylor_Jake_Jarvis_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), FOLK CONTEMPORAINE, COUNTRY, WESTERN, FOLK ETHNIQUE TRADITIONNEL, FOLK AMÉRICAIN TRADITIONNEL, ETHNIQUE, FORT, ÉPIQUE, FORT, PUISSANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, CORDES, BANJO, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN NYLON, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN MÉTAL,, AMERIQUE DU NORD, FOLK AMERICAIN TRADITIONNEL, ETATS-UNIS, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), EPIQUE, CORDES EN METAL Enthousiasmant et épique. Des couplets punchy basculent vers des refrains puissants et euphorisants. wom 252 tk004 charlie taylor jake jarvis blaze of glory (a) wom 252 indie folk west one music country folk children north america usa main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) contemporary folk country western traditional ethnic folk traditional american folk ethnic strong epic strong powerful uplifting uplifting happy feel good movies epic tv radio leisure lifestyle travel strings rousing and epic. punchy verses break to powerful uplifting choruses. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="21985" name="My World (b)" code="WOM 269 tk022" libraryid="6" albumid="471" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_269_Hitlist/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Tyler Van Den Berg / Kevin Ronnie Mcpherson" comment="De la pop R&amp;B euphorisante et inspirante." styleid="7" lengthseconds="166" time="2:46" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_269_Hitlist/WOM269_trk022_MY_WORLD_(B)_Tyler_Van_Den_Berg_Kevin_Ronnie_Mcpherson_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="22" tracktotal="" search="FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, R &amp; B CLASSIQUE, POP, R&amp;B CONTEMPORAIN, POP, UNDERSCORE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEFILE DE MODE, DEFILE De la pop R&amp;B euphorisante et inspirante. wom 269 tk022 tyler van den berg kevin ronnie mcpherson my world (b) wom 269 hitlist west one music pop funk soul r&amp;b funk soul r&amp;b classic r&amp;b pop contemporary r&amp;b pop underscore activities settings fashion show tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style uplifting uplifting tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) uplifting and inspiring r&amp;b pop. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="22124" name="Silver Morning (a)" code="WOM 273 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="475" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_273_Inspiring_Anthems_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jay Price" comment="Glorieux, euphorisant et anthémique. Avec des cuivres et des envolées de cordes." styleid="11" lengthseconds="178" time="2:58" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_273_Inspiring_Anthems_2/WOM273_trk001_SILVER_MORNING_(A)_Jay_Price_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, PRESTIGE , BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, POP, POP ORCHESTRALE, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, DOCUMENTAIRE, SPORT, JEUX OLYMPIQUES, TV, RADIO, SPORT, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EMBLÉMATIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, JAILLIR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EVOLUTIF, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), SERIEUX, DETERMINE, EMBLEMATIQUE, REVELER, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Glorieux, euphorisant et anthémique. Avec des cuivres et des envolées de cordes. wom 273 tk001 jay price silver morning (a) wom 273 inspiring anthems 2 west one music corporate business business corporate bright optimistic business corporate motivational business corporate prestige business corporate reveal launch pop orchestral pop main business corporate documentary sports olympics tv radio sports happy feel good serious determined strong prestigious glorious uplifting and anthemic. featuring brass and soaring strings. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="166" name="Keep on Running (b)" code="EDS 009 tk017" libraryid="1" albumid="5" albumartpath="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_009_Dance-Punk_Electro/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Samuel Rupert Cole Sutton / Alexander David Bachell" comment="Mélange breakbeat énergetique avec une croustillante ligne de guitare, une basse grognante et un vocal masculin." styleid="1" lengthseconds="187" time="3:07" samplefile="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_009_Dance-Punk_Electro/EDS_009_trk017_KEEP_ON_RUNNING_(B)_Samuel_Rupert_Cole_Sutton_Alexander_David_Bachell_Electronic_Dance_Series.mp3" track="17" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CHEMICAL BEATS, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRO, UNDERSCORE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, SPORT, EXERCICE, FITNESS, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ENERGIQUE, DEFILE DE MODE, DEFILE Mélange breakbeat énergetique avec une croustillante ligne de guitare, une basse grognante et un vocal masculin. eds 009 tk017 samuel rupert cole sutton alexander david bachell keep on running (b) eds 009 dance-punk electro electronic dance series dance electro club electronica breakbeat club electronica chemical beats club electronica electro underscore activities settings fashion show sports exercise fitness tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio sports strong energetic tempo energetic breakbeat mash-up with crunchy guitar hook and growling live bass. without vocal knees up, mess piano, cockney, east london, singalong, pub joanna, piano bar, piano-bar, live" waveformpath="" version="Without vocal" publisher="Electronic Dance Series" cae="00666407133"/>
    <item id="25697" name="Feel My Heartbeat (b)" code="WOM 345 tk021" libraryid="6" albumid="550" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_345_Electro_Indie_Alternative/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Philip Hochstrate" comment="Indie intense, vive et positive avec des synthétiseurs légers et des beats massifs." styleid="34" lengthseconds="152" time="2:32" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_345_Electro_Indie_Alternative/WOM_345_trk021_FEEL_MY_HEARTBEAT_(B)_Philip_Hochstrate_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="21" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, INDIE, POP, ELECTRO POP, UNDERSCORE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, HEUREUX, FESTIF, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EMBLÉMATIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, COOL, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, GROUPE DE ROCK, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, FORMATIONS GENERALES, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, DETERMINE, EMBLEMATIQUE, TELE REALITE, ELECTRIQUE Indie intense, vive et positive avec des synthétiseurs légers et des beats massifs. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 345 tk021 philip hochstrate feel my heartbeat (b) wom 345 electro indie alternative west one music indie rock indie pop electro pop underscore activities settings city urban human environment tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio reality tv happy celebratory happy feel good strong determined strong big bold positive indie with bright synths and solid beats. underscore" waveformpath="" version="Underscore" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="25172" name="We Won’t Break (a)" code="WOM 336A tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="541" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_336A_Supercharger_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Tyler Van Den Berg / Kevin Ronnie Mcpherson" comment="Indie emblématique, épique et exaltante." styleid="34" lengthseconds="121" time="2:01" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_336A_Supercharger_2/WOM_336A_trk001_WE_WONT_BREAK_(A)_Tyler_Van_Den_Berg_Kevin_Ronnie_Mcpherson_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, ROCK, GROUPE DE ROCK, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, PRESTIGE , ROCK, INDIE, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, JAILLIR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, ROAD TRIP, SPORT, JEUX OLYMPIQUES, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TELE REALITE Indie emblématique, épique et exaltante. wom 336a tk001 tyler van den berg kevin ronnie mcpherson we won’t break (a) wom 336a supercharger 2 west one music indie rock rock band main business corporate prestige rock indie strong confident strong exciting strong strong uplifting inspirational uplifting motivational uplifting positive uplifting soaring uplifting uplifting movement rhythmic driving activities settings road trip an epic and uplifting indie anthem. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
  </items>
</librarycollection>
