<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<librarycollection>
  <items>
    <item id="26540" name="Life Sanctuary (a)" code="WOM 335 tk007" libraryid="6" albumid="569" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_335_Inspiring_Minimalism/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Diana Yukawa" comment="Paysage sonore épars, atmosphérique et futuriste qui évolue en de somptueuses, fluides lignes de cordes." styleid="4" lengthseconds="152" time="2:32" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_335_Inspiring_Minimalism/WOM_335_trk007_LIFE_SANCTUARY_(A)_Diana_Yukawa_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, PRINCIPAL, CLASSIQUE, STYLE MINIMALISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, PRESTIGE , BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, SOUND DESIGN, TENDRE, GRACIEUX, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, GENTIL, TENDRE, AFFECTUEUX, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, MONTÉE, BEAU, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, DIVIN, MONTÉE, ASCENDANT, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, DIVIN, CÉLESTE, CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, VIOLON, ELEMENTS SONORES, MONTEE, ATMOSPHERES, AERIEN, ELEGANT, ELEMENTS, CELESTE Paysage sonore épars, atmosphérique et futuriste qui évolue en de somptueuses, fluides lignes de cordes. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 335 tk007 diana yukawa life sanctuary (a) wom 335 inspiring minimalism west one music film score orchestral film score orchestral documentary strings string section main classical minimalist style business corporate luxury business corporate prestige film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic sound elements atmospheres sound elements atmospheres sound design sparse futuristic and atmospheric soundscape evolving into luxurious flowing string lines. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="5853" name="Pieces of Pleasure (a)" code="TSH 057 tk002" libraryid="5" albumid="142" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_057_Cafe_Culture/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Edward Jay / Fiona Ruth Barrow" comment="Swing doux et facile pour guitare, trompette, viola et accordéon." styleid="18" lengthseconds="136" time="2:16" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_057_Cafe_Culture/TSH_057_trk002_PIECES_OF_PLEASURE_(A)_Edward_Jay_Fiona_Ruth_Barrow_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="JAZZ, HOT CLUB DE FRANCE, EUROPE, EUROPE DE L'OUEST, FRANCE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 30, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 40, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), HEUREUX, HEUREUX, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, BAR, BAR À COCKTAILS, RESTAURANT, RESTAURANT, ETHNIQUE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, SOLEIL, CHALEUR, CUIVRES, TROMPETTE, CORNET, CORDES, VIOLE,, PERIODE, 20E SIECLE, BAR A COCKTAILS, ANNEES 30, ANNEES 40, ELEMENTS, METEO, ETE Swing doux et facile pour guitare, trompette, viola et accordéon. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 057 tk002 edward jay fiona ruth barrow pieces of pleasure (a) tsh 057 cafe culture the scoring house world jazz hot club of france europe western europe france time period modern era 20th century 1930s time period modern era 20th century 1940s main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) happy happy activities settings bar cocktail lounge restaurant restaurant ethnic tv radio leisure gentle easy swing for guitar trumpet viola and accordion. main delicate, gentle, soft dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="20206" name="Loving You (b)" code="WOM 231A tk009" libraryid="6" albumid="431" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_231A_Showtime/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Paul Reeves (Gb 2)" comment="Un swing léger avec un arrangement luxueux de cordes et un solo de piano." styleid="9" lengthseconds="155" time="2:35" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_231A_Showtime/WOM231A_trk009_LOVING_YOU_(B)_Paul_Reeves_(Gb_2)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="STYLES DE DANSE TRADITIONNEL, JAZZ, BIG BAND, JAZZ, SWING, ALTERNATIF, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, BAR, BAR À COCKTAILS, RESTAURANT, BAR À COCKTAILS, BAR , SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, LAS VEGAS, SPECTACLE LIVE, THÉÂTRE, COMÉDIE MUSICALE, BROADWAY, FILMS, COMÉDIE MUSICALE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, TENDRE, LÉGER, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CUIVRES, BIG BAND, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, DANSE DE SALON, BALADE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 50, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 60, STYLE VINTAGE, AMERIQUE DU NORD, PERIODE, ETATS-UNIS, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), LEGER, THEATRE, COMEDIE, COMEDIE MUSICALE, 20E SIECLE, BAR A COCKTAILS, ANNEES 50, ANNEES 60 Un swing léger avec un arrangement luxueux de cordes et un solo de piano. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 231a tk009 paul reeves (gb 2) loving you (b) wom 231a showtime west one music period vintage traditional dance styles jazz big band jazz swing alternate activities settings bar cocktail lounge restaurant cocktail lounge bar activities settings showbiz las vegas live entertainment theater musicals broadway movies musical tv radio talkshow entertainment tender light swing with lush string arrangement with piano solo. instrumental dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel knees up, mess piano, cockney, east london, singalong, pub joanna, piano bar, piano-bar, live" waveformpath="" version="Instrumental" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="2486" name="Lovers Waltz" code="RFM 021 tk004" libraryid="4" albumid="77" albumartpath="Music/Refuel Music/RFM_021_On_Screen_Nostalgia/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Franz Liszt / Robert Farnon" comment="Thème romantique et doux. Authentique enregistrement d'époque." styleid="8" lengthseconds="189" time="3:09" samplefile="Music/Refuel Music/RFM_021_On_Screen_Nostalgia/RFM021_trk004_LOVERS_WALTZ_Franz_Liszt_Robert_Farnon_Refuel_Music.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="STYLES DE DANSE TRADITIONNEL, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 50, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 60, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 70, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), EASY LISTENING, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, STYLE VINTAGE, ENREGISTREMENT D'ARCHIVE, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, DANSE DE SALON, VALSE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, ASCENSEUR, EN ATTENTE, MUSIQUE DE FOND POUR MAGASINS, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, FILMS, IDYLLE, TV, RADIO,, PERIODE, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 50, ANNEES 60, ANNEES 70 Thème romantique et doux. Authentique enregistrement d'époque. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz rfm 021 tk004 franz liszt robert farnon lovers waltz rfm 021 on screen nostalgia refuel music kitsch retro traditional dance styles time period modern era 20th century 1950s time period modern era 20th century 1960s time period modern era 20th century 1970s main tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) easy listening film score orchestral trailer vintage style archival recording flowing romantic theme. authentic period recording. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Refuel Music" cae="00617450359"/>
    <item id="8729" name="Taste of Love" code="TSH 080 tk020" libraryid="5" albumid="182" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_080_Guitarist_John_Williams/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="John Williams (PRS)" comment="Thème romantique persistant." styleid="13" lengthseconds="155" time="2:35" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_080_Guitarist_John_Williams/TSH_080_trk020_TASTE_OF_LOVE_John_Williams_(PRS)_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="20" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, ELEMENTS, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, ART, ANTIQUITÉS, ANTIQUITES, PAISIBLE, CALME, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, DÉTENDU, DETENDU, PAISIBLE, APAISANT, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TENDRE, TENDRE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, ACOUSTIQUE, BEAU, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ACOUSTIQUE, FORMATIONS GENERALES, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN NYLON, SOLO Thème romantique persistant. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz tsh 080 tk020 john williams (prs) taste of love tsh 080 guitarist john williams the scoring house acoustic film score orchestral pastoral classical classical styling film score orchestral documentary main documentary biographical historical the arts movies romance nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral tv radio leisure lifestyle arts antiques peaceful lingering romantic theme. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="615215382"/>
    <item id="7496" name="Love of a Lifetime (a)" code="TSH 074 tk014" libraryid="5" albumid="169" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_074_Symphonic_Sketchbook/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Arthur Rhodes" comment="Thème chaleureux et romantique." styleid="4" lengthseconds="171" time="2:51" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_074_Symphonic_Sketchbook/TSH_074_trk014_LOVE_OF_A_LIFETIME_(A)_Simon_Arthur_Rhodes_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="14" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, TRAILER, CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, FAMILIAL, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, PERIODE, PERIODES, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, ELEMENTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, ELEMENTS, PAISIBLE, CALME, PAISIBLE, LYRIQUE, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, SÉRIEUX, ÉMOUVANT, SERIEUX, EMOUVANT, SÉRIEUX, ATTENTIONNÉ, SERIEUX, ATTENTIONNE, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, MÉLODIQUE, LYRIQUE, MELODIQUE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT, ELEGANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, BOIS, HAUTBOIS, HAUTBOIS, COR ANGLAIS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL Thème chaleureux et romantique. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz tsh 074 tk014 simon arthur rhodes love of a lifetime (a) tsh 074 symphonic sketchbook the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer classical classical styling film score orchestral panoramic film score orchestral pastoral main movies children storytelling movies family movies period historical costume drama movies romance nature wildlife the elements land landscapes warm romantic theme. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="5429" name="Golden Hearts" code="TSH 052 tk068" libraryid="5" albumid="137" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_052_The_Mighty_Wurlitzer/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Leonard George Rawle" comment="Trop-plein d'émotions sincères." styleid="17" lengthseconds="100" time="1:40" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_052_The_Mighty_Wurlitzer/TSH052_trk068_GOLDEN_HEARTS_Leonard_George_Rawle_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="68" tracktotal="" search="KITSCH, RETRO, CHEESY, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 30, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 40, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 50, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), KITSCH, RETRO, CHEESY, STYLE VINTAGE, DROLE, MANIÉRÉ, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, MÉLODRAMATIQUE, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, À L'EAU DE ROSE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, CLAVIER, WURLITZER,, PERIODE, A L'EAU DE ROSE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), MANIERE, MELODRAMATIQUE, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 30, ANNEES 40, ANNEES 50 Trop-plein d'émotions sincères. tsh 052 tk068 leonard george rawle golden hearts tsh 052 the mighty wurlitzer the scoring house comedy kitsch retro cheesy time period modern era 20th century 1930s time period modern era 20th century 1940s time period modern era 20th century 1950s main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) kitsch retro cheesy vintage style funny campy funny comedic funny melodramatic tender heartfelt schmaltz. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="2456" name="Remember When" code="RFM 018 tk010" libraryid="4" albumid="74" albumartpath="Music/Refuel Music/RFM_018_Mood_for_Love/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Tony Osborne (Gb 1)" comment="Une atmosphère détendue et rêveuse. Authentique enregistrement d'époque." styleid="8" lengthseconds="164" time="2:44" samplefile="Music/Refuel Music/RFM_018_Mood_for_Love/RFM018_trk010_REMEMBER_WHEN_Tony_Osborne_(Gb_1)_Refuel_Music.mp3" track="10" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 60, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 70, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), EASY LISTENING, STYLE VINTAGE, ENREGISTREMENT D'ARCHIVE, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, À L'EAU DE ROSE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, ASCENSEUR, EN ATTENTE, MUSIQUE DE FOND POUR MAGASINS, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, TV, RADIO, CLAVIER, PIANO,, PERIODE, A L'EAU DE ROSE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 60, ANNEES 70 Une atmosphère détendue et rêveuse. Authentique enregistrement d'époque. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live rfm 018 tk010 tony osborne (gb 1) remember when rfm 018 mood for love refuel music kitsch retro film score orchestral trailer time period modern era 20th century 1960s time period modern era 20th century 1970s main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) easy listening vintage style archival recording peaceful dreamy tender romantic schmaltzy activities settings elevator dreamy laid-back mood. authentic period recording. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Refuel Music" cae="00617450359"/>
    <item id="9827" name="Full Moon Waltz" code="WOM 009 tk007" libraryid="6" albumid="199" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_009_Wireless_(Archive)/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Bill Connor" comment="Un swing band velouté." styleid="9" lengthseconds="201" time="3:21" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_009_Wireless_(Archive)/WOM009_trk007_FULL_MOON_WALTZ_Bill_Connor_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, JAZZ, BIG BAND, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, FETE, HAUTE SOCIÉTÉ, FILMS, COMÉDIE, CONTEMPORAIN, FILMS, COMÉDIE ROMANTIQUE, PAISIBLE, SEREIN, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), CUIVRES, BIG BAND, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 20, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 30, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 40, STYLE VINTAGE, PERIODE, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), COMEDIE, COMEDIE ROMANTIQUE, 20E SIECLE, HAUTE SOCIETE, ANNEES 20, ANNEES 30, ANNEES 40, ETE Un swing band velouté. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 009 tk007 bill connor full moon waltz wom 009 wireless (archive) west one music period vintage film score orchestral trailer jazz big band main activities settings party upscale society movies comedy contemporary movies romantic comedy peaceful serene tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) brass big band time period modern era 20th century 1920s time period velvety swing band. main dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="585" name="Gowns and Glamour (a)" code="FEM 004 tk003" libraryid="2" albumid="18" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_004_Bellitas/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Robert Leslie Bennett" comment="Une valse entraînante et romantique. Un rêve de princesse." styleid="2" lengthseconds="91" time="1:31" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_004_Bellitas/FEM004_trk003_GOWNS_AND_GLAMOUR_(A)_Robert_Leslie_Bennett_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="CLASSIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, STYLES DE DANSE TRADITIONNEL, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, FILM NOIR, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, CINÉMA ITALIEN, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, DROLE, MÉLODRAMATIQUE, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, À L'EAU DE ROSE, FORT EN ÉMOTIONS, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), EUROPE, EUROPE DU SUD, ITALIE, DANSE DE SALON, VALSE, DANSE CLASSIQUE, VALSE, CLASSIQUE, STYLE VINTAGE, PERIODE, A L'EAU DE ROSE, FORT EN EMOTIONS, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), MELODRAMATIQUE, CINEMA ITALIEN, PERIODES Une valse entraînante et romantique. Un rêve de princesse. fem 004 tk003 robert leslie bennett gowns and glamour (a) fem 004 bellitas fired earth music trailer classical film score orchestral trailer traditional dance styles main movies film noir movies human drama movies italian cinema movies period historical costume drama trailers trailer track funny melodramatic peaceful contented tender hopeful tender nostalgic tender sweeping romantic waltz. princess' dream. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
    <item id="15913" name="Let's Dance Together ('Til Morning) (a)" code="WOM 140A tk010" libraryid="6" albumid="334" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_140A_Quirky_Vintage_A/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Paul Reeves (Gb 2)" comment="Une chanson romantique dans la tradition des années 30, avec une voix d'homme." styleid="8" lengthseconds="62" time="1:02" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_140A_Quirky_Vintage_A/WOM140A_trk010_LET'S_DANCE_TOGETHER_('TIL_MORNING)_(A)_Paul_Reeves_(Gb_2)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="10" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, JAZZ, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, SPECTACLE LIVE, THÉÂTRE, VAUDEVILLE, MUSIC HALL , FILMS, COMÉDIE, FILMS, GUERRE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, ART, ANTIQUITÉS, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ENSEMBLE DE JAZZ, GROUPE DE JAZZ, VOCAL, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 20, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 30, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 40, STYLE VINTAGE, FORMATIONS GENERALES, PERIODE, ESPIEGLE, DECALE, THEATRE, COMEDIE, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 20, ANNEES 30, ANNEES 40, ANTIQUITES Une chanson romantique dans la tradition des années 30, avec une voix d'homme. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 140a tk010 paul reeves (gb 2) let's dance together ('til morning) (a) wom 140a quirky vintage a west one music kitsch retro film score orchestral trailer jazz main activities settings showbiz live entertainment theater vaudeville music hall movies comedy movies war tv radio leisure lifestyle arts antiques funny comedic funny eccentric funny mischievous funny quirky tempo a song in the 1930s romantic tradition featuring male vocal. main dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel knees up, mess piano, cockney, east london, singalong, pub joanna, piano bar, piano-bar, live" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="7134" name="Romanza (a)" code="TSH 029 tk016" libraryid="5" albumid="164" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_029_Symphonic_Fantasia/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Arthur Rhodes" comment="Une ouverture intime vers un thème romantique de grande envergure." styleid="4" lengthseconds="229" time="3:49" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_029_Symphonic_Fantasia/TSH029_trk016_ROMANZA_(A)_Simon_Arthur_Rhodes_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="16" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, MUSIQUE DE CHAMBRE, ENSEMBLE CLASSIQUE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, DROLE, MÉLODRAMATIQUE, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, FORT EN ÉMOTIONS, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, DIVIN, CÉLESTE,, FORT EN EMOTIONS, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), MELODRAMATIQUE, DEPRIMANT, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, CELESTE Une ouverture intime vers un thème romantique de grande envergure. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede tsh 029 tk016 simon arthur rhodes romanza (a) tsh 029 symphonic fantasia the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer classical and semi classical chamber music classical ensemble main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) film score orchestral pastoral funny melodramatic peaceful dreamy peaceful peaceful tender intimate tender nostalgic tender romantic tender intimate opening to romantic sweeping theme and poignant end. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="25179" name="Daytona Run (a)" code="WOM 336A tk008" libraryid="6" albumid="541" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_336A_Supercharger_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Tristan Ivemy" comment="Une intro funky laisse la place à des chorus rock épiques. Énergique et intrépide." styleid="34" lengthseconds="190" time="3:10" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_336A_Supercharger_2/WOM_336A_trk008_DAYTONA_RUN_(A)_Tristan_Ivemy_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="8" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, GROUPE DE ROCK, PRINCIPAL, ROCK, INDIE, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, JAILLIR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, MACHO, ARROGANCE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, ROAD TRIP, SPORT, SPORTS EXTREMES, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TELE REALITE Une intro funky laisse la place à des chorus rock épiques. Énergique et intrépide. wom 336a tk008 tristan ivemy daytona run (a) wom 336a supercharger 2 west one music indie rock rock band main rock indie strong confident strong exciting strong strong uplifting inspirational uplifting motivational uplifting positive uplifting soaring uplifting uplifting movement rhythmic driving movement rhythmic rugged macho swagger activities settings funky intro breaks to epic rock choruses. energising and fearless. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="7384" name="Big Blue Sky (a)" code="TSH 059 tk004" libraryid="5" albumid="168" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_059_Orchestral_Fantasia/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Arthur Rhodes" comment="Panoramas chauds et dérivants." styleid="4" lengthseconds="266" time="4:26" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_059_Orchestral_Fantasia/TSH_059_trk004_BIG_BLUE_SKY_(A)_Simon_Arthur_Rhodes_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, PRINCIPAL, CLASSIQUE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN NYLON, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN MÉTAL,, PERIODE, 20E SIECLE, AERIEN, ELEGANT, ELEMENTS, CORDES EN METAL Panoramas chauds et dérivants. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 059 tk004 simon arthur rhodes big blue sky (a) tsh 059 orchestral fantasia the scoring house film score orchestral classical classical styling classical and semi classical symphony orchestra time period modern era 20th century main classical business corporate luxury film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic tender intimate tender nostalgic tender romantic tender warm warm drifting panoramas. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="23745" name="Walking the Ghost (b)" code="WOM 309 tk024" libraryid="6" albumid="514" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_309_Indie_Organica/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="John-Paul Jones" comment="Sensible et nostalgique. Motifs de guitare réverbérants accompagné d'un piano distant et de cordes simples." styleid="34" lengthseconds="124" time="2:04" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_309_Indie_Organica/WOM_309_trk024_WALKING_THE_GHOST_(B)_John-Paul_Jones_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="24" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, INDIE, ALTERNATIF, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, SOLEIL, CHALEUR, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, ABSTRAIT, SIMPLE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ELEMENTS, METEO, ETE Sensible et nostalgique. Motifs de guitare réverbérants accompagné d'un piano distant et de cordes simples. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 309 tk024 john-paul jones walking the ghost (b) wom 309 indie organica west one music indie rock indie alternate nature wildlife the elements land sun tropical seaside nature wildlife the elements weather sun heat tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio sports abstract simple tender warm tempo emotive and wistful. reverberant guitar patterns with distant piano and simple strings. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="6292" name="Life Journeys" code="TSH 065A tk024" libraryid="5" albumid="148" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_065A_The_Piano_Book/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Ostinati fluides, expressifs." styleid="25" lengthseconds="185" time="3:05" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_065A_The_Piano_Book/TSH065A_trk024_LIFE_JOURNEYS_Richard_Allen_Harvey_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="24" tracktotal="" search="CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIÈCLE, PRINCIPAL, ENFANTS, CONTES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, INNOCENT, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, BEAU, MÉLODIQUE, LYRIQUE, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, CLAVIER, PIANO, SOLO, MELODIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIECLE, DEPRIMANT, 20E SIECLE, ELEMENTS Ostinati fluides, expressifs. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 065a tk024 richard allen harvey life journeys tsh 065a the piano book the scoring house classical opera classical 20th century classical style main children storytelling film score orchestral documentary film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral pastoral peaceful peaceful sad depressing poignant sad depressing sad tender hopeful tender innocent tender intimate expressive flowing ostinati. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="23530" name="Turning the Tide (a)" code="WOM 305 tk008" libraryid="6" albumid="510" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_305_Inspiring_Indie/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Matthew James Robertson / Mike Reed / Tom Howe" comment="Une introduction menée au piano mène à un hymne indie qui ne cesse de grandir." styleid="34" lengthseconds="153" time="2:33" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_305_Inspiring_Indie/WOM_305_trk008_TURNING_THE_TIDE_(A)_Matthew_James_Robertson_Mike_Reed_Tom_Howe_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="8" tracktotal="" search="TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, ROCK, INDIE, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, RALENTI, EVOLUTIF, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, SPORT, JEUX OLYMPIQUES,, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), REVELER, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Une introduction menée au piano mène à un hymne indie qui ne cesse de grandir. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 305 tk008 matthew james robertson mike reed tom howe turning the tide (a) wom 305 inspiring indie west one music indie business corporate reveal launch main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) business corporate motivational business corporate reveal launch rock indie strong prestigious uplifting motivational movement smooth slow motion building business corporate tv radio sports sports piano-based introduction leads to ever-growing indie anthem. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="22447" name="The Afterlife" code="WOM 280 tk012" libraryid="6" albumid="482" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_280_Cinematic_Indie/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Timothy Stephen Pierce / Brett Carr Boyett" comment="Une introduction optimiste entame une progression épique à 2:18. Inspirant et cinématographique." styleid="34" lengthseconds="282" time="4:42" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_280_Cinematic_Indie/WOM280_trk012_THE_AFTERLIFE_Timothy_Stephen_Pierce_Brett_Carr_Boyett_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, ENFANTS, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), ROCK, ROCK ALTERNATIF, ROCK, INDIE, FORT, ÉPIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE,, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), EPIQUE Une introduction optimiste entame une progression épique à 2:18. Inspirant et cinématographique. wom 280 tk012 timothy stephen pierce brett carr boyett the afterlife wom 280 cinematic indie west one music indie children main tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) rock alternative rock rock indie strong epic uplifting optimistic movies epic tv radio children youth tv optimistic introduction starts epic build at 2:18. inspiring and cinematic. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="26024" name="Into the Last Light (a)" code="WOM 352 tk009" libraryid="6" albumid="557" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_352_Cinematic_Indie_Drama/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Dylan Parsons / Dan Cassady" comment="Une ouverture songeuse se métamorphose en humeur exaltée, avec un violoncelle plein d'espoir et une batterie paroxystique." styleid="14" lengthseconds="162" time="2:42" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_352_Cinematic_Indie_Drama/WOM_352_trk009_INTO_THE_LAST_LIGHT_(A)_Dylan_Parsons_Dan_Cassady_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, TRAILER, ROCK, POST ROCK, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, FILMS INDÉPENDANTS, FILMS INDEPENDANTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, ELEMENTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, DRAME TV, TROUBLANT, AGITÉ, AGITE, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, DOUX-AMER, DEPRIMANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, DEPRIMANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, DEPRIMANT, SÉRIEUX, ÉMOUVANT, SERIEUX, EMOUVANT, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, SERIEUX, SÉRIEUX, ATTENTIONNÉ, SERIEUX, ATTENTIONNE, FORT, MAJESTUEUX, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, IMPRESSIONANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, JAILLIR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, BEAU, EVOLUTIF, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION, MÉLODIQUE, LYRIQUE, MELODIQUE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, AERIEN, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, FORMATIONS GENERALES, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, ETHNIQUE, CITHARE, BATTERIE, BATTERIE, CLAVIER, CELESTE, CLAVIER, HARMONIUM, CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, BASSE, BASSE ÉLECTRIQUE, BASSE ELECTRIQUE, CORDES, VIOLONCELLE, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE Une ouverture songeuse se métamorphose en humeur exaltée, avec un violoncelle plein d'espoir et une batterie paroxystique. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 352 tk009 dylan parsons dan cassady into the last light (a) wom 352 cinematic indie drama west one music drama film score orchestral trailer rock post rock main movies human drama movies indie films nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife the elements sky aerial clouds tv radio tv drama disturbing restless disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense pensive opening transforms into an inspiring mood with hopeful cello and climactic drums. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="17300" name="Life's Great Adventure (a)" code="WOM 168 tk007" libraryid="6" albumid="363" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_168_Emotional_Ambience/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Dan Graham" comment="Une introduction atmosphérique, optimiste progresse doucement pour devenir un véritable morceau à 1:22, avec une batterie, un piano et des voix de femmes lointaines." styleid="12" lengthseconds="203" time="3:23" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_168_Emotional_Ambience/WOM168_trk007_LIFE'S_GREAT_ADVENTURE_(A)_Dan_Graham_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, BALADE, FILMS, IDYLLE,, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO) Une introduction atmosphérique, optimiste progresse doucement pour devenir un véritable morceau à 1:22, avec une batterie, un piano et des voix de femmes lointaines. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 168 tk007 dan graham life's great adventure (a) wom 168 emotional ambience west one music atmospheres film score orchestral trailer main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) film score orchestral trailer uplifting optimistic tender romantic ballad movies romance atmospheric optimistic introduction slowly builds into full track at 1:22 with drums piano and distant female vocals. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="2769" name="Pure Release (a)" code="TSH 002 tk021" libraryid="5" albumid="93" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_002_Evolutions/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Robert Henry Peter White" comment="Une ascension émouvante vers une fin triomphante." styleid="11" lengthseconds="129" time="2:09" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_002_Evolutions/TSH002_trk021_PURE_RELEASE_(A)_Robert_Henry_Peter_White_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="21" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, POP CORPORATE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, PRESTIGE , BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FORMATION, INFORMATION, EASY LISTENING, MIDDLE OF THE ROAD, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SPORT, JEUX OLYMPIQUES, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, SÉRIEUX, ÉMOUVANT, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, FORT, TRIOMPHAL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EVOLUTIF, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, RALENTI, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), SERIEUX, EMOUVANT, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Une ascension émouvante vers une fin triomphante. tsh 002 tk021 robert henry peter white pure release (a) tsh 002 evolutions the scoring house corporate business business corporate bright optimistic business corporate corporate pop business corporate motivational business corporate prestige business corporate training information easy listening middle of the road main business corporate sports olympics tv radio leisure lifestyle emotional ascent to triumphant end. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="25183" name="Divide and Conquer (a)" code="WOM 336A tk012" libraryid="6" albumid="541" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_336A_Supercharger_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Dean Saban" comment="Skate punk à fond les ballons avec énorme chorus à 1:02" styleid="34" lengthseconds="132" time="2:12" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_336A_Supercharger_2/WOM_336A_trk012_DIVIDE_AND_CONQUER_(A)_Dean_Saban_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, SKATE PUNK, GROUPE DE ROCK, PRINCIPAL, ROCK, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, MACHO, ARROGANCE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, ROAD TRIP, SPORT, SPORTS EXTREMES, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TELE REALITE Skate punk à fond les ballons avec énorme chorus à 1:02 wom 336a tk012 dean saban divide and conquer (a) wom 336a supercharger 2 west one music indie rock skate punk rock band main rock strong confident strong exciting strong strong uplifting inspirational uplifting motivational uplifting positive uplifting uplifting movement rhythmic driving movement rhythmic rugged macho swagger activities settings road trip sports full-tilt skate punk leading to huge chorus at 1:02. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="20397" name="Waves of Light (a)" code="WOM 233 tk009" libraryid="6" albumid="434" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_233_Atmospheric_Indie/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Matthew James Robertson / Mike Reed / Tom Howe" comment="Des atmosphères sonores riches et expansives avec des motifs de piano éblouissants. Progression dès 1:45." styleid="34" lengthseconds="209" time="3:29" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_233_Atmospheric_Indie/WOM233_trk009_WAVES_OF_LIGHT_(A)_Matthew_James_Robertson_Mike_Reed_Tom_Howe_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, ROCK, INDIE, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, MÉDICAL, SCIENCES DE LA VIE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, EVOLUTIF, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), SOUND DESIGN, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), AERIEN, ELEMENTS, MEDICAL, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Des atmosphères sonores riches et expansives avec des motifs de piano éblouissants. Progression dès 1:45. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 233 tk009 matthew james robertson mike reed tom howe waves of light (a) wom 233 atmospheric indie west one music indie business corporate science technology business corporate luxury rock indie main business corporate nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife science technology industry medical life science tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden tv radio leisure rich expansive soundscapes with stunning piano patterns. building from 1:45. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="25680" name="Walk Into the Light (a)" code="WOM 345 tk004" libraryid="6" albumid="550" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_345_Electro_Indie_Alternative/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Philip Hochstrate" comment="Electro indie expansive et éthérée, avec un chant féminin émouvant, de gros synthétiseurs et une batterie jouant un rythme de half time shuffle." styleid="34" lengthseconds="185" time="3:05" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_345_Electro_Indie_Alternative/WOM_345_trk004_WALK_INTO_THE_LIGHT_(A)_Philip_Hochstrate_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, INDIE, POP, ELECTRO POP, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, HEUREUX, FESTIF, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EMBLÉMATIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EVOLUTIF, COOL, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, GROUPE DE ROCK, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, VOCAL, FÉMININ, FÉMININ, FORMATIONS GENERALES, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, DETERMINE, FEMININ, EMBLEMATIQUE, ELECTRIQUE, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Electro indie expansive et éthérée, avec un chant féminin émouvant, de gros synthétiseurs et une batterie jouant un rythme de half time shuffle. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 345 tk004 philip hochstrate walk into the light (a) wom 345 electro indie alternative west one music indie rock indie pop electro pop main activities settings city urban human environment tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio sports happy celebratory happy feel good strong determined strong strong expansive and ethereal indie electro with big synths half time drums and emotive female vocals. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="3442" name="To Better Times" code="TSH 013 tk015" libraryid="5" albumid="103" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_013_It's_My_Life/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Ian Paul Livingstone" comment="Un thème émouvant et plein d'espoir menant graduellement à une fin heureuse." styleid="10" lengthseconds="158" time="2:38" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_013_It's_My_Life/TSH013_trk015_TO_BETTER_TIMES_Ian_Paul_Livingstone_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="15" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), STYLE VINTAGE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, SÉRIEUX, ÉMOUVANT, EVOLUTIF, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, FILMS, IDYLLE, TV, RADIO,, PERIODE, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, EMOUVANT, PERIODES, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Un thème émouvant et plein d'espoir menant graduellement à une fin heureuse. tsh 013 tk015 ian paul livingstone to better times tsh 013 it's my life the scoring house documentary film score orchestral trailer main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) vintage style uplifting positive tender hopeful tender intimate tender nostalgic tender reflective tender romantic tender sentimental sad depressing lonely sad depressing poignant sad depressing sad hopeful emotional theme gradually building to positive end. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="18029" name="Pure and Simple (a)" code="WOM 185 tk008" libraryid="6" albumid="381" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_185_Indie_Rock_&amp;_Pop_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jared Nathan Sweetman / Paul James Borg" comment="Une beauté maussade et chatoyante. Des couplets calmes et tendres basculent vers des refrains massifs et expansifs." styleid="6" lengthseconds="169" time="2:49" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_185_Indie_Rock_&amp;_Pop_2/WOM185_trk008_PURE_AND_SIMPLE_(A)_Jared_Nathan_Sweetman_Paul_James_Borg_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="8" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, PRESTIGE , BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, ROCK, INDIE, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SPORT, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, DOUX, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, TENDRE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EVOLUTIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UN TRAIN, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), BATTERIE, CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, BASSE, BASSE ÉLECTRIQUE, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN NYLON, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN MÉTAL, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, CORDES, VIOLON , PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PERIODE, SERIEUX, DETERMINE, DEFILE DE MODE, ANNEES 2000, DEFILE, ELECTRIQUE, BASSE ELECTRIQUE, REVELER, ANNEES 20, CORDES EN METAL, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Une beauté maussade et chatoyante. Des couplets calmes et tendres basculent vers des refrains massifs et expansifs. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 185 tk008 jared nathan sweetman paul james borg pure and simple (a) wom 185 indie rock &amp; pop 2 west one music rock business corporate business corporate motivational business corporate prestige business corporate reveal launch rock indie main activities settings fashion show business corporate sports tv radio children youth tv tv radio sports peaceful contented peaceful dreamy bleak shimmering beauty. quiet tender verses break to big expansive choruses. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="24401" name="Lovers’ Requiem (a)" code="WOM 322 tk005" libraryid="6" albumid="526" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_322_Cinematic_Drama/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Martin Tillmann" comment="Des lignes de piano à la beauté troublante entremelées avec des cordes enveloppantes, émouvantes." styleid="14" lengthseconds="151" time="2:31" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_322_Cinematic_Drama/WOM322_trk005_LOVERS_REQUIEM_(A)_Martin_Tillmann_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, MODERNE, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, DRAME FAMILIAL, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, DRAME HOSPITALIER, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, ANXIEUX, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, PASSIONNÉ, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, MÉLANCOLIE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, SÉRIEUX, INQUIET, SÉRIEUX, ÉMOUVANT, SÉRIEUX, SOLENNEL, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, CLAVIER, PIANO, FORMATIONS GENERALES, SERIEUX, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, PASSIONNE, DEPRIMANT, EMOUVANT, MELANCOLIE, ELEGANT Des lignes de piano à la beauté troublante entremelées avec des cordes enveloppantes, émouvantes. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 322 tk005 martin tillmann lovers’ requiem (a) wom 322 cinematic drama west one music drama film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral documentary main movies human drama movies modern tv radio tv drama family drama tv radio tv drama medical drama tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing anxious disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense hauntingly beautiful piano lines intertwined with rich emotive strings. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="20904" name="Stars Like Dust (a)" code="WOM 246 tk006" libraryid="6" albumid="447" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_246_Atmospheric_Guitar/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Dan Cassady" comment="Une introduction sombre et maussade se change en une beauté impressionnante à 1:52." styleid="12" lengthseconds="236" time="3:56" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_246_Atmospheric_Guitar/WOM246_trk006_STARS_LIKE_DUST_(A)_Dan_Cassady_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="6" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, PAISIBLE, DÉTENDU, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, ELEMENTS SONORES, AMERIQUE DU NORD, ATMOSPHERES, ETATS-UNIS, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETENDU, ELECTRIQUE, ELEMENTS Une introduction sombre et maussade se change en une beauté impressionnante à 1:52. wom 246 tk006 dan cassady stars like dust (a) wom 246 atmospheric guitar west one music atmospheres sound elements atmospheres main documentary nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama disturbing dark peaceful relaxed tender reflective tender sentimental tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) strings guitar electric north america usa dark and brooding introduction changes to awe-inspiring beauty at 1:52. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="21815" name="Respite (b)" code="WOM 264 tk026" libraryid="6" albumid="467" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_264_Emotive_Acoustic/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Alistair Bruce Henry Friend / Ted Brett Barnes" comment="Une guitare acoustique tendre et intime." styleid="13" lengthseconds="154" time="2:34" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_264_Emotive_Acoustic/WOM264_trk026_RESPITE_(B)_Alistair_Bruce_Henry_Friend_Ted_Brett_Barnes_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="26" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, ALTERNATIF, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, ÉTÉ, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, TENDRE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, ACOUSTIQUE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, MUSIQUE DE CHAMBRE, ENSEMBLE CLASSIQUE, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN NYLON, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN MÉTAL, CORDES, VIOLON, ELEMENTS, CORDES EN METAL, ETE Une guitare acoustique tendre et intime. wom 264 tk026 alistair bruce henry friend ted brett barnes respite (b) wom 264 emotive acoustic west one music acoustic film score orchestral pastoral alternate nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral nature wildlife the elements seasons time summer tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden peaceful contented peaceful dreamy tender intimate tender tender acoustic guitar and intimate. alternative" waveformpath="" version="Alternative" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="7893" name="The End of the Day (a)" code="TSH 004 tk028" libraryid="5" albumid="173" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_004_Natural_Wonders/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon David Chamberlain" comment="Un morceau de piano solitaire et introspectif qui se construit graduellement avec une tristesse sous-jacente." styleid="26" lengthseconds="182" time="3:02" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_004_Natural_Wonders/TSH004_trk028_THE_END_OF_THE_DAY_(A)_Simon_David_Chamberlain_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="28" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), DROLE, MÉLODRAMATIQUE, PAISIBLE, INTROSPECTIF, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, EVOLUTIF, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, DOCUMENTAIRE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, CLAVIER, PIANO,, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), MELODRAMATIQUE, DEPRIMANT, ELEMENTS, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Un morceau de piano solitaire et introspectif qui se construit graduellement avec une tristesse sous-jacente. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 004 tk028 simon david chamberlain the end of the day (a) tsh 004 natural wonders the scoring house nature wildlife children main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) funny melodramatic peaceful introspective peaceful peaceful tender nostalgic tender reflective tender romantic tender sentimental sad depressing lonely sad depressing poignant sad depressing sad building movies human drama solitary introspective piano gradually building with an undercurrent of sadness. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="591" name="Penance (a)" code="FEM 004 tk009" libraryid="2" albumid="18" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_004_Bellitas/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Robert Leslie Bennett" comment="Des cygnes sur le lac. La tristesse causée par un amour perdu." styleid="2" lengthseconds="116" time="1:56" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_004_Bellitas/FEM004_trk009_PENANCE_(A)_Robert_Leslie_Bennett_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ART ET ESSAI, FILMS, FILM NOIR, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, IDYLLE, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRAGIQUE, EFFRAYANT, MENAÇANT, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, À L'EAU DE ROSE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, BATTERIE, CLAVIER, PIANO, EUROPE, EUROPE DU SUD, ITALIE, EUROPE, EUROPE DE L'OUEST, FRANCE, STYLE VINTAGE, SERIEUX, A L'EAU DE ROSE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, MENACANT Des cygnes sur le lac. La tristesse causée par un amour perdu. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live fem 004 tk009 robert leslie bennett penance (a) fem 004 bellitas fired earth music trailer film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic main movies art house movies film noir movies human drama movies romance trailers trailer track disturbing mysterious sad depressing lonely sad depressing poignant sad depressing sad sad depressing tragic swans on the lake. sadness of lost love. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
    <item id="26303" name="The Last Farewell (a)" code="WOM 177 tk012" libraryid="6" albumid="563" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_177_Reflections/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Déchirant et tendre. Des cordes légères et fragiles soutiennent des mélodies chaleureuses de piano." styleid="4" lengthseconds="155" time="2:35" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_177_Reflections/WOM177_trk012_THE_LAST_FAREWELL_(A)_Richard_Allen_Harvey_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, MÉDICAL, SCIENCES DE LA VIE, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRAGIQUE, TENDRE, LÉGER, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TENDRE, TENDRE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, VIOLON, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, LEGER, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, MEDICAL Déchirant et tendre. Des cordes légères et fragiles soutiennent des mélodies chaleureuses de piano. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 177 tk012 richard allen harvey the last farewell (a) wom 177 reflections west one music film score orchestral business corporate beds business corporate science technology film score orchestral trailer main business corporate documentary movies human drama nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife science technology industry medical life science disturbing mysterious heart-rending and tender. light fragile strings support warm piano melodies. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="6271" name="Amour (a)" code="TSH 065A tk003" libraryid="5" albumid="148" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_065A_The_Piano_Book/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Thème plein de sensibilité et d'émotion." styleid="25" lengthseconds="162" time="2:42" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_065A_The_Piano_Book/TSH065A_trk003_AMOUR_(A)_Richard_Allen_Harvey_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIÈCLE, PÉRIODE, ÈRES CULTURELLES, PÉRIODE EDWARDIENNE (1901 - 1910), PÉRIODE, ÈRES CULTURELLES, PÉRIODE VICTORIENNE (1837 - 1901), PRINCIPAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, INNOCENT, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, BEAU, MÉLODIQUE, LYRIQUE, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, CLAVIER, PIANO, SOLO, PERIODE, MELODIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIECLE, ERES CULTURELLES, DEPRIMANT, PERIODE EDWARDIENNE (1901 - 1910), PERIODE VICTORIENNE (1837 - 1901), 20E SIECLE, ELEMENTS Thème plein de sensibilité et d'émotion. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 065a tk003 richard allen harvey amour (a) tsh 065a the piano book the scoring house classical opera classical 20th century classical style time period cultural eras edwardian period (1901 - 1910) time period cultural eras victorian period (1837 - 1901) main film score orchestral documentary film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral pastoral peaceful peaceful sad emotional tender-hearted theme. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="19552" name="Zuma (a)" code="WOM 216 tk011" libraryid="6" albumid="415" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_216_Catch_the_Sun/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Ian Mccutcheon" comment="Souvenirs de rêve d'un voyage sur la côte Ouest. Voix d'homme." styleid="6" lengthseconds="168" time="2:48" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_216_Catch_the_Sun/WOM216_trk011_ZUMA_(A)_Ian_Mccutcheon_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="11" tracktotal="" search="POP, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PAISIBLE, REVEUR, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, VOCAL, MASCULIN,, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO) Souvenirs de rêve d'un voyage sur la côte Ouest. Voix d'homme. wom 216 tk011 ian mccutcheon zuma (a) wom 216 catch the sun west one music rock pop main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) peaceful dreamy tv radio leisure lifestyle travel vocals male dreamy memories of a west coast road trip. male vocal. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="20402" name="Under the Stars (a)" code="WOM 233 tk014" libraryid="6" albumid="434" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_233_Atmospheric_Indie/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Matthew James Robertson / Mike Reed / Tom Howe" comment="Des atmosphères méditatives charmantes." styleid="34" lengthseconds="92" time="1:32" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_233_Atmospheric_Indie/WOM233_trk014_UNDER_THE_STARS_(A)_Matthew_James_Robertson_Mike_Reed_Tom_Howe_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="14" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, ROCK, INDIE, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, TENDRE, SONGEUR, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, DOCUMENTAIRE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, MÉDICAL, SCIENCES DE LA VIE,, ELEMENTS SONORES, PERIODE, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ANNEES 2000, AERIEN, ANNEES 20, ELEMENTS, MEDICAL Des atmosphères méditatives charmantes. wom 233 tk014 matthew james robertson mike reed tom howe under the stars (a) wom 233 atmospheric indie west one music indie business corporate science technology time period modern era 2000s main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) business corporate rock indie sound elements atmospheres tender reflective movement smooth aerial floating business corporate documentary nature wildlife the elements reflective engaging atmospheres. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="19169" name="Mercury Falls (a)" code="WOM 208 tk003" libraryid="6" albumid="406" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_208_Lost_Highways/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Patrick Robert Murdoch" comment="Nostalgique et mélancolique avec une batterie live réverbérante, des ondes généreuses de slide guitare et une guitare lead lyrique." styleid="6" lengthseconds="190" time="3:10" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_208_Lost_Highways/WOM208_trk003_MERCURY_FALLS_(A)_Patrick_Robert_Murdoch_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 70, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), COUNTRY, COUNTRY ROCK, EASY LISTENING, AOR, PAISIBLE, LYRIQUE, MÉLODIQUE, LYRIQUE, FILMS, ROAD MOVIE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, CORDES, GUITARE, BOTTLENECK, SLIDE, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE,, AMERIQUE DU NORD, PERIODE, MELODIQUE, ETATS-UNIS, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), 20E SIECLE, ELECTRIQUE, ANNEES 70 Nostalgique et mélancolique avec une batterie live réverbérante, des ondes généreuses de slide guitare et une guitare lead lyrique. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 208 tk003 patrick robert murdoch mercury falls (a) wom 208 lost highways west one music rock film score orchestral trailer north america usa time period modern era 20th century 1970s main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) country country rock easy listening aor peaceful lyrical melodic lyrical movies road movie tv radio leisure lifestyle travel strings guitar wistful and melancholic with reverberant live drums waves of rich slide guitar and lyrical lead guitar. main knees up, mess piano, cockney, east london, singalong, pub joanna, piano bar, piano-bar, live" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="17701" name="Abandon Me (a)" code="WOM 361 tk013" libraryid="6" albumid="373" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_361_Female_Indie_Pop/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Wayne Roberts (PRS)" comment="Sombre et poignant, avec cordes cinématiques, beats maussades, guitare ambient et chant féminin stupéfiant." styleid="34" lengthseconds="191" time="3:11" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_361_Female_Indie_Pop/WOM_361_trk013_ABANDON_ME_(A)_Wayne_Roberts_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="13" tracktotal="" search="POP, POP, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, TRIP HOP, POP, POP ORCHESTRALE, ROCK, INDIE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, CRIME, DƒTECTIVE, MYSTéRE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, FILMS, ƒPIQUE, EPIQUE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, FILMS INDƒPENDANTS, FILMS INDEPENDANTS, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, FILMS, GUERRE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, TENDU, TRISTE, DƒPRIMANT, DOUX-AMER, DEPRIMANT, TRISTE, DƒPRIMANT, COEUR BRISƒ, DEPRIMANT, COEUR BRISE, TRISTE, DƒPRIMANT, LOURD, DEPRIMANT, TRISTE, DƒPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, DEPRIMANT, TRISTE, DƒPRIMANT, MƒLANCOLIE, DEPRIMANT, MELANCOLIE, TRISTE, DƒPRIMANT, LUGUBRE, DEPRIMANT, TRISTE, DƒPRIMANT, PATHOS, DEPRIMANT, TRISTE, DƒPRIMANT, POIGNANT, DEPRIMANT, TRISTE, DƒPRIMANT, TRISTE, DEPRIMANT, TRISTE, DƒPRIMANT, TRAGIQUE, DEPRIMANT, SƒRIEUX, INQUIET, SERIEUX, SƒRIEUX, ƒMOUVANT, SERIEUX, EMOUVANT, SƒRIEUX, ATTENTIONNƒ, SERIEUX, ATTENTIONNE, FORT, ƒPIQUE, EPIQUE, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, FORT, NERVEUX, MƒLODIQUE, LYRIQUE, MELODIQUE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AƒRIEN, FLOTTANT, AERIEN, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, BATTERIE, BOITE Ë RYTHMES, BATTERIE ƒLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ƒLECTRONIQUES, ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ELECTRONIQUES, CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, VIOLONCELLE, CORDES, GUITARE, ƒLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE, VOCAL, FƒMININ, FEMININ, AVEC PAROLES, SUJET DE LA CHANSON, MOMENTS DIFFICILES, TRAGƒDIE, TRAGEDIE, SUJET DE LA CHANSON, AMOUR, MENƒ PAR L'ARTISTE, MENE PAR L'ARTISTE Sombre et poignant, avec cordes cinématiques, beats maussades, guitare ambient et chant féminin stupéfiant. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 361 tk013 wayne roberts (prs) abandon me (a) wom 361 female indie pop west one music indie pop club electronica trip hop pop orchestral pop rock indie main movies crime detective mystery movies epic movies human drama movies indie films movies urban drama movies war tv radio children youth tv disturbing dark disturbing tense sad depressing bittersweet sad dark and poignant featuring cinematic strings moody beats and stunning female vocals. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="428434750"/>
    <item id="8402" name="Smooth Cat" code="TSH 071A tk038" libraryid="5" albumid="179" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_071A_One_Liners/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Diogo Vascocellos, Paul Reeves (Gb 2)" comment="Tango lounge séduisant." styleid="16" lengthseconds="35" time="0:35" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_071A_One_Liners/TSH_071_trk038_SMOOTH_CAT_Diogo_Vascocellos,_Paul_Reeves_(Gb_2)_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="38" tracktotal="" search="KITSCH, RETRO, CHEESY, KITSCH, RETRO, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, BAR, BAR À COCKTAILS, RESTAURANT, RESTAURANT, ETHNIQUE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, ASCENSEUR, EN ATTENTE, MUSIQUE DE FOND POUR MAGASINS, FILMS, COMÉDIE, CHEESY, KITSCH, FILMS, COMÉDIE, PARODIE, SATIRE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, IRONIQUE, SEXY, SÉDUISANT, SEXY, SEXY, SEXY, SENSUEL, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, CLAVIER, PIANO, DANSE DE SALON, TANGO, STYLE VINTAGE, SEDUISANT, COMEDIE, BAR A COCKTAILS Tango lounge séduisant. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 071a tk038 diogo vascocellos paul reeves (gb 2) smooth cat tsh 071a one liners the scoring house quirky classical main documentary biographical historical the arts movies comedy chase tv radio leisure lifestyle arts antiques tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden happy happy happy lighthearted melodic lyrical movement rhythmic busy movement rhythmic alluring lounge tango. main dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="21372" name="Angel in the Dark (b)" code="WOM 255 tk017" libraryid="6" albumid="458" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_255_Nocturnes/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Johnny Bernstein" comment="Des breaks hip hop brumeux et jazzy avec une voix sombre d'homme et une voix mélancolique de femme." styleid="10" lengthseconds="159" time="2:39" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_255_Nocturnes/WOM255_trk017_ANGEL_IN_THE_DARK_(B)_Johnny_Bernstein_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="17" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, SOUL CLASSIQUE, FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, SOUL CONTEMPORAINE, FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, NORTHERN SOUL, JAZZ, FUSION, JAZZ, SMOOTH JAZZ, UNDERSCORE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, MODERNE, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, NUIT, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, SEXY, ÉROTIQUE , SEXY, SEXY, SEXY, SENSUEL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), DUO, VOCAL, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), EROTIQUE Des breaks hip hop brumeux et jazzy avec une voix sombre d'homme et une voix mélancolique de femme. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 255 tk017 johnny bernstein angel in the dark (b) wom 255 nocturnes west one music documentary film score orchestral trailer funk soul r&amp;b classic soul funk soul r&amp;b contemporary soul funk soul r&amp;b northern soul jazz fusion jazz smooth jazz underscore movies human drama movies modern movies urban drama tv radio talkshow entertainment late night tv radio smoky jazzy hip-hop breaks. without vocal dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="24211" name="Black Tie Affair (a)" code="WOM 319 tk004" libraryid="6" albumid="523" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_319_Elegant_Strings_and_Beats/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Thorsten Laewe / Robert Leslie Bennett" comment="Élégance et qualité à la nuit tombée. Thèmes pour cordes et piano à queue enveloppants et émouvants." styleid="14" lengthseconds="127" time="2:07" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_319_Elegant_Strings_and_Beats/WOM319_trk004_BLACK_TIE_AFFAIR_(A)_Thorsten_Laewe_Robert_Leslie_Bennett_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, ORCHESTRAL HYBRIDE , PRINCIPAL, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, FILMS, FILM NOIR, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, DRAMATIQUE, PASSIONNÉ, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, COEUR BRISÉ, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, MÉLANCOLIE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, LUGUBRE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRAGIQUE, SEXY, SÉDUISANT, SEXY, SENSUEL, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, SOPHISTIQUÉ, CLASSE, FORT EN ÉMOTIONS, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES, ORCHESTRE À CORDES, CLAVIER, PIANO, FORMATIONS GENERALES, SOPHISTIQUE, FORT EN EMOTIONS, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, A CORDES, ORCHESTRE A CORDES, PASSIONNE, DEPRIMANT, SEDUISANT, COEUR BRISE, MELANCOLIE, ELEGANT, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE Élégance et qualité à la nuit tombée. Thèmes pour cordes et piano à queue enveloppants et émouvants. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 319 tk004 thorsten laewe robert leslie bennett black tie affair (a) wom 319 elegant strings and beats west one music drama film score orchestral trailer business corporate luxury film score orchestral orchestral hybrid main movies crime detective mystery movies espionage spy movies film noir movies human drama movies urban drama dramatic passionate sad depressing heartbroken sad depressing after dark quality and elegance. rich emotive strings and grand piano themes. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="23488" name="Give Me Your Love (a)" code="WOM 303 tk005" libraryid="6" albumid="509" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_303_Commercial_Dance/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Charlie Tenku / Jamie Paul Reddington / Emre Ramazanoglu" comment="Désirs sombres: house sophistiquée et nerveuse. Avec chant masculin." styleid="1" lengthseconds="154" time="2:34" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_303_Commercial_Dance/WOM303_trk005_GIVE_ME_YOUR_LOVE_(A)_Charlie_Tenku_Jamie_Paul_Reddington_Emre_Ramazanoglu_West_One_Music.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRO, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRO, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HOUSE, POP, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, NERVEUX, SOPHISTIQUÉ, GLOSSY, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, SPORT, EXERCICE, FITNESS, VOCAL, MASCULIN,, SOPHISTIQUE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO) Désirs sombres: house sophistiquée et nerveuse. Avec chant masculin. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 303 tk005 charlie tenku jamie paul reddington emre ramazanoglu give me your love (a) wom 303 commercial dance west one music dance electro club electronica electro main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) club electronica electro club electronica house pop disturbing dark edgy slick glossy tv radio children youth tv tv radio sports sports exercise fitness vocals male dark desires slick edgy house. featuring male vocals. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="4693" name="Ultra Neon (a)" code="TSH 036 tk004" libraryid="5" albumid="126" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_036_The_Hard_Edge/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Robert Henry Peter White" comment="Un rythme curieux et excitant allant vers une exposition brutale." styleid="10" lengthseconds="135" time="2:15" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_036_The_Hard_Edge/TSH036_trk004_ULTRA_NEON_(A)_Robert_Henry_Peter_White_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, STRIPTEASE, BURLESQUE, FILMS, FILM NOIR, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, SEXY, COCHON, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE) Un rythme curieux et excitant allant vers une exposition brutale. tsh 036 tk004 robert henry peter white ultra neon (a) tsh 036 the hard edge the scoring house documentary film score orchestral trailer main activities settings striptease burlesque movies film noir movies urban drama tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style sexy sleazy glamorous luxurious movement rhythmic rugged tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) intriguing tantalising groove to raw exposure. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="20217" name="Come Here (b)" code="WOM 231A tk020" libraryid="6" albumid="431" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_231A_Showtime/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Paul Reeves (Gb 2)" comment="Coquin, sexy et sulfureux. Avec des cordes et un piano." styleid="9" lengthseconds="155" time="2:35" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_231A_Showtime/WOM231A_trk020_COME_HERE_(B)_Paul_Reeves_(Gb_2)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="20" tracktotal="" search="STYLES DE DANSE TRADITIONNEL, JAZZ, SWING, UNDERSCORE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, BAR, BAR À COCKTAILS, RESTAURANT, BAR À COCKTAILS, BAR , SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, HOLLYWOOD, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, LAS VEGAS, SPECTACLE LIVE, THÉÂTRE, COMÉDIE MUSICALE, BROADWAY, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, NUIT, SEXY, SEXY, SEXY, SENSUEL, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CUIVRES, BIG BAND, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ORCHESTRE DE DANSE TRADITIONNELLE, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, DANSE DE SALON, FORMATIONS GENERALES, AMERIQUE DU NORD, ETATS-UNIS, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), THEATRE, COMEDIE, COMEDIE MUSICALE, BAR A COCKTAILS Coquin, sexy et sulfureux. Avec des cordes et un piano. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 231a tk020 paul reeves (gb 2) come here (b) wom 231a showtime west one music period vintage traditional dance styles jazz swing underscore activities settings bar cocktail lounge restaurant cocktail lounge bar activities settings showbiz hollywood activities settings showbiz las vegas live entertainment theater musicals broadway tv radio talkshow entertainment sassy sexy and sultry. featuring strings and piano. without vocal dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel knees up, mess piano, cockney, east london, singalong, pub joanna, piano bar, piano-bar, live" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="19833" name="Dirty Funk" code="WOM 223 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="423" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_223_Superfly_Funk_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David William Smith / David Jonathan Crane" comment="100% superfly." styleid="30" lengthseconds="164" time="2:44" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_223_Superfly_Funk_2/WOM223_trk001_DIRTY_FUNK_David_William_Smith_David_Jonathan_Crane_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, FILMS, BLAXPLOITATION, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, NUIT, SEXY, SEXY, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BATTERIE, CLAVIER, ORGUE HAMMOND, CORDES, BASSE, BASSE ÉLECTRIQUE, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, CORDES, GUITARE, WAH WAH, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 70, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEFILE DE MODE, 20E SIECLE, DEFILE, ELECTRIQUE, BASSE ELECTRIQUE, ANNEES 70 100% superfly. wom 223 tk001 david william smith david jonathan crane dirty funk wom 223 superfly funk 2 west one music r&amp;b soul funk soul r&amp;b club electronica film score orchestral trailer main activities settings fashion show activities settings showbiz movies blaxploitation tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio talkshow entertainment late night sexy sexy glamorous luxurious tempo superfly to the core. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="27084" name="X-rated" code="WOM 367 tk011" libraryid="6" albumid="581" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_367_Twerk/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Diogo do Santos (PRS), Subatomic (PRS)" comment="Trap relax, sensuel et érotique, avec un groove moelleux et un chant féminin explicite." styleid="1" lengthseconds="117" time="1:57" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_367_Twerk/WOM_367_trk011_X-RATED_Diogo_do_Santos_(PRS),_Subatomic_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="11" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CHILL OUT, DOWNTEMPO, EASY LISTENING, LOUNGE, HIP HOP, URBAIN, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, BAR, BAR À COCKTAILS, RESTAURANT, BAR À COCKTAILS, BAR, BAR A COCKTAILS, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FETE, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, STRIPTEASE, BURLESQUE, FILMS, POUR ADULTES, PORNO, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, SEXY, COOL, SEXY, ÉROTIQUE , EROTIQUE, SEXY, CHARMEUR, SEXY, GRIVOIS, SEXY, SÉDUISANT, SEDUISANT, SEXY, SEXY, SEXY, COCHON, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, ENERGIQUE, FORT, EXALTANT, FORT, FORT, TENDRE, INTIME, COOL, NERVEUX, ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BATTERIE, BOITE À RYTHMES, BATTERIE ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, VOCAL, FÉMININ, FÉMININ, FEMININ Trap relax, sensuel et érotique, avec un groove moelleux et un chant féminin explicite. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 367 tk011 diogo do santos (prs) subatomic (prs) x-rated wom 367 twerk west one music dance electro club electronica club electronica club electronica chill out downtempo easy listening lounge hip hop urban main activities settings bar cocktail lounge restaurant cocktail lounge bar activities settings party activities settings striptease burlesque movies sultry and erotic chill trap with mellow groove and explicit female vocals. main dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="428434750"/>
    <item id="19736" name="Sans Lumiere (a)" code="WOM 221A tk011" libraryid="6" albumid="420" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_221A_Big_Chill_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Gavin Skinner" comment="Sombre et mystérieux, avec des voix de femmes sensuelles." styleid="15" lengthseconds="192" time="3:12" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_221A_Big_Chill_2/WOM221A_trk011_SANS_LUMIERE_(A)_Gavin_Skinner_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="11" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CHILL OUT, DOWNTEMPO, ASIE, ASIE DU SUD, INDE, MOYEN-ORIENT, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLUB, ELECTRONICA, GROOVES, DANSE ETHNIQUE, STYLE POP, SEXY, ÉROTIQUE , SEXY, SEXY, SEXY, SENSUEL, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, DRAMATIQUE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, STRIPTEASE, BURLESQUE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, DOCUMENTAIRE, VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, TEXTURE VOCALE,, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), EROTIQUE Sombre et mystérieux, avec des voix de femmes sensuelles. wom 221a tk011 gavin skinner sans lumiere (a) wom 221a big chill 2 west one music ambient chill club electronica chill out downtempo asia south asia india middle east main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) club electronica grooves ethnic dance pop style sexy erotic sexy sexy sexy sultry disturbing dark disturbing mysterious dramatic activities settings striptease dark and mysterious with sultry female vocals. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="20655" name="The Devil's Bride (b)" code="WOM 239 tk015" libraryid="6" albumid="440" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_239_Devils_&amp;_Demons/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jay Price" comment="Sexy et légèrement sinistre, progressant vers un refrain entraînant." styleid="6" lengthseconds="157" time="2:37" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_239_Devils_&amp;_Demons/WOM239_trk015_THE_DEVIL'S_BRIDE_(B)_Jay_Price_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="15" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BLUES, ROCK, ROCK, ROCK 'N' ROLL, UNDERSCORE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, STRIPTEASE, BURLESQUE, FILMS, ROAD MOVIE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, NUIT, SEXY, SEXY, EVOLUTIF, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), GROUPE DE ROCK, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 60, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), 20E SIECLE, ELECTRIQUE, ANNEES 60, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Sexy et légèrement sinistre, progressant vers un refrain entraînant. wom 239 tk015 jay price the devil's bride (b) wom 239 devils &amp; demons west one music rock film score orchestral trailer blues rock rock rock &amp; roll underscore activities settings striptease burlesque movies road movie tv radio talkshow entertainment late night sexy sexy building tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) rock band strings guitar electric time period sexy and sinister building to a catchy chorus. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="2607" name="Play That Thing (b)" code="RFM 030 tk015" libraryid="4" albumid="86" albumartpath="Music/Refuel Music/RFM_030_Refuelled_Funkadelia/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Johnny Hawksworth" comment="Un rythme kitsch et funky. Authentique enregistrement d'époque." styleid="8" lengthseconds="184" time="3:04" samplefile="Music/Refuel Music/RFM_030_Refuelled_Funkadelia/RFM030_trk015_PLAY_THAT_THING_(B)_Johnny_Hawksworth_Refuel_Music.mp3" track="15" tracktotal="" search="KITSCH, RETRO, CHEESY, KITSCH, RETRO, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, TV, RADIO, DROLE, MANIÉRÉ, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, GROOVY, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 60, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 70, STYLE VINTAGE, ENREGISTREMENT D'ARCHIVE, PERIODE, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), MANIERE, DECALE, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 60, ANNEES 70 Un rythme kitsch et funky. Authentique enregistrement d'époque. rfm 030 tk015 johnny hawksworth play that thing (b) rfm 030 refuelled funkadelia refuel music kitsch retro kitsch retro cheesy kitsch retro main activities settings showbiz tv radio funny campy funny comedic funny eccentric funny quirky groovy tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) time period modern era 20th century 1960s time period modern era 20th century 1970s kitsch funky groove. authentic period recording. alternative" waveformpath="" version="Alternative" publisher="Refuel Music" cae="00617450359"/>
    <item id="8294" name="Takes Two to Tango (a)" code="TSH 061 tk028" libraryid="5" albumid="178" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_061_Life_Little_Whimsies/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Alexander Rudd / Zach Lemmon Lemmon" comment="Tango tourbillonant, virevoltant et enjoué." styleid="16" lengthseconds="140" time="2:20" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_061_Life_Little_Whimsies/TSH061_trk028_TAKES_TWO_TO_TANGO_(A)_Alexander_Rudd_Zach_Lemmon_Lemmon_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="28" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, BOIS, SECTION DE BOIS, PRINCIPAL, ENFANTS, CONTES, STYLES DE DANSE TRADITIONNEL, STYLES DE DANSE LATINE, WORLD BEAT, STYLES ETHNIQUES, INFLUENCE LATINE, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, DROLE, IRONIQUE, HEUREUX, ENJOUÉ, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, FILMS, COMÉDIE, CHEESY, KITSCH, FILMS, COMÉDIE, PARODIE, SATIRE, FILMS, COMÉDIE ROMANTIQUE, CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, VIOLON , BOIS, BASSON, BOIS, CLARINETTE, FORMATIONS GENERALES, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, ESPIEGLE, DECALE, ENJOUE, COMEDIE, COMEDIE ROMANTIQUE Tango tourbillonant, virevoltant et enjoué. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 061 tk028 alexander rudd zach lemmon lemmon takes two to tango (a) tsh 061 life's little whimsies the scoring house quirky film score orchestral trailer general lineups electronic and acoustic strings string section woodwind woodwind section main children storytelling traditional dance styles latin dance styles world beat ethnic stylings latin influenced funny comedic funny eccentric funny swirling twirling playful tango. dramedy. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="26955" name="Light Waves (a)" code="WOM 321 tk014" libraryid="6" albumid="578" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_321_Light_Bright_and_Playful/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Mike Reed / Tom Howe" comment="Phrases décalées et perplexes de piano, pizzicati de cordes et marimba. Espiègle et amusant." styleid="10" lengthseconds="109" time="1:49" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_321_Light_Bright_and_Playful/WOM321_trk014_LIGHT_WAVES_(A)_Mike_Reed_Tom_Howe_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="14" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, FAMILIAL, FILMS, COMÉDIE ROMANTIQUE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, ENJOUÉ, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, INNOCENT, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, PINCÉ, PIZZICATO, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, OCCUPÉ, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, RÉPÉTITIF, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, CLAVIER, PIANO, PERCUSSION, MARIMBA, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN MÉTAL, CORDES, CORDES PIZZICATO, PINCE, DECALE, ENJOUE, COMEDIE, COMEDIE ROMANTIQUE, OCCUPE, REPETITIF, ELEMENTS, CORDES EN METAL Phrases décalées et perplexes de piano, pizzicati de cordes et marimba. Espiègle et amusant. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 321 tk014 mike reed tom howe light waves (a) wom 321 light bright and playful west one music documentary children storytelling film score orchestral documentary film score orchestral trailer main movies children storytelling movies family movies romantic comedy nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden quirky and quizzical piano pizzicato strings and marimba phrases. playful and fun. dramedy. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="8398" name="Moonlight Bossa" code="TSH 071A tk034" libraryid="5" albumid="179" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_071A_One_Liners/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Laurence Cottle" comment="Bossa reveuse, romantique. Avec trombone." styleid="16" lengthseconds="33" time="0:33" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_071A_One_Liners/TSH_071_trk034_MOONLIGHT_BOSSA_Laurence_Cottle_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="34" tracktotal="" search="KITSCH, RETRO, CHEESY, EASY LISTENING, LOUNGE, KITSCH, RETRO, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, BAR, BAR À COCKTAILS, RESTAURANT, BAR À COCKTAILS, BAR , SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, ASCENSEUR, EN ATTENTE, MUSIQUE DE FOND POUR MAGASINS, FILMS, COMÉDIE, CHEESY, KITSCH, FILMS, COMÉDIE, PARODIE, SATIRE, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, NONCHALANT, PAISIBLE, DÉTENDU, SEXY, SEXY, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, CUIVRES, TROMBONE, DANSE DE SALON, BOSSA NOVA, DETENDU, COMEDIE, BAR A COCKTAILS Bossa reveuse, romantique. Avec trombone. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 071a tk034 laurence cottle moonlight bossa tsh 071a one liners the scoring house quirky traditional ethnic folk national and ethnic national folk dance main nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tender warm folksy movement rhythmic busy tempo dreamy romantic bossa featuring trombone. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="11011" name="Sex in a City" code="WOM 034 tk016" libraryid="6" albumid="224" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_034_Lounge/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Peter Sander (Gb)" comment="Une danse latine, une flûte caracolante, une guitare douce, et un piano et une trompette jazzy." styleid="8" lengthseconds="202" time="3:22" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_034_Lounge/WOM034_trk016_SEX_IN_A_CITY_Peter_Sander_(Gb)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="16" tracktotal="" search="STYLES DE DANSE TRADITIONNEL, EASY LISTENING, LOUNGE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, JAZZ, LATIN, STYLES DE DANSE LATINE, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, BAR, BAR À COCKTAILS, RESTAURANT, BAR À COCKTAILS, BAR , SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, FETE, COCKTAIL, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, HEUREUX, JOYEUX, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BOIS, CUIVRES, TROMPETTE, CORNET, BOIS, FLUTE, DANSE DE SALON, RUMBA, DANSE DE SALON, SALSA, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 60, STYLE VINTAGE, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), 20E SIECLE, BAR A COCKTAILS, ANNEES 60 Une danse latine, une flûte caracolante, une guitare douce, et un piano et une trompette jazzy. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 034 tk016 peter sander (gb) sex in a city wom 034 lounge west one music kitsch retro traditional dance styles easy listening lounge film score orchestral trailer jazz latin latin dance styles main activities settings bar cocktail lounge restaurant cocktail lounge bar activities settings party cocktail tv radio leisure lifestyle happy cheerful tempo latin dance prancing flute smooth guitar jazzed up piano and trumpet. main dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="3824" name="Talk Shop (a)" code="TSH 019 tk004" libraryid="5" albumid="110" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_019_Throw_Me_the_Groove/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Gwilym Raymond Simcock / Curtis Frederick Schwartz / James Thomas Maddren / Yuri Goloubev" comment="Fun, cool et léger." styleid="19" lengthseconds="152" time="2:32" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_019_Throw_Me_the_Groove/TSH019_trk004_TALK_SHOP_(A)_Gwilym_Raymond_Simcock_Curtis_Frederick_Schwartz_James_Thomas_Maddren_Yu.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="JAZZ, JAZZ COOL, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), JAZZ, STYLE VINTAGE, HEUREUX, FUN, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, DROLE, IRONIQUE, TENDRE, LÉGER, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, MARCHE, TV, RADIO, DESSINS ANIMÉS, TV, RADIO, SITCOM, CORDES, BASSE, CONTREBASSE, CONTREBASSE,, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DECALE, LEGER, DESSINS ANIMES Fun, cool et léger. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz tsh 019 tk004 gwilym raymond simcock curtis frederick schwartz james thomas maddren yuri goloubev talk shop (a) tsh 019 throw me the groove the scoring house jazz jazz cool jazz main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) jazz vintage style happy fun happy happy funny comedic funny eccentric funny quirky funny wry tender light movement rhythmic walking tv radio cartoons tv radio sitcom strings bass stringed bass double bass super cool light fun. main dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="23209" name="Just a Feeling" code="WOM 297 tk002" libraryid="6" albumid="502" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_297_Something_Simple/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Thomas Greenberg" comment="Irrésistible, décalé et amusant. Avec de douces mélodies de piano." styleid="16" lengthseconds="78" time="1:18" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_297_Something_Simple/WOM297_trk002_JUST_A_FEELING_Thomas_Greenberg_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="POP, POP POUR ENFANTS, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), ENFANTS, POP, POP POUR ENFANTS, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, FUN, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, TV, RADIO, DESSINS ANIMÉS, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE,, DECALE, DESSINS ANIMES, JOURNEE Irrésistible, décalé et amusant. Avec de douces mélodies de piano. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 297 tk002 thomas greenberg just a feeling wom 297 something simple west one music quirky pop kiddie pop main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) children pop kiddie pop happy feel good happy fun happy happy happy playful funny quirky tv radio cartoons tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden tv radio talkshow entertainment daytime infectious quirky and fun with gentle piano melodies. main delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="26021" name="Wilderness Polka (a)" code="WOM 352 tk006" libraryid="6" albumid="557" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_352_Cinematic_Indie_Drama/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Dylan Parsons / Dan Cassady" comment="Polka rythmée et fanfaronnante avec batterie, contrebasse, piano mélodieux et guitare lead." styleid="14" lengthseconds="123" time="2:03" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_352_Cinematic_Indie_Drama/WOM_352_trk006_WILDERNESS_POLKA_(A)_Dylan_Parsons_Dan_Cassady_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="6" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, TRAILER, COUNTRY, COUNTRY, WESTERN, COUNTRY, WESTERN, COWBOY, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, FILMS INDÉPENDANTS, FILMS INDEPENDANTS, FILMS, ROAD MOVIE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, CHAUD, DÉSERT, DESERT, ELEMENTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, ELEMENTS, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, DRAME TV, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, ESPIEGLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, DECALE, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, PAISIBLE, DÉTENDU, DETENDU, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, FORT, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, FORMATIONS GENERALES, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, ETHNIQUE, CITHARE, BATTERIE, BATTERIE, CLAVIER, HARMONIUM, CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, BASSE, CONTREBASSE, CONTREBASSE, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN MÉTAL, CORDES EN METAL, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE, CORDES, MANDOLINE Polka rythmée et fanfaronnante avec batterie, contrebasse, piano mélodieux et guitare lead. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 352 tk006 dylan parsons dan cassady wilderness polka (a) wom 352 cinematic indie drama west one music drama film score orchestral trailer country western country western cowboy main movies human drama movies indie films movies road movie nature wildlife the elements land hot desert nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama tv radio tv drama funny mischievous polka with rhythm and swagger featuring drums double bass melodic piano and lead guitar. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="26443" name="Nectar of Life (a)" code="WOM 256 tk013" libraryid="6" albumid="567" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_256_Life_in_Motion_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Paul Reeves (Gb 2)" comment="Une valse bizarre et captivante." styleid="4" lengthseconds="164" time="2:44" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_256_Life_in_Motion_2/WOM256_trk013_NECTAR_OF_LIFE_(A)_Paul_Reeves_(Gb_2)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="13" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, STYLES DE DANSE TRADITIONNEL, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, DANSE DE SALON, VALSE, FILMS, ANIMATION, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, FILMS, COMÉDIE ROMANTIQUE,, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ESPIEGLE, DECALE, COMEDIE, COMEDIE ROMANTIQUE, ELEGANT Une valse bizarre et captivante. wom 256 tk013 paul reeves (gb 2) nectar of life (a) wom 256 life in motion 2 west one music film score orchestral children storytelling main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) film score orchestral trailer traditional dance styles funny comedic funny mischievous funny quirky movement rhythmic stealthy movement smooth elegant movement smooth graceful ballroom dance waltz movies animation a quirky and intriguing waltz. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="3461" name="What a Cheek (b)" code="TSH 014A tk007" libraryid="5" albumid="104" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_014A_Smile-_A_Most_Cheerful_Earful/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Brian Douglas Gulland" comment="Une dose souriante de bonne humeur." styleid="17" lengthseconds="132" time="2:12" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_014A_Smile-_A_Most_Cheerful_Earful/TSH_014A_trk007_WHAT_A_CHEEK_(B)_Brian_Douglas_Gulland_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, ENFANTS, MATERNELLE, ALTERNATIF, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, ENFANTS, MATERNELLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, MATERNELLE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, DROLE, COMIQUE, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, ENJOUÉ, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, TENDRE, INNOCENT, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, EMPOTÉ, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, EXCENTRIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, MARCHE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ENJOUE, IRREGULIER, EMPOTE, ELEMENTS, JOURNEE Une dose souriante de bonne humeur. tsh 014a tk007 brian douglas gulland what a cheek (b) tsh 014a smile: a most cheerful earful the scoring house comedy traditional ethnic folk national and ethnic national folk dance traditional ethnic folk national and ethnic national folk music alternate documentary biographical historical the arts nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral funny comedic happy happy building a smiley dose of jollity. alternative" waveformpath="" version="Alternative" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="19407" name="Pizzicato Polka" code="WOM 213 tk007" libraryid="6" albumid="412" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_213_Classical_Evolutions/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Patrick Thomas Hawes" comment="Enjoué et léger, avec des cordes pizzicati délicates." styleid="25" lengthseconds="140" time="2:20" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_213_Classical_Evolutions/WOM213_trk007_PIZZICATO_POLKA_Patrick_Thomas_Hawes_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, MUSIQUE DE CHAMBRE, ENSEMBLE CLASSIQUE, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, ANGLETERRE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), ENFANTS, CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, HEUREUX, VIF, TENDRE, DÉLICAT, TENDRE, INNOCENT, TENDRE, LÉGER, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, PRINTEMPS, CORDES, CORDES PIZZICATO,, DELICAT, LEGER, ELEMENTS Enjoué et léger, avec des cordes pizzicati délicates. wom 213 tk007 patrick thomas hawes pizzicato polka wom 213 classical evolutions west one music classical opera children storytelling classical and semi classical chamber music classical ensemble europe northern europe england main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) children classical classical styling film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral pastoral happy bright tender bright and light featuring delicate pizzicato strings. main delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="12342" name="Flirting (a)" code="WOM 058 tk008" libraryid="6" albumid="248" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_058_Irresistible/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Matt Norman" comment="Un thème jazzy, fun et gai. Sortie tonique à 1:58." styleid="31" lengthseconds="177" time="2:57" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_058_Irresistible/WOM058_trk008_FLIRTING_(A)_Matt_Norman_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="8" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, JAZZ, RAGTIME, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, SPECTACLE LIVE, THÉÂTRE, COMÉDIE MUSICALE, BROADWAY, FILMS, COMÉDIE MUSICALE, FILMS, COMÉDIE ROMANTIQUE, HEUREUX, FUN, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ENSEMBLE DE JAZZ, GROUPE DE JAZZ, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 20, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 30, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 40, STYLE VINTAGE, FORMATIONS GENERALES, AMERIQUE DU NORD, PERIODE, ETATS-UNIS, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), THEATRE, COMEDIE, COMEDIE MUSICALE, COMEDIE ROMANTIQUE, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 20, ANNEES 30, ANNEES 40 Un thème jazzy, fun et gai. Sortie tonique à 1:58. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 058 tk008 matt norman flirting (a) wom 058 irresistible west one music romantic film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral trailer jazz ragtime main documentary biographical historical the arts live entertainment theater musicals broadway movies musical movies romantic comedy happy fun happy upbeat tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) fun upbeat jazzy theme. lively outro at 1:58. main dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel knees up, mess piano, cockney, east london, singalong, pub joanna, piano bar, piano-bar, live" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="26792" name="On Tip Toes (a)" code="WOM 248 tk002" libraryid="6" albumid="575" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_248_Dramedy/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Philip Hochstrate / Bill Connor" comment="Léger, délicat et espiègle." styleid="14" lengthseconds="134" time="2:14" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_248_Dramedy/WOM248_trk002_ON_TIP_TOES_(A)_Philip_Hochstrate_Bill_Connor_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, COMÉDIE, FILMS, COMÉDIE ROMANTIQUE, TV, RADIO, SITCOM, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, HUMORISTIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, SEXY, GRIVOIS, TENDRE, DÉLICAT, TENDRE, LÉGER, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ESPIEGLE, DECALE, DELICAT, LEGER, COMEDIE, COMEDIE ROMANTIQUE Léger, délicat et espiègle. wom 248 tk002 philip hochstrate bill connor on tip toes (a) wom 248 dramedy west one music drama film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral trailer main movies comedy movies romantic comedy tv radio sitcom funny comedic funny eccentric funny humorous funny mischievous funny quirky happy playful sexy saucy tender delicate tender light movement rhythmic light delicate and playful. dramedy. main delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="8445" name="On Tiptoe (a)" code="TSH 071A tk081" libraryid="5" albumid="179" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_071A_One_Liners/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Barnaby J Robson" comment="Activité discrète et enjouée, jusqu'à l'accentuation." styleid="16" lengthseconds="33" time="0:33" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_071A_One_Liners/TSH_071_trk081_ON_TIPTOE_(A)_Barnaby_J_Robson_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="81" tracktotal="" search="KITSCH, RETRO, CHEESY, KITSCH, RETRO, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, COMÉDIE, TARTE A LA CRÈME, FILMS, COMÉDIE, PARODIE, SATIRE, TV, RADIO, DESSINS ANIMÉS, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, DROLE, DROLE, IDIOT, DROLE, IRONIQUE, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, EXCENTRIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, STYLE VINTAGE, IRREGULIER, COMEDIE, TARTE A LA CREME, DESSINS ANIMES Activité discrète et enjouée, jusqu'à l'accentuation. tsh 071a tk081 barnaby j robson on tiptoe (a) tsh 071a one liners the scoring house quirky kitsch retro cheesy kitsch retro main movies comedy slapstick movies comedy spoof satire tv radio cartoons funny comedic funny eccentric funny funny funny silly funny wry movement irregular eccentric movement rhythmic stealthy vintage style light-hearted stealthy activity to accent. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="17574" name="Short Theme 5" code="WOM 174 tk010" libraryid="6" albumid="370" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_174_Age_of_Innocence/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Thomas Greenberg" comment="Une répartie enjouée. Piano et bois." styleid="10" lengthseconds="36" time="0:36" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_174_Age_of_Innocence/WOM174_trk010_SHORT_THEME_5_Thomas_Greenberg_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="10" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, ENFANTS, COMPTINE, ENFANTS, MATERNELLE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, ENFANTS, MATERNELLE, FILMS, ANIMATION, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, TV, RADIO, DESSINS ANIMÉS, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, HEUREUX, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BOIS, CLAVIER, CELESTE, CLAVIER, PIANO, PERCUSSION, CYMBALES, BOIS, CLARINETTE, STYLE VINTAGE, AIR CONNU, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DECALE, DESSINS ANIMES Une répartie enjouée. Piano et bois. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 174 tk010 thomas greenberg short theme 5 wom 174 age of innocence west one music documentary children children nursery rhyme children pre school film score orchestral trailer main activities settings children pre school movies animation movies children storytelling movies fantasy adventure tv radio cartoons funny quirky happy peaceful contented tempo jolly repartee. piano and woodwind. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="6979" name="On the Move" code="TSH 011 tk012" libraryid="5" albumid="160" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_011_Orchestral_Elements/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Bill Connor" comment="Des rythmes syncopés de cordes évoquant le voyage." styleid="4" lengthseconds="164" time="2:44" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_011_Orchestral_Elements/TSH011_trk012_ON_THE_MOVE_Bill_Connor_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, CLASSIQUE, STYLE MINIMALISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, FILMS, FILM NOIR, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, AUTOMATISATION, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, SYNCOPÉ, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UN TRAIN, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, STYLE VINTAGE, ELEMENTS SONORES, PERIODE, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), IRREGULIER, 20E SIECLE, SYNCOPE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS Des rythmes syncopés de cordes évoquant le voyage. tsh 011 tk012 bill connor on the move tsh 011 orchestral elements the scoring house film score orchestral sound elements atmospheres classical minimalist style business corporate beds film score orchestral trailer main movies crime detective mystery movies fantasy adventure movies film noir nature wildlife the elements science technology industry automation disturbing syncopated travelling string rhythms. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="8218" name="Faltering Steps" code="TSH 051 tk031" libraryid="5" albumid="177" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_051_Nearfield/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Everard Lawrence Wells / Robert John Foster" comment="Humour incertain et narquois." styleid="10" lengthseconds="93" time="1:33" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_051_Nearfield/TSH051_trk031_FALTERING_STEPS_Richard_Everard_Lawrence_Wells_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="31" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, HUMORISTIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, DROLE, IRONIQUE, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, EXCENTRIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), ESPIEGLE, DECALE, IRREGULIER, ELEMENTS Humour incertain et narquois. tsh 051 tk031 richard everard lawrence wells robert john foster faltering steps tsh 051 nearfield the scoring house documentary film score orchestral trailer main nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife funny comedic funny eccentric funny humorous funny mischievous funny quirky funny wry movement irregular eccentric movement rhythmic stealthy tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) quizzical uncertain humour. dramedy. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="27003" name="Playful Mischief (a)" code="WOM 350A tk012" libraryid="6" albumid="579" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_350A_British_Drama/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Michael Price, Laurence Greed" comment="Un pizzicato rythmé de cordes est combiné avec piano, vibraphone et bois avant de se développer jusqu'à un final entrainant." styleid="14" lengthseconds="118" time="1:58" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_350A_British_Drama/WOM_350A_trk012_PLAYFUL_MISCHIEF_(A)_Michael_Price,_Laurence_Greed_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ANIMATION, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, FILMS, FAMILIAL, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, PERIODE, PERIODES, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, MATERNELLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, DRAME TV, DROLE, HUMORISTIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, ESPIEGLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, DECALE, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, ENJOUÉ, ENJOUE, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, TENDRE, INNOCENT, TENDRE, LÉGER, LEGER, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, PIZZICATO, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, BOIS, SECTION DE BOIS, CUIVRES, COR, COR D'HARMONIE, BATTERIE, CAISSE CLAIRE, CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, CORDES PIZZICATO, BOIS, BASSON, BOIS, CLARINETTE, BOIS, FLUTE, BOIS, HAUTBOIS, HAUTBOIS, COR ANGLAIS, DRAME, BRITANNIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL Un pizzicato rythmé de cordes est combiné avec piano, vibraphone et bois avant de se développer jusqu'à un final entrainant. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 350a tk012 michael price laurence greed playful mischief (a) wom 350a british drama west one music drama film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral documentary film score orchestral trailer main movies animation movies children storytelling movies espionage spy movies family movies period historical costume drama tv radio children youth tv pre school tv radio rhythmic pizzicato strings combine with piano vibes and woodwind before building to a lively finish. dramedy. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="6405" name="Cover of Darkness" code="TSH 066 tk009" libraryid="5" albumid="150" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_066_Discreet_Emotive/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Paul Reeves (Gb 2) / Jay Price" comment="Bed évocateur, plein de tension." styleid="14" lengthseconds="135" time="2:15" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_066_Discreet_Emotive/TSH066_trk009_COVER_OF_DARKNESS_Paul_Reeves_(Gb_2)_Jay_Price_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, PRINCIPAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, TROUBLANT, ANXIEUX, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, CRAINTIF, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, AGITÉ, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, QUI A DU CRAN, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, FORMATIONS GENERALES, SERIEUX, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, AGITE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE Bed évocateur, plein de tension. tsh 066 tk009 paul reeves (gb 2) jay price cover of darkness tsh 066 discreet emotive the scoring house drama film score orchestral documentary general lineups electronic and acoustic main film score orchestral trailer disturbing anxious disturbing dark disturbing fearful disturbing mysterious disturbing restless disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense scary ominous serious serious tense atmospheric bed. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="8042" name="Naughty but Nice" code="TSH 039 tk016" libraryid="5" albumid="175" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_039_Life_in_Colour/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Alexander Paul Rudd / Zach Lemmon Lemmon" comment="Petits plaisirs personnels et complaisants." styleid="20" lengthseconds="215" time="3:35" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_039_Life_in_Colour/TSH039_trk016_NAUGHTY_BUT_NICE_Alexander_Paul_Rudd_Zach_Lemmon_Lemmon_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="16" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, ENFANTS, MATERNELLE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, ENFANTS, MATERNELLE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, MAGIE, ILLUSIONS, NOËL, ENFANTS, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, MATERNELLE, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, TENDRE, INNOCENT, MAGIQUE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), NOEL, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DECALE Petits plaisirs personnels et complaisants. tsh 039 tk016 alexander paul rudd zach lemmon lemmon naughty but nice tsh 039 life in colour the scoring house children children storytelling children pre school film score orchestral trailer main activities settings children pre school activities settings magic illusions christmas children movies children storytelling tv radio children youth tv pre school funny comedic funny eccentric indulgent personal pleasures. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="7943" name="Hysteria Lane" code="TSH 038 tk043" libraryid="5" albumid="174" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_038_Oddities/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Paul Reeves (Gb 2)" comment="Un morceau excentrique et imprévisible, avec des cordes pizzicati avec des interjections de percussions." styleid="17" lengthseconds="61" time="1:01" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_038_Oddities/TSH038_trk043_HYSTERIA_LANE_Paul_Reeves_(Gb_2)_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="43" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), HEUREUX, FUN, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, DROLE, IRONIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, PIZZICATO, FILMS, ANIMATION, FILMS, COMÉDIE ROMANTIQUE, TV, RADIO, DESSINS ANIMÉS, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, CORDES, CORDES PIZZICATO,, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ESPIEGLE, DECALE, COMEDIE, COMEDIE ROMANTIQUE, DESSINS ANIMES Un morceau excentrique et imprévisible, avec des cordes pizzicati avec des interjections de percussions. tsh 038 tk043 paul reeves (gb 2) hysteria lane tsh 038 oddities the scoring house comedy film score orchestral trailer main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) happy fun happy playful funny comedic funny eccentric funny mischievous funny quirky funny wry tender romantic movement rhythmic stealthy pizzicato movies animation movies romantic comedy tv radio oddball and unpredictable featuring pizzicato strings with percussion interjections. dramedy. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="26793" name="Secret Liaisons (a)" code="WOM 248 tk003" libraryid="6" albumid="575" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_248_Dramedy/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Philip Hochstrate / Bill Connor" comment="L'intrigue se corse… Relations cachées et plans secrets." styleid="14" lengthseconds="129" time="2:09" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_248_Dramedy/WOM248_trk003_SECRET_LIAISONS_(A)_Philip_Hochstrate_Bill_Connor_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, ENFANTS, CONTES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ANIMATION, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, COMÉDIE, FILMS, COMÉDIE ROMANTIQUE, TV, RADIO, SITCOM, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, HUMORISTIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, SEXY, GRIVOIS, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ESPIEGLE, DECALE, COMEDIE, COMEDIE ROMANTIQUE L'intrigue se corse… Relations cachées et plans secrets. wom 248 tk003 philip hochstrate bill connor secret liaisons (a) wom 248 dramedy west one music drama children storytelling children storytelling film score orchestral trailer main movies animation movies children storytelling movies comedy movies romantic comedy tv radio sitcom funny comedic funny eccentric funny humorous funny mischievous funny quirky happy playful the plot thickens... undercover dealings and covert plans. dramedy. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="16902" name="Sneaking Around (a)" code="WOM 359 tk019" libraryid="6" albumid="356" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_359_Modern_Dramedy/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Thomas Greenberg (PRS)" comment="Intrigue et enquete: détective undercover. Guitares et célesta furtifs sont alliés à des beats hip-hop. Pour dramedy." styleid="16" lengthseconds="117" time="1:57" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_359_Modern_Dramedy/WOM_359_trk019_SNEAKING_AROUND_(A)_Thomas_Greenberg_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="19" tracktotal="" search="LATIN, HIP HOP, URBAIN, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, CRIME, DƒTECTIVE, MYSTéRE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TƒLƒ RƒALITƒ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SITCOM, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SOAP OPERA, TELENOVELA, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, DROLE, ESPIéGLE, ESPIEGLE, DROLE, DƒCALƒ, DECALE, HEUREUX, ENJOUƒ, ENJOUE, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, NEUTRE, SƒRIEUX, SƒRIEUX, SERIEUX, TENDRE, LƒGER, LEGER, PIZZICATO, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, BATTERIE, BOITE Ë RYTHMES, BATTERIE ƒLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, CLAVIER, CELESTE, CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, GUITARE, ƒLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE Intrigue et enquete: détective undercover. Guitares et célesta furtifs sont alliés à des beats hip-hop. Pour dramedy. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 359 tk019 thomas greenberg (prs) sneaking around (a) wom 359 modern dramedy west one music quirky latin hip hop urban main activities settings city urban human environment documentary movies crime detective mystery tv radio reality tv tv radio sitcom tv radio soap opera telenovela disturbing mysterious funny mischievous funny quirky happy lighthearted happy intrigue &amp; investigation: undercover detective. covert guitars and celeste join with hip hop beats. dramedy. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="428434750"/>
    <item id="21361" name="Mercury and Moonlight (a)" code="WOM 255 tk006" libraryid="6" albumid="458" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_255_Nocturnes/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Johnny Bernstein" comment="Le dernier orchestre swing de la ville. Des rythmes jazzy épurés, mystérieux et chics." styleid="10" lengthseconds="147" time="2:27" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_255_Nocturnes/WOM255_trk006_MERCURY_AND_MOONLIGHT_(A)_Johnny_Bernstein_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="6" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, JAZZ, JAZZ COOL, JAZZ, MODERN JAZZ, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, STRIPTEASE, BURLESQUE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, DÉTENDU, SEXY, ÉROTIQUE , SEXY, SEXY, SEXY, SENSUEL, COOL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, CHALOUPÉ , TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), ESPIEGLE, DETENDU, EROTIQUE, CHALOUPE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE Le dernier orchestre swing de la ville. Des rythmes jazzy épurés, mystérieux et chics. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 255 tk006 johnny bernstein mercury and moonlight (a) wom 255 nocturnes west one music documentary film score orchestral trailer jazz cool jazz jazz modern jazz main activities settings striptease burlesque movies crime detective mystery movies espionage spy movies urban drama tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing mysterious funny comedic funny the last swing band in town. mysterious and sassy stripped-back jazzy grooves. main dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="26798" name="Lovers' Tryst (a)" code="WOM 248 tk008" libraryid="6" albumid="575" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_248_Dramedy/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Philip Hochstrate / Bill Connor" comment="Un tango décontracté et bizarre, basculant sur une section de fanfare complète à 0:32." styleid="14" lengthseconds="160" time="2:40" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_248_Dramedy/WOM248_trk008_LOVERS'_TRYST_(A)_Philip_Hochstrate_Bill_Connor_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="8" tracktotal="" search="STYLES DE DANSE TRADITIONNEL, AMÉRIQUE LATINE, AMÉRIQUE DU SUD, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, LATIN, STYLES DE DANSE LATINE, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, HUMORISTIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, SEXY, GRIVOIS, DANSE DE SALON, TANGO, FILMS, COMÉDIE, FILMS, COMÉDIE ROMANTIQUE, TV, RADIO, SITCOM,, AMERIQUE LATINE, AMERIQUE DU SUD, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), ESPIEGLE, DECALE, COMEDIE, COMEDIE ROMANTIQUE Un tango décontracté et bizarre, basculant sur une section de fanfare complète à 0:32. wom 248 tk008 philip hochstrate bill connor lovers' tryst (a) wom 248 dramedy west one music drama traditional dance styles latin america south america main tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) film score orchestral trailer latin latin dance styles happy playful funny comedic funny eccentric funny humorous funny mischievous funny quirky sexy saucy ballroom dance tango a cool quirky tango breaking to full band section at 0:32. dramedy. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="25178" name="Hey Yeah (a)" code="WOM 336A tk007" libraryid="6" albumid="541" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_336A_Supercharger_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jay Price" comment="Une intro au développement lent se heurte à 0:26 à un chorus épique et euphorique. Avec hook vocal simple et accrocheur." styleid="34" lengthseconds="114" time="1:54" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_336A_Supercharger_2/WOM_336A_trk007_HEY_YEAH_(A)_Jay_Price_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, GROUPE DE ROCK, PRINCIPAL, ROCK, INDIE, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, ROAD TRIP, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TV, RADIO, SPORT, VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, PHRASE VOCALE, CRI, APPEL, TELE REALITE Une intro au développement lent se heurte à 0:26 à un chorus épique et euphorique. Avec hook vocal simple et accrocheur. wom 336a tk007 jay price hey yeah (a) wom 336a supercharger 2 west one music indie rock rock band main rock indie strong confident strong strong uplifting inspirational uplifting motivational uplifting positive uplifting uplifting movement rhythmic driving activities settings road trip tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden tv radio slowly building intro hits epic euphoric chorus at 0:26. with a simple catchy vocal hook. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="26950" name="Hope Springs (a)" code="WOM 321 tk009" libraryid="6" albumid="578" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_321_Light_Bright_and_Playful/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Mike Reed / Tom Howe" comment="Animé et original. Avec pizzicati de cordes dansantes et un piano vif." styleid="10" lengthseconds="115" time="1:55" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_321_Light_Bright_and_Playful/WOM321_trk009_HOPE_SPRINGS_(A)_Mike_Reed_Tom_Howe_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, COMMUNICATION, ACTUALITÉS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, FAMILIAL, FILMS, COMÉDIE ROMANTIQUE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, HEUREUX, BONDISSANT, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, TENDRE, INNOCENT, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, PINCÉ, PIZZICATO, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, OCCUPÉ, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, PULSATION, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, RÉPÉTITIF, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, CLAVIER, PIANO, PERCUSSION, MARIMBA, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN MÉTAL, CORDES, CORDES PIZZICATO, PINCE, DECALE, COMEDIE, COMEDIE ROMANTIQUE, OCCUPE, REPETITIF, ACTUALITES, ELEMENTS, CORDES EN METAL Animé et original. Avec pizzicati de cordes dansantes et un piano vif. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 321 tk009 mike reed tom howe hope springs (a) wom 321 light bright and playful west one music documentary children storytelling business corporate beds business corporate bright optimistic business corporate communication news film score orchestral documentary film score orchestral trailer main movies children storytelling movies family movies romantic comedy nature wildlife vibrant and fresh with gentle dancing pizzicato strings and crisp piano. dramedy. main delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="23497" name="The Time is Now (b)" code="WOM 303 tk014" libraryid="6" albumid="509" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_303_Commercial_Dance/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Charlie Tenku / Jamie Paul Reddington / Emre Ramazanoglu / Sara Jane Novak" comment="Un morceau club emblématique, positif et réjouissant." styleid="1" lengthseconds="189" time="3:09" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_303_Commercial_Dance/WOM303_trk014_THE_TIME_IS_NOW_(B)_Charlie_Tenku_Jamie_Paul_Reddington_Emre_Ramazanoglu_Sara_Jane_Novak_.mp3" track="14" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRO, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRO, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HOUSE, POP, UNDERSCORE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, SPORT, EXERCICE, FITNESS, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), VOCAL, FÉMININ, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEFILE DE MODE, FEMININ, DEFILE Un morceau club emblématique, positif et réjouissant. wom 303 tk014 charlie tenku jamie paul reddington emre ramazanoglu sara jane novak the time is now (b) wom 303 commercial dance west one music dance electro club electronica electro club electronica electro club electronica house pop underscore activities settings fashion show sports exercise fitness tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio sports uplifting euphoric tempo a spine-tingling life affirming club anthem. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="22960" name="Young Guns (a)" code="WOM 291 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="496" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_291_Go_Go_Indie/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Wesley Ayers" comment="Indé euphorique et significatif." styleid="34" lengthseconds="184" time="3:04" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_291_Go_Go_Indie/WOM_291_trk001_YOUNG_GUNS_(A)_David_Wesley_Ayers_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="POP, POP POUR ENFANTS, ENFANTS, ROCK, INDIE, PRINCIPAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, SPORT, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), ELEMENTS, JOURNEE Indé euphorique et significatif. wom 291 tk001 david wesley ayers young guns (a) wom 291 go go indie west one music indie pop kiddie pop children rock indie main nature wildlife the elements land sun tropical seaside sports tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio talkshow entertainment daytime happy feel good uplifting euphoric movement rhythmic driving euphoric life-affirming indie. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="22232" name="We Could Be Happy (b)" code="WOM 275 tk013" libraryid="6" albumid="477" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_275_Acoustic_Pop/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Rob Rewes" comment="Entraînant, insouciant et fun. Voix de femme." styleid="7" lengthseconds="152" time="2:32" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_275_Acoustic_Pop/WOM275_trk013_WE_COULD_BE_HAPPY_(B)_Rob_Rewes_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="13" tracktotal="" search="POP, POP POUR ENFANTS, ENFANTS, POP, UNDERSCORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, SOLEIL, CHALEUR, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, FUN, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, ENJOUÉ, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PERIODE, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), ENJOUE, ANNEES 2000, ANNEES 20, ELEMENTS, METEO, JOURNEE, ETE Entraînant, insouciant et fun. Voix de femme. wom 275 tk013 rob rewes we could be happy (b) wom 275 acoustic pop west one music pop pop kiddie pop children pop underscore nature wildlife the elements land sun tropical seaside nature wildlife the elements weather sun heat tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio talkshow entertainment daytime happy feel good happy fun happy happy happy catchy carefree and fun. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="21406" name="Until Youre Mine (a)" code="WOM 362 tk009" libraryid="6" albumid="459" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_362_Teen_Pop_Rock/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Tyler Van Den Berg (PRS), Thomas Collins (ASCAP)" comment="Synth pop rock classe et excitant avec chant positif de boy band." styleid="7" lengthseconds="204" time="3:24" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_362_Teen_Pop_Rock/WOM_362_trk009_UNTIL_YOURE_MINE_(A)_Tyler_Van_Den_Berg_(PRS),_Thomas_Collins_(ASCAP)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="POP, POP, POP, POP POUR ENFANTS, POP, SYNTH POP, POP, PRÉ-ADOLESCENT, PRE-ADOLESCENT, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, CÉRÉMONIE DE REMISE DE PRIX, CEREMONIE DE REMISE DE PRIX, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, ENFANTS, MATERNELLE, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FETE, SPORT, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, PRÉ-ADOLESCENTS, PRE-ADOLESCENT, PRE-ADOLESCENTS, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SITCOM, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, FESTIF, HEUREUX, EXCITÉ, EXCITE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, SEXY, COOL, SEXY, SEXY, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, ENERGIQUE, FORT, ÉPIQUE, EPIQUE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EMBLÉMATIQUE, EMBLEMATIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, COOL, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, SOPHISTIQUÉ, GLOSSY, SOPHISTIQUE, BOY BAND, BATTERIE, BOITE À RYTHMES, BATTERIE ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ÉLECTRONIQUES, ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ELECTRONIQUES, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE, VOCAL, MASCULIN, AVEC PAROLES, SUJET DE LA CHANSON, ESPOIR, SOUHAITER, SUJET DE LA CHANSON, AMOUR, TROUVER L'AMOUR VÉRITABLE, TROUVER L'AMOUR VERITABLE, SUJET DE LA CHANSON, AMOUR, TENSION SEXUELLE, MENÉ PAR L'ARTISTE, MENE PAR L'ARTISTE Synth pop rock classe et excitant avec chant positif de boy band. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 362 tk009 tyler van den berg (prs) thomas collins (ascap) until youre mine (a) wom 362 teen pop rock west one music pop pop pop kiddie pop pop synth pop pop tween main activities settings awards show activities settings children pre school activities settings party sports tv radio children youth tv tweens tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio reality tv tv radio sitcom exciting and stylish synth pop rock featuring positive boy band vocals. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="428434750"/>
    <item id="8039" name="Realise the Dream" code="TSH 039 tk013" libraryid="5" albumid="175" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_039_Life_in_Colour/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Alexander Paul Rudd / Zach Lemmon Lemmon" comment="Un motif festif de progression." styleid="20" lengthseconds="107" time="1:47" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_039_Life_in_Colour/TSH039_trk013_REALISE_THE_DREAM_Alexander_Paul_Rudd_Zach_Lemmon_Lemmon_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="13" tracktotal="" search="POP, POP POUR ENFANTS, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ENFANTS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, COMMUNICATION, ACTUALITÉS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, POP, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, HEUREUX, FESTIF, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, EVOLUTIF, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE,, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ACTUALITES, JOURNEE, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Un motif festif de progression. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede tsh 039 tk013 alexander paul rudd zach lemmon lemmon realise the dream tsh 039 life in colour the scoring house children pop kiddie pop main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) children business corporate bright optimistic business corporate communication news business corporate motivational pop uplifting motivational uplifting uplifting happy celebratory happy feel good happy happy building building celebratory motif. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="21978" name="You Make Me Smile (b)" code="WOM 269 tk015" libraryid="6" albumid="471" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_269_Hitlist/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Tyler Van Den Berg / Kevin Ronnie Mcpherson" comment="Du new wave/R&amp;B qui se met au gospel. Vibrant, euphorique et terriblement entraînant." styleid="7" lengthseconds="152" time="2:32" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_269_Hitlist/WOM269_trk015_YOU_MAKE_ME_SMILE_(B)_Tyler_Van_Den_Berg_Kevin_Ronnie_Mcpherson_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="15" tracktotal="" search="TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, POP, POP POUR ENFANTS, FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, SOUL CONTEMPORAINE, POP, R&amp;B CONTEMPORAIN, POP, RELIGIEUX, CHRÉTIEN, PROTESTANT, CHANSONS GOSPEL, NEGRO SPIRITUALS, UNDERSCORE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CHRETIEN, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEFILE DE MODE, DEFILE Du new wave/R&amp;B qui se met au gospel. Vibrant, euphorique et terriblement entraînant. wom 269 tk015 tyler van den berg kevin ronnie mcpherson you make me smile (b) wom 269 hitlist west one music pop pop kiddie pop funk soul r&amp;b contemporary soul pop contemporary r&amp;b pop religious christian protestant gospel songs spirituals underscore activities settings fashion show tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio talkshow nu-wave r&amp;b goes gospel. vibrant euphoric and catchy as hell. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="23738" name="Something Good (b)" code="WOM 309 tk017" libraryid="6" albumid="514" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_309_Indie_Organica/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="John-Paul Jones" comment="Audacieuses guitares infusées de soleil et batterie entrainante. Édifiant et inspirant." styleid="34" lengthseconds="145" time="2:25" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_309_Indie_Organica/WOM_309_trk017_SOMETHING_GOOD_(B)_John-Paul_Jones_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="17" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, POP CORPORATE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, ROCK, INDIE, ALTERNATIF, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, SPORT, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ELECTRIQUE, ELEMENTS Audacieuses guitares infusées de soleil et batterie entrainante. Édifiant et inspirant. wom 309 tk017 john-paul jones something good (b) wom 309 indie organica west one music indie business corporate corporate pop business corporate motivational rock indie alternate business corporate nature wildlife the elements land sun tropical seaside sports tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio sports strong prestigious uplifting motivational uplifting bold sunshine-soaked guitars and driving drums. uplifting and inspiring. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="21262" name="The Breakthrough (a)" code="WOM 254A tk004" libraryid="6" albumid="456" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_254A_Supercharger_-_Indie/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Tyler Van Den Berg" comment="Des guitares stridentes et des refrains épiques qui célèbrent la vie." styleid="34" lengthseconds="124" time="2:04" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_254A_Supercharger_-_Indie/WOM254A_trk004_THE_BREAKTHROUGH_(A)_Tyler_Van_Den_Berg_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, INDIE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 90, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ROCK, ROCK DE STADE, FORT, ÉPIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, SPORT, SPORTS EXTREMES,, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), EPIQUE, ANNEES 2000, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 20, ANNEES 90 Des guitares stridentes et des refrains épiques qui célèbrent la vie. wom 254a tk004 tyler van den berg the breakthrough (a) wom 254a supercharger - indie west one music indie rock indie time period modern era 20th century 1990s time period modern era 2000s main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) rock stadium rock strong epic movement rhythmic driving movement rhythmic rugged movies epic tv radio sports sports extreme sports jangling guitars and epic life affirming choruses. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="22456" name="Summer Sun (a)" code="WOM 281 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="483" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_281_Catchy_Carefree_&amp;_Cool/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jonathan D Wiesler / Scott Blackwell Stafford / David Lebolt / Alexis Harte" comment="Entraînant et insouciant avec des guitares acoustiques ensoleillées et entremêlées avec des accroches de clavier." styleid="7" lengthseconds="122" time="2:02" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_281_Catchy_Carefree_&amp;_Cool/WOM281_trk001_SUMMER_SUN_(A)_Jonathan_D_Wiesler_Scott_Blackwell_Stafford_David_Lebolt_Alexis_Hart.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="POP, POP POUR ENFANTS, ENFANTS, PRINCIPAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, ENJOUÉ, PAISIBLE, DÉTENDU, ACOUSTIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UN TRAIN, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), ENJOUE, DETENDU, ELEMENTS, JOURNEE Entraînant et insouciant avec des guitares acoustiques ensoleillées et entremêlées avec des accroches de clavier. wom 281 tk001 jonathan d wiesler scott blackwell stafford david lebolt alexis harte summer sun (a) wom 281 catchy carefree &amp; cool west one music pop pop kiddie pop children main nature wildlife the elements land sun tropical seaside tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio talkshow entertainment daytime happy feel good happy happy catchy and carefree with sunny intertwining acoustic guitars and keyboard hooks. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="17690" name="Spellbound Symphony (a)" code="WOM 361 tk002" libraryid="6" albumid="373" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_361_Female_Indie_Pop/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Victoria F. Beaumont (PRS)" comment="Indie pop spectaculaire avec chant féminin sur de soi. Des couplets atmoshériques se développent en un chorus exaltant." styleid="34" lengthseconds="226" time="3:46" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_361_Female_Indie_Pop/WOM_361_trk002_SPELLBOUND_SYMPHONY_(A)_Victoria_F._Beaumont_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="POP, POP, POP, ELECTRO POP, POP, SYNTH POP, ROCK, ROCK ALTERNATIF, ROCK, INDIE, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, ROAD TRIP, FILMS, ƒPIQUE, EPIQUE, FILMS, FILMS INDƒPENDANTS, FILMS INDEPENDANTS, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TƒLƒ RƒALITƒ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, FESTIF, HEUREUX, EXCITƒ, EXCITE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, FUN, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, SEXY, COOL, FORT, ƒPIQUE, EPIQUE, FORT, EXALTANT, FORT, PUISSANT, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EMBLƒMATIQUE, EMBLEMATIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EVOLUTIF, MONTEE, MONTƒE, EVOLUTION, MƒLODIQUE, LYRIQUE, MELODIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, BATTERIE, BATTERIE, BATTERIE, TOMS, INSTRUMENTS ƒLECTRONIQUES, ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ELECTRONIQUES, CORDES, BASSE, BASSE ƒLECTRIQUE, BASSE ELECTRIQUE, CORDES, GUITARE, ƒLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE, VOCAL, FƒMININ, FEMININ, AVEC PAROLES, SUJET DE LA CHANSON, ESPOIR, INSPIRATION, SUJET DE LA CHANSON, AMOUR, TROUVER L'AMOUR VƒRITABLE, TROUVER L'AMOUR VERITABLE, MENƒ PAR L'ARTISTE, MENE PAR L'ARTISTE Indie pop spectaculaire avec chant féminin sur de soi. Des couplets atmoshériques se développent en un chorus exaltant. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 361 tk002 victoria f. beaumont (prs) spellbound symphony (a) wom 361 female indie pop west one music indie pop pop electro pop pop synth pop rock alternative rock rock indie main activities settings road trip movies epic movies indie films movies urban drama tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio reality tv tv radio sports happy epic indie pop with empowering female vocals. atmospheric verses build to inspiring choruses. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="428434750"/>
  </items>
</librarycollection>
