<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<librarycollection>
  <items>
    <item id="26488" name="Peaceful Perfection (a)" code="WOM 304 tk014" libraryid="6" albumid="568" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_304_Emotive_Minimalism/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Piano léger et mélodies éblouissantes de cordes solo, avec un accompagnement subtil." styleid="4" lengthseconds="229" time="3:49" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_304_Emotive_Minimalism/WOM304_trk014_PEACEFUL_PERFECTION_(A)_Richard_Allen_Harvey_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="14" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, ENFANTS, CONTES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, AUTOMNE, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TENDRE, INNOCENT, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, ANGLETERRE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), AERIEN, ELEMENTS Piano léger et mélodies éblouissantes de cordes solo, avec un accompagnement subtil. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 304 tk014 richard allen harvey peaceful perfection (a) wom 304 emotive minimalism west one music film score orchestral children storytelling children storytelling film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic film score orchestral pastoral main movies children storytelling nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife the elements land rural gentle piano and stunning solo string melodies with subtle backing. main delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="3508" name="A Perfect Stillness (d)" code="TSH 014A tk054" libraryid="5" albumid="104" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_014A_Smile-_A_Most_Cheerful_Earful/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Brian Douglas Gulland" comment="Contemplation tranquille avec un piano en solo lent." styleid="17" lengthseconds="274" time="4:34" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_014A_Smile-_A_Most_Cheerful_Earful/TSH_014A_trk054_A_PERFECT_STILLNESS_(D)_Brian_Douglas_Gulland_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="54" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, ALTERNATIF, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, PAISIBLE, TRANQUILLE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, SÉRIEUX, DIGNE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, RALENTI, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CLAVIER, PIANO, SOLO, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, ANGLETERRE, PERIODE, SERIEUX, DEPRIMANT, PERIODES, ELEMENTS Contemplation tranquille avec un piano en solo lent. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 014a tk054 brian douglas gulland a perfect stillness (d) tsh 014a smile: a most cheerful earful the scoring house comedy traditional ethnic folk national and ethnic national folk dance film score orchestral trailer main documentary biographical historical the arts movies period historical costume drama nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral happy rollicking tempo tranquil contemplation for slow solo piano. alternative" waveformpath="" version="Alternative" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="20397" name="Waves of Light (a)" code="WOM 233 tk009" libraryid="6" albumid="434" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_233_Atmospheric_Indie/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Matthew James Robertson / Mike Reed / Tom Howe" comment="Des atmosphères sonores riches et expansives avec des motifs de piano éblouissants. Progression dès 1:45." styleid="34" lengthseconds="209" time="3:29" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_233_Atmospheric_Indie/WOM233_trk009_WAVES_OF_LIGHT_(A)_Matthew_James_Robertson_Mike_Reed_Tom_Howe_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, ROCK, INDIE, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, MÉDICAL, SCIENCES DE LA VIE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, EVOLUTIF, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), SOUND DESIGN, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), AERIEN, ELEMENTS, MEDICAL, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Des atmosphères sonores riches et expansives avec des motifs de piano éblouissants. Progression dès 1:45. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 233 tk009 matthew james robertson mike reed tom howe waves of light (a) wom 233 atmospheric indie west one music indie business corporate science technology business corporate luxury rock indie main business corporate nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife science technology industry medical life science tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden tv radio leisure rich expansive soundscapes with stunning piano patterns. building from 1:45. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="26120" name="Light Stream" code="WOM 062 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="559" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_062_Chilled_Orchestral/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Paul Reeves (Gb 2)" comment="Un motif de cordes clair et tranquille avec des harmoniques lancinants." styleid="4" lengthseconds="99" time="1:39" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_062_Chilled_Orchestral/WOM062_trk001_LIGHT_STREAM_Paul_Reeves_(Gb_2)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, TRANQUILLE, TROUBLANT, STÉRILE, TROUBLANT, FROID , TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE,, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), STERILE, ELEMENTS Un motif de cordes clair et tranquille avec des harmoniques lancinants. wom 062 tk001 paul reeves (gb 2) light stream wom 062 chilled orchestral west one music film score orchestral sound elements atmospheres main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) business corporate beds peaceful dreamy peaceful tranquil disturbing barren disturbing cold disturbing mysterious business corporate clear and tranquil string pattern with haunting harmonics. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="2758" name="Spatial Horizons (a)" code="TSH 002 tk010" libraryid="5" albumid="93" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_002_Evolutions/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Robert Henry Peter White" comment="Des dimensions musicales évoluant graduellement." styleid="11" lengthseconds="133" time="2:13" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_002_Evolutions/TSH002_trk010_SPATIAL_HORIZONS_(A)_Robert_Henry_Peter_White_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="10" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, AMBIANCES ET FONDS SONORES POUR PROJETS, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, NUIT, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, ZEN, MÉDITATION , COOL, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, RALENTI, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, FUTURISTE, ELEMENTS SONORES, PERIODE, ATMOSPHERES, MEDITATION, ACCELERE, AERIEN, ELEMENTS Des dimensions musicales évoluant graduellement. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz tsh 002 tk010 robert henry peter white spatial horizons (a) tsh 002 evolutions the scoring house corporate business sound elements atmospheres business corporate beds business corporate luxury business corporate science technology main business corporate documentary science technology science technology industry design beds tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio talkshow gradually evolving dimensions. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="26239" name="Still Life" code="WOM 163 tk007" libraryid="6" albumid="562" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_163_Modern_Solo_Piano/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Clifford Eric Haywood" comment="Une beauté méditative et intense." styleid="4" lengthseconds="175" time="2:55" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_163_Modern_Solo_Piano/WOM163_trk007_STILL_LIFE_Clifford_Eric_Haywood_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SOLO, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, SÉRIEUX, ATTENTIONNÉ, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, DOCUMENTAIRE, CLAVIER, PIANO,, ELEMENTS SONORES, SERIEUX, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ATTENTIONNE, ELEMENTS Une beauté méditative et intense. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 163 tk007 clifford eric haywood still life wom 163 modern solo piano west one music film score orchestral sound elements atmospheres main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) business corporate solo tender nostalgic tender reflective tender romantic tender sentimental serious thoughtful dramatic intense movement rhythmic clock like business corporate documentary keyboard piano thoughtful and intense beauty. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="17341" name="Sea of Tranquillity (a)" code="WOM 169 tk012" libraryid="6" albumid="364" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_169_Brave_New_World/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Patrick Thomas Hawes" comment="Atmosphérique et calmant. Des phrases réverbérantes de harpe avec un alto lead éthéré." styleid="12" lengthseconds="128" time="2:08" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_169_Brave_New_World/WOM169_trk012_SEA_OF_TRANQUILLITY_(A)_Patrick_Thomas_Hawes_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PRINCIPAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MER, SOUS-MARIN, PAISIBLE, LYRIQUE, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TRANQUILLE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, MÉLANCOLIE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CORDES, VIOLE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, MELANCOLIE, ELEMENTS Atmosphérique et calmant. Des phrases réverbérantes de harpe avec un alto lead éthéré. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 169 tk012 patrick thomas hawes sea of tranquillity (a) wom 169 brave new world west one music atmospheres film score orchestral pastoral main nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife nature wildlife the elements sea underwater peaceful lyrical peaceful peaceful peaceful tranquil sad depressing lonely sad depressing melancholy sad depressing poignant tempo atmospheric and calming. reverberant harp phrases with ethereal viola lead. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="17613" name="Orbital Moods (a)" code="WOM 175 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="371" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_175_Zero_Gravity/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Bill Connor" comment="Rêveur et optimiste. Des fonds sonores flottants de textures lumineuses progressent vers des percussions comme des battements de cœur et des mélodies délicates de célesta." styleid="12" lengthseconds="184" time="3:04" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_175_Zero_Gravity/WOM175_trk001_ORBITAL_MOODS_(A)_Bill_Connor_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, CLASSIQUE, STYLE MINIMALISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MER, SOUS-MARIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, AUBE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, ESPACE, INTERSIDÉRAL, TROUBLANT, DÉSORIENTÉ, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, TENDRE, DÉLICAT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, COOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, RALENTI, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLAVIER, CELESTE, EFFETS SONORES, HUMAIN, BATTEMENTS DE COEUR, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DESORIENTE, DELICAT, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, INTERSIDERAL Rêveur et optimiste. Des fonds sonores flottants de textures lumineuses progressent vers des percussions comme des battements de cœur et des mélodies délicates de célesta. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 175 tk001 bill connor orbital moods (a) wom 175 zero gravity west one music atmospheres sound elements atmospheres classical minimalist style business corporate science technology main documentary science technology nature wildlife the elements sea underwater nature wildlife the elements seasons time dawn nature wildlife the elements sky aerial clouds dream-like and optimistic. drifting beds of luminous textures build with heartbeat percussion and delicate celeste melodies. main delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="7080" name="Strange Forms (b)" code="TSH 026A tk019" libraryid="5" albumid="162" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_026A_Dimensions/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Dave Hewson / Alexander Balanescu" comment="Une étrange asymétrie angulaire de quintette de violons." styleid="4" lengthseconds="122" time="2:02" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_026A_Dimensions/TSH026A_trk019_STRANGE_FORMS_(B)_Dave_Hewson_Alexander_Balanescu_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="19" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, CLASSIQUE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, ALTERNATIF, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, TROUBLANT, ÉTRANGE , TROUBLANT, BIZARRE, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, EXCENTRIQUE, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, INSECTE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ELEMENTS SONORES, PERIODE, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ETRANGE, IRREGULIER, 20E SIECLE, ELEMENTS Une étrange asymétrie angulaire de quintette de violons. tsh 026a tk019 dave hewson alexander balanescu strange forms (b) tsh 026a dimensions the scoring house film score orchestral sound elements atmospheres classical business corporate science technology alternate documentary biographical historical the arts documentary science technology nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife science technology industry disturbing strange disturbing bizarre angular asymmetry for violin quintet. alternative" waveformpath="" version="Alternative" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="26297" name="L'Aura (a)" code="WOM 177 tk006" libraryid="6" albumid="563" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_177_Reflections/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Des motifs de piano luxueux et tranquilles glissent sur des cordes rêveuses suspendues." styleid="4" lengthseconds="125" time="2:05" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_177_Reflections/WOM177_trk006_L'AURA_(A)_Richard_Allen_Harvey_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="6" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, HIVER, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, MÉDICAL, SCIENCES DE LA VIE, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TRANQUILLE, SÉRIEUX, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, TEMPO, 66 - 76 À L'AISE (ADAGIO), CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, VIOLON, SERIEUX, 66 - 76 A L'AISE (ADAGIO), ACCELERE, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, MEDICAL Des motifs de piano luxueux et tranquilles glissent sur des cordes rêveuses suspendues. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 177 tk006 richard allen harvey l'aura (a) wom 177 reflections west one music film score orchestral business corporate beds business corporate bright optimistic business corporate science technology film score orchestral trailer main business corporate movies human drama nature wildlife the elements seasons time winter nature wildlife the elements sky aerial clouds lush and tranquil piano patterns drift over dreamy suspended strings. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="26369" name="Silent Beauty (a)" code="WOM 209 tk005" libraryid="6" albumid="565" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_209_Absolution/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Toby Y. Chu" comment="Emouvant et méditatif. Un piano magnifique glisse sur des cordes et un design sonore luxueux." styleid="4" lengthseconds="126" time="2:06" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_209_Absolution/WOM209_trk005_SILENT_BEAUTY_(A)_Toby_Y._Chu_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, SOUND DESIGN, TITRE POUR TRAILER, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRAGIQUE, SÉRIEUX, TROUBLANT, FILMS, ART ET ESSAI, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, TRAILERS, DOCUMENTAIRE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, CLAVIER, PIANO,, ELEMENTS SONORES, SERIEUX, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, ELEMENTS Emouvant et méditatif. Un piano magnifique glisse sur des cordes et un design sonore luxueux. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 209 tk005 toby y. chu silent beauty (a) wom 209 absolution west one music film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) sound elements atmospheres sound design trailer track peaceful contented tender nostalgic tender reflective tender romantic tender sentimental sad depressing poignant sad depressing sad sad depressing emotive and reflective. gorgeous piano drifts over lush strings and sound design. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="17301" name="Infinite Peace (a)" code="WOM 168 tk008" libraryid="6" albumid="363" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_168_Emotional_Ambience/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Dan Graham" comment="Des phrases douces de guitare électrique glissent sur un piano et des cordes super détendus." styleid="12" lengthseconds="221" time="3:41" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_168_Emotional_Ambience/WOM168_trk008_INFINITE_PEACE_(A)_Dan_Graham_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="8" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, DÉTENDU, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, DIVIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, DIVIN, CÉLESTE,, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETENDU, ELEGANT, ELEMENTS, CELESTE Des phrases douces de guitare électrique glissent sur un piano et des cordes super détendus. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 168 tk008 dan graham infinite peace (a) wom 168 emotional ambience west one music atmospheres sound elements atmospheres main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) sound elements atmospheres uplifting euphoric peaceful dreamy peaceful relaxed tender romantic movement smooth elegant movement smooth flowing movement smooth graceful heavenly nature wildlife the elements sky mellow electric guitar phrases drifting over super-chilled piano and strings. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="2835" name="Wide Blue" code="TSH 003 tk022" libraryid="5" albumid="94" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_003_Deeper_Minimal/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Robert John Foster" comment="Une vue large et tranquille / un paysage sonore large." styleid="12" lengthseconds="75" time="1:15" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_003_Deeper_Minimal/TSH003_trk022_WIDE_BLUE_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="22" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, TRANQUILLE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, MONTÉE, DOCUMENTAIRE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MER, PAYSAGE MARIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MER, SOUS-MARIN,, ELEMENTS SONORES, MONTEE, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), AERIEN, ELEMENTS Une vue large et tranquille / un paysage sonore large. tsh 003 tk022 robert john foster wide blue tsh 003 deeper minimal the scoring house atmospheres sound elements atmospheres main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) peaceful dreamy peaceful tranquil movement smooth aerial floating movement smooth aerial flying movement smooth flowing movement smooth rising documentary nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife broad tranquil vista broad soundscape. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="7888" name="Dancing Light (a)" code="TSH 004 tk023" libraryid="5" albumid="173" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_004_Natural_Wonders/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon David Chamberlain" comment="Des textures délicates crystallines et chatoyantes." styleid="26" lengthseconds="185" time="3:05" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_004_Natural_Wonders/TSH004_trk023_DANCING_LIGHT_(A)_Simon_David_Chamberlain_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="23" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, ZEN, MÉDITATION , TENDRE, DÉLICAT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, DIVIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MER, SOUS-MARIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, DIVIN, CÉLESTE,, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DELICAT, MEDITATION, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, CELESTE Des textures délicates crystallines et chatoyantes. tsh 004 tk023 simon david chamberlain dancing light (a) tsh 004 natural wonders the scoring house nature wildlife sound elements atmospheres main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) peaceful dreamy peaceful peaceful peaceful zen meditation tender delicate movement smooth aerial floating heavenly nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife nature wildlife the elements sea underwater delicate crystalline shimmering textures. main delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="3111" name="Story's End (a)" code="TSH 008 tk002" libraryid="5" albumid="99" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_008_Ambient_Spirit/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Everard Lawrence Wells / Robert John Foster" comment="Conclusion évocatrice." styleid="15" lengthseconds="139" time="2:19" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_008_Ambient_Spirit/TSH008_trk002_STORY'S_END_(A)_Richard_Everard_Lawrence_Wells_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, NEIGE, GLACE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MER, SOUS-MARIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, ESPACE, INTERSIDÉRAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, FROID, STÉRILE, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, RALENTI, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), STERILE, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, METEO, ETE, INTERSIDERAL Conclusion évocatrice. tsh 008 tk002 richard everard lawrence wells robert john foster story's end (a) tsh 008 ambient spirit the scoring house ambient chill sound elements atmospheres main nature wildlife the elements land snow ice nature wildlife the elements sea underwater nature wildlife the elements sky aerial clouds nature wildlife the elements sky space outer space nature wildlife the elements weather cold barren evocative conclusion. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="4052" name="Memories in Sepia" code="TSH 022 tk017" libraryid="5" albumid="114" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_022_Human_Stories/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Michael Price" comment="Un piano solo profond et hésitant." styleid="10" lengthseconds="141" time="2:21" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_022_Human_Stories/TSH022_trk017_MEMORIES_IN_SEPIA_Michael_Price_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="17" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), SOLO, TENDRE, INNOCENT, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, SÉRIEUX, ATTENTIONNÉ, DOCUMENTAIRE, CLAVIER, PIANO,, SERIEUX, ATTENTIONNE Un piano solo profond et hésitant. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 022 tk017 michael price memories in sepia tsh 022 human stories the scoring house documentary children main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) solo tender innocent tender intimate tender nostalgic tender romantic tender sentimental serious thoughtful documentary keyboard piano thoughtful hesitant solo piano. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="7062" name="Celestial Journeys (a)" code="TSH 026A tk001" libraryid="5" albumid="162" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_026A_Dimensions/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Dave Hewson / Alexander Balanescu" comment="L'imagerie légère et nébuleuse de l'errance." styleid="4" lengthseconds="134" time="2:14" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_026A_Dimensions/TSH026A_trk001_CELESTIAL_JOURNEYS_(A)_Dave_Hewson_Alexander_Balanescu_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PRINCIPAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, DIVIN, CÉLESTE, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TENDRE, LÉGER, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, CORDES, VIOLON, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), LEGER, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, CELESTE L'imagerie légère et nébuleuse de l'errance. tsh 026a tk001 dave hewson alexander balanescu celestial journeys (a) tsh 026a dimensions the scoring house film score orchestral sound elements atmospheres film score orchestral pastoral main nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife nature wildlife the elements sky aerial light nebulous drifting imagery. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="3439" name="Wishes in the Wind" code="TSH 013 tk012" libraryid="5" albumid="103" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_013_It's_My_Life/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Ian Paul Livingstone" comment="Des espérances silencieuses et secrètes." styleid="10" lengthseconds="111" time="1:51" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_013_It's_My_Life/TSH013_trk012_WISHES_IN_THE_WIND_Ian_Paul_Livingstone_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, TROUBLANT, DROLE, MÉLODRAMATIQUE, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, INTROSPECTIF, PAISIBLE, DOUX, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, SÉRIEUX, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLAVIER, PIANO, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), MELODRAMATIQUE, DEPRIMANT, ELEMENTS Des espérances silencieuses et secrètes. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 013 tk012 ian paul livingstone wishes in the wind tsh 013 it's my life the scoring house documentary film score orchestral pastoral main documentary movies human drama nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife disturbing funny melodramatic peaceful dreamy peaceful introspective peaceful quiet sad depressing lonely sad depressing poignant sad depressing sad quiet introspective hopes. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="17148" name="The Water Nymph" code="WOM 165 tk013" libraryid="6" albumid="360" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_165_The_Pastoral_Album/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Patrick Thomas Hawes" comment="Un solo éthéré de harpe. Des couleurs harmoniques, atmosphériques et spacieuses." styleid="26" lengthseconds="127" time="2:07" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_165_The_Pastoral_Album/WOM165_trk013_THE_WATER_NYMPH_Patrick_Thomas_Hawes_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="13" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PRINCIPAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MER, SOUS-MARIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, ÉTÉ, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CORDES, HARPE, SOLO, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, ETE Un solo éthéré de harpe. Des couleurs harmoniques, atmosphériques et spacieuses. wom 165 tk013 patrick thomas hawes the water nymph wom 165 the pastoral album west one music nature wildlife sound elements atmospheres film score orchestral pastoral main nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife nature wildlife the elements sea underwater nature wildlife the elements seasons time summer ethereal solo harp. atmospheric and spacious harmonic colours. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="3142" name="Floating By" code="TSH 008 tk033" libraryid="5" albumid="99" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_008_Ambient_Spirit/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Everard Lawrence Wells / Robert John Foster" comment="Un motif chaleureux et apaisé." styleid="15" lengthseconds="98" time="1:38" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_008_Ambient_Spirit/TSH008_trk033_FLOATING_BY_Richard_Everard_Lawrence_Wells_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="33" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS SONORES, SIFFLEMENT, CRÉPITEMENT, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MER, SOUS-MARIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, AUBE,, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), CREPITEMENT, AERIEN, ELEMENTS Un motif chaleureux et apaisé. tsh 008 tk033 richard everard lawrence wells robert john foster floating by tsh 008 ambient spirit the scoring house ambient chill sound elements atmospheres sound effects hiss crackle main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) peaceful dreamy peaceful peaceful tender reflective tender warm movement smooth aerial floating movement smooth aerial flying movement smooth flowing nature wildlife the elements warm peaceful motif. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="20899" name="Into Thin Air (a)" code="WOM 246 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="447" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_246_Atmospheric_Guitar/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Dan Cassady" comment="Epars, spacieux et merveilleusement évocateur." styleid="12" lengthseconds="221" time="3:41" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_246_Atmospheric_Guitar/WOM246_trk001_INTO_THIN_AIR_(A)_Dan_Cassady_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EASY LISTENING, NEW AGE, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, ABSTRAIT, CLAIRSEMÉ, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, DÉTENDU, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, COOL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, RALENTI, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ELEMENTS SONORES, PERIODE, ATMOSPHERES, CLAIRSEME, DETENDU, ACCELERE, AERIEN, ELECTRIQUE, ELEMENTS Epars, spacieux et merveilleusement évocateur. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 246 tk001 dan cassady into thin air (a) wom 246 atmospheric guitar west one music atmospheres sound elements atmospheres easy listening new age main documentary biographical historical the arts nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife nature wildlife the elements sky aerial clouds abstract sparse peaceful dreamy peaceful relaxed tender warm cool sparse spacious and wonderfully evocative. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="26476" name="Inner Beauty (a)" code="WOM 304 tk002" libraryid="6" albumid="568" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_304_Emotive_Minimalism/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Une beauté cristalline. Cordes tendres, piano répétitif et chant féminin sans paroles." styleid="4" lengthseconds="178" time="2:58" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_304_Emotive_Minimalism/WOM304_trk002_INNER_BEAUTY_(A)_Richard_Allen_Harvey_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE, CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MER, PAYSAGE MARIN, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, TENDRE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, TEXTURE VOCALE, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, ANGLETERRE, AERIEN, ELEMENTS Une beauté cristalline. Cordes tendres, piano répétitif et chant féminin sans paroles. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 304 tk002 richard allen harvey inner beauty (a) wom 304 emotive minimalism west one music film score orchestral classical classical styling classical classical styling film score orchestral panoramic film score orchestral pastoral main documentary biographical historical the arts nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside crystalline beauty with tender strings and repeating piano patterns. featuring wordless female vocal. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="7670" name="Bubble Stream" code="TSH 041 tk006" libraryid="5" albumid="171" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_041_Through_the_Lens/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Colin John Riley" comment="Une progression sonore de couleurs kaléidoscopiques." styleid="24" lengthseconds="159" time="2:39" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_041_Through_the_Lens/TSH041_trk006_BUBBLE_STREAM_Colin_John_Riley_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="6" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, CLASSIQUE, STYLE MINIMALISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, COMMUNICATION, ACTUALITÉS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MER, SOUS-MARIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, PLUIE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, AMBIANCES ET FONDS SONORES POUR PROJETS, TENDRE, DÉLICAT, EVOLUTIF, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, INSECTE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, FUTURISTE, ELEMENTS SONORES, PERIODE, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DELICAT, IRREGULIER, ACCELERE, ACTUALITES, ELEMENTS, METEO, ETE, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Une progression sonore de couleurs kaléidoscopiques. tsh 041 tk006 colin john riley bubble stream tsh 041 through the lens the scoring house science new technology sound elements atmospheres classical minimalist style business corporate beds business corporate communication news business corporate science technology main documentary science technology nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife nature wildlife the elements sea building kaleidoscopic colours. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="7065" name="One Perfect Day (a)" code="TSH 026A tk004" libraryid="5" albumid="162" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_026A_Dimensions/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Dave Hewson / Alexander Balanescu" comment="Tranquilité lyrique." styleid="4" lengthseconds="107" time="1:47" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_026A_Dimensions/TSH026A_trk004_ONE_PERFECT_DAY_(A)_Dave_Hewson_Alexander_Balanescu_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, MUSIQUE DE CHAMBRE, ENSEMBLE CLASSIQUE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, LYRIQUE, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MÉLODIQUE, LYRIQUE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, CORDES, VIOLON ,, MELODIQUE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), AERIEN, ELEMENTS Tranquilité lyrique. tsh 026a tk004 dave hewson alexander balanescu one perfect day (a) tsh 026a dimensions the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral pastoral classical and semi classical chamber music classical ensemble main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) peaceful dreamy peaceful lyrical peaceful peaceful movement smooth aerial flying melodic lyrical nature wildlife the elements nature study lyrical tranquillity. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="26380" name="Inner World (b)" code="WOM 209 tk016" libraryid="6" albumid="565" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_209_Absolution/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Toby Y. Chu" comment="Un thème beau et délicat, avec un gamelan et des guitares électriques." styleid="4" lengthseconds="143" time="2:23" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_209_Absolution/WOM209_trk016_INNER_WORLD_(B)_Toby_Y._Chu_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="16" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, CLASSIQUE, STYLE MINIMALISTE, ALTERNATIF, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, ART ET ESSAI, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, DÉTENDU, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, SÉRIEUX, TENDRE, DÉLICAT, TENDRE, SONGEUR, BEAU, CHUTE, DESCENTE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ETHNIQUE, PERCUSSION, GAMELAN, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETENDU, DEPRIMANT, DELICAT, ACCELERE, AERIEN, ELECTRIQUE, ELEMENTS Un thème beau et délicat, avec un gamelan et des guitares électriques. wom 209 tk016 toby y. chu inner world (b) wom 209 absolution west one music film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer classical minimalist style alternate documentary movies art house movies human drama nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife trailer track disturbing mysterious peaceful contented beautiful delicate theme featuring gamelan and electric guitars. alternative delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Alternative" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="7122" name="Nirvana (a)" code="TSH 029 tk004" libraryid="5" albumid="164" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_029_Symphonic_Fantasia/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Arthur Rhodes" comment="Serein, enveloppant, flottant." styleid="4" lengthseconds="199" time="3:19" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_029_Symphonic_Fantasia/TSH029_trk004_NIRVANA_(A)_Simon_Arthur_Rhodes_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, ESPACE, INTERSIDÉRAL, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, SEREIN, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, RALENTI, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, CLAVIER, PIANO, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, DEPRIMANT, ACCELERE, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, INTERSIDERAL Serein, enveloppant, flottant. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 029 tk004 simon arthur rhodes nirvana (a) tsh 029 symphonic fantasia the scoring house film score orchestral sound elements atmospheres film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic main movies romance nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife nature wildlife the elements sky aerial clouds nature serene immersive drifting. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="5510" name="A Peculiar Story" code="TSH 054 tk018" libraryid="5" albumid="139" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_054_Humouresque/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Stefan Melzak" comment="Thème curieux et énigmatique." styleid="17" lengthseconds="121" time="2:01" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_054_Humouresque/TSH054_trk018_A_PECULIAR_STORY_Stefan_Melzak_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="18" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, EUROPE, EUROPE DE L'OUEST, FRANCE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ENFANTS, CONTES, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS,, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ESPIEGLE Thème curieux et énigmatique. tsh 054 tk018 stefan melzak a peculiar story tsh 054 humouresque the scoring house comedy children storytelling europe western europe france main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) children storytelling funny comedic funny mischievous movement rhythmic stealthy movies children storytelling documentary biographical historical the arts curious enigmatic theme. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="4146" name="House of Hide and Seek (a)" code="TSH 025 tk024" libraryid="5" albumid="116" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_025_Tangled_Tales/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Marc Frederick Teitler" comment="Des jeux fragmentaires et furtifs." styleid="20" lengthseconds="58" time="0:58" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_025_Tangled_Tales/TSH025_trk024_HOUSE_OF_HIDE_AND_SEEK_(A)_Marc_Frederick_Teitler_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="24" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, HUMORISTIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, PIZZICATO, FILMS, ANIMATION, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, TV, RADIO, DESSINS ANIMÉS, CORDES, CORDES PIZZICATO,, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ESPIEGLE, DECALE, DESSINS ANIMES Des jeux fragmentaires et furtifs. tsh 025 tk024 marc frederick teitler house of hide and seek (a) tsh 025 tangled tales the scoring house children children storytelling main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) funny comedic funny eccentric funny humorous funny mischievous funny quirky movement rhythmic stealthy pizzicato movies animation movies children storytelling tv radio cartoons strings pizzicato strings furtive fragmentary games. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="2868" name="Small Wonders" code="TSH 003 tk055" libraryid="5" albumid="94" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_003_Deeper_Minimal/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Robert John Foster" comment="Un émerveillement simple et enfantin." styleid="12" lengthseconds="86" time="1:26" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_003_Deeper_Minimal/TSH003_trk055_SMALL_WONDERS_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="55" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TENDRE, INNOCENT, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, ABSTRAIT, SIMPLE, ENFANTIN, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, DOCUMENTAIRE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE,, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), DEPRIMANT, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS Un émerveillement simple et enfantin. tsh 003 tk055 robert john foster small wonders tsh 003 deeper minimal the scoring house atmospheres children main tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) peaceful dreamy peaceful peaceful tender innocent tender warm sad depressing poignant sad depressing sad disturbing mysterious abstract simple childlike movies crime detective mystery movies human drama documentary simple childlike wonderment. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="23231" name="Life Circle" code="WOM 297 tk024" libraryid="6" albumid="502" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_297_Something_Simple/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Thomas Greenberg" comment="Motifs minimalistes de piano et marimbas. Songeur et attentionné." styleid="16" lengthseconds="115" time="1:55" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_297_Something_Simple/WOM297_trk024_LIFE_CIRCLE_Thomas_Greenberg_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="24" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ENFANTS, MATERNELLE, TENDRE, INNOCENT, TENDRE, SONGEUR, SÉRIEUX, ATTENTIONNÉ, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, RÉPÉTITIF, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, ENFANTS, MATERNELLE, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, MATERNELLE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN,, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ATTENTIONNE, REPETITIF Motifs minimalistes de piano et marimbas. Songeur et attentionné. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 297 tk024 thomas greenberg life circle wom 297 something simple west one music quirky children main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) children pre school tender innocent tender reflective serious thoughtful movement rhythmic clock like movement rhythmic repetitive activities settings children pre school tv radio children youth tv pre school tv radio leisure minimal piano patterns and marimbas. reflective and thoughtful. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="12350" name="Cheeky Glance (c)" code="WOM 058 tk016" libraryid="6" albumid="248" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_058_Irresistible/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Matt Norman" comment="Un plaisir orchestral mystérieux et excentrique." styleid="31" lengthseconds="65" time="1:05" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_058_Irresistible/WOM058_trk016_CHEEKY_GLANCE_(C)_Matt_Norman_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="16" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ALTERNATIF, FILMS, COMÉDIE, FILMS, FAMILIAL, FILMS, COMÉDIE ROMANTIQUE, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TENDRE, DÉLICAT, TENDRE, LÉGER, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ENSEMBLE DE JAZZ, GROUPE DE JAZZ, CUIVRES, TUBA, SOUSAPHONE, FORMATIONS GENERALES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DELICAT, LEGER, COMEDIE, COMEDIE ROMANTIQUE Un plaisir orchestral mystérieux et excentrique. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 058 tk016 matt norman cheeky glance (c) wom 058 irresistible west one music romantic film score orchestral trailer alternate movies comedy movies family movies romantic comedy trailers trailer track tender delicate tender light tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) general lineups jazz ensemble jazz band brass tuba sousaphone mysterious and quirky orchestral fun. alternative delicate, gentle, soft dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Alternative" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="12025" name="Delicate Quickstep (a)" code="WOM 053 tk018" libraryid="6" albumid="243" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_053_Other_Worlds/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Helene Charlotte Evelyn Muddiman" comment="Un mouvement d'insecte minuscule et rapide." styleid="10" lengthseconds="117" time="1:57" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_053_Other_Worlds/WOM053_trk018_DELICATE_QUICKSTEP_(A)_Helene_Charlotte_Evelyn_Muddiman_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="18" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, INSECTE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), SOUND DESIGN, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DECALE, IRREGULIER, ELEMENTS Un mouvement d'insecte minuscule et rapide. wom 053 tk018 helene charlotte evelyn muddiman delicate quickstep (a) wom 053 other worlds west one music documentary sound elements atmospheres main nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife funny quirky movement irregular insectile tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) sound design tiny fast paced insectile movement. main delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="15851" name="Illuminati (b)" code="WOM 138 tk025" libraryid="6" albumid="332" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_138_Drama_Works/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jay Price" comment="Une bande son de drame atmosphérique contemporain." styleid="14" lengthseconds="127" time="2:07" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_138_Drama_Works/WOM138_trk025_ILLUMINATI_(B)_Jay_Price_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="25" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, ALTERNATIF, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, TV, RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, TENDU, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), SOUND DESIGN, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETECTIVE, TELE REALITE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS Une bande son de drame atmosphérique contemporain. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 138 tk025 jay price illuminati (b) wom 138 drama works west one music drama sound elements atmospheres business corporate science technology alternate documentary science technology movies crime detective mystery science technology industry tv radio reality tv tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing mysterious disturbing tense atmospheric contemporary drama soundtrack. alternative" waveformpath="" version="Alternative" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="17568" name="Short Theme 2" code="WOM 174 tk004" libraryid="6" albumid="370" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_174_Age_of_Innocence/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Thomas Greenberg" comment="Un thème léger et gai pour piano et bois." styleid="10" lengthseconds="39" time="0:39" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_174_Age_of_Innocence/WOM174_trk004_SHORT_THEME_2_Thomas_Greenberg_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, ENFANTS, MATERNELLE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, UNDERSCORE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, ENFANTS, MATERNELLE, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, COMÉDIE, FILMS, FAMILIAL, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, MATERNELLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, TENDRE, INNOCENT, TENDRE, LÉGER, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), BOIS, CLAVIER, PIANO, BOIS, CLARINETTE, DECALE, LEGER, COMEDIE Un thème léger et gai pour piano et bois. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 174 tk004 thomas greenberg short theme 2 wom 174 age of innocence west one music documentary children storytelling children pre school business corporate beds film score orchestral trailer underscore activities settings children pre school movies children storytelling movies comedy movies family tv radio children youth tv pre school funny quirky happy happy light jaunty them for piano and woodwinds. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="4137" name="Stealthy Steps (a)" code="TSH 025 tk015" libraryid="5" albumid="116" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_025_Tangled_Tales/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Marc Frederick Teitler" comment="Un thème malicieux et mystérieux." styleid="20" lengthseconds="52" time="0:52" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_025_Tangled_Tales/TSH025_trk015_STEALTHY_STEPS_(A)_Marc_Frederick_Teitler_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="15" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES,, ESPIEGLE, DECALE Un thème malicieux et mystérieux. tsh 025 tk015 marc frederick teitler stealthy steps (a) tsh 025 tangled tales the scoring house children children storytelling main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) funny comedic funny eccentric funny mischievous funny quirky movement rhythmic stealthy movies children storytelling mischievous secretive theme. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="26194" name="It's a Life (b)" code="WOM 098 tk033" libraryid="6" albumid="560" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_098_Emotive_Orchestral/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Bill Connor" comment="Des marimbas vifs et minimalistes superposés." styleid="4" lengthseconds="112" time="1:52" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_098_Emotive_Orchestral/WOM098_trk033_IT'S_A_LIFE_(B)_Bill_Connor_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="33" tracktotal="" search="CLASSIQUE, CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIÈCLE, CLASSIQUE, STYLE MINIMALISTE, ALTERNATIF, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, PRINTEMPS, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), NON OCCIDENTAL, PERCUSSION, BOIS, SAXOPHONE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, PERIODE, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIECLE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), 20E SIECLE, ELEMENTS Des marimbas vifs et minimalistes superposés. wom 098 tk033 bill connor it's a life (b) wom 098 emotive orchestral west one music film score orchestral classical classical 20th century classical style classical minimalist style alternate documentary science technology nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife nature wildlife the elements seasons time spring uplifting uplifting tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) sprightly minimalist layered marimbas. alternative" waveformpath="" version="Alternative" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="19407" name="Pizzicato Polka" code="WOM 213 tk007" libraryid="6" albumid="412" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_213_Classical_Evolutions/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Patrick Thomas Hawes" comment="Enjoué et léger, avec des cordes pizzicati délicates." styleid="25" lengthseconds="140" time="2:20" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_213_Classical_Evolutions/WOM213_trk007_PIZZICATO_POLKA_Patrick_Thomas_Hawes_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, MUSIQUE DE CHAMBRE, ENSEMBLE CLASSIQUE, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, ANGLETERRE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), ENFANTS, CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, HEUREUX, VIF, TENDRE, DÉLICAT, TENDRE, INNOCENT, TENDRE, LÉGER, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, PRINTEMPS, CORDES, CORDES PIZZICATO,, DELICAT, LEGER, ELEMENTS Enjoué et léger, avec des cordes pizzicati délicates. wom 213 tk007 patrick thomas hawes pizzicato polka wom 213 classical evolutions west one music classical opera children storytelling classical and semi classical chamber music classical ensemble europe northern europe england main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) children classical classical styling film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral pastoral happy bright tender bright and light featuring delicate pizzicato strings. main delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="4134" name="Footsteps" code="TSH 025 tk012" libraryid="5" albumid="116" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_025_Tangled_Tales/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Marc Frederick Teitler" comment="Un morceau de cordes pizzicati furtives." styleid="20" lengthseconds="94" time="1:34" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_025_Tangled_Tales/TSH025_trk012_FOOTSTEPS_Marc_Frederick_Teitler_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, EUROPE, EUROPE DE L'OUEST, FRANCE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, EXCENTRIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, PIZZICATO, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, CINÉMA FRANCAIS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, CORDES, CORDES PIZZICATO,, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ESPIEGLE, DECALE, IRREGULIER, CINEMA FRANCAIS, ELEMENTS Un morceau de cordes pizzicati furtives. tsh 025 tk012 marc frederick teitler footsteps tsh 025 tangled tales the scoring house children children storytelling europe western europe france main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) film score orchestral trailer funny comedic funny eccentric funny mischievous funny quirky movement irregular eccentric movement rhythmic stealthy pizzicato movies children storytelling stealthy pizzicato string feature. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="26822" name="Strange Goings On (c)" code="WOM 248 tk032" libraryid="6" albumid="575" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_248_Dramedy/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Philip Hochstrate / Bill Connor" comment="Des bois mystérieux et des cordes pizzicati tendues." styleid="14" lengthseconds="114" time="1:54" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_248_Dramedy/WOM248_trk032_STRANGE_GOINGS_ON_(C)_Philip_Hochstrate_Bill_Connor_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="32" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, UNDERSCORE, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, COMÉDIE, FILMS, COMÉDIE ROMANTIQUE, TV, RADIO, SITCOM, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, SEXY, GRIVOIS, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), CORDES, CORDES PIZZICATO, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), ESPIEGLE, DECALE, COMEDIE, COMEDIE ROMANTIQUE Des bois mystérieux et des cordes pizzicati tendues. wom 248 tk032 philip hochstrate bill connor strange goings on (c) wom 248 dramedy west one music drama film score orchestral trailer underscore movies children storytelling movies comedy movies romantic comedy tv radio sitcom disturbing mysterious disturbing tense funny comedic funny mischievous funny quirky happy playful sexy saucy tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) mysterious woodwinds and tense pizzicato strings. dramedy. underscore" waveformpath="" version="Underscore" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="26856" name="The Mischievous Clock (b)" code="WOM 266 tk017" libraryid="6" albumid="576" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_266_Quirky_Orchestral/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jack Wall" comment="Des cordes pizzicati mystérieuses et des bois." styleid="16" lengthseconds="139" time="2:19" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_266_Quirky_Orchestral/WOM266_trk017_THE_MISCHIEVOUS_CLOCK_(B)_Jack_Wall_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="17" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, ENFANTS, CONTES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, ALTERNATIF, FILMS, ANIMATION, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, COMÉDIE, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, SEXY, SEXY, PIZZICATO, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, INSECTE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, CHALOUPÉ , TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), CORDES, CORDES PIZZICATO, EFFETS SONORES, MOUVEMENT D'HORLOGE, PENDULE, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), DECALE, IRREGULIER, COMEDIE, CHALOUPE, ELEMENTS Des cordes pizzicati mystérieuses et des bois. wom 266 tk017 jack wall the mischievous clock (b) wom 266 quirky orchestral west one music quirky children storytelling children storytelling film score orchestral trailer sound elements atmospheres effects alternate movies animation movies children storytelling movies comedy movies fantasy adventure nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife disturbing mysterious pizzicato strings and woodwinds. dramedy. alternative" waveformpath="" version="Alternative" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="4136" name="Sleight of Mind" code="TSH 025 tk014" libraryid="5" albumid="116" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_025_Tangled_Tales/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Marc Frederick Teitler" comment="Une étrangeté curieuse et magique." styleid="20" lengthseconds="168" time="2:48" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_025_Tangled_Tales/TSH025_trk014_SLEIGHT_OF_MIND_Marc_Frederick_Teitler_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="14" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, MAGIE, ILLUSIONS, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, TENDRE, INNOCENT, MAGIQUE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CLAVIER, CELESTE Une étrangeté curieuse et magique. tsh 025 tk014 marc frederick teitler sleight of mind tsh 025 tangled tales the scoring house children children storytelling main activities settings magic illusions movies children storytelling tender innocent magical tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) keyboard celeste curious magical strangeness. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="26852" name="Mystery Waltz (b)" code="WOM 266 tk013" libraryid="6" albumid="576" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_266_Quirky_Orchestral/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jack Wall" comment="Une valse superbe et étrange. Des cordes pizzicati entremêlées avec des bois lyriques." styleid="16" lengthseconds="151" time="2:31" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_266_Quirky_Orchestral/WOM266_trk013_MYSTERY_WALTZ_(B)_Jack_Wall_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="13" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ALTERNATIF, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, PAISIBLE, LYRIQUE, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, MÉLODIQUE, LYRIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CORDES, CORDES PIZZICATO, DANSE DE SALON, VALSE, MELODIQUE, ESPIEGLE, DECALE, ELEMENTS Une valse superbe et étrange. Des cordes pizzicati entremêlées avec des bois lyriques. wom 266 tk013 jack wall mystery waltz (b) wom 266 quirky orchestral west one music quirky children storytelling film score orchestral trailer alternate movies children storytelling movies fantasy adventure nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife funny comedic funny eccentric funny mischievous funny quirky peaceful lyrical peaceful peaceful melodic a gorgeous off-kilter waltz. pizzicato strings intertwine with lyrical woodwinds. dramedy. alternative" waveformpath="" version="Alternative" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="7943" name="Hysteria Lane" code="TSH 038 tk043" libraryid="5" albumid="174" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_038_Oddities/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Paul Reeves (Gb 2)" comment="Un morceau excentrique et imprévisible, avec des cordes pizzicati avec des interjections de percussions." styleid="17" lengthseconds="61" time="1:01" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_038_Oddities/TSH038_trk043_HYSTERIA_LANE_Paul_Reeves_(Gb_2)_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="43" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), HEUREUX, FUN, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, DROLE, IRONIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, PIZZICATO, FILMS, ANIMATION, FILMS, COMÉDIE ROMANTIQUE, TV, RADIO, DESSINS ANIMÉS, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, CORDES, CORDES PIZZICATO,, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ESPIEGLE, DECALE, COMEDIE, COMEDIE ROMANTIQUE, DESSINS ANIMES Un morceau excentrique et imprévisible, avec des cordes pizzicati avec des interjections de percussions. tsh 038 tk043 paul reeves (gb 2) hysteria lane tsh 038 oddities the scoring house comedy film score orchestral trailer main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) happy fun happy playful funny comedic funny eccentric funny mischievous funny quirky funny wry tender romantic movement rhythmic stealthy pizzicato movies animation movies romantic comedy tv radio oddball and unpredictable featuring pizzicato strings with percussion interjections. dramedy. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="17340" name="Strange Phenomenon" code="WOM 169 tk011" libraryid="6" albumid="364" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_169_Brave_New_World/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Patrick Thomas Hawes" comment="Des motifs de flûte répétitifs alternent avec des phrases excentriques de marimba." styleid="12" lengthseconds="127" time="2:07" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_169_Brave_New_World/WOM169_trk011_STRANGE_PHENOMENON_Patrick_Thomas_Hawes_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="11" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PRINCIPAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, INSECTE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), PERCUSSION, MARIMBA, DECALE, IRREGULIER, ELEMENTS Des motifs de flûte répétitifs alternent avec des phrases excentriques de marimba. wom 169 tk011 patrick thomas hawes strange phenomenon wom 169 brave new world west one music atmospheres film score orchestral pastoral main nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife funny quirky movement irregular insectile tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) percussion marimba repeating flute patterns alternate with quirky marimba phrases. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="8042" name="Naughty but Nice" code="TSH 039 tk016" libraryid="5" albumid="175" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_039_Life_in_Colour/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Alexander Paul Rudd / Zach Lemmon Lemmon" comment="Petits plaisirs personnels et complaisants." styleid="20" lengthseconds="215" time="3:35" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_039_Life_in_Colour/TSH039_trk016_NAUGHTY_BUT_NICE_Alexander_Paul_Rudd_Zach_Lemmon_Lemmon_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="16" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, ENFANTS, MATERNELLE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, ENFANTS, MATERNELLE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, MAGIE, ILLUSIONS, NOËL, ENFANTS, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, MATERNELLE, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, TENDRE, INNOCENT, MAGIQUE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), NOEL, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DECALE Petits plaisirs personnels et complaisants. tsh 039 tk016 alexander paul rudd zach lemmon lemmon naughty but nice tsh 039 life in colour the scoring house children children storytelling children pre school film score orchestral trailer main activities settings children pre school activities settings magic illusions christmas children movies children storytelling tv radio children youth tv pre school funny comedic funny eccentric indulgent personal pleasures. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="17574" name="Short Theme 5" code="WOM 174 tk010" libraryid="6" albumid="370" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_174_Age_of_Innocence/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Thomas Greenberg" comment="Une répartie enjouée. Piano et bois." styleid="10" lengthseconds="36" time="0:36" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_174_Age_of_Innocence/WOM174_trk010_SHORT_THEME_5_Thomas_Greenberg_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="10" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, ENFANTS, COMPTINE, ENFANTS, MATERNELLE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, ENFANTS, MATERNELLE, FILMS, ANIMATION, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, TV, RADIO, DESSINS ANIMÉS, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, HEUREUX, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BOIS, CLAVIER, CELESTE, CLAVIER, PIANO, PERCUSSION, CYMBALES, BOIS, CLARINETTE, STYLE VINTAGE, AIR CONNU, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DECALE, DESSINS ANIMES Une répartie enjouée. Piano et bois. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 174 tk010 thomas greenberg short theme 5 wom 174 age of innocence west one music documentary children children nursery rhyme children pre school film score orchestral trailer main activities settings children pre school movies animation movies children storytelling movies fantasy adventure tv radio cartoons funny quirky happy peaceful contented tempo jolly repartee. piano and woodwind. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="7069" name="Twisted Nerve (a)" code="TSH 026A tk008" libraryid="5" albumid="162" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_026A_Dimensions/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Dave Hewson / Alexander Balanescu" comment="Un insidieux et sombre patchwork musical." styleid="4" lengthseconds="106" time="1:46" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_026A_Dimensions/TSH026A_trk008_TWISTED_NERVE_(A)_Dave_Hewson_Alexander_Balanescu_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="8" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, SOUND DESIGN, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, ÉTRANGE , TROUBLANT, SURNATUREL, TROUBLANT, BIZARRE, EFFRAYANT, HORREUR, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CORDES, VIOLON, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), INQUIETANT, ETRANGE, ELEMENTS Un insidieux et sombre patchwork musical. tsh 026a tk008 dave hewson alexander balanescu twisted nerve (a) tsh 026a dimensions the scoring house film score orchestral sound elements atmospheres sound design main movies horror thriller movies human drama nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife disturbing dark disturbing eerie disturbing strange disturbing supernatural disturbing weird scary horror tempo insidious dark collage. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="7883" name="Small Wonders (a)" code="TSH 004 tk018" libraryid="5" albumid="173" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_004_Natural_Wonders/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon David Chamberlain" comment="Aperçus angulaires et intrigants." styleid="26" lengthseconds="164" time="2:44" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_004_Natural_Wonders/TSH004_trk018_SMALL_WONDERS_(A)_Simon_David_Chamberlain_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="18" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, HUMORISTIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, EXCENTRIQUE, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, INSECTE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, FILMS, COMÉDIE, FILMS, COMÉDIE ROMANTIQUE, DOCUMENTAIRE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE,, ESPIEGLE, DECALE, IRREGULIER, COMEDIE, COMEDIE ROMANTIQUE, ELEMENTS Aperçus angulaires et intrigants. tsh 004 tk018 simon david chamberlain small wonders (a) tsh 004 natural wonders the scoring house nature wildlife film score orchestral trailer main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) funny comedic funny eccentric funny humorous funny mischievous funny quirky movement irregular eccentric movement irregular insectile movement rhythmic stealthy movies comedy movies romantic comedy intriguing angular insights. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="26814" name="Feeling Curious (c)" code="WOM 248 tk024" libraryid="6" albumid="575" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_248_Dramedy/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Philip Hochstrate / Bill Connor" comment="Des cordes pizzicati espiègles." styleid="14" lengthseconds="98" time="1:38" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_248_Dramedy/WOM248_trk024_FEELING_CURIOUS_(C)_Philip_Hochstrate_Bill_Connor_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="24" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, UNDERSCORE, FILMS, ANIMATION, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, COMÉDIE, FILMS, COMÉDIE ROMANTIQUE, TV, RADIO, SITCOM, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CORDES, CORDES PIZZICATO, ESPIEGLE, COMEDIE, COMEDIE ROMANTIQUE Des cordes pizzicati espiègles. wom 248 tk024 philip hochstrate bill connor feeling curious (c) wom 248 dramedy west one music drama children storytelling film score orchestral trailer underscore movies animation movies children storytelling movies comedy movies romantic comedy tv radio sitcom funny comedic funny mischievous happy playful movement rhythmic stealthy tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) playful pizzicato strings. dramedy. underscore" waveformpath="" version="Underscore" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="23401" name="Security Threat (a)" code="WOM 301 tk009" libraryid="6" albumid="507" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_301_Dark_Motion/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Christian Telford / Matthew St. Laurent / Galileo Seven / Koichi Sanchez-Imahashi / Nigel William Graham" comment="Textures mystérieuses et fascinantes, en constante évolution." styleid="14" lengthseconds="168" time="2:48" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_301_Dark_Motion/WOM301_trk009_SECURITY_THREAT_(A)_Christian_Telford_Matthew_St._Laurent_Galileo_Seven_Koichi_Sanchez-Imahash.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, JOURNALISME D'INVESTIGATION, TV, RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, TENDU, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), DETECTIVE, ACTUALITES, TELE REALITE, MYSTERE Textures mystérieuses et fascinantes, en constante évolution. wom 301 tk009 christian telford matthew st. laurent galileo seven koichi sanchez-imahashi nigel william graham security threat (a) wom 301 dark motion west one music drama business corporate science technology business corporate science technology main movies crime detective mystery movies urban drama tv radio news and current affairs investigative reporting tv radio reality tv tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing mysterious captivating textures continuously evolving. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="22348" name="Sleep Spindles" code="WOM 277 tk041" libraryid="6" albumid="479" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_277_Reconstruction_-_Textures/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Des touches de harpe captivantes sur un fond sonore de cordes pulsant doucement." styleid="12" lengthseconds="106" time="1:46" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_277_Reconstruction_-_Textures/WOM277_trk041_SLEEP_SPINDLES_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="41" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ANIMATION, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, TENDRE, DÉLICAT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, PULSATION, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), DELICAT Des touches de harpe captivantes sur un fond sonore de cordes pulsant doucement. wom 277 tk041 david ashton sleep spindles wom 277 reconstruction - textures west one music atmospheres children storytelling film score orchestral trailer main movies animation movies children storytelling movies fantasy adventure peaceful dreamy tender delicate movement rhythmic pulsing tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) captivating harp touches over a gently pulsing string bed. main delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="2827" name="The Watcher" code="TSH 003 tk014" libraryid="5" albumid="94" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_003_Deeper_Minimal/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Robert John Foster" comment="Anticipation neutre." styleid="12" lengthseconds="38" time="0:38" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_003_Deeper_Minimal/TSH003_trk014_THE_WATCHER_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="14" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, PLUIE, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, SÉRIEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, RÉPÉTITIF, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), ELEMENTS SONORES, SERIEUX, ATMOSPHERES, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), REPETITIF, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS, METEO, ETE Anticipation neutre. tsh 003 tk014 robert john foster the watcher tsh 003 deeper minimal the scoring house atmospheres sound elements atmospheres main documentary movies crime detective mystery nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife nature wildlife the elements weather rain tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing mysterious disturbing suspenseful disturbing neutral anticipation. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="3651" name="With Intent (c)" code="TSH 016 tk027" libraryid="5" albumid="107" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_016_A_Clearer_Vision/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Andrew Clark" comment="Fond sonore calme d'anticipation." styleid="11" lengthseconds="51" time="0:51" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_016_A_Clearer_Vision/TSH016_trk027_WITH_INTENT_(C)_Simon_Andrew_Clark_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="27" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, COMMUNICATION, ACTUALITÉS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, ALTERNATIF, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, ESPACE, INTERSIDÉRAL, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, ATMOSPHÈRE SCIENTIFIQUE, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, JOURNALISME D'INVESTIGATION, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, PAISIBLE, DOUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ACCELERE, ACTUALITES, ELEMENTS, ATMOSPHERE SCIENTIFIQUE, INTERSIDERAL Fond sonore calme d'anticipation. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz tsh 016 tk027 simon andrew clark with intent (c) tsh 016 a clearer vision the scoring house corporate business sound elements atmospheres business corporate communication news business corporate science technology alternate business corporate documentary science technology nature wildlife the elements sky space outer space science technology industry scientific atmospheres tv radio quiet anticipatory bed. alternative" waveformpath="" version="Alternative" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="18660" name="The Subterfuge (b)" code="WOM 199 tk015" libraryid="6" albumid="395" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_199_Murder_Files/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Johnny Bernstein" comment="Une bande son lente et dramatique avec des lignes douces de piano surdes cordes atmosphériques." styleid="14" lengthseconds="215" time="3:35" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_199_Murder_Files/WOM199_trk015_THE_SUBTERFUGE_(B)_Johnny_Bernstein_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="15" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ALTERNATIF, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, ÉTRANGE , TROUBLANT, SURNATUREL, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, TROUBLANT, BIZARRE, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, VIOLON, INQUIETANT, ETRANGE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE Une bande son lente et dramatique avec des lignes douces de piano surdes cordes atmosphériques. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 199 tk015 johnny bernstein the subterfuge (b) wom 199 murder files west one music drama film score orchestral trailer alternate movies crime detective mystery movies espionage spy movies horror thriller movies human drama tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing eerie disturbing mysterious disturbing strange disturbing supernatural slow dramatic soundtrack with gentle piano lines over atmospheric strings. alternative delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Alternative" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="4794" name="Unidentified (a)" code="TSH 040 tk006" libraryid="5" albumid="127" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_040_Science_of_Uncertainty/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Graham Paul Donovan" comment="Un fond sonore perplexe et insistant, évoluant graduellement." styleid="10" lengthseconds="123" time="2:03" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_040_Science_of_Uncertainty/TSH040_trk006_UNIDENTIFIED_(A)_Graham_Paul_Donovan_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="6" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, ATMOSPHÈRE SCIENTIFIQUE, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, JOURNALISME D'INVESTIGATION, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, ÉTRANGE , TROUBLANT, BIZARRE, SÉRIEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INSISTANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, PULSATION, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), CLOCHES, ELEMENTS SONORES, SERIEUX, ATMOSPHERES, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), INQUIETANT, ETRANGE, DETECTIVE, ACTUALITES, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS, ATMOSPHERE SCIENTIFIQUE Un fond sonore perplexe et insistant, évoluant graduellement. tsh 040 tk006 graham paul donovan unidentified (a) tsh 040 science of uncertainty the scoring house documentary sound elements atmospheres business corporate science technology sound elements atmospheres effects main documentary science technology movies crime detective mystery movies human drama science technology industry scientific atmospheres tv radio news and current affairs questioning insistent bed gradually evolving. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="2838" name="The Unexplained" code="TSH 003 tk025" libraryid="5" albumid="94" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_003_Deeper_Minimal/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Robert John Foster" comment="Underscore investigateur." styleid="12" lengthseconds="84" time="1:24" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_003_Deeper_Minimal/TSH003_trk025_THE_UNEXPLAINED_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="25" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, JOURNALISME D'INVESTIGATION, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE,, DETECTIVE, ACTUALITES, MYSTERE Underscore investigateur. tsh 003 tk025 robert john foster the unexplained tsh 003 deeper minimal the scoring house atmospheres business corporate science technology main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) disturbing mysterious disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense movement rhythmic clock like movies crime detective mystery tv radio news and current affairs investigative reporting tv radio tv drama investigative underscore. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="3640" name="Every Last Second (d)" code="TSH 016 tk016" libraryid="5" albumid="107" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_016_A_Clearer_Vision/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Andrew Clark" comment="Fond sonore tendu et anticipatif." styleid="11" lengthseconds="65" time="1:05" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_016_A_Clearer_Vision/TSH016_trk016_EVERY_LAST_SECOND_(D)_Simon_Andrew_Clark_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="16" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, FUTURISTE, UNDERSCORE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INSISTANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, TV, RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE,, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ACCELERE, TELE REALITE Fond sonore tendu et anticipatif. tsh 016 tk016 simon andrew clark every last second (d) tsh 016 a clearer vision the scoring house corporate business business corporate beds time period modern era futuristic underscore tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) business corporate science technology disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense movement rhythmic clock like movement rhythmic insistent movement rhythmic speeded up time lapse tense anticipatory bed. alternative" waveformpath="" version="Alternative" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="3638" name="Every Last Second (b)" code="TSH 016 tk014" libraryid="5" albumid="107" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_016_A_Clearer_Vision/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Andrew Clark" comment="Fond sonore tendu et insistant, sans beats." styleid="11" lengthseconds="177" time="2:57" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_016_A_Clearer_Vision/TSH016_trk014_EVERY_LAST_SECOND_(B)_Simon_Andrew_Clark_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="14" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FORMATION, INFORMATION, UNDERSCORE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, JOURNALISME D'INVESTIGATION, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INSISTANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, FUTURISTE, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ACCELERE, ACTUALITES Fond sonore tendu et insistant, sans beats. tsh 016 tk014 simon andrew clark every last second (b) tsh 016 a clearer vision the scoring house corporate business business corporate beds business corporate science technology business corporate training information underscore business corporate documentary science technology science technology industry tv radio news and current affairs investigative reporting tv radio tv drama police insistent tension bed without beats. ambient mix" waveformpath="" version="Ambient Mix" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="26378" name="Pressure Zone (b)" code="WOM 209 tk014" libraryid="6" albumid="565" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_209_Absolution/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Toby Y. Chu" comment="Tendu et menaçant avec des percussions fesant tic-tac et un piano suberbe. Progresse avec une batterie tribale." styleid="4" lengthseconds="144" time="2:24" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_209_Absolution/WOM209_trk014_PRESSURE_ZONE_(B)_Toby_Y._Chu_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="14" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ALTERNATIF, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, FORT, MAJESTUEUX, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BATTERIE, CLAVIER, PIANO, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETECTIVE, MYSTERE Tendu et menaçant avec des percussions fesant tic-tac et un piano suberbe. Progresse avec une batterie tribale. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 209 tk014 toby y. chu pressure zone (b) wom 209 absolution west one music film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer alternate movies action adventure movies crime detective mystery movies horror thriller movies human drama tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing mysterious disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense scary ominous serious tense and ominous with ticking percussion and lush piano. builds with tribal drums. alternative" waveformpath="" version="Alternative" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="15794" name="Science Fiction (b)" code="WOM 136 tk018" libraryid="6" albumid="330" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_136_High_Drama/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Johnny Bernstein" comment="Un thriller urban grungy, captivant et atmosphérique." styleid="14" lengthseconds="175" time="2:55" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_136_High_Drama/WOM136_trk018_SCIENCE_FICTION_(B)_Johnny_Bernstein_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="18" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ALTERNATIF, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, JOURNALISME D'INVESTIGATION, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, TENDU, CRADE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELEMENTS SONORES, ELECTRONIQUE, ATMOSPHERES, DETECTIVE, ACTUALITES, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS Un thriller urban grungy, captivant et atmosphérique. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 136 tk018 johnny bernstein science fiction (b) wom 136 high drama west one music drama sound elements atmospheres club electronica alternate movies crime detective mystery movies horror thriller movies urban drama tv radio news and current affairs investigative reporting tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing dark disturbing mysterious grungy absorbing and atmospheric urban thriller. alternative" waveformpath="" version="Alternative" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="4619" name="Moments of Time" code="TSH 035 tk015" libraryid="5" albumid="125" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_035_A_Winner_is_Born/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Mark Lasker" comment="Une animation haletante et suspendue." styleid="22" lengthseconds="155" time="2:35" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_035_A_Winner_is_Born/TSH035_trk015_MOMENTS_OF_TIME_Mark_Lasker_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="15" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, FILMS, ANIMATION, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MER, SOUS-MARIN, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, ATMOSPHÈRE SCIENTIFIQUE, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, ÉTRANGE , TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, TROUBLANT, BIZARRE, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, RALENTI, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, INQUIETANT, ETRANGE, DEPRIMANT, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS, ATMOSPHERE SCIENTIFIQUE Une animation haletante et suspendue. tsh 035 tk015 mark lasker moments of time tsh 035 a winner is born the scoring house sport sound elements atmospheres business corporate science technology main documentary science technology movies animation movies crime detective mystery nature wildlife the elements sea underwater science technology industry scientific atmospheres disturbing eerie disturbing breathless suspended animation. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="4697" name="Shadowmaker (b)" code="TSH 036 tk008" libraryid="5" albumid="126" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_036_The_Hard_Edge/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Robert Henry Peter White" comment="Une ouverture éparse d'anticipation vers une fin pleine de suspense." styleid="10" lengthseconds="92" time="1:32" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_036_The_Hard_Edge/TSH036_trk008_SHADOWMAKER_(B)_Robert_Henry_Peter_White_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="8" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, ALTERNATIF, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, INDUSTRIE LOURDE, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, JOURNALISME D'INVESTIGATION, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, ABSTRAIT, CLAIRSEMÉ, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), CLAIRSEME, DETECTIVE, ACTUALITES, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS Une ouverture éparse d'anticipation vers une fin pleine de suspense. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede tsh 036 tk008 robert henry peter white shadowmaker (b) tsh 036 the hard edge the scoring house documentary sound elements atmospheres alternate movies crime detective mystery movies urban drama science technology industry heavy industry tv radio news and current affairs investigative reporting tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama abstract sparse disturbing mysterious sparse anticipatory opening to uneasy resolve. alternative" waveformpath="" version="Alternative" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="4614" name="Hidden Depths" code="TSH 035 tk010" libraryid="5" albumid="125" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_035_A_Winner_is_Born/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Mark Lasker" comment="Un développement rythmique mystérieux et énigmatique, et une reprise." styleid="22" lengthseconds="180" time="3:00" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_035_A_Winner_is_Born/TSH035_trk010_HIDDEN_DEPTHS_Mark_Lasker_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="10" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, COMMUNICATION, ACTUALITÉS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FORMATION, INFORMATION, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, JOURNALISME D'INVESTIGATION, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, CRAINTIF, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, TENDU, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), DETECTIVE, ACTUALITES, MYSTERE Un développement rythmique mystérieux et énigmatique, et une reprise. tsh 035 tk010 mark lasker hidden depths tsh 035 a winner is born the scoring house sport business corporate beds business corporate communication news business corporate science technology business corporate training information main documentary science technology movies crime detective mystery movies urban drama tv radio news and current affairs mysterious enigmatic rhythmic development and reprise. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="7674" name="Under Observation" code="TSH 041 tk026" libraryid="5" albumid="171" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_041_Through_the_Lens/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Colin John Riley" comment="Une anticipation pleine d'inquiétude." styleid="24" lengthseconds="102" time="1:42" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_041_Through_the_Lens/TSH041_trk026_UNDER_OBSERVATION_Colin_John_Riley_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="26" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, SÉRIEUX, INQUIET, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), ELEMENTS SONORES, SERIEUX, ATMOSPHERES, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS Une anticipation pleine d'inquiétude. tsh 041 tk026 colin john riley under observation tsh 041 through the lens the scoring house science new technology sound elements atmospheres main documentary movies crime detective mystery nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing mysterious disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense serious concerned movement rhythmic concerned anticipation. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="26669" name="Mist" code="WOM 012 tk004" libraryid="6" albumid="572" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_012_Clarity/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Daryl Neil Alexander Griffith" comment="Un motif de piano simple et méditatif avec des cordes suspendues." styleid="4" lengthseconds="156" time="2:36" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_012_Clarity/WOM012_trk004_MIST_Daryl_Neil_Alexander_Griffith_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="CLASSIQUE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIÈCLE, CLASSIQUE, STYLE MINIMALISTE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, ABSTRAIT, SIMPLE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, DOCUMENTAIRE, CLAVIER, PIANO,, PERIODE, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIECLE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, 20E SIECLE Un motif de piano simple et méditatif avec des cordes suspendues. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 012 tk004 daryl neil alexander griffith mist wom 012 clarity west one music film score orchestral classical time period modern era 20th century main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) classical 20th century classical style classical minimalist style film score orchestral trailer tender reflective sad depressing poignant sad depressing sad abstract simple movies human drama simple reflective piano pattern with suspended strings. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="23396" name="Bleak Worlds (a)" code="WOM 301 tk004" libraryid="6" albumid="507" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_301_Dark_Motion/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Christian Telford / Matthew St. Laurent / Galileo Seven / Koichi Sanchez-Imahashi / Nigel William Graham" comment="Expectative qui incite à la réflexion, se construisant tout du long du morceau." styleid="14" lengthseconds="145" time="2:25" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_301_Dark_Motion/WOM301_trk004_BLEAK_WORLDS_(A)_Christian_Telford_Matthew_St._Laurent_Galileo_Seven_Koichi_Sanchez-Imahashi_N.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, DRONES, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, EVOLUTIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, PULSATION, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETECTIVE, TELE REALITE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Expectative qui incite à la réflexion, se construisant tout du long du morceau. wom 301 tk004 christian telford matthew st. laurent galileo seven koichi sanchez-imahashi nigel william graham bleak worlds (a) wom 301 dark motion west one music drama film score orchestral trailer sound elements atmospheres sound elements atmospheres drones main movies crime detective mystery movies urban drama tv radio reality tv tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense building movement thought provoking anticipation gently building throughout. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="3628" name="Precision Timing (a)" code="TSH 016 tk004" libraryid="5" albumid="107" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_016_A_Clearer_Vision/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Andrew Clark" comment="Interaction rythmique complexe." styleid="11" lengthseconds="193" time="3:13" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_016_A_Clearer_Vision/TSH016_trk004_PRECISION_TIMING_(A)_Simon_Andrew_Clark_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, COMMUNICATION, ACTUALITÉS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FORMATION, INFORMATION, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, AUTOMATISATION, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, JOURNALISME D'INVESTIGATION, TROUBLANT, TENDU, EVOLUTIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INSISTANT, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, FUTURISTE, PERIODE, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), ACTUALITES, REVELER, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Interaction rythmique complexe. tsh 016 tk004 simon andrew clark precision timing (a) tsh 016 a clearer vision the scoring house corporate business business corporate beds business corporate communication news business corporate reveal launch business corporate science technology business corporate training information main business corporate documentary science technology science technology industry automation tv intricate rhythmic interplay. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="15775" name="The Right Track (b)" code="WOM 135 tk023" libraryid="6" albumid="329" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_135_Modern_Drama/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Caspar John Valentine Kedros / Scott Doran" comment="Une atmosphère positive, puissante et fluide." styleid="14" lengthseconds="185" time="3:05" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_135_Modern_Drama/WOM135_trk023_THE_RIGHT_TRACK_(B)_Caspar_John_Valentine_Kedros_Scott_Doran_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="23" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ALTERNATIF, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, TENDU, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, DÉTENDU, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELEMENTS SONORES, ELECTRONIQUE, ATMOSPHERES, DETENDU, ACCELERE, DETECTIVE, TELE REALITE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS Une atmosphère positive, puissante et fluide. wom 135 tk023 caspar john valentine kedros scott doran the right track (b) wom 135 modern drama west one music drama sound elements atmospheres club electronica alternate documentary movies crime detective mystery movies urban drama tv radio reality tv tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing mysterious disturbing tense peaceful dreamy peaceful relaxed strong strong positive strong flowing atmosphere. alternative" waveformpath="" version="Alternative" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="2814" name="Waiting and Watching" code="TSH 003 tk001" libraryid="5" albumid="94" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_003_Deeper_Minimal/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Robert John Foster" comment="Fond sonore raffiné et plein de suspense." styleid="12" lengthseconds="72" time="1:12" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_003_Deeper_Minimal/TSH003_trk001_WAITING_AND_WATCHING_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, CHAUD, DÉSERT, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, ESPACE, INTERSIDÉRAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, FROID, STÉRILE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, SOLEIL, CHALEUR, TROUBLANT, STÉRILE, TROUBLANT, FROID , TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SURNATUREL, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), EFFETS SONORES, SIFFLEMENT, CRÉPITEMENT, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), STERILE, INQUIETANT, CREPITEMENT, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS, METEO, DESERT, ETE, INTERSIDERAL Fond sonore raffiné et plein de suspense. tsh 003 tk001 robert john foster waiting and watching tsh 003 deeper minimal the scoring house atmospheres sound elements atmospheres business corporate science technology main movies crime detective mystery nature wildlife the elements land hot desert nature wildlife the elements sky space outer space nature wildlife the elements weather cold barren nature wildlife understated suspenseful bed. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
  </items>
</librarycollection>
