<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<librarycollection>
  <items>
    <item id="10305" name="Drift (a)" code="WOM 019 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="209" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_019_Arco_1_(Drama_Strings)/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Profond, dangereux et lancinant." styleid="14" lengthseconds="128" time="2:08" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_019_Arco_1_(Drama_Strings)/WOM019_trk001_DRIFT_(A)_Richard_Allen_Harvey_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, DRONES, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRAGIQUE, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, DRAMATIQUE, DANGEUREUX, DRONE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER,, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), INQUIETANT, DEPRIMANT, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS Profond, dangereux et lancinant. wom 019 tk001 richard allen harvey drift (a) wom 019 arco 1 (drama strings) west one music drama sound elements atmospheres main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) film score orchestral trailer sound elements atmospheres drones sad depressing sad sad depressing tragic disturbing dark disturbing eerie disturbing mysterious scary ominous dramatic dangerous drone movies deep dangerous and haunting. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="20155" name="Tribal Danger" code="WOM 229 tk076" libraryid="6" albumid="429" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="L'approche du danger." styleid="2" lengthseconds="44" time="0:44" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk076_TRIBAL_DANGER_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="76" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, ÉTRANGE , TROUBLANT, SURNATUREL, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, TROUBLANT, BIZARRE, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, JUNGLE, TROPICAL,, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), INQUIETANT, ETRANGE, ELEMENTS L'approche du danger. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede wom 229 tk076 david ashton tribal danger wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) disturbing eerie disturbing strange disturbing supernatural disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense disturbing weird scary ominous movies horror thriller nature wildlife the elements land jungle tropical the approach to danger. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="6826" name="Dark Repeater" code="TSH 072 tk031" libraryid="5" albumid="156" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_072_Essential_Minimal/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Robert John Foster" comment="Images sombres, dérangeantes." styleid="10" lengthseconds="129" time="2:09" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_072_Essential_Minimal/TSH_072_trk031_DARK_REPEATER_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="31" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, PRINCIPAL, TROUBLANT, ANXIEUX, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, TROUBLANT, TROUBLANT, CRAINTIF, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, TROUBLÉ, DRAMATIQUE, DANGEUREUX, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, EFFRAYANT, EFFRAYANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, RÉPÉTITIF, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, GUERRE, MILITAIRE, HISTORIQUE, GUERRE MODERNE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, RADIO, DRAME TVDOCUMENTAIRE, MINIMAL, FORMATIONS GENERALES, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, TROUBLE, REPETITIF, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE Images sombres, dérangeantes. tsh 072 tk031 robert john foster dark repeater tsh 072 essential minimal the scoring house documentary film score orchestral trailer general lineups electronic and acoustic main disturbing anxious disturbing dark disturbing disturbing disturbing fearful disturbing mysterious disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense dramatic agitated dramatic dangerous scary ominous scary sombre disturbing imagery. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="17333" name="Hidden Danger (a)" code="WOM 169 tk004" libraryid="6" albumid="364" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_169_Brave_New_World/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Patrick Thomas Hawes" comment="Des échanges de clarinette lancinante et de harpe soutenus par des cordes menaçantes qui pulsent." styleid="12" lengthseconds="131" time="2:11" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_169_Brave_New_World/WOM169_trk004_HIDDEN_DANGER_(A)_Patrick_Thomas_Hawes_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, SÉRIEUX, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, PULSATION, PARASITES, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, MÉDICAL, SCIENCES DE LA VIE,, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS, MEDICAL Des échanges de clarinette lancinante et de harpe soutenus par des cordes menaçantes qui pulsent. wom 169 tk004 patrick thomas hawes hidden danger (a) wom 169 brave new world west one music atmospheres business corporate science technology classical and semi classical symphony orchestra main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) business corporate science technology film score orchestral panoramic serious disturbing mysterious scary ominous movement rhythmic pulsing static ominous pulsing strings underpin haunting clarinet and harp interchange. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="2814" name="Waiting and Watching" code="TSH 003 tk001" libraryid="5" albumid="94" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_003_Deeper_Minimal/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Robert John Foster" comment="Fond sonore raffiné et plein de suspense." styleid="12" lengthseconds="72" time="1:12" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_003_Deeper_Minimal/TSH003_trk001_WAITING_AND_WATCHING_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, CHAUD, DÉSERT, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, ESPACE, INTERSIDÉRAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, FROID, STÉRILE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, SOLEIL, CHALEUR, TROUBLANT, STÉRILE, TROUBLANT, FROID , TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SURNATUREL, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), EFFETS SONORES, SIFFLEMENT, CRÉPITEMENT, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), STERILE, INQUIETANT, CREPITEMENT, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS, METEO, DESERT, ETE, INTERSIDERAL Fond sonore raffiné et plein de suspense. tsh 003 tk001 robert john foster waiting and watching tsh 003 deeper minimal the scoring house atmospheres sound elements atmospheres business corporate science technology main movies crime detective mystery nature wildlife the elements land hot desert nature wildlife the elements sky space outer space nature wildlife the elements weather cold barren nature wildlife understated suspenseful bed. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="7130" name="Trail of Deception" code="TSH 029 tk012" libraryid="5" albumid="164" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_029_Symphonic_Fantasia/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Arthur Rhodes" comment="Des sous-entendus mystérieux et fascinants." styleid="4" lengthseconds="181" time="3:01" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_029_Symphonic_Fantasia/TSH029_trk012_TRAIL_OF_DECEPTION_Simon_Arthur_Rhodes_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), STYLE VINTAGE, SÉRIEUX, TROUBLANT, CRAINTIF, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE,, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS Des sous-entendus mystérieux et fascinants. tsh 029 tk012 simon arthur rhodes trail of deception tsh 029 symphonic fantasia the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) vintage style serious disturbing fearful disturbing mysterious disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense movies crime detective mystery movies human drama movies espionage spy tv radio tv drama police legal intriguing mysterious undercurrents. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="8202" name="Pulsing Threat (a)" code="TSH 051 tk015" libraryid="5" albumid="177" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_051_Nearfield/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Everard Lawrence Wells / Robert John Foster" comment="Courrants sous-jacents sombres et insidieux." styleid="10" lengthseconds="111" time="1:51" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_051_Nearfield/TSH051_trk015_PULSING_THREAT_(A)_Richard_Everard_Lawrence_Wells_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="15" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, JOURNALISME D'INVESTIGATION, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, SÉRIEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, PULSATION, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETECTIVE, ACTUALITES, MYSTERE Courrants sous-jacents sombres et insidieux. tsh 051 tk015 richard everard lawrence wells robert john foster pulsing threat (a) tsh 051 nearfield the scoring house documentary business corporate science technology main documentary science technology movies crime detective mystery science technology industry tv radio news and current affairs investigative reporting tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing dark serious movement dark insidious undercurrents. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="7419" name="Veil of Shadows (a)" code="TSH 059 tk039" libraryid="5" albumid="168" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_059_Orchestral_Fantasia/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Arthur Rhodes" comment="Atmosphère tendue et empreinte de mal à l'aise, dans la veine de 'The Illusionist'." styleid="4" lengthseconds="198" time="3:18" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_059_Orchestral_Fantasia/TSH_059_trk039_VEIL_OF_SHADOWS_(A)_Simon_Arthur_Rhodes_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="39" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SURNATUREL, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, DANGEUREUX, EFFRAYANT, MENAÇANT, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, SERIEUX, INQUIETANT, MENACANT, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS Atmosphère tendue et empreinte de mal à l'aise, dans la veine de 'The Illusionist'. tsh 059 tk039 simon arthur rhodes veil of shadows (a) tsh 059 orchestral fantasia the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer main movies crime detective mystery movies espionage spy movies fantasy adventure movies horror thriller nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife disturbing eerie disturbing mysterious disturbing supernatural disturbing suspenseful tense uneasy atmosphere thematic to 'the illusionist'. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="6071" name="The Raging Silence" code="TSH 062 tk012" libraryid="5" albumid="144" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_062_Cause_for_Concern/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Zac Jordan" comment="Atmosphère sombre et haletante." styleid="14" lengthseconds="92" time="1:32" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_062_Cause_for_Concern/TSH_062_trk012_THE_RAGING_SILENCE_Zac_Jordan_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, DRONES, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, SOUND DESIGN, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ART ET ESSAI, FILMS, FILM NOIR, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, JOURNALISME D'INVESTIGATION, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, DRAME FAMILIAL, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, DRAME HOSPITALIER, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, ÉTRANGE , TROUBLANT, SURNATUREL, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, TROUBLANT, BIZARRE, EFFRAYANT, MENAÇANT, ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELEMENTS SONORES, ELECTRONIQUE, ATMOSPHERES, INQUIETANT, ETRANGE, MENACANT, ACTUALITES, ELEMENTS Atmosphère sombre et haletante. tsh 062 tk012 zac jordan the raging silence tsh 062 cause for concern the scoring house drama sound elements atmospheres film score orchestral trailer sound elements atmospheres drones sound elements atmospheres sound design main movies art house movies film noir tv radio news and current affairs investigative reporting tv radio tv drama family drama tv radio brooding suspenseful atmosphere. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="6405" name="Cover of Darkness" code="TSH 066 tk009" libraryid="5" albumid="150" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_066_Discreet_Emotive/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Paul Reeves (Gb 2) / Jay Price" comment="Bed évocateur, plein de tension." styleid="14" lengthseconds="135" time="2:15" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_066_Discreet_Emotive/TSH066_trk009_COVER_OF_DARKNESS_Paul_Reeves_(Gb_2)_Jay_Price_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, PRINCIPAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, TROUBLANT, ANXIEUX, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, CRAINTIF, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, AGITÉ, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, QUI A DU CRAN, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, FORMATIONS GENERALES, SERIEUX, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, AGITE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE Bed évocateur, plein de tension. tsh 066 tk009 paul reeves (gb 2) jay price cover of darkness tsh 066 discreet emotive the scoring house drama film score orchestral documentary general lineups electronic and acoustic main film score orchestral trailer disturbing anxious disturbing dark disturbing fearful disturbing mysterious disturbing restless disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense scary ominous serious serious tense atmospheric bed. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="1400" name="Moscow (c)" code="FEM 015 tk022" libraryid="2" albumid="35" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_015_Zeitgeist/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Stephen Dean Hilton" comment="Suspense ambiant pour cette piste de bande-annonce mysterieuse avec une subtile guitare acoustique." styleid="2" lengthseconds="160" time="2:40" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_015_Zeitgeist/FEM_015_trk022_MOSCOW_(C)_Stephen_Dean_Hilton_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="22" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, ORCHESTRAL HYBRIDE , ROCK, INDIE, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, SOUND DESIGN, ALTERNATIF, FILMS, CINÉMA FRANCAIS, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, FILMS INDÉPENDANTS, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, AGITÉ, TROUBLANT, TENDU, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, EVOLUTIF, GLITCHY, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), EUROPE, EUROPE DE L'OUEST, FRANCE, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, AGITE, CINEMA FRANCAIS, FILMS INDEPENDANTS, ELEMENTS, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Suspense ambiant pour cette piste de bande-annonce mysterieuse avec une subtile guitare acoustique. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede fem 015 tk022 stephen dean hilton moscow (c) fem 015 zeitgeist fired earth music trailer film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral orchestral hybrid rock indie sound elements atmospheres sound design alternate movies french cinema movies human drama movies indie films movies urban drama trailers trailer track disturbing restless disturbing tense ambient thriller mystery trailer cue with subtle acoustic guitar theme. alternative" waveformpath="" version="Alternative" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
    <item id="24408" name="Black Ops (a)" code="WOM 322 tk012" libraryid="6" albumid="526" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_322_Cinematic_Drama/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Martin Tillmann" comment="Musique subtile, évolutive, pleine de suspense et de tension. Progresse jusqu'au coup final." styleid="14" lengthseconds="142" time="2:22" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_322_Cinematic_Drama/WOM322_trk012_BLACK_OPS_(A)_Martin_Tillmann_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, DRONES, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, SOUND DESIGN, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TROUBLANT, ANXIEUX, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, CRAINTIF, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, AGITÉ, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, EFFRAYANT, MENAÇANT, SÉRIEUX, INQUIET, EVOLUTIF, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, ELEMENTS SONORES, FORMATIONS GENERALES, SERIEUX, ATMOSPHERES, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, INQUIETANT, AGITE, MENACANT, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Musique subtile, évolutive, pleine de suspense et de tension. Progresse jusqu'au coup final. wom 322 tk012 martin tillmann black ops (a) wom 322 cinematic drama west one music drama film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral documentary sound elements atmospheres sound elements atmospheres drones sound elements atmospheres sound design main movies crime detective mystery movies espionage spy movies horror thriller movies human drama movies subtle evolving score full of suspense and tension. building to big final hit. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="26378" name="Pressure Zone (b)" code="WOM 209 tk014" libraryid="6" albumid="565" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_209_Absolution/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Toby Y. Chu" comment="Tendu et menaçant avec des percussions fesant tic-tac et un piano suberbe. Progresse avec une batterie tribale." styleid="4" lengthseconds="144" time="2:24" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_209_Absolution/WOM209_trk014_PRESSURE_ZONE_(B)_Toby_Y._Chu_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="14" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ALTERNATIF, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, FORT, MAJESTUEUX, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BATTERIE, CLAVIER, PIANO, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETECTIVE, MYSTERE Tendu et menaçant avec des percussions fesant tic-tac et un piano suberbe. Progresse avec une batterie tribale. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 209 tk014 toby y. chu pressure zone (b) wom 209 absolution west one music film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer alternate movies action adventure movies crime detective mystery movies horror thriller movies human drama tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing mysterious disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense scary ominous serious tense and ominous with ticking percussion and lush piano. builds with tribal drums. alternative" waveformpath="" version="Alternative" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="6732" name="A Dark Enticement" code="TSH 070A tk002" libraryid="5" albumid="154" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_070A_Divided_Worlds/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Nicolas John Harvey" comment="Bed soutenu et de mauvais augure." styleid="10" lengthseconds="153" time="2:33" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_070A_Divided_Worlds/TSH_070_trk002_A_DARK_ENTICEMENT_Nicolas_John_Harvey_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, PRINCIPAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, SOUND DESIGN, TROUBLANT, STÉRILE, TROUBLANT, FROID , TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, CRAINTIF, TROUBLANT, SURNATUREL, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, FROID, STÉRILE, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, ELEMENTS SONORES, FORMATIONS GENERALES, ATMOSPHERES, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, STERILE, INQUIETANT, DEPRIMANT, ELEMENTS, METEO, ETE Bed soutenu et de mauvais augure. tsh 070a tk002 nicolas john harvey a dark enticement tsh 070a divided worlds the scoring house documentary film score orchestral documentary general lineups electronic and acoustic main film score orchestral trailer sound elements atmospheres sound design disturbing barren disturbing cold disturbing eerie disturbing mysterious disturbing supernatural disturbing suspenseful sustained ominous bed. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="6219" name="Cause and Effect" code="TSH 064A tk010" libraryid="5" albumid="146" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_064A_The_Observing_Eye/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Zac Jordan" comment="Atmosphère de sérieux, qui invite à réfléchir. Se développe progressivement." styleid="12" lengthseconds="124" time="2:04" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_064A_The_Observing_Eye/TSH064A_trk010_CAUSE_AND_EFFECT_Zac_Jordan_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="10" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, PRINCIPAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, TROUBLANT, ANXIEUX, TROUBLANT, FLIPPANT, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, ÉTRANGE , TROUBLANT, SURNATUREL, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, SÉRIEUX, INQUIET, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, ESPACE, INTERSIDÉRAL, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, ATMOSPHÈRE SCIENTIFIQUE, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, DRAME HOSPITALIER, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, ELEMENTS SONORES, FORMATIONS GENERALES, SERIEUX, ATMOSPHERES, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, ETRANGE, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, ATMOSPHERE SCIENTIFIQUE, INTERSIDERAL Atmosphère de sérieux, qui invite à réfléchir. Se développe progressivement. tsh 064a tk010 zac jordan cause and effect tsh 064a the observing eye the scoring house atmospheres sound elements atmospheres general lineups electronic and acoustic main film score orchestral documentary disturbing anxious disturbing creepy disturbing dark disturbing mysterious disturbing strange disturbing supernatural disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense serious serious thought-provoking mood gradually developing. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="3112" name="Darker Waters" code="TSH 008 tk003" libraryid="5" albumid="99" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_008_Ambient_Spirit/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Everard Lawrence Wells / Robert John Foster" comment="Un fond sonore anxieux et dérangeant avec des ponctuations graves." styleid="15" lengthseconds="74" time="1:14" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_008_Ambient_Spirit/TSH008_trk003_DARKER_WATERS_Richard_Everard_Lawrence_Wells_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, TROUBLANT, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, NERVEUX, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MER, SOUS-MARIN, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, ATMOSPHÈRE SCIENTIFIQUE,, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), INQUIETANT, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS, ATMOSPHERE SCIENTIFIQUE Un fond sonore anxieux et dérangeant avec des ponctuations graves. tsh 008 tk003 richard everard lawrence wells robert john foster darker waters tsh 008 ambient spirit the scoring house ambient chill sound elements atmospheres main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) business corporate science technology disturbing dark disturbing disturbing disturbing eerie disturbing mysterious edgy movies crime detective mystery tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama documentary edgy disturbing bed with low punctuations. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="3110" name="Spiritual Vision" code="TSH 008 tk001" libraryid="5" albumid="99" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_008_Ambient_Spirit/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Everard Lawrence Wells / Robert John Foster" comment="Suspension aérienne." styleid="15" lengthseconds="107" time="1:47" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_008_Ambient_Spirit/TSH008_trk001_SPIRITUAL_VISION_Richard_Everard_Lawrence_Wells_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MER, SOUS-MARIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, DIVIN, CÉLESTE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, ESPACE, INTERSIDÉRAL, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, ATMOSPHÈRE SCIENTIFIQUE, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, DIVIN, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), EFFETS SONORES, SIFFLEMENT, CRÉPITEMENT, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), CREPITEMENT, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, ATMOSPHERE SCIENTIFIQUE, CELESTE, INTERSIDERAL Suspension aérienne. tsh 008 tk001 richard everard lawrence wells robert john foster spiritual vision tsh 008 ambient spirit the scoring house ambient chill sound elements atmospheres business corporate science technology main documentary science technology nature wildlife the elements sea underwater nature wildlife the elements sky heavenly celestial nature wildlife the elements sky space outer space science technology ethereal suspension. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="4613" name="Each New Day (a)" code="TSH 035 tk009" libraryid="5" albumid="125" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_035_A_Winner_is_Born/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Mark Lasker" comment="Un morceau chaleureux et plein d'attentes évoluant graduellement." styleid="22" lengthseconds="138" time="2:18" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_035_A_Winner_is_Born/TSH035_trk009_EACH_NEW_DAY_(A)_Mark_Lasker_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EVOLUTIF, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, RALENTI, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, REVELER, ELEMENTS, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Un morceau chaleureux et plein d'attentes évoluant graduellement. tsh 035 tk009 mark lasker each new day (a) tsh 035 a winner is born the scoring house sport business corporate reveal launch business corporate luxury film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic main business corporate movies human drama movies romance nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama tv radio sports sad depressing warm and expectant gradually evolving. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="22308" name="Fields of Wonder" code="WOM 277 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="479" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_277_Reconstruction_-_Textures/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Spirales glorieuses de lumière chatoyante." styleid="12" lengthseconds="90" time="1:30" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_277_Reconstruction_-_Textures/WOM277_trk001_FIELDS_OF_WONDER_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, DÉTENDU, TENDRE, LÉGER, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, DIVIN, CÉLESTE,, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), DETENDU, LEGER, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, CELESTE Spirales glorieuses de lumière chatoyante. wom 277 tk001 david ashton fields of wonder wom 277 reconstruction - textures west one music atmospheres sound elements atmospheres classical and semi classical symphony orchestra main tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) film score orchestral panoramic sound elements atmospheres peaceful dreamy peaceful peaceful peaceful relaxed tender light movement smooth aerial floating glorious swirls of shimmering light. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="6223" name="Shadow Sequence" code="TSH 064A tk014" libraryid="5" albumid="146" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_064A_The_Observing_Eye/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Zac Jordan" comment="Intensité calme, pulsante." styleid="12" lengthseconds="79" time="1:19" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_064A_The_Observing_Eye/TSH064A_trk014_SHADOW_SEQUENCE_Zac_Jordan_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="14" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, PRINCIPAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, TROUBLANT, ANXIEUX, TROUBLANT, STÉRILE, TROUBLANT, FROID , TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, ÉTRANGE , TROUBLANT, SURNATUREL, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, SÉRIEUX, INQUIET, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, PULSATION, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, SCIENCE FICTION, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, NEIGE, GLACE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, ESPACE, INTERSIDÉRAL, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, ATMOSPHÈRE SCIENTIFIQUE, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, JOURNALISME D'INVESTIGATION, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, DRAME HOSPITALIER, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, ELEMENTS SONORES, FORMATIONS GENERALES, SERIEUX, ATMOSPHERES, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, STERILE, INQUIETANT, ETRANGE, ACTUALITES, ELEMENTS, ATMOSPHERE SCIENTIFIQUE, INTERSIDERAL Intensité calme, pulsante. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz tsh 064a tk014 zac jordan shadow sequence tsh 064a the observing eye the scoring house atmospheres sound elements atmospheres general lineups electronic and acoustic main film score orchestral documentary disturbing anxious disturbing barren disturbing cold disturbing dark disturbing eerie disturbing mysterious disturbing strange disturbing supernatural disturbing quiet pulsing intensity. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="6421" name="Dream Drifter (b)" code="TSH 066 tk025" libraryid="5" albumid="150" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_066_Discreet_Emotive/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Paul Reeves (Gb 2) / Jay Price" comment="Atmosphère reveuse et chaleureuse." styleid="14" lengthseconds="157" time="2:37" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_066_Discreet_Emotive/TSH066_trk025_DREAM_DRIFTER_(B)_Paul_Reeves_(Gb_2)_Jay_Price_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="25" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, UNDERSCORE, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, DÉTENDU, PAISIBLE, APAISANT, PAISIBLE, TRANQUILLE, TENDRE, DÉLICAT, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, BEAU, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, CLAVIER, PIANO, ELEMENTS SONORES, FORMATIONS GENERALES, ATMOSPHERES, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, DETENDU, DELICAT, AERIEN, ELEGANT, ELEMENTS Atmosphère reveuse et chaleureuse. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 066 tk025 paul reeves (gb 2) jay price dream drifter (b) tsh 066 discreet emotive the scoring house drama film score orchestral documentary general lineups electronic and acoustic underscore sound elements atmospheres peaceful contented peaceful dreamy peaceful relaxed peaceful soothing peaceful tranquil tender delicate tender intimate tender reflective tender romantic tender warm dreamy mood. underscore delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Underscore" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="6229" name="Horizons of Time" code="TSH 064A tk020" libraryid="5" albumid="146" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_064A_The_Observing_Eye/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Zac Jordan" comment="Textures flottantes et énigmatiques." styleid="12" lengthseconds="109" time="1:49" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_064A_The_Observing_Eye/TSH064A_trk020_HORIZONS_OF_TIME_Zac_Jordan_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="20" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, PRINCIPAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, TROUBLANT, ANXIEUX, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, ÉTRANGE , TROUBLANT, SURNATUREL, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, SÉRIEUX, INQUIET, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, PULSATION, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MER, SOUS-MARIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, ESPACE, INTERSIDÉRAL, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, ATMOSPHÈRE SCIENTIFIQUE, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, JOURNALISME D'INVESTIGATION, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, DRAME HOSPITALIER, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, ELEMENTS SONORES, FORMATIONS GENERALES, SERIEUX, ATMOSPHERES, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, INQUIETANT, ETRANGE, DEPRIMANT, AERIEN, ACTUALITES, ELEMENTS, ATMOSPHERE SCIENTIFIQUE, INTERSIDERAL Textures flottantes et énigmatiques. tsh 064a tk020 zac jordan horizons of time tsh 064a the observing eye the scoring house atmospheres sound elements atmospheres general lineups electronic and acoustic main film score orchestral documentary disturbing anxious disturbing eerie disturbing mysterious disturbing strange disturbing supernatural disturbing suspenseful sad depressing sad serious concerned movement enigmatic floating textures. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="6810" name="In Balance" code="TSH 072 tk015" libraryid="5" albumid="156" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_072_Essential_Minimal/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Robert John Foster" comment="Construction logique et sans empressement." styleid="10" lengthseconds="123" time="2:03" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_072_Essential_Minimal/TSH_072_trk015_IN_BALANCE_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="15" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES, QUATUOR A CORDES , PRINCIPAL, CLASSIQUE, STYLE MINIMALISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FORMATION, INFORMATION, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, RÉPÉTITIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, AUTOMATISATION, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, AMBIANCES ET FONDS SONORES POUR PROJETS, TV, RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉBUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, FORMATIONS GENERALES, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, DETERMINE, REPETITIF, ACCELERE, TELE REALITE Construction logique et sans empressement. tsh 072 tk015 robert john foster in balance tsh 072 essential minimal the scoring house documentary business corporate beds general lineups electronic and acoustic strings string quartet main classical minimalist style business corporate training information film score orchestral documentary strong determined uplifting optimistic uplifting positive movement rhythmic logical unhurried construction. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="17144" name="The Flower Opens (a)" code="WOM 165 tk009" libraryid="6" albumid="360" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_165_The_Pastoral_Album/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Patrick Thomas Hawes" comment="Minimal et intrigant. Un duo enchanteur entre une harpe et une flûte." styleid="26" lengthseconds="130" time="2:10" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_165_The_Pastoral_Album/WOM165_trk009_THE_FLOWER_OPENS_(A)_Patrick_Thomas_Hawes_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, PARASITES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MER, SOUS-MARIN, CORDES, HARPE, BOIS, FLUTE,, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), AERIEN, ELEMENTS Minimal et intrigant. Un duo enchanteur entre une harpe et une flûte. wom 165 tk009 patrick thomas hawes the flower opens (a) wom 165 the pastoral album west one music nature wildlife sound elements atmospheres classical and semi classical symphony orchestra main tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) film score orchestral pastoral peaceful dreamy peaceful peaceful movement smooth aerial flying static nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife minimal and intriguing. an enchanting duet between harp and flute. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="2971" name="Gentle Flow" code="TSH 005 tk010" libraryid="5" albumid="96" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_005_Acoustic_Groove/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Paolo Maddaloni" comment="Contemplative intéraction rythmique." styleid="13" lengthseconds="108" time="1:48" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_005_Acoustic_Groove/TSH005_trk010_GENTLE_FLOW_Paolo_Maddaloni_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="10" tracktotal="" search="EASY LISTENING, MIDDLE OF THE ROAD, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, SÉRIEUX, ATTENTIONNÉ, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, DOCUMENTAIRE, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN NYLON, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN MÉTAL,, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, ATTENTIONNE, CORDES EN METAL, JOURNEE Contemplative intéraction rythmique. tsh 005 tk010 paolo maddaloni gentle flow tsh 005 acoustic groove the scoring house acoustic easy listening middle of the road main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) peaceful peaceful tender nostalgic tender reflective tender romantic tender sentimental sad depressing lonely sad depressing poignant sad depressing sad serious thoughtful movement smooth flowing thoughtful rhythmic interplay. main delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="7670" name="Bubble Stream" code="TSH 041 tk006" libraryid="5" albumid="171" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_041_Through_the_Lens/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Colin John Riley" comment="Une progression sonore de couleurs kaléidoscopiques." styleid="24" lengthseconds="159" time="2:39" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_041_Through_the_Lens/TSH041_trk006_BUBBLE_STREAM_Colin_John_Riley_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="6" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, CLASSIQUE, STYLE MINIMALISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, COMMUNICATION, ACTUALITÉS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MER, SOUS-MARIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, PLUIE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, AMBIANCES ET FONDS SONORES POUR PROJETS, TENDRE, DÉLICAT, EVOLUTIF, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, INSECTE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, FUTURISTE, ELEMENTS SONORES, PERIODE, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DELICAT, IRREGULIER, ACCELERE, ACTUALITES, ELEMENTS, METEO, ETE, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Une progression sonore de couleurs kaléidoscopiques. tsh 041 tk006 colin john riley bubble stream tsh 041 through the lens the scoring house science new technology sound elements atmospheres classical minimalist style business corporate beds business corporate communication news business corporate science technology main documentary science technology nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife nature wildlife the elements sea building kaleidoscopic colours. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="17148" name="The Water Nymph" code="WOM 165 tk013" libraryid="6" albumid="360" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_165_The_Pastoral_Album/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Patrick Thomas Hawes" comment="Un solo éthéré de harpe. Des couleurs harmoniques, atmosphériques et spacieuses." styleid="26" lengthseconds="127" time="2:07" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_165_The_Pastoral_Album/WOM165_trk013_THE_WATER_NYMPH_Patrick_Thomas_Hawes_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="13" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PRINCIPAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MER, SOUS-MARIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, ÉTÉ, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CORDES, HARPE, SOLO, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, ETE Un solo éthéré de harpe. Des couleurs harmoniques, atmosphériques et spacieuses. wom 165 tk013 patrick thomas hawes the water nymph wom 165 the pastoral album west one music nature wildlife sound elements atmospheres film score orchestral pastoral main nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife nature wildlife the elements sea underwater nature wildlife the elements seasons time summer ethereal solo harp. atmospheric and spacious harmonic colours. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="1381" name="Day (a)" code="FEM 015 tk003" libraryid="2" albumid="35" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_015_Zeitgeist/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Stephen Dean Hilton" comment="Un piano mélancholique et des textures de cordes ambiantes ouvrent cette piste nostalgique et pensive. Des atmospheres rêveuses et des effets sonores excentriques se combinent avec des cordes experimentales afin de créer une scène rêveuse. Outro subtile composée de réverbes fantomes." styleid="2" lengthseconds="214" time="3:34" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_015_Zeitgeist/FEM_015_trk003_DAY_(A)_Stephen_Dean_Hilton_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, SOUND DESIGN, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ART ET ESSAI, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, AUBE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, DIVIN, CÉLESTE, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, TENDRE, DÉLICAT, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, PIZZICATO, MONTÉE, ASCENDANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, MONTÉE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CORDES, CORDES PIZZICATO, ELEMENTS SONORES, MONTEE, ATMOSPHERES, DELICAT, ACCELERE, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, CELESTE Un piano mélancholique et des textures de cordes ambiantes ouvrent cette piste nostalgique et pensive. Des atmospheres rêveuses et des effets sonores excentriques se combinent avec des cordes experimentales afin de créer une scène rêveuse. Outro subtile composée de réverbes fantomes. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live fem 015 tk003 stephen dean hilton day (a) fem 015 zeitgeist fired earth music trailer film score orchestral trailer sound elements atmospheres sound elements atmospheres sound design main movies art house movies romance nature wildlife the elements seasons time dawn nature wildlife the elements sky aerial clouds nature wildlife the elements sky heavenly a melancholic piano and ambient string textures open this pensive nostalgic trailer track. dreamy atmospheres and quirky sound effects combine with glitchy experimental strings to create a dreamy scene. subtle outro featuring ghostly reverb. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
    <item id="6239" name="Floating Through Clouds" code="TSH 064A tk030" libraryid="5" albumid="146" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_064A_The_Observing_Eye/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Zac Jordan" comment="Textures aériennes à la dérive." styleid="12" lengthseconds="115" time="1:55" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_064A_The_Observing_Eye/TSH064A_trk030_FLOATING_THROUGH_CLOUDS_Zac_Jordan_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="30" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, PRINCIPAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, MONTÉE, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MER, SOUS-MARIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, DIVIN, CÉLESTE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, ATMOSPHÈRE SCIENTIFIQUE, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, DRAME FAMILIAL, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, DRAME HOSPITALIER, ELEMENTS SONORES, FORMATIONS GENERALES, MONTEE, ATMOSPHERES, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, ATMOSPHERE SCIENTIFIQUE, CELESTE Textures aériennes à la dérive. tsh 064a tk030 zac jordan floating through clouds tsh 064a the observing eye the scoring house atmospheres sound elements atmospheres general lineups electronic and acoustic main film score orchestral documentary disturbing mysterious peaceful dreamy peaceful peaceful movement smooth aerial floating movement smooth rising documentary science technology movies human drama nature airy drifting textures. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="7062" name="Celestial Journeys (a)" code="TSH 026A tk001" libraryid="5" albumid="162" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_026A_Dimensions/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Dave Hewson / Alexander Balanescu" comment="L'imagerie légère et nébuleuse de l'errance." styleid="4" lengthseconds="134" time="2:14" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_026A_Dimensions/TSH026A_trk001_CELESTIAL_JOURNEYS_(A)_Dave_Hewson_Alexander_Balanescu_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PRINCIPAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, DIVIN, CÉLESTE, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TENDRE, LÉGER, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, CORDES, VIOLON, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), LEGER, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, CELESTE L'imagerie légère et nébuleuse de l'errance. tsh 026a tk001 dave hewson alexander balanescu celestial journeys (a) tsh 026a dimensions the scoring house film score orchestral sound elements atmospheres film score orchestral pastoral main nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife nature wildlife the elements sky aerial light nebulous drifting imagery. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="26535" name="Life’s Wonder (a)" code="WOM 335 tk002" libraryid="6" albumid="569" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_335_Inspiring_Minimalism/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Steven Gutheinz" comment="Morceau émouvant et au bon coeur pour piano solo. Avec accompagnement de cordes expressives." styleid="4" lengthseconds="173" time="2:53" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_335_Inspiring_Minimalism/WOM_335_trk002_LIFES_WONDER_(A)_Steven_Gutheinz_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, PRINCIPAL, CLASSIQUE, STYLE MINIMALISTE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, SÉRIEUX, ÉMOUVANT, SÉRIEUX, ATTENTIONNÉ, TENDRE, INNOCENT, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TENDRE, TENDRE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, BEAU, EVOLUTIF, DIVIN, MÉLODIQUE, LYRIQUE, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, HIVER, CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, VIOLONCELLE, SERIEUX, MELODIQUE, EMOUVANT, ATTENTIONNE, ELEGANT, ELEMENTS, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Morceau émouvant et au bon coeur pour piano solo. Avec accompagnement de cordes expressives. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 335 tk002 steven gutheinz life’s wonder (a) wom 335 inspiring minimalism west one music film score orchestral film score orchestral documentary strings string section main classical minimalist style film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic serious emotional serious thoughtful tender innocent tender nostalgic tender reflective tender romantic tender sentimental emotional tender-hearted solo piano with expressive string accompaniment. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="21801" name="Respite (a)" code="WOM 264 tk012" libraryid="6" albumid="467" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_264_Emotive_Acoustic/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Alistair Bruce Henry Friend / Ted Brett Barnes" comment="Une guitare acoustique tendre et des cordes intimes et émouvantes." styleid="13" lengthseconds="247" time="4:07" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_264_Emotive_Acoustic/WOM264_trk012_RESPITE_(A)_Alistair_Bruce_Henry_Friend_Ted_Brett_Barnes_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, MUSIQUE DE CHAMBRE, ENSEMBLE CLASSIQUE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, TENDRE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, ACOUSTIQUE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, ÉTÉ, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN NYLON, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN MÉTAL, CORDES, VIOLON ,, ELEMENTS, CORDES EN METAL, ETE Une guitare acoustique tendre et des cordes intimes et émouvantes. wom 264 tk012 alistair bruce henry friend ted brett barnes respite (a) wom 264 emotive acoustic west one music acoustic film score orchestral pastoral classical and semi classical chamber music classical ensemble main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) peaceful contented peaceful dreamy tender intimate tender nostalgic tender romantic tender tender tender warm acoustic tv radio leisure tender acoustic guitar and intimate emotive strings. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="27023" name="Distant Tales (b)" code="WOM 350A tk032" libraryid="6" albumid="579" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_350A_British_Drama/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Michael Price, Nicholas Hill" comment="Des histoires venues de loin. Avec cordes orchestrales chaleureuses et émouvantes." styleid="14" lengthseconds="132" time="2:12" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_350A_British_Drama/WOM_350A_trk032_DISTANT_TALES_(B)_Michael_Price,_Nicholas_Hill_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="32" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, UNDERSCORE, FILMS, FAMILIAL, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, PERIODE, PERIODES, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, ELEMENTS, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, DRAME TV, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, INTROSPECTIF, PAISIBLE, LYRIQUE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, DOUX-AMER, DEPRIMANT, SÉRIEUX, ÉMOUVANT, SERIEUX, EMOUVANT, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, SERIEUX, SÉRIEUX, ATTENTIONNÉ, SERIEUX, ATTENTIONNE, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, JAILLIR, BEAU, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, AERIEN, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT, ELEGANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, DRAME, BRITANNIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL Des histoires venues de loin. Avec cordes orchestrales chaleureuses et émouvantes. wom 350a tk032 michael price nicholas hill distant tales (b) wom 350a british drama west one music drama film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral documentary film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral pastoral underscore movies family movies human drama movies period historical costume drama movies romance nature wildlife the elements land rural telling stories from afar. emotive and warm orchestral strings. underscore" waveformpath="" version="Underscore" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="7068" name="Glass Spires (a)" code="TSH 026A tk007" libraryid="5" albumid="162" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_026A_Dimensions/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Dave Hewson / Alexander Balanescu" comment="Des textures fluides, hypnotiques et légères." styleid="4" lengthseconds="112" time="1:52" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_026A_Dimensions/TSH026A_trk007_GLASS_SPIRES_(A)_Dave_Hewson_Alexander_Balanescu_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), PAISIBLE, REVEUR, TENDRE, LÉGER, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, NEIGE, GLACE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, DIVIN, CÉLESTE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, FROID, STÉRILE, CORDES, VIOLON ,, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), STERILE, LEGER, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, METEO, ETE, CELESTE Des textures fluides, hypnotiques et légères. tsh 026a tk007 dave hewson alexander balanescu glass spires (a) tsh 026a dimensions the scoring house film score orchestral sound elements atmospheres main tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) peaceful dreamy tender light movement smooth aerial floating movement smooth aerial flying nature wildlife the elements land snow ice nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature mesmerising fluid light textures. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="8500" name="Touching Hands (a)" code="TSH 060 tk009" libraryid="5" albumid="180" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_060_Life_In_Pictures/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Robert Henry Peter White / Alexander Stephen Gray" comment="Pensées douces et intimes." styleid="14" lengthseconds="178" time="2:58" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_060_Life_In_Pictures/TSH_060_trk009_TOUCHING_HANDS_(A)_Robert_Henry_Peter_White_Alexander_Stephen_Gray_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, PRINCIPAL, ENFANTS, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TENDRE, TENDRE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, DOCUMENTAIRE,, DEPRIMANT, ELEGANT Pensées douces et intimes. tsh 060 tk009 robert henry peter white alexander stephen gray touching hands (a) tsh 060 life in pictures the scoring house drama children storytelling main children peaceful dreamy peaceful peaceful tender intimate tender reflective tender sentimental tender tender sad depressing lonely movement smooth elegant movement smooth graceful movies children storytelling tv radio children youth tv tv tender intimate reflections. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="7484" name="Humming Birds (a)" code="TSH 074 tk002" libraryid="5" albumid="169" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_074_Symphonic_Sketchbook/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Arthur Rhodes" comment="Images chaleureuses, qui se déroulent. Avec voix féminine." styleid="4" lengthseconds="181" time="3:01" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_074_Symphonic_Sketchbook/TSH_074_trk002_HUMMING_BIRDS_(A)_Simon_Arthur_Rhodes_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, TRAILER, CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, FAMILIAL, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, ELEMENTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, ELEMENTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ELEMENTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, DIVIN, CÉLESTE, CELESTE, ELEMENTS, PAISIBLE, CALME, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, LYRIQUE, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, SÉRIEUX, ÉMOUVANT, SERIEUX, EMOUVANT, TENDRE, LÉGER, LEGER, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, BEAU, MAGIQUE, MÉLODIQUE, LYRIQUE, MELODIQUE, ÉTINCELANT, ETINCELANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, AERIEN, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT, ELEGANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, CLAVIER, PIANO, BOIS, FLUTE, VOCAL, FÉMININ, SOPRANO, FEMININ, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL Images chaleureuses, qui se déroulent. Avec voix féminine. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 074 tk002 simon arthur rhodes humming birds (a) tsh 074 symphonic sketchbook the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer classical classical styling film score orchestral panoramic film score orchestral pastoral main movies family movies human drama movies romance nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife the elements land rural warm unfolding imagery with female voice. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="26372" name="Ray of Hope (a)" code="WOM 209 tk008" libraryid="6" albumid="565" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_209_Absolution/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Toby Y. Chu" comment="Des cordes enthousiasmantes et optimistes fusionnées avec des motifs de guitare évocateurs." styleid="4" lengthseconds="128" time="2:08" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_209_Absolution/WOM209_trk008_RAY_OF_HOPE_(A)_Toby_Y._Chu_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="8" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, DIVIN, CÉLESTE, TITRE POUR TRAILER, DROLE, MÉLODRAMATIQUE, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, DÉTENDU, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, COOL, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), MELODRAMATIQUE, DETENDU, AERIEN, ELECTRIQUE, ELEMENTS, CELESTE Des cordes enthousiasmantes et optimistes fusionnées avec des motifs de guitare évocateurs. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 209 tk008 toby y. chu ray of hope (a) wom 209 absolution west one music film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic main movies human drama movies romance nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife the elements sky aerial clouds nature wildlife the elements sky heavenly celestial trailer track stirring optimistic strings fused with evocative guitar patterns. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="7122" name="Nirvana (a)" code="TSH 029 tk004" libraryid="5" albumid="164" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_029_Symphonic_Fantasia/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Arthur Rhodes" comment="Serein, enveloppant, flottant." styleid="4" lengthseconds="199" time="3:19" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_029_Symphonic_Fantasia/TSH029_trk004_NIRVANA_(A)_Simon_Arthur_Rhodes_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, ESPACE, INTERSIDÉRAL, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, SEREIN, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, RALENTI, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, CLAVIER, PIANO, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, DEPRIMANT, ACCELERE, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, INTERSIDERAL Serein, enveloppant, flottant. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 029 tk004 simon arthur rhodes nirvana (a) tsh 029 symphonic fantasia the scoring house film score orchestral sound elements atmospheres film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic main movies romance nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife nature wildlife the elements sky aerial clouds nature serene immersive drifting. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="6210" name="A Fragile Balance" code="TSH 064A tk001" libraryid="5" albumid="146" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_064A_The_Observing_Eye/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Zac Jordan" comment="Observations chaleureuses et introspectives." styleid="12" lengthseconds="127" time="2:07" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_064A_The_Observing_Eye/TSH064A_trk001_A_FRAGILE_BALANCE_Zac_Jordan_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, PRINCIPAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, PAISIBLE, CALME, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TENDRE, DÉLICAT, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, SONGEUR, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, RALENTI, BEAU, ÉTINCELANT, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, DIVIN, CÉLESTE, CLAVIER, PIANO, ELEMENTS SONORES, FORMATIONS GENERALES, ETINCELANT, ATMOSPHERES, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, DELICAT, AERIEN, ELEGANT, ELEMENTS, CELESTE Observations chaleureuses et introspectives. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 064a tk001 zac jordan a fragile balance tsh 064a the observing eye the scoring house atmospheres sound elements atmospheres general lineups electronic and acoustic main film score orchestral documentary peaceful calm peaceful dreamy peaceful peaceful tender delicate tender intimate tender reflective movement smooth aerial floating movement smooth elegant movement warm introspective observations. main delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="3437" name="Walking Away" code="TSH 013 tk010" libraryid="5" albumid="103" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_013_It's_My_Life/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Ian Paul Livingstone" comment="Un thème profond et émotionnel." styleid="10" lengthseconds="95" time="1:35" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_013_It's_My_Life/TSH013_trk010_WALKING_AWAY_Ian_Paul_Livingstone_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="10" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, TROUBLANT, DROLE, MÉLODRAMATIQUE, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, SÉRIEUX, ÉMOUVANT, SÉRIEUX, ATTENTIONNÉ, TENDRE, INNOCENT, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EVOLUTIF, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, MUSIQUE DE CHAMBRE, ENSEMBLE CLASSIQUE, STYLE VINTAGE, PERIODE, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), MELODRAMATIQUE, DEPRIMANT, EMOUVANT, ATTENTIONNE, PERIODES, ELEMENTS, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Un thème profond et émotionnel. tsh 013 tk010 ian paul livingstone walking away tsh 013 it's my life the scoring house documentary children business corporate luxury film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral pastoral main movies human drama movies period historical costume drama movies romance nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral nature wildlife the elements thoughtful emotional theme. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="7390" name="Our Heritage (a)" code="TSH 059 tk010" libraryid="5" albumid="168" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_059_Orchestral_Fantasia/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Arthur Rhodes" comment="Thème plein d'attention et de dignité." styleid="4" lengthseconds="149" time="2:29" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_059_Orchestral_Fantasia/TSH_059_trk010_OUR_HERITAGE_(A)_Simon_Arthur_Rhodes_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="10" tracktotal="" search="CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE, CLASSIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, SÉRIEUX, DIGNE, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, ATTENTIONNÉ, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, PATRIOTIQUE, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, CLAVIER, PIANO, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, PÉRIODE, PRÉ-20E SIÈCLE, 19E SIÈCLE, AMERIQUE DU NORD, PERIODE, SERIEUX, ETATS-UNIS, PRE-20E SIECLE, ATTENTIONNE, PERIODES, 20E SIECLE, 19E SIECLE, ELEMENTS Thème plein d'attention et de dignité. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 059 tk010 simon arthur rhodes our heritage (a) tsh 059 orchestral fantasia the scoring house film score orchestral classical classical styling classical film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic film score orchestral pastoral main documentary biographical historical the arts movies period historical costume drama nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama thoughtful dignified theme. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="26540" name="Life Sanctuary (a)" code="WOM 335 tk007" libraryid="6" albumid="569" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_335_Inspiring_Minimalism/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Diana Yukawa" comment="Paysage sonore épars, atmosphérique et futuriste qui évolue en de somptueuses, fluides lignes de cordes." styleid="4" lengthseconds="152" time="2:32" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_335_Inspiring_Minimalism/WOM_335_trk007_LIFE_SANCTUARY_(A)_Diana_Yukawa_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, PRINCIPAL, CLASSIQUE, STYLE MINIMALISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, PRESTIGE , BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, SOUND DESIGN, TENDRE, GRACIEUX, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, GENTIL, TENDRE, AFFECTUEUX, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, MONTÉE, BEAU, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, DIVIN, MONTÉE, ASCENDANT, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, DIVIN, CÉLESTE, CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, VIOLON, ELEMENTS SONORES, MONTEE, ATMOSPHERES, AERIEN, ELEGANT, ELEMENTS, CELESTE Paysage sonore épars, atmosphérique et futuriste qui évolue en de somptueuses, fluides lignes de cordes. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 335 tk007 diana yukawa life sanctuary (a) wom 335 inspiring minimalism west one music film score orchestral film score orchestral documentary strings string section main classical minimalist style business corporate luxury business corporate prestige film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic sound elements atmospheres sound elements atmospheres sound design sparse futuristic and atmospheric soundscape evolving into luxurious flowing string lines. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="4618" name="Beauty in Motion" code="TSH 035 tk014" libraryid="5" albumid="125" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_035_A_Winner_is_Born/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Mark Lasker" comment="Des images descriptives et émotionnelles avec un ensemble violoncelle." styleid="22" lengthseconds="118" time="1:58" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_035_A_Winner_is_Born/TSH035_trk014_BEAUTY_IN_MOTION_Mark_Lasker_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="14" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, SÉRIEUX, ÉMOUVANT, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, CORDES, VIOLONCELLE, STYLE VINTAGE, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, EMOUVANT, ELEMENTS Des images descriptives et émotionnelles avec un ensemble violoncelle. tsh 035 tk014 mark lasker beauty in motion tsh 035 a winner is born the scoring house sport film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral pastoral main documentary movies human drama movies romance nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral peaceful dreamy peaceful peaceful sad emotional descriptive imagery featuring cello ensemble. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="6831" name="Solitary Lives" code="TSH 072 tk036" libraryid="5" albumid="156" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_072_Essential_Minimal/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Robert John Foster" comment="Poignant, qui invite à réfléchir." styleid="10" lengthseconds="70" time="1:10" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_072_Essential_Minimal/TSH_072_trk036_SOLITARY_LIVES_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="36" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, PRINCIPAL, PAISIBLE, CALME, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, ZEN, MÉDITATION , TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TENDRE, SONGEUR, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, RALENTI, BEAU, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, CLAVIER, PIANO, SOLODOCUMENTAIRE, MINIMAL, DEPRIMANT, MEDITATION, AERIEN, ELEMENTS Poignant, qui invite à réfléchir. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 072 tk036 robert john foster solitary lives tsh 072 essential minimal the scoring house documentary film score orchestral documentary main peaceful calm peaceful dreamy peaceful peaceful peaceful zen meditation sad depressing poignant tender reflective movement smooth aerial floating movement smooth slow motion beautiful documentary biographical historical the arts poignant thought-provoking. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="26586" name="Morning Calm (a)" code="WOM 338 tk003" libraryid="6" albumid="570" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_338_Life_In_Conflict/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Wayne Roberts" comment="Underscore de cordes optimiste, qui réchauffe le coeur. Avec de tendres cordes en accompagnement." styleid="4" lengthseconds="113" time="1:53" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_338_Life_In_Conflict/WOM_338_trk003_MORNING_CALM_(A)_Wayne_Roberts_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, DRONES, PAISIBLE, INTROSPECTIF, SÉRIEUX, ÉMOUVANT, SÉRIEUX, ATTENTIONNÉ, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, AFFECTUEUX, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, BEAU, DIVIN, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, GUERRE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, AUBE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, CLAVIER, PIANO, ELEMENTS SONORES, SERIEUX, ATMOSPHERES, EMOUVANT, ATTENTIONNE, AERIEN, ELEMENTS Underscore de cordes optimiste, qui réchauffe le coeur. Avec de tendres cordes en accompagnement. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 338 tk003 wayne roberts morning calm (a) wom 338 life in conflict west one music film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer strings string section main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) film score orchestral documentary sound elements atmospheres sound elements atmospheres drones peaceful introspective serious emotional serious thoughtful tender hopeful tender loving optimistic heartwarming piano lead with tender string accompaniment. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="26367" name="Inner World (a)" code="WOM 209 tk003" libraryid="6" albumid="565" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_209_Absolution/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Toby Y. Chu" comment="Une belle et délicate introduction progresse graduellement vers un climax mené par des cordes à 1:54. Avec un gamelan et des guitares électriques." styleid="4" lengthseconds="142" time="2:22" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_209_Absolution/WOM209_trk003_INNER_WORLD_(A)_Toby_Y._Chu_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, CLASSIQUE, STYLE MINIMALISTE, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, ART ET ESSAI, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, DÉTENDU, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, SÉRIEUX, TENDRE, DÉLICAT, TENDRE, SONGEUR, BEAU, CHUTE, DESCENTE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ETHNIQUE, PERCUSSION, GAMELAN, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETENDU, DEPRIMANT, DELICAT, ACCELERE, AERIEN, ELECTRIQUE, ELEMENTS Une belle et délicate introduction progresse graduellement vers un climax mené par des cordes à 1:54. Avec un gamelan et des guitares électriques. wom 209 tk003 toby y. chu inner world (a) wom 209 absolution west one music film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer classical minimalist style main documentary movies art house movies human drama nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife trailer track disturbing mysterious peaceful contented beautiful delicate introduction gradually builds to stunning string-led climax at 1:54. featuring gamelan and electric guitars. main delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="25778" name="Natures Son (a)" code="WOM 347 tk003" libraryid="6" albumid="552" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_347_Environment/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jay Price" comment="Défense de la faune et flore: une nouvelle vie. Marimbas et percussions pleins de rythmes se développent en d'optimistes chorus avec harmonium et guitare acoustique." styleid="24" lengthseconds="133" time="2:13" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_347_Environment/WOM_347_trk003_NATURES_SON_(A)_Jay_Price_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="DOCUMENTAIRE, ORCHESTRAL HYBRIDE , BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, COMMUNICATION, ACTUALITÉS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, ÉTÉ, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, SOLEIL, CHALEUR, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, ENJOUÉ, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, ETHNIQUE, CITHARE, CLAVIER, HARMONIUM, INHABITUEL, PERCUSSION CORPORELLE, PERCUSSION, MARIMBA, CORDES, BASSE, BASSE ÉLECTRIQUE, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN MÉTAL, CORDES, UKULELE, EFFETS SONORES, HUMAIN, APPLAUDISSEMENTS, ENJOUE, ACTUALITES, ELECTRIQUE, BASSE ELECTRIQUE, ELEMENTS, CORDES EN METAL, METEO, ETE Défense de la faune et flore: une nouvelle vie. Marimbas et percussions pleins de rythmes se développent en d'optimistes chorus avec harmonium et guitare acoustique. wom 347 tk003 jay price natures son (a) wom 347 environment west one music science new technology film score orchestral documentary business corporate bright optimistic business corporate communication news film score orchestral panoramic main business corporate documentary science technology nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife wildlife &amp; conservation: a new life. rhythmic marimbas and percussion develop into optimistic choruses with harmonium and acoustic guitar. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="20396" name="Inner Warmth (a)" code="WOM 233 tk008" libraryid="6" albumid="434" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_233_Atmospheric_Indie/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Matthew James Robertson / Mike Reed / Tom Howe" comment="Intime, doux et fun. Des instruments acoustiques superbes serpentent autour d'une percussion légère." styleid="34" lengthseconds="159" time="2:39" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_233_Atmospheric_Indie/WOM233_trk008_INNER_WARMTH_(A)_Matthew_James_Robertson_Mike_Reed_Tom_Howe_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="8" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, ROCK, INDIE, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, SOLEIL, CHALEUR, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, FUN, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, LÉGER, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, ACOUSTIQUE, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ORCHESTRE POP, FORMATIONS GENERALES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), LEGER, ELEMENTS, METEO, JOURNEE, ETE Intime, doux et fun. Des instruments acoustiques superbes serpentent autour d'une percussion légère. wom 233 tk008 matthew james robertson mike reed tom howe inner warmth (a) wom 233 atmospheric indie west one music indie business corporate beds business corporate bright optimistic business corporate luxury rock indie main business corporate nature wildlife the elements weather sun heat tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio intimate gentle and fun. gorgeous acoustic instruments weaving around light percussion. main delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="26954" name="Busy Bodies (a)" code="WOM 321 tk013" libraryid="6" albumid="578" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_321_Light_Bright_and_Playful/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Mike Reed / Tom Howe" comment="Marimba minimaliste répétitive et pizzicati de cordes. Chaleureux et positif. Pour la journée." styleid="10" lengthseconds="98" time="1:38" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_321_Light_Bright_and_Playful/WOM321_trk013_BUSY_BODIES_(A)_Mike_Reed_Tom_Howe_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="13" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, COMMUNICATION, ACTUALITÉS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, FAMILIAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, PAISIBLE, DÉTENDU, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, INNOCENT, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, PINCÉ, PIZZICATO, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, OCCUPÉ, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, RÉPÉTITIF, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, PERCUSSION, MARIMBA, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN MÉTAL, CORDES, CORDES PIZZICATO, PINCE, DETENDU, OCCUPE, REPETITIF, ACTUALITES, ELEMENTS, CORDES EN METAL Marimba minimaliste répétitive et pizzicati de cordes. Chaleureux et positif. Pour la journée. wom 321 tk013 mike reed tom howe busy bodies (a) wom 321 light bright and playful west one music documentary children storytelling business corporate beds business corporate bright optimistic business corporate communication news film score orchestral documentary film score orchestral trailer main movies children storytelling movies family nature wildlife the elements land repeating minimalist marimba and pizzicato strings. warm positive and daytime. dramedy. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="26841" name="Silly Boy (a)" code="WOM 266 tk002" libraryid="6" albumid="576" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_266_Quirky_Orchestral/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jack Wall" comment="Enjoué, accrocheur et espiègle. Des sections rythmiques légères alternent avec des mélodies luxuriantes de grande envergure." styleid="16" lengthseconds="167" time="2:47" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_266_Quirky_Orchestral/WOM266_trk002_SILLY_BOY_(A)_Jack_Wall_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), HEUREUX, ENJOUÉ, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, TENDRE, LÉGER, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, EXCENTRIQUE, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, INSECTE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, FORT EN ÉMOTIONS, FILMS, ANIMATION, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, COMÉDIE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE,, FORT EN EMOTIONS, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ESPIEGLE, DECALE, ENJOUE, LEGER, IRREGULIER, COMEDIE, ELEMENTS Enjoué, accrocheur et espiègle. Des sections rythmiques légères alternent avec des mélodies luxuriantes de grande envergure. wom 266 tk002 jack wall silly boy (a) wom 266 quirky orchestral west one music quirky film score orchestral trailer main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) happy lighthearted happy playful happy upbeat funny comedic funny eccentric funny mischievous funny quirky tender light movement irregular eccentric movement irregular insectile movement rhythmic stealthy upbeat catchy and playful. light rhythmical sections alternate with lush sweeping melodies. dramedy. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="26996" name="Lively and Fanciful (a)" code="WOM 350A tk005" libraryid="6" albumid="579" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_350A_British_Drama/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Michael Price, Laurence Greed" comment="Pizzicatos énergiques de cordes combinés avec des thèmes orchestraux fantasques." styleid="14" lengthseconds="99" time="1:39" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_350A_British_Drama/WOM_350A_trk005_LIVELY_AND_FANCIFUL_(A)_Michael_Price,_Laurence_Greed_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, FAMILIAL, FILMS, COMÉDIE ROMANTIQUE, COMEDIE, COMEDIE ROMANTIQUE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, ART, ANTIQUITÉS, ANTIQUITES, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, DRAME TV, DROLE, HUMORISTIQUE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, DECALE, DROLE, FANTASQUE, DROLE, IRONIQUE, HEUREUX, BONDISSANT, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, JOYEUX, HEUREUX, ENJOUÉ, ENJOUE, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, NEUTRE, TENDRE, INNOCENT, TENDRE, LÉGER, LEGER, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, PIZZICATO, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, BONDISSANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, OCCUPÉ, OCCUPE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, BOIS, SECTION DE BOIS, CUIVRES, COR, COR D'HARMONIE, CORDES, HARPE, CORDES, CORDES PIZZICATO, BOIS, BASSON, BOIS, CLARINETTE, BOIS, FLUTE, BOIS, HAUTBOIS, HAUTBOIS, COR ANGLAIS, DRAME, BRITANNIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL Pizzicatos énergiques de cordes combinés avec des thèmes orchestraux fantasques. wom 350a tk005 michael price laurence greed lively and fanciful (a) wom 350a british drama west one music drama film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral documentary main movies family movies romantic comedy tv radio leisure lifestyle arts antiques tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden tv radio reality tv tv radio tv drama funny humorous funny quirky energetic pizzicato strings combine with whimsical orchestral themes. dramedy. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="26538" name="Colourful Future (a)" code="WOM 335 tk005" libraryid="6" albumid="569" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_335_Inspiring_Minimalism/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="jono Buchanan" comment="Thème au piano léger, percutant et positif avec pizzicati de cordes, guitare acoustique et claquements de mains." styleid="4" lengthseconds="112" time="1:52" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_335_Inspiring_Minimalism/WOM_335_trk005_COLOURFUL_FUTURE_(A)_jono_Buchanan_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, COMMUNICATION, ACTUALITÉS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, HEUREUX, BONDISSANT, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, JOYEUX, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, FUN, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, GUILLERET, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, BONDISSANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, SAUTER, ACOUSTIQUE, ENFANTIN, PIZZICATO, ÉTINCELANT, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, ENFANTS, MATERNELLE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, AMBIANCES ET FONDS SONORES POUR PROJETS, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, MATERNELLE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, CLAVIER, CELESTE, CLAVIER, PIANO, JOUET, INHABITUEL, PERCUSSION CORPORELLE, PERCUSSION, MARIMBA, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN NYLON, ETINCELANT, ACTUALITES Thème au piano léger, percutant et positif avec pizzicati de cordes, guitare acoustique et claquements de mains. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 335 tk005 jono buchanan colourful future (a) wom 335 inspiring minimalism west one music film score orchestral business corporate bright optimistic strings string section main business corporate beds business corporate communication news film score orchestral documentary happy bouncy happy bright happy cheerful happy feel good happy fun happy happy happy perky happy playful light percussive and positive piano-led theme with pizzicato strings acoustic guitar and handclaps. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="6462" name="Perpetual Production" code="TSH 067 tk014" libraryid="5" albumid="151" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_067_Inspiring_Innovation/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Mark Peter Revell" comment="Rythmes entremelés, insistants, complexes, avec passages qui accélèrent." styleid="11" lengthseconds="141" time="2:21" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_067_Inspiring_Innovation/TSH067_trk014_PERPETUAL_PRODUCTION_Mark_Peter_Revell_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="14" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, COMMUNICATION, ACTUALITÉS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FORMATION, INFORMATION, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, OCCUPÉ, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, TAPIS ROULANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INDUSTRIE, MACHINES, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, PERCUSSIF, PINCÉ, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, AUTOMATISATION, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, AMBIANCES ET FONDS SONORES POUR PROJETS, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, ART, ANTIQUITÉS, CLAVIER, PIANO, FORMATIONS GENERALES, PINCE, OCCUPE, ACCELERE, ACTUALITES, ANTIQUITES Rythmes entremelés, insistants, complexes, avec passages qui accélèrent. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 067 tk014 mark peter revell perpetual production tsh 067 inspiring innovation the scoring house corporate business business corporate motivational general lineups acoustic strings string section main business corporate communication news business corporate motivational business corporate science technology business corporate training information uplifting inspirational uplifting insistent intricate cross rhythms and accelerating passages. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="23816" name="Less is More (a)" code="WOM 311 tk004" libraryid="6" albumid="516" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_311_Minimalist_Acoustica/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Andrew David Prosser / Mark David Allaway" comment="Techniques minimalistes classiques. Des motifs répétés de clarinette se développent avec des petites touches de flute." styleid="13" lengthseconds="138" time="2:18" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_311_Minimalist_Acoustica/WOM_311_trk004_LESS_IS_MORE_(A)_Andrew_David_Prosser_Mark_David_Allaway_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE, STYLE MINIMALISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, EXCENTRIQUE, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, INSECTE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, OCCUPÉ, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, AMBIANCES ET FONDS SONORES POUR PROJETS,, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DECALE, IRREGULIER, 20E SIECLE, OCCUPE, ELEMENTS Techniques minimalistes classiques. Des motifs répétés de clarinette se développent avec des petites touches de flute. wom 311 tk004 andrew david prosser mark david allaway less is more (a) wom 311 minimalist acoustica west one music acoustic children time period modern era 20th century main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) classical minimalist style business corporate beds happy playful funny comedic funny quirky movement irregular eccentric movement irregular insectile movement rhythmic busy business corporate classic minimalist techniques. repeating clarinet patterns build with touches of flute. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="25494" name="River Flow (b)" code="WOM 340 tk057" libraryid="6" albumid="545" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_340_Acoustic_Delights/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Alistair Bruce Henry Friend, Ted Brett Barnes" comment="Intime et organique, avec marimba et de chaleureuses guitares acoustiques." styleid="13" lengthseconds="196" time="3:16" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_340_Acoustic_Delights/WOM340_trk057_RIVER_FLOW_(B)_Alistair_Bruce_Henry_Friend,_Ted_Brett_Barnes_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="57" tracktotal="" search="POP, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ACOUSTIQUE, UNDERSCORE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, ENJOUÉ, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, NONCHALANT, PAISIBLE, LYRIQUE, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, AFFECTUEUX, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TENDRE, TENDRE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, ACOUSTIQUE, BEAU, RUSTIQUE, VACANCES, DE SAISON, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, BATTERIE, BATTERIE, INHABITUEL, PERCUSSION CORPORELLE, PERCUSSION, MARIMBA, CORDES, BASSE, BASSE ÉLECTRIQUE, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN NYLON, FORMATIONS GENERALES, ENJOUE, ELECTRIQUE, BASSE ELECTRIQUE, ELEMENTS Intime et organique, avec marimba et de chaleureuses guitares acoustiques. wom 340 tk057 alistair bruce henry friend ted brett barnes river flow (b) wom 340 acoustic delights west one music acoustic pop general lineups acoustic underscore happy feel good happy lighthearted peaceful contented peaceful dreamy peaceful leisurely peaceful lyrical tender intimate tender loving tender reflective tender sentimental tender tender tender warm movement smooth flowing intimate and organic featuring marimba and warm acoustic guitars. underscore" waveformpath="" version="Underscore" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="7402" name="Night Sprites (a)" code="TSH 059 tk022" libraryid="5" albumid="168" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_059_Orchestral_Fantasia/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Arthur Rhodes" comment="Allégresse fantastique." styleid="4" lengthseconds="186" time="3:06" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_059_Orchestral_Fantasia/TSH_059_trk022_NIGHT_SPRITES_(A)_Simon_Arthur_Rhodes_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="22" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, PRINCIPAL, CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, TROUBLANT, AGITÉ, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, EXCENTRIQUE, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, COMÉDIE, FILMS, FAMILIAL, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE,, PERIODE, AGITE, DECALE, IRREGULIER, COMEDIE, 20E SIECLE, ELEMENTS Allégresse fantastique. tsh 059 tk022 simon arthur rhodes night sprites (a) tsh 059 orchestral fantasia the scoring house film score orchestral children storytelling time period modern era 20th century main classical classical styling film score orchestral trailer funny comedic funny quirky disturbing restless movement irregular eccentric movies children storytelling movies comedy movies family movies fantastical playfulness. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="17588" name="Short Theme 12" code="WOM 174 tk024" libraryid="6" albumid="370" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_174_Age_of_Innocence/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Thomas Greenberg" comment="Un motif rapide qui détale. Un piano et des cordes pizzicati." styleid="10" lengthseconds="34" time="0:34" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_174_Age_of_Innocence/WOM174_trk024_SHORT_THEME_12_Thomas_Greenberg_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="24" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, ENFANTS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, COMMUNICATION, ACTUALITÉS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FILMS, ANIMATION, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, FAMILIAL, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, TENDRE, INNOCENT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COURANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UN TRAIN, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ACCOMPAGNEMENT AU PIANO, CORDES, CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, CORDES PIZZICATO, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ACTUALITES Un motif rapide qui détale. Un piano et des cordes pizzicati. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 174 tk024 thomas greenberg short theme 12 wom 174 age of innocence west one music documentary children storytelling children business corporate bright optimistic business corporate communication news film score orchestral trailer main business corporate movies animation movies children storytelling movies family tv radio leisure lifestyle travel happy feel good fast running motif. piano and pizzicato strings. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="29113" name="Human Behaviour" code="WOMG 021 tk007" libraryid="7" albumid="625" albumartpath="Music/West One Music Group/WOMG_021_This_Is_Oddball_Orchestral/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Bill Connor" comment="Décalé, fun et accrocheur. Un dialogue instrumental joyeux avec de légers rythmes de bossa nova." styleid="16" lengthseconds="132" time="2:12" samplefile="Music/West One Music Group/WOMG_021_This_Is_Oddball_Orchestral/WOMG_021_trk007_HUMAN_BEHAVIOUR_Bill_Connor_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, PRINCIPAL, ENFANTS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, INSENSÉ, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, FUN, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, ENJOUÉ, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, TENDRE, LÉGER, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, EXCENTRIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, POURSUITE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, PIZZICATO, DANSE DE SALON, BOSSA NOVA, FILMS, ANIMATION, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, COMÉDIE ROMANTIQUE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, CORDES, CORDES PIZZICATO, INSENSE, DECALE, ENJOUE, LEGER, IRREGULIER, COMEDIE, COMEDIE ROMANTIQUE, ELEGANT, ELEMENTS Décalé, fun et accrocheur. Un dialogue instrumental joyeux avec de légers rythmes de bossa nova. womg 021 tk007 bill connor human behaviour womg 021 this is oddball orchestral west one music group quirky children storytelling main children film score orchestral trailer funny comedic funny eccentric funny madcap funny quirky happy bright happy fun happy happy happy lighthearted happy playful tender light movement irregular eccentric movement rhythmic chase movement quirky catchy and fun. a bright and happy instrumental dialogue with light bossa nova rhythms. dramedy. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="0428434750"/>
    <item id="26169" name="It's a Life (a)" code="WOM 098 tk008" libraryid="6" albumid="560" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_098_Emotive_Orchestral/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Bill Connor" comment="Des marimbas vifs et minimalistes superposés, accompagnés par un saxophone après 1:00." styleid="4" lengthseconds="143" time="2:23" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_098_Emotive_Orchestral/WOM098_trk008_IT'S_A_LIFE_(A)_Bill_Connor_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="8" tracktotal="" search="CLASSIQUE, CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIÈCLE, CLASSIQUE, STYLE MINIMALISTE, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, PRINTEMPS, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), NON OCCIDENTAL, PERCUSSION, BOIS, SAXOPHONE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, PERIODE, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIECLE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), 20E SIECLE, ELEMENTS Des marimbas vifs et minimalistes superposés, accompagnés par un saxophone après 1:00. wom 098 tk008 bill connor it's a life (a) wom 098 emotive orchestral west one music film score orchestral classical classical 20th century classical style classical minimalist style main documentary science technology nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife nature wildlife the elements seasons time spring uplifting uplifting tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) non western sprightly minimalist layered marimbas accompanied by saxophone after 1:00. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="7882" name="The Joy of Living (a)" code="TSH 004 tk017" libraryid="5" albumid="173" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_004_Natural_Wonders/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon David Chamberlain" comment="Exaltant mouvement rythmique." styleid="26" lengthseconds="167" time="2:47" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_004_Natural_Wonders/TSH004_trk017_THE_JOY_OF_LIVING_(A)_Simon_David_Chamberlain_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="17" tracktotal="" search="WORLD BEAT, STYLES ETHNIQUES, GLOBAL, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), FORT, EXALTANT, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, POURSUITE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, SPORT, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE,, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), AERIEN, ELEMENTS Exaltant mouvement rythmique. tsh 004 tk017 simon david chamberlain the joy of living (a) tsh 004 natural wonders the scoring house nature wildlife world beat ethnic stylings global main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) strong exhilarating strong prestigious happy feel good movement rhythmic chase movement smooth aerial flying tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio sports sports nature wildlife the elements exhilarating rhythmic movement. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="7131" name="Dancing With Time (a)" code="TSH 029 tk013" libraryid="5" albumid="164" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_029_Symphonic_Fantasia/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Arthur Rhodes" comment="Un enchaînement gai et saugrenu." styleid="4" lengthseconds="150" time="2:30" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_029_Symphonic_Fantasia/TSH029_trk013_DANCING_WITH_TIME_(A)_Simon_Arthur_Rhodes_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="13" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, ANIMATION, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, FANTASQUE, TENDRE, LÉGER, PIZZICATO, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, EXCENTRIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, OCCUPÉ, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FRÉNÉSIE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CORDES, CORDES PIZZICATO, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), LEGER, IRREGULIER, OCCUPE, FRENESIE, ELEMENTS Un enchaînement gai et saugrenu. tsh 029 tk013 simon arthur rhodes dancing with time (a) tsh 029 symphonic fantasia the scoring house film score orchestral children storytelling film score orchestral trailer main documentary movies animation movies children storytelling movies fantasy adventure nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife funny comedic funny whimsical tender light pizzicato movement irregular eccentric light-hearted whimsical sequence. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="7879" name="A Curious Nature (a)" code="TSH 004 tk014" libraryid="5" albumid="173" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_004_Natural_Wonders/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon David Chamberlain" comment="Une joyeuse et étrange excentricité." styleid="26" lengthseconds="164" time="2:44" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_004_Natural_Wonders/TSH004_trk014_A_CURIOUS_NATURE_(A)_Simon_David_Chamberlain_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="14" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, COMÉDIE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, COMÉDIE ROMANTIQUE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, DROLE, IRONIQUE, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, INSECTE, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), DECALE, IRREGULIER, COMEDIE, COMEDIE ROMANTIQUE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS Une joyeuse et étrange excentricité. tsh 004 tk014 simon david chamberlain a curious nature (a) tsh 004 natural wonders the scoring house nature wildlife film score orchestral trailer main movies comedy movies crime detective mystery movies romantic comedy nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden funny comedic funny eccentric funny quirky funny wry happy playful quirky eccentricity. dramedy. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="23813" name="Natural Selection (a)" code="WOM 311 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="516" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_311_Minimalist_Acoustica/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Andrew David Prosser / Mark David Allaway" comment="Des entrelacs de motifs de guitare acoustique, avec une clarinette douce, se transforment en un groove irrésistible." styleid="13" lengthseconds="110" time="1:50" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_311_Minimalist_Acoustica/WOM_311_trk001_NATURAL_SELECTION_(A)_Andrew_David_Prosser_Mark_David_Allaway_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, ENJOUÉ, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, TENDRE, INNOCENT, ACOUSTIQUE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), ENJOUE Des entrelacs de motifs de guitare acoustique, avec une clarinette douce, se transforment en un groove irrésistible. wom 311 tk001 andrew david prosser mark david allaway natural selection (a) wom 311 minimalist acoustica west one music acoustic children business corporate beds main business corporate tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden happy feel good happy lighthearted happy playful tender innocent acoustic tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) intertwining acoustic guitar patterns with gentle clarinets develop to an infectious groove. main delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="6117" name="Multiplication" code="TSH 063 tk011" libraryid="5" albumid="145" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_063_Innovation_Communication/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Mark Peter Revell" comment="Progression complexe et industrielle." styleid="24" lengthseconds="137" time="2:17" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_063_Innovation_Communication/TSH063_trk011_MULTIPLICATION_Mark_Peter_Revell_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="11" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, COMMUNICATION, ACTUALITÉS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FORMATION, INFORMATION, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, TAPIS ROULANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INSISTANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UN TRAIN, PINCÉ, PIZZICATO, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, AMBIANCES ET FONDS SONORES POUR PROJETS, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, HI TECH, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, SANTÉ, BIEN-ÊTRE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, FORMATIONS GENERALES, PINCE, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, ACTUALITES, SANTE, BIEN-ETRE Progression complexe et industrielle. tsh 063 tk011 mark peter revell multiplication tsh 063 innovation communication the scoring house science new technology business corporate beds general lineups electronic and acoustic main business corporate bright optimistic business corporate communication news business corporate motivational business corporate training information film score orchestral documentary film score orchestral industrious intricate progression. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="7069" name="Twisted Nerve (a)" code="TSH 026A tk008" libraryid="5" albumid="162" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_026A_Dimensions/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Dave Hewson / Alexander Balanescu" comment="Un insidieux et sombre patchwork musical." styleid="4" lengthseconds="106" time="1:46" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_026A_Dimensions/TSH026A_trk008_TWISTED_NERVE_(A)_Dave_Hewson_Alexander_Balanescu_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="8" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, SOUND DESIGN, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, ÉTRANGE , TROUBLANT, SURNATUREL, TROUBLANT, BIZARRE, EFFRAYANT, HORREUR, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CORDES, VIOLON, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), INQUIETANT, ETRANGE, ELEMENTS Un insidieux et sombre patchwork musical. tsh 026a tk008 dave hewson alexander balanescu twisted nerve (a) tsh 026a dimensions the scoring house film score orchestral sound elements atmospheres sound design main movies horror thriller movies human drama nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife disturbing dark disturbing eerie disturbing strange disturbing supernatural disturbing weird scary horror tempo insidious dark collage. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="19445" name="Cold Sweat (a)" code="WOM 214 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="413" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_214_Tribal_Percussion_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Dan Graham" comment="Une progression éléphantesque." styleid="2" lengthseconds="62" time="1:02" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_214_Tribal_Percussion_Trailers/WOM214_trk001_COLD_SWEAT_(A)_Dan_Graham_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, ACTION, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, PUISSANT, EVOLUTIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, POURSUITE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FRÉNÉSIE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), FRENESIE, ELEMENTS, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Une progression éléphantesque. wom 214 tk001 dan graham cold sweat (a) wom 214 tribal percussion trailers west one music trailer film score orchestral trailer main movies action adventure movies action drama nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife trailers trailer track strong exciting strong powerful building movement rhythmic chase movement rhythmic frenzy tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) mammoth building cue. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="23649" name="Tribal Battles (b)" code="WOM 307 tk013" libraryid="6" albumid="512" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_307_Epic_World_/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Daniel Law Heath / Jane Antonia Cornish" comment="Une composition d'action rapide. Énormes percussions tribales et cordes dramatiques." styleid="2" lengthseconds="158" time="2:38" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_307_Epic_World_/WOM_307_trk013_TRIBAL_BATTLES_(B)_Daniel_Law_Heath_Jane_Antonia_Cornish_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="13" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, UNDERSCORE, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, SPORT, SPORTS EXTREMES, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, FORT, FORT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), BATTERIE, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), EPIQUE Une composition d'action rapide. Énormes percussions tribales et cordes dramatiques. wom 307 tk013 daniel law heath jane antonia cornish tribal battles (b) wom 307 epic world west one music trailer film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral trailer underscore movies action adventure movies epic movies fantasy adventure sports extreme sports trailers trailer track strong strong movement rhythmic driving movement rhythmic rugged tempo fast-paced action cue. huge tribal percussion and dramatic strings. underscore" waveformpath="" version="Underscore" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="7041" name="Epic Battle (b)" code="TSH 024 tk037" libraryid="5" albumid="161" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_024_Conflict/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Everard Lawrence Wells / Robert John Foster" comment="Une tension profonde et menaçante." styleid="4" lengthseconds="71" time="1:11" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_024_Conflict/TSH024_trk037_EPIC_BATTLE_(B)_Richard_Everard_Lawrence_Wells_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="37" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, UNDERSCORE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, GUERRE, MILITAIRE, HISTORIQUE, ANCIEN, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, GUERRE, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, FORT, HÉROIQUE, FORT, IMPLACABLE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PÉRIODE, CIVILISATIONS ANCIENNES, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), EPIQUE, HEROIQUE Une tension profonde et menaçante. tsh 024 tk037 richard everard lawrence wells robert john foster epic battle (b) tsh 024 conflict the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer underscore activities settings war military historical ancient movies action drama movies epic movies war trailers trailer track strong heroic strong relentless tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) time period ancient civilizations deep ominous tension. underscore" waveformpath="" version="Underscore" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="26588" name="Imminent Force (a)" code="WOM 338 tk005" libraryid="6" albumid="570" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_338_Life_In_Conflict/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Wayne Roberts" comment="Ambiance tendue, de mauvaise augure dans cette ouverture faite de textures de cordes et piano. Progression avec des cordes puissantes." styleid="4" lengthseconds="129" time="2:09" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_338_Life_In_Conflict/WOM_338_trk005_IMMINENT_FORCE_(A)_Wayne_Roberts_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, PRINCIPAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, TROUBLANT, ANXIEUX, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, CRAINTIF, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, TROUBLÉ, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, SÉRIEUX, INQUIET, SÉRIEUX, ÉMOUVANT, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, FORT, PUISSANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INSISTANT, EVOLUTIF, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, GUERRE, MILITAIRE, GUERRE GÉNÉRALE, SCÈNES DE COMBAT, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, FILMS, GUERRE, BATTERIE, TIMBALES, CLAVIER, PIANO, SERIEUX, TROUBLE, EMOUVANT, EPIQUE, GUERRE GENERALE, SCENES DE COMBAT, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Ambiance tendue, de mauvaise augure dans cette ouverture faite de textures de cordes et piano. Progression avec des cordes puissantes. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 338 tk005 wayne roberts imminent force (a) wom 338 life in conflict west one music film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer strings string section main film score orchestral documentary film score orchestral panoramic disturbing anxious disturbing dark disturbing fearful disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense dramatic agitated dramatic intense serious concerned tense ominous opening piano and string texture developing into powerful driving strings. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="7497" name="Bid For Freedom (a)" code="TSH 074 tk015" libraryid="5" albumid="169" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_074_Symphonic_Sketchbook/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Arthur Rhodes" comment="Mouvement dramatique plein d'urgence, se développant jusqu'au climax." styleid="4" lengthseconds="175" time="2:55" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_074_Symphonic_Sketchbook/TSH_074_trk015_BID_FOR_FREEDOM_(A)_Simon_Arthur_Rhodes_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="15" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, TRAILER, CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, NAVIGATION, PIRATES, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, EPIQUE, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, PERIODE, PERIODES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, ELEMENTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, TEMPETES, TONNERRE, VENT, OURAGANS, ELEMENTS, METEO, FORT, AVENTUREUX, FORT, COURAGEUX, FORT, ÉPIQUE, EPIQUE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, EXALTANT, FORT, HÉROIQUE, HEROIQUE, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, IMPLACABLE, FORT, FORT, EVOLUTIF, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION, DE CAPE ET D'ÉPÉE, DE CAPE ET D'EPEE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL Mouvement dramatique plein d'urgence, se développant jusqu'au climax. tsh 074 tk015 simon arthur rhodes bid for freedom (a) tsh 074 symphonic sketchbook the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer classical classical styling film score orchestral panoramic main activities settings seafaring pirates movies action drama movies epic movies period historical costume drama nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature urgent dramatic movement building to climax. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="24399" name="All Seeing Eye (a)" code="WOM 322 tk003" libraryid="6" albumid="526" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_322_Cinematic_Drama/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Martin Tillmann" comment="Tension pulsante pour surveillance, enquete et cinematica sombre." styleid="14" lengthseconds="180" time="3:00" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_322_Cinematic_Drama/WOM322_trk003_ALL_SEEING_EYE_(A)_Martin_Tillmann_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, MODERNE, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, TROUBLANT, ANXIEUX, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, EFFRAYANT, MENAÇANT, SÉRIEUX, INQUIET, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, FORMATIONS GENERALES, SERIEUX, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, INQUIETANT, MENACANT, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE Tension pulsante pour surveillance, enquete et cinematica sombre. wom 322 tk003 martin tillmann all seeing eye (a) wom 322 cinematic drama west one music drama film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral documentary main movies crime detective mystery movies espionage spy movies human drama movies modern tv radio tv drama disturbing anxious disturbing dark disturbing eerie disturbing mysterious disturbing suspenseful pulsing tension for surveillance investigation and dark cinematica. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="7005" name="The Invaders" code="TSH 024 tk001" libraryid="5" albumid="161" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_024_Conflict/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Everard Lawrence Wells / Robert John Foster" comment="Une avancée puissante et résolue." styleid="4" lengthseconds="135" time="2:15" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_024_Conflict/TSH024_trk001_THE_INVADERS_Richard_Everard_Lawrence_Wells_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, GUERRE, MILITAIRE, HISTORIQUE, ANCIEN, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, FILMS, GUERRE, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, PUISSANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PÉRIODE, CIVILISATIONS ANCIENNES, ROME ANTIQUE (500 AV. J-C - 476 AP. J-C), PERIODE, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETERMINE, EPIQUE, PERIODES Une avancée puissante et résolue. tsh 024 tk001 richard everard lawrence wells robert john foster the invaders tsh 024 conflict the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer main activities settings war military historical ancient movies epic movies period historical costume drama movies war trailers trailer track scary ominous serious determined strong determined strong powerful tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) powerful determined advance. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="670" name="Poison Arrows (b)" code="FEM 009 tk016" libraryid="2" albumid="21" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_009_Immortality/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Ryan Amon" comment="Des cordes rythmiques dark ouvrent cet explosif thème pour bande-annonce qui évolue de façon spectaculaire à mesure que l'on se rapproche de la fin." styleid="2" lengthseconds="116" time="1:56" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_009_Immortality/FEM009_trk016_POISON_ARROWS_(B)_Ryan_Amon_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="16" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, MARCHES, ORCHESTRE MILITAIRE, ALTERNATIF, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, BACK END, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, GUERRE, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, AGRESSIF, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, PATRIOTIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, DÉFILÉ, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, CHEVAUCHER, ÉQUESTRE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, MARCHE, PÉRIODE, CIVILISATIONS ANCIENNES, ROME ANTIQUE (500 AV. J-C - 476 AP. J-C), PÉRIODE, ÈRES CULTURELLES, GUERRE DE SÉCESSION (1861 - 1865), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, PERIODE, SERIEUX, ERES CULTURELLES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETERMINE, EPIQUE, GUERRE DE SECESSION (1861 - 1865), 20E SIECLE, DEFILE, EQUESTRE, GUERRE DE SECESSION Des cordes rythmiques dark ouvrent cet explosif thème pour bande-annonce qui évolue de façon spectaculaire à mesure que l'on se rapproche de la fin. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede fem 009 tk016 ryan amon poison arrows (b) fem 009 immortality fired earth music trailer film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic marches military band alternate movies action adventure movies back end movies epic movies war trailers trailer track disturbing dark disturbing tense dramatic aggressive scary ominous serious determined dark rhythmical strings open this explosive thematic trailer cue that builds to huge back end. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
    <item id="28017" name="Rugged Landscapes (a)" code="WOM 241A tk004" libraryid="6" albumid="598" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_241A_Natural_World_Landscapes/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Matt Norman (PRS)" comment="Intrépide et dramatique, avec des motifs de cordes stridents, des percussions puissantes et des mélodies de cuivres vibrantes." styleid="26" lengthseconds="133" time="2:13" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_241A_Natural_World_Landscapes/WOM_241A_trk004_RUGGED_LANDSCAPES_(A)_Matt_Norman_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, TRAILERS, TV, RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, TENDU, FORT, PUISSANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), TELE REALITE, ELEMENTS Intrépide et dramatique, avec des motifs de cordes stridents, des percussions puissantes et des mélodies de cuivres vibrantes. wom 241a tk004 matt norman (prs) rugged landscapes (a) wom 241a natural world: landscapes west one music nature wildlife volcanos nature wildlife planet earth natural world landscape exploration countryside deserts geology bold and dramatic featuring strident string motifs powerful percussion and stirring brass melodies. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="7891" name="Hunters and Hunted (a)" code="TSH 004 tk026" libraryid="5" albumid="173" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_004_Natural_Wonders/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon David Chamberlain" comment="Un mouvement comme une poursuite menant à une fin paroxysmique et une sombre conclusion." styleid="26" lengthseconds="160" time="2:40" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_004_Natural_Wonders/TSH004_trk026_HUNTERS_AND_HUNTED_(A)_Simon_David_Chamberlain_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="26" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, DRAMATIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, POURSUITE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FRÉNÉSIE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COURANT, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, COMÉDIE, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE,, COMEDIE, FRENESIE, ELEMENTS Un mouvement comme une poursuite menant à une fin paroxysmique et une sombre conclusion. tsh 004 tk026 simon david chamberlain hunters and hunted (a) tsh 004 natural wonders the scoring house nature wildlife children storytelling main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) film score orchestral trailer dramatic movement rhythmic chase movement rhythmic frenzy movement rhythmic running movies action drama movies children storytelling movies comedy movies fantasy adventure nature chase like movement leading to a climactic end and sombre conclusion. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="7400" name="Situation Critical (a)" code="TSH 059 tk020" libraryid="5" albumid="168" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_059_Orchestral_Fantasia/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Arthur Rhodes" comment="Allusions dramatiques, soutenues." styleid="4" lengthseconds="68" time="1:08" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_059_Orchestral_Fantasia/TSH_059_trk020_SITUATION_CRITICAL_(A)_Simon_Arthur_Rhodes_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="20" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, TROUBLANT, AGITÉ, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, POURSUITE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE,, SERIEUX, AGITE, DETERMINE, ACCELERE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE Allusions dramatiques, soutenues. tsh 059 tk020 simon arthur rhodes situation critical (a) tsh 059 orchestral fantasia the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer main serious determined disturbing restless disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense movement rhythmic chase movement rhythmic clock like movement rhythmic speeded up time lapse movies action adventure movies action drama movies crime sustained dramatic undercurrents. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="25788" name="Natural Havoc (a)" code="WOM 347 tk013" libraryid="6" albumid="552" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_347_Environment/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Matt Norman" comment="Catastrophes naturelles: l'oeil du cyclone. Bois et cordes nerveuses préparent un final spectaculaire avec cuivres et percussions fracassantes." styleid="24" lengthseconds="144" time="2:24" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_347_Environment/WOM_347_trk013_NATURAL_HAVOC_(A)_Matt_Norman_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="13" tracktotal="" search="DOCUMENTAIRE, ORCHESTRAL HYBRIDE , BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, ORCHESTRAL HYBRIDE , BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, GUERRE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, TEMPETES, TONNERRE, VENT, OURAGANS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, FOUGUEUX, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, EFFRAYANT, FAIRE PEUR, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, EFFRAYANT, TERRIFIANT, EVOLUTIF, CUIVRES, SECTION DE CUIVRES, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, BOIS, SECTION DE BOIS, BATTERIE, GROSSE CAISSE, BATTERIE, TOMS, PERCUSSION, CYMBALES, ELEMENTS, METEO, ETE, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Catastrophes naturelles: l'oeil du cyclone. Bois et cordes nerveuses préparent un final spectaculaire avec cuivres et percussions fracassantes. wom 347 tk013 matt norman natural havoc (a) wom 347 environment west one music science new technology film score orchestral documentary film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral orchestral hybrid film score orchestral panoramic main movies action drama movies war nature wildlife the elements weather storms thunder wind hurricanes disturbing tense dramatic fiery natural disasters: eye of the storm. tense strings and woodwind build into a dramatic finale with crashing percussion and brass. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="22353" name="Black Waves" code="WOM 277 tk046" libraryid="6" albumid="479" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_277_Reconstruction_-_Textures/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Des pulsations sinistres et inquiétantes de cordes graves avec des touches de cuivres menaçantes." styleid="12" lengthseconds="87" time="1:27" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_277_Reconstruction_-_Textures/WOM277_trk046_BLACK_WAVES_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="46" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), SÉRIEUX, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, EFFRAYANT, MENAÇANT, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE,, PERIODE, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), MENACANT, PERIODES, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS Des pulsations sinistres et inquiétantes de cordes graves avec des touches de cuivres menaçantes. wom 277 tk046 david ashton black waves wom 277 reconstruction - textures west one music atmospheres film score orchestral trailer main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) serious disturbing mysterious disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense scary menacing scary ominous movies action adventure movies crime detective mystery movies human drama movies period historical brooding ominous low string pulses with touches of menacing brass. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="26584" name="Approaching Danger (a)" code="WOM 338 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="570" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_338_Life_In_Conflict/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Wayne Roberts" comment="Bed de cordes à broyer du noir. Effet d'horlogerie de bien mauvais augure. Piano lead clairsemé." styleid="4" lengthseconds="167" time="2:47" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_338_Life_In_Conflict/WOM_338_trk001_APPROACHING_DANGER_(A)_Wayne_Roberts_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, PRINCIPAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, DRONES, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, SOUND DESIGN, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, CRAINTIF, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, SÉRIEUX, INQUIET, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, FORT, PUISSANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, PULSATION, NERVEUX, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, FILMS, GUERRE, CLAVIER, PIANO, ELEMENTS SONORES, SERIEUX, ATMOSPHERES, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS Bed de cordes à broyer du noir. Effet d'horlogerie de bien mauvais augure. Piano lead clairsemé. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 338 tk001 wayne roberts approaching danger (a) wom 338 life in conflict west one music film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer strings string section main film score orchestral documentary sound elements atmospheres sound elements atmospheres drones sound elements atmospheres sound design disturbing dark disturbing fearful disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense serious dark brooding string bed with ominous ticking effect and sparse piano lead. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="28019" name="Volcanic Lands (a)" code="WOM 241A tk006" libraryid="6" albumid="598" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_241A_Natural_World_Landscapes/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Matt Norman (PRS)" comment="Sombre et primitif. Une section de sortie colossale commence à 1:14." styleid="26" lengthseconds="149" time="2:29" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_241A_Natural_World_Landscapes/WOM_241A_trk006_VOLCANIC_LANDS_(A)_Matt_Norman_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="6" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, GUERRE, MILITAIRE, HISTORIQUE, FILMS, GUERRE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, NEIGE, GLACE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, FROID, STÉRILE, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, DRAMATIQUE, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), STERILE, ELEMENTS, METEO, ETE Sombre et primitif. Une section de sortie colossale commence à 1:14. wom 241a tk006 matt norman (prs) volcanic lands (a) wom 241a natural world: landscapes west one music nature wildlife volcanos nature wildlife planet earth natural world landscape exploration countryside deserts geology dark and primal. huge outro section begins at 1:14. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="7392" name="The Bringer of Fire (a)" code="TSH 059 tk012" libraryid="5" albumid="168" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_059_Orchestral_Fantasia/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Arthur Rhodes" comment="Action dramatique et ponctuée" styleid="4" lengthseconds="86" time="1:26" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_059_Orchestral_Fantasia/TSH_059_trk012_THE_BRINGER_OF_FIRE_(A)_Simon_Arthur_Rhodes_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE, CLASSIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, FILMS, GUERRE, TITRE POUR TRAILER, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, FORT, CONFIANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, PESANT, LOURD, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, PERIODE, SERIEUX, DETERMINE, EPIQUE, 20E SIECLE Action dramatique et ponctuée tsh 059 tk012 simon arthur rhodes the bringer of fire (a) tsh 059 orchestral fantasia the scoring house film score orchestral classical classical styling classical film score orchestral trailer main movies action adventure movies action drama movies epic movies fantasy adventure movies war trailer track serious determined serious serious strong confident movement rhythmic ponderous heavy punctuated dramatic action. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="465" name="Precession (b)" code="FEM 007 tk012" libraryid="2" albumid="14" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_007_Ultimatum/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jesper Kyd" comment="Une bande-annonce épique. Des cordes dark plantent le décor d'un morceau percussif avec des crescendos de cuivres." styleid="2" lengthseconds="112" time="1:52" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_007_Ultimatum/FEM007_trk012_PRECESSION_(B)_Jesper_Kyd_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, ALTERNATIF, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, BACK END, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, AGRESSIF, DRAMATIQUE, DANGEUREUX, DRAMATIQUE, VIOLENT, EFFRAYANT, MENAÇANT, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, ÉPIQUE, EVOLUTIF, PERCUSSIF, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PÉRIODE, CIVILISATIONS ANCIENNES, ROME ANTIQUE (500 AV. J-C - 476 AP. J-C), PERIODE, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), MENACANT, DETERMINE, EPIQUE, PERIODES, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Une bande-annonce épique. Des cordes dark plantent le décor d'un morceau percussif avec des crescendos de cuivres. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede fem 007 tk012 jesper kyd precession (b) fem 007 ultimatum fired earth music trailer film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic alternate movies action adventure movies back end movies epic movies period historical costume drama trailers trailer track disturbing dark disturbing tense dramatic aggressive dramatic dangerous dramatic epic trailer cue. dark strings set up for giant percussive cue with brass swells. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
    <item id="7127" name="Take to the Sky (a)" code="TSH 029 tk009" libraryid="5" albumid="164" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_029_Symphonic_Fantasia/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Arthur Rhodes" comment="Une ouverture lyrique et atmosphérique vers une conclusion panoramique et une reprise." styleid="4" lengthseconds="148" time="2:28" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_029_Symphonic_Fantasia/TSH029_trk009_TAKE_TO_THE_SKY_(A)_Simon_Arthur_Rhodes_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, FILMS, SCIENCE FICTION, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, PAISIBLE, LYRIQUE, FORT, MAJESTUEUX, MÉLODIQUE, LYRIQUE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, RALENTI, TEMPO, 66 - 76 À L'AISE (ADAGIO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 90, PERIODE, MELODIQUE, 66 - 76 A L'AISE (ADAGIO), EPIQUE, 20E SIECLE, AERIEN, ELEGANT, ANNEES 90, ELEMENTS Une ouverture lyrique et atmosphérique vers une conclusion panoramique et une reprise. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz tsh 029 tk009 simon arthur rhodes take to the sky (a) tsh 029 symphonic fantasia the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic main movies epic movies fantasy adventure movies science fiction nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife the elements sky aerial clouds peaceful lyrical strong majestic melodic lyrical atmospheric opening to majestic panoramic conclusion and reprise. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="28016" name="Majestic Peaks (a)" code="WOM 241A tk003" libraryid="6" albumid="598" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_241A_Natural_World_Landscapes/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Matt Norman (PRS)" comment="Une intoduction grondante et profonde bascule dans un thème complet à 0:47." styleid="26" lengthseconds="116" time="1:56" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_241A_Natural_World_Landscapes/WOM_241A_trk003_MAJESTIC_PEAKS_(A)_Matt_Norman_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, GUERRE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, PATRIOTIQUE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, PÉRIODE, ÈRES CULTURELLES, GUERRE DE SÉCESSION (1861 - 1865), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 40, PERIODE, SERIEUX, ERES CULTURELLES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETERMINE, EPIQUE, GUERRE DE SECESSION (1861 - 1865), 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 40, ELEMENTS, GUERRE DE SECESSION Une intoduction grondante et profonde bascule dans un thème complet à 0:47. wom 241a tk003 matt norman (prs) majestic peaks (a) wom 241a natural world: landscapes west one music nature wildlife volcanos nature wildlife planet earth natural world landscape exploration countryside deserts geology deep rumbling introduction breaks to full theme at 0:47. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="4613" name="Each New Day (a)" code="TSH 035 tk009" libraryid="5" albumid="125" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_035_A_Winner_is_Born/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Mark Lasker" comment="Un morceau chaleureux et plein d'attentes évoluant graduellement." styleid="22" lengthseconds="138" time="2:18" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_035_A_Winner_is_Born/TSH035_trk009_EACH_NEW_DAY_(A)_Mark_Lasker_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EVOLUTIF, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, RALENTI, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, REVELER, ELEMENTS, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Un morceau chaleureux et plein d'attentes évoluant graduellement. tsh 035 tk009 mark lasker each new day (a) tsh 035 a winner is born the scoring house sport business corporate reveal launch business corporate luxury film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic main business corporate movies human drama movies romance nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama tv radio sports sad depressing warm and expectant gradually evolving. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="26639" name="Echoes" code="WOM 012 tk012" libraryid="6" albumid="572" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_012_Clarity/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Daryl Neil Alexander Griffith" comment="Un morceau optimiste et fort." styleid="4" lengthseconds="155" time="2:35" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_012_Clarity/WOM012_trk012_ECHOES_Daryl_Neil_Alexander_Griffith_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="CLASSIQUE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIÈCLE, CLASSIQUE, STYLE MINIMALISTE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, FORT, PUISSANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, FILMS, FAMILIAL, FILMS, IDYLLE,, PERIODE, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIECLE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), 20E SIECLE, ACCELERE Un morceau optimiste et fort. wom 012 tk012 daryl neil alexander griffith echoes wom 012 clarity west one music film score orchestral classical time period modern era 20th century main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) classical 20th century classical style classical minimalist style film score orchestral trailer strong powerful uplifting optimistic movement rhythmic speeded up time lapse movies family movies optimistic and powerful piece. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="28018" name="Panoramic Valley (a)" code="WOM 241A tk005" libraryid="6" albumid="598" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_241A_Natural_World_Landscapes/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Matt Norman (PRS)" comment="Des cordes luxueuses avec des mélodies de cor et de bois de grande envergure." styleid="26" lengthseconds="119" time="1:59" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_241A_Natural_World_Landscapes/WOM_241A_trk005_PANORAMIC_VALLEY_(A)_Matt_Norman_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PRINCIPAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, NEIGE, GLACE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MER, PAYSAGE MARIN, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, SEREIN, FORT EN ÉMOTIONS, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, FORT EN EMOTIONS, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ELEMENTS Des cordes luxueuses avec des mélodies de cor et de bois de grande envergure. wom 241a tk005 matt norman (prs) panoramic valley (a) wom 241a natural world: landscapes west one music nature wildlife volcanos nature wildlife planet earth natural world landscape exploration countryside deserts geology lush strings with sweeping horn and woodwind melodies. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="15298" name="Legacy (a)" code="WOM 124 tk004" libraryid="6" albumid="318" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_124_Life_in_Motion/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Paul Reeves (Gb 2)" comment="Une figure tranquille et répétitive, progressant graduellement vers un thème de violon." styleid="26" lengthseconds="201" time="3:21" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_124_Life_in_Motion/WOM124_trk004_LEGACY_(A)_Paul_Reeves_(Gb_2)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="CLASSIQUE, CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE, CLASSIQUE, STYLE MINIMALISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, PRESTIGE , BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FORMATION, INFORMATION, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, PAISIBLE, TRANQUILLE, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EVOLUTIF, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), 20E SIECLE, AERIEN, ELEGANT, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Une figure tranquille et répétitive, progressant graduellement vers un thème de violon. wom 124 tk004 paul reeves (gb 2) legacy (a) wom 124 life in motion west one music nature wildlife classical classical classical styling classical minimalist style business corporate beds business corporate prestige business corporate training information main business corporate peaceful tranquil strong prestigious tender romantic uplifting motivational uplifting tranquil repeating figure gradually building into a violin theme. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="7487" name="Endless Sky (a)" code="TSH 074 tk005" libraryid="5" albumid="169" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_074_Symphonic_Sketchbook/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Arthur Rhodes" comment="Thème panoramique sincère jusqu'à développement et reprise." styleid="4" lengthseconds="217" time="3:37" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_074_Symphonic_Sketchbook/TSH_074_trk005_ENDLESS_SKY_(A)_Simon_Arthur_Rhodes_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, TRAILER, CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, FAMILIAL, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, PERIODE, PERIODES, FILMS, IDYLLE, FILMS, WESTERN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, ELEMENTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, ELEMENTS, PAISIBLE, LYRIQUE, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, SÉRIEUX, ÉMOUVANT, SERIEUX, EMOUVANT, SÉRIEUX, ATTENTIONNÉ, SERIEUX, ATTENTIONNE, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EVOLUTIF, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION, MÉLODIQUE, LYRIQUE, MELODIQUE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT, ELEGANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, AMERIQUE DU NORD, ETATS-UNIS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL Thème panoramique sincère jusqu'à développement et reprise. tsh 074 tk005 simon arthur rhodes endless sky (a) tsh 074 symphonic sketchbook the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer classical classical styling film score orchestral panoramic film score orchestral pastoral main movies family movies period historical costume drama movies romance movies western nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature heartfelt panoramic theme to build and reprise. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="1424" name="Freefall (b)" code="FEM 017 tk011" libraryid="2" albumid="36" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_017_Jesper_Kyd_Legacy/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jesper Kyd" comment="Grand et émouvant morceau orchestral. Avec des percussions, un thème de cordes enveloppant et enorme. Intro jusqu'à 0:35, puis partie centrale à 1:15, jusqu'à une reprise des cordes à 2:05." styleid="2" lengthseconds="154" time="2:34" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_017_Jesper_Kyd_Legacy/FEM_017_trk011_FREEFALL_(B)_Jesper_Kyd_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="11" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, ALTERNATIF, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, TRAILERS, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, DRAMATIQUE, PASSIONNÉ, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, SÉRIEUX, DIGNE, SÉRIEUX, ÉMOUVANT, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, COURAGEUX, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, ÉPIQUE, FORT, HÉROIQUE, FORT, MAJESTUEUX, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, FORT, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE DE CHAMBRE, PETIT ORCHESTRE, SERIEUX, PASSIONNE, DETERMINE, EMOUVANT, EPIQUE, HEROIQUE, ELEMENTS Grand et émouvant morceau orchestral. Avec des percussions, un thème de cordes enveloppant et enorme. Intro jusqu'à 0:35, puis partie centrale à 1:15, jusqu'à une reprise des cordes à 2:05. fem 017 tk011 jesper kyd freefall (b) fem 017 jesper kyd's legacy fired earth music trailer film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic alternate movies action adventure movies action drama movies epic nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama trailers dramatic intense dramatic passionate serious determined serious dignified serious huge emotive orchestral epic featuring percussion and massive sweeping string theme. intro to 0:35 building mid-section to 1:15 then driving through to 2:05 with string reprise. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without vocal" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
    <item id="7384" name="Big Blue Sky (a)" code="TSH 059 tk004" libraryid="5" albumid="168" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_059_Orchestral_Fantasia/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Arthur Rhodes" comment="Panoramas chauds et dérivants." styleid="4" lengthseconds="266" time="4:26" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_059_Orchestral_Fantasia/TSH_059_trk004_BIG_BLUE_SKY_(A)_Simon_Arthur_Rhodes_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, PRINCIPAL, CLASSIQUE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN NYLON, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN MÉTAL,, PERIODE, 20E SIECLE, AERIEN, ELEGANT, ELEMENTS, CORDES EN METAL Panoramas chauds et dérivants. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 059 tk004 simon arthur rhodes big blue sky (a) tsh 059 orchestral fantasia the scoring house film score orchestral classical classical styling classical and semi classical symphony orchestra time period modern era 20th century main classical business corporate luxury film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic tender intimate tender nostalgic tender romantic tender warm warm drifting panoramas. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="26635" name="Beyond the Stratosphere (a)" code="WOM 257 tk002" libraryid="6" albumid="571" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_257_Cinematic_Soundscapes/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Daniel Law Heath / James Brian Brasher" comment="Des cordes planantes et somptueuses, des flûtes etniques rêveuses, et des motifs de piano magnifiques et évocateurs." styleid="4" lengthseconds="167" time="2:47" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_257_Cinematic_Soundscapes/WOM257_trk002_BEYOND_THE_STRATOSPHERE_(A)_Daniel_Law_Heath_James_Brian_Brasher_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, JAILLIR, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, SÉRIEUX, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, DOCUMENTAIRE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, MÉDICAL, SCIENCES DE LA VIE,, SERIEUX, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, MEDICAL Des cordes planantes et somptueuses, des flûtes etniques rêveuses, et des motifs de piano magnifiques et évocateurs. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 257 tk002 daniel law heath james brian brasher beyond the stratosphere (a) wom 257 cinematic soundscapes west one music film score orchestral business corporate science technology main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) uplifting soaring peaceful dreamy peaceful peaceful tender reflective serious movement smooth aerial flying business corporate documentary nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife nature soaring sumptuous strings dreamy ethnic flutes and gorgeous evocative piano patterns. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="6968" name="Valleys and Hills (a)" code="TSH 011 tk001" libraryid="5" albumid="160" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_011_Orchestral_Elements/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Bill Connor" comment="Une pastorale descriptive et lyrique." styleid="4" lengthseconds="210" time="3:30" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_011_Orchestral_Elements/TSH011_trk001_VALLEYS_AND_HILLS_(A)_Bill_Connor_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, DROLE, MÉLODRAMATIQUE, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, LYRIQUE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, PATRIOTIQUE, MÉLODIQUE, LYRIQUE, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, ANGLETERRE, PÉRIODE, ÈRES CULTURELLES, PERIODES DE LA MUSIQUE CLASSIQUE, PERIODE CLASSIQUE (1750 - 1830), STYLE VINTAGE, PERIODE, MELODIQUE, ERES CULTURELLES, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), MELODRAMATIQUE, DEPRIMANT, PERIODES, ELEMENTS Une pastorale descriptive et lyrique. tsh 011 tk001 bill connor valleys and hills (a) tsh 011 orchestral elements the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer classical classical styling film score orchestral pastoral main documentary biographical historical the arts movies period historical costume drama movies romance nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife lyrical descriptive pastorale. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="6479" name="Reach for the Skies" code="TSH 067 tk031" libraryid="5" albumid="151" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_067_Inspiring_Innovation/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Everard Lawrence Wells / Robert John Foster" comment="Imagerie ambitieuse et évolutive." styleid="11" lengthseconds="181" time="3:01" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_067_Inspiring_Innovation/TSH067_trk031_REACH_FOR_THE_SKIES_Richard_Everard_Lawrence_Wells_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="31" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, PRESTIGE , FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, PRINCIPAL, CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIÈCLE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, FORT, PUISSANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, JAILLIR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MÉLODIQUE, LYRIQUE, SOPHISTIQUÉ, CLASSE, ÉTINCELANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, CLAVIER, PIANO, FORMATIONS GENERALES, SERIEUX, MELODIQUE, SOPHISTIQUE, ETINCELANT, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIECLE, 20E SIECLE, AERIEN, ELEGANT Imagerie ambitieuse et évolutive. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 067 tk031 richard everard lawrence wells robert john foster reach for the skies tsh 067 inspiring innovation the scoring house corporate business business corporate prestige general lineups acoustic strings string section main classical 20th century classical style business corporate luxury serious serious strong powerful uplifting inspirational uplifting soaring uplifting uplifting movement smooth aerial flying aspirational evolving imagery. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="6907" name="The High Plains (a)" code="TSH 001 tk004" libraryid="5" albumid="158" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_001_Cinematic_Adventures/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Des figures méditatives au piano et des cordes luxueuses, menant à un développement épique et panoramique et une reprise profonde." styleid="4" lengthseconds="253" time="4:13" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_001_Cinematic_Adventures/TSH001_trk004_THE_HIGH_PLAINS_(A)_Richard_Allen_Harvey_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, SÉRIEUX, ATTENTIONNÉ, FORT, ÉPIQUE, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, PATRIOTIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EVOLUTIF, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, PÉRIODE, PRÉ-20E SIÈCLE, 19E SIÈCLE, AMERIQUE DU NORD, PERIODE, SERIEUX, ETATS-UNIS, PRE-20E SIECLE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, ATTENTIONNE, EPIQUE, 20E SIECLE, 19E SIECLE, ELEMENTS, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Des figures méditatives au piano et des cordes luxueuses, menant à un développement épique et panoramique et une reprise profonde. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 001 tk004 richard allen harvey the high plains (a) tsh 001 cinematic adventures the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic main documentary biographical historical the arts movies human drama movies romance nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama trailers trailer track sad depressing poignant sad depressing sad pensive piano figures to expansive strings building to epic panoramic development and thoughtful reprise. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="469" name="Absolute Magnitude (b)" code="FEM 007 tk016" libraryid="2" albumid="14" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_007_Ultimatum/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jesper Kyd" comment="Une bande-annonce orchestrale épique et envoûtante. Une ouverture émouvante conduit à un thème vaillant avec des percussions massives." styleid="2" lengthseconds="132" time="2:12" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_007_Ultimatum/FEM007_trk016_ABSOLUTE_MAGNITUDE_(B)_Jesper_Kyd_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="16" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, ALTERNATIF, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, DRAMATIQUE, PASSIONNÉ, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, ÉPIQUE, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EVOLUTIF, FORT EN ÉMOTIONS, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), PÉRIODE, CIVILISATIONS ANCIENNES, ROME ANTIQUE (500 AV. J-C - 476 AP. J-C), PERIODE, FORT EN EMOTIONS, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), PASSIONNE, DEPRIMANT, EPIQUE, PERIODES, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Une bande-annonce orchestrale épique et envoûtante. Une ouverture émouvante conduit à un thème vaillant avec des percussions massives. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede fem 007 tk016 jesper kyd absolute magnitude (b) fem 007 ultimatum fired earth music trailer film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic alternate movies action adventure movies epic movies period historical costume drama nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama trailers trailer track disturbing tense dramatic intense dramatic sweeping epic orchestral trailer cue. emotive opening leads into valiant theme with huge percussion. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
    <item id="17151" name="Summer Sunrise (b)" code="WOM 165 tk016" libraryid="6" albumid="360" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_165_The_Pastoral_Album/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Patrick Thomas Hawes" comment="Une ouverture optimiste et calme progresse vers des phrases expansives de cordes." styleid="26" lengthseconds="145" time="2:25" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_165_The_Pastoral_Album/WOM165_trk016_SUMMER_SUNRISE_(B)_Patrick_Thomas_Hawes_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="16" tracktotal="" search="CLASSIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, ALTERNATIF, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, PRINTEMPS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, ÉTÉ, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, PAISIBLE, CALME, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, ACOUSTIQUE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, ELEMENTS, ETE Une ouverture optimiste et calme progresse vers des phrases expansives de cordes. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 165 tk016 patrick thomas hawes summer sunrise (b) wom 165 the pastoral album west one music nature wildlife classical film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral pastoral alternate movies romance nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral nature wildlife the elements seasons time spring nature wildlife the elements seasons time summer tv radio optimistic and calm opening build to expansive strings phrases. alternative" waveformpath="" version="Alternative" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="28014" name="Great Wilderness (a)" code="WOM 241A tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="598" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_241A_Natural_World_Landscapes/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Matt Norman (PRS)" comment="Un thème puissant de grande envergure." styleid="26" lengthseconds="137" time="2:17" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_241A_Natural_World_Landscapes/WOM_241A_trk001_GREAT_WILDERNESS_(A)_Matt_Norman_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, FORT, PUISSANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, PATRIOTIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, FORT EN ÉMOTIONS, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, PERIODE, FORT EN EMOTIONS, PERIODES, ELEMENTS Un thème puissant de grande envergure. wom 241a tk001 matt norman (prs) great wilderness (a) wom 241a natural world: landscapes west one music nature wildlife volcanos nature wildlife planet earth natural world landscape exploration countryside deserts geology powerful sweeping theme. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="7132" name="Our Beautiful World" code="TSH 029 tk014" libraryid="5" albumid="164" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_029_Symphonic_Fantasia/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Arthur Rhodes" comment="Un thème spacieux, majestueux et sincère avec une conclusion calme." styleid="4" lengthseconds="112" time="1:52" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_029_Symphonic_Fantasia/TSH029_trk014_OUR_BEAUTIFUL_WORLD_Simon_Arthur_Rhodes_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="14" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MER, PAYSAGE MARIN, DRAMATIQUE, PAISIBLE, CALME, FORT, MAJESTUEUX, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, ANGLETERRE, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, AMERIQUE DU NORD, ETATS-UNIS, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), AERIEN, ELEMENTS Un thème spacieux, majestueux et sincère avec une conclusion calme. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz tsh 029 tk014 simon arthur rhodes our beautiful world tsh 029 symphonic fantasia the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic main documentary biographical historical the arts movies fantasy adventure nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral nature wildlife broad majestic heart-felt theme with calm conclusion. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
  </items>
</librarycollection>
