<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<librarycollection>
  <items>
    <item id="16051" name="Communication Breakdown (b)" code="WOM 141 tk015" libraryid="6" albumid="336" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_141_Electrosonic/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Oliver Adam Silk / Peter Boyes" comment="Une ligne de basse dense et dirty, des beats énergiques et crunchy avec des vibrations positives." styleid="1" lengthseconds="126" time="2:06" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_141_Electrosonic/WOM141_trk015_COMMUNICATION_BREAKDOWN_(B)_Oliver_Adam_Silk_Peter_Boyes_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="15" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 80, UNDERSCORE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRO, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, EURO POP, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HOUSE, ELECTRO HOUSE, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, RETRO, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COURANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, SPORT, EXERCICE, FITNESS,, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ENERGIQUE, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 80 Une ligne de basse dense et dirty, des beats énergiques et crunchy avec des vibrations positives. wom 141 tk015 oliver adam silk peter boyes communication breakdown (b) wom 141 electrosonic west one music dance electro business corporate beds time period modern era 20th century 1980s underscore tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) club electronica electro club electronica club electronica euro pop club electronica house electro house club electronica retro strong energetic uplifting positive big dirty bassline energetic crunchy beats with a positive vibe. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="2662" name="Saturday Night Strikes" code="RFM 034 tk001" libraryid="4" albumid="90" albumartpath="Music/Refuel Music/RFM_034_Ultimate_Archive_Kitsch_Collection/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Pete Moore" comment="Remix breakbeat funky et groovy de 'Saturday night Live', remixé par Alexander S. Gray." styleid="8" lengthseconds="135" time="2:15" samplefile="Music/Refuel Music/RFM_034_Ultimate_Archive_Kitsch_Collection/RFM034_trk001_SATURDAY_NIGHT_STRIKES_Pete_Moore_Refuel_Music.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="KITSCH, RETRO, CHEESY, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, REMIXES, KITSCH, RETRO, CHEESY, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, DROLE, MANIÉRÉ, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, HUMORISTIQUE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, ENJOUÉ, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), REMIX, STYLE VINTAGE, ENREGISTREMENT D'ARCHIVE, MANIERE, ENJOUE Remix breakbeat funky et groovy de 'Saturday night Live', remixé par Alexander S. Gray. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live rfm 034 tk001 pete moore saturday night strikes rfm 034 ultimate archive kitsch collection refuel music kitsch retro kitsch retro cheesy club electronica breakbeat club electronica remixes kitsch retro cheesy main activities settings showbiz tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio a funked up groove led breakbeat remix of 'saturday night live' remixed by alexander s. gray. main knees up, mess piano, cockney, east london, singalong, pub joanna, piano bar, piano-bar, live" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Refuel Music" cae="00617450359"/>
    <item id="21119" name="Get it Back Together (a)" code="WOM 251A tk006" libraryid="6" albumid="452" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_251A_Breakbeat_Deluxe/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Steven Guy Hellier / Charles James Nicholas Casey" comment="La rencontre d'un gros beat avec du gospel et du rock 60's. Alléluia !" styleid="1" lengthseconds="167" time="2:47" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_251A_Breakbeat_Deluxe/WOM251A_trk006_GET_IT_BACK_TOGETHER_(A)_Steven_Guy_Hellier_Charles_James_Nicholas_Casey_West_One_Musi.mp3" track="6" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, RELIGIEUX, CHRÉTIEN, PROTESTANT, CHANSONS GOSPEL, NEGRO SPIRITUALS, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, HOLLYWOOD, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, JEU, QUIZZ, SPECTACLE DE VARIÉTÉS, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, VOIX TRAITÉES, MODIFIÉES, CHRETIEN, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEFILE DE MODE, DEFILE, VOIX TRAITEES, MODIFIEES, SPECTACLE DE VARIETES, ETE La rencontre d'un gros beat avec du gospel et du rock 60's. Alléluia ! wom 251a tk006 steven guy hellier charles james nicholas casey get it back together (a) wom 251a breakbeat deluxe west one music dance electro club electronica breakbeat religious christian protestant gospel songs spirituals main activities settings fashion show activities settings showbiz hollywood tv radio children youth tv tv radio game quiz variety show tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style happy big beat meets gospel and 60s rock. hallelujah brother! main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="21080" name="Hammerhead" code="WOM 250 tk009" libraryid="6" albumid="451" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_250_Dubstep/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Steve Ruff" comment="Des synthés trance classiques avec des basses dubstep féroces et des breaks." styleid="28" lengthseconds="280" time="4:40" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_250_Dubstep/WOM250_trk009_HAMMERHEAD_Steve_Ruff_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, DUBSTEP, PRINCIPAL, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TROUBLANT, ÉTRANGE , TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ETRANGE, ANNEES 2000, ANNEES 20 Des synthés trance classiques avec des basses dubstep féroces et des breaks. wom 250 tk009 steve ruff hammerhead wom 250 dubstep west one music hip-hop urban club electronica club electronica dubstep main tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style disturbing strange tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) time period modern era 2000s classic trance synths with fierce dubstep bass and breaks. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="60" name="Stampede" code="EDS 002 tk003" libraryid="1" albumid="2" albumartpath="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_002_Dirty_Electro/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Sharooz Raoofi" comment="Une montée éléphantesque menant à une sub-basse massive et un son digital à vous percer les tympans." styleid="1" lengthseconds="293" time="4:53" samplefile="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_002_Dirty_Electro/EDS002_trk003_STAMPEDE_Sharooz_Raoofi_Electronic_Dance_Series.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRO, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HOUSE, ACID HOUSE, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HOUSE, ELECTRO HOUSE, PRINCIPAL, SPORT, EXERCICE, FITNESS, SPORT, SPORTS EXTREMES, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, NUIT, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, FORT, EVOLUTIF, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, EXCENTRIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, MÉCANIQUE, ROBOTIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COURANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PERIODE, MECANIQUE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETERMINE, IRREGULIER, ANNEES 2000, ANNEES 20, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Une montée éléphantesque menant à une sub-basse massive et un son digital à vous percer les tympans. eds 002 tk003 sharooz raoofi stampede eds 002 dirty electro electronic dance series dance electro club electronica club electronica electro club electronica house acid house club electronica house electro house main sports exercise fitness sports extreme sports tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio sports tv radio talkshow entertainment late night mammoth building intro breaks to enormous sub-bass and ear-piercing digital noise. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Electronic Dance Series" cae="00666407133"/>
    <item id="386" name="Another Galaxy" code="EDS 004 tk001" libraryid="1" albumid="12" albumartpath="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_004_Future_Disco/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Sample Magic / Colin Anthony Flynn / David Felton" comment="Un rythme four-on-the-floor joyeux avec une accroche qui met de bonne humeur." styleid="1" lengthseconds="234" time="3:54" samplefile="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_004_Future_Disco/EDS004_trk001_ANOTHER_GALAXY_Sample_Magic_Colin_Anthony_Flynn_David_Felton_Electronic_Dance_Series.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 70, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLUB, ELECTRONICA, DISCO, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HOUSE, FRENCH HOUSE, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HOUSE, HANDBAG HOUSE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE,, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEFILE DE MODE, ANNEES 2000, 20E SIECLE, DEFILE, ANNEES 20, ANNEES 70, JOURNEE Un rythme four-on-the-floor joyeux avec une accroche qui met de bonne humeur. eds 004 tk001 sample magic colin anthony flynn david felton another galaxy eds 004 future disco electronic dance series dance electro club electronica time period modern era 20th century 1970s time period modern era 2000s main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) club electronica disco club electronica house french house club electronica house handbag house happy feel good happy upbeat activities settings upbeat four-on-the-floor with an infectious feelgood hook. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Electronic Dance Series" cae="00666407133"/>
    <item id="2626" name="LA Breaks" code="RFM 032 tk001" libraryid="4" albumid="88" albumartpath="Music/Refuel Music/RFM_032_Ultimate_Archive_Soul_Collection/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Pete Moore" comment="Remix breakbeat groovy et funky de 'LA Beat' par Alexander S. Gray." styleid="8" lengthseconds="119" time="1:59" samplefile="Music/Refuel Music/RFM_032_Ultimate_Archive_Soul_Collection/RFM_032_trk001_LA_BREAKS_Pete_Moore_Refuel_Music.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, REMIXES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), REMIX, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 60, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 70, STYLE VINTAGE, ENREGISTREMENT D'ARCHIVE, PERIODE, 20E SIECLE, DETECTIVE, ANNEES 60, ANNEES 70, MYSTERE Remix breakbeat groovy et funky de 'LA Beat' par Alexander S. Gray. rfm 032 tk001 pete moore la breaks rfm 032 ultimate archive soul collection refuel music kitsch retro club electronica breakbeat club electronica remixes film score orchestral trailer funk soul r&amp;b main activities settings showbiz movies action adventure movies crime detective mystery movies espionage spy tv radio children youth tv happy feel good glamorous luxurious funky groove-led breakbeat remix of 'la beat' remixed by alexander s. gray. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Refuel Music" cae="00617450359"/>
    <item id="20166" name="Watch a Girl (a)" code="WOM 230 tk005" libraryid="6" albumid="430" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_230_Urban_Pop/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Felix Roderick Tod / David Wesley Ayers" comment="Un mash up battant de ragga dancehall et de pop. Voix d'homme." styleid="7" lengthseconds="198" time="3:18" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_230_Urban_Pop/WOM230_trk005_WATCH_A_GIRL_(A)_Felix_Roderick_Tod_David_Wesley_Ayers_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, DANSE ETHNIQUE, STYLE POP, RAGGA, HIP HOP, URBAIN, RAP, LATIN, LATIN HOUSE, PRINCIPAL, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, NUIT, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), VOCAL, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO) Un mash up battant de ragga dancehall et de pop. Voix d'homme. wom 230 tk005 felix roderick tod david wesley ayers watch a girl (a) wom 230 urban pop west one music pop club electronica ethnic dance pop style ragga hip hop urban rap latin latin house main tv radio children youth tv tv radio talkshow entertainment late night happy upbeat tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) vocals pumping ragga dancehall and pop mash up. male vocal. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="18263" name="Filth Funk (a)" code="WOM 191 tk003" libraryid="6" albumid="387" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_191_Festival_Dance_Tent/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Steven Guy Hellier / Charles James Nicholas Casey" comment="Une basse live grondante et battante avec des gros beats, des synthés hurlants et des voix tordues." styleid="1" lengthseconds="157" time="2:37" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_191_Festival_Dance_Tent/WOM191_trk003_FILTH_FUNK_(A)_Steven_Guy_Hellier_Charles_James_Nicholas_Casey_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BIG BEAT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CHEMICAL BEATS, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRO, FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, LIQUID FUNK, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, HOLLYWOOD, SPORT, EXERCICE, FITNESS, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, NUIT, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, CONFIANT, EVOLUTIF, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CORDES, BASSE, BASSE ÉLECTRIQUE, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, CORDES, GUITARE, WAH WAH, VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, VOIX TRAITÉES, MODIFIÉES, VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, TEXTURE VOCALE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 90, PERIODE, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETERMINE, DEFILE DE MODE, ANNEES 2000, 20E SIECLE, DEFILE, ELECTRIQUE, BASSE ELECTRIQUE, VOIX TRAITEES, ANNEES 20, ANNEES 90, MODIFIEES, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Une basse live grondante et battante avec des gros beats, des synthés hurlants et des voix tordues. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 191 tk003 steven guy hellier charles james nicholas casey filth funk (a) wom 191 festival dance tent west one music dance electro club electronica club electronica big beat club electronica breakbeat club electronica chemical beats club electronica electro funk soul r&amp;b liquid funk main activities settings fashion show activities settings showbiz hollywood sports exercise fitness tv radio leisure growling pumping live bass with fat beats screaming synths and twisted vocals. main knees up, mess piano, cockney, east london, singalong, pub joanna, piano bar, piano-bar, live" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="22965" name="Choco Loco (a)" code="WOM 291 tk006" libraryid="6" albumid="496" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_291_Go_Go_Indie/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Wesley Ayers" comment="Des vocaux entrainants et excentriques pour une fin retro-soul croustillante." styleid="34" lengthseconds="194" time="3:14" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_291_Go_Go_Indie/WOM_291_trk006_CHOCO_LOCO_(A)_David_Wesley_Ayers_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="6" tracktotal="" search="POP, POP POUR ENFANTS, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ENFANTS, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, JEU, QUIZZ, SPECTACLE DE VARIÉTÉS, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, VOCAL,, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DECALE, SPECTACLE DE VARIETES, JOURNEE, ETE Des vocaux entrainants et excentriques pour une fin retro-soul croustillante. wom 291 tk006 david wesley ayers choco loco (a) wom 291 go go indie west one music indie pop kiddie pop main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) children happy feel good funny comedic funny eccentric funny quirky tv radio children youth tv tv radio game quiz variety show tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio talkshow entertainment daytime vocals quirky catchy vocals over crunchy retro-soul style backing. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="57" name="Starfighter" code="EDS 002 tk009" libraryid="1" albumid="2" albumartpath="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_002_Dirty_Electro/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Sample Magic / David Felton / Andrei Axinte" comment="De l'electro house boostée et énergique. Passage euphorique à 1:18." styleid="1" lengthseconds="219" time="3:39" samplefile="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_002_Dirty_Electro/EDS002_trk009_STARFIGHTER_Sample_Magic_David_Felton_Andrei_Axinte_Electronic_Dance_Series.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRO, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HOUSE, ELECTRO HOUSE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, PRINCIPAL, SPORT, EXERCICE, FITNESS, SPORT, SPORTS EXTREMES, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, NUIT, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, EVOLUTIF, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, EXCENTRIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INSISTANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, MÉCANIQUE, ROBOTIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COURANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PERIODE, MECANIQUE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ENERGIQUE, IRREGULIER, ANNEES 2000, REVELER, ANNEES 20, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION De l'electro house boostée et énergique. Passage euphorique à 1:18. eds 002 tk009 sample magic david felton andrei axinte starfighter eds 002 dirty electro electronic dance series dance electro business corporate reveal launch club electronica electro club electronica house electro house business corporate science technology main sports exercise fitness sports extreme sports tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio sports tv radio talkshow pumping energetic electro house. euphoric breakdown at 1:18. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Electronic Dance Series" cae="00666407133"/>
    <item id="22269" name="Do it Right (a)" code="WOM 276 tk002" libraryid="6" albumid="478" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_276_Freestyle_Beats/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Russell Mcnamara" comment="Des rythmes terriblement entraînants. Vous ne tiendrez pas en place !" styleid="1" lengthseconds="144" time="2:24" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_276_Freestyle_Beats/WOM276_trk002_DO_IT_RIGHT_(A)_Russell_Mcnamara_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLUB, ELECTRONICA, GROOVES, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, ENJOUÉ, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, VOIX TRAITÉES, MODIFIÉES,, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DECALE, ENJOUE, VOIX TRAITEES, MODIFIEES Des rythmes terriblement entraînants. Vous ne tiendrez pas en place ! wom 276 tk002 russell mcnamara do it right (a) wom 276 freestyle beats west one music dance electro club electronica breakbeat main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) club electronica grooves happy happy happy lighthearted happy playful happy upbeat funny quirky tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio talkshow entertainment vocals deadly upbeat grooves. sit still at your peril! main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="22364" name="Push it Out (a)" code="WOM 278 tk007" libraryid="6" albumid="480" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_278_Drums_Rule_the_World/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Emre Ramazanoglu / Geoffrey James Pidcock Holroyde" comment="Des rythmes rétro-funk contagieux et punchy, avec des cuivres et des vocales excentriques." styleid="22" lengthseconds="168" time="2:48" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_278_Drums_Rule_the_World/WOM278_trk007_PUSH_IT_OUT_(A)_Emre_Ramazanoglu_Geoffrey_James_Pidcock_Holroyde_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="WORLD BEAT, STYLES ETHNIQUES, INFLUENCE LATINE, PRINCIPAL, OCCASIONS SPÉCIALES, VACANCES, VACANCES HORS USA, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CUIVRES, TROMPETTE, CORNET, BATTERIE, AMÉRIQUE LATINE, AMÉRIQUE DU SUD, AMERIQUE LATINE, OCCASIONS SPECIALES, AMERIQUE DU SUD, DECALE Des rythmes rétro-funk contagieux et punchy, avec des cuivres et des vocales excentriques. wom 278 tk007 emre ramazanoglu geoffrey james pidcock holroyde push it out (a) wom 278 drums rule the world west one music sport world beat ethnic stylings latin influenced main special occasions holidays non usa holidays tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style funny quirky tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) brass trumpet cornet drums latin america south america infectious and punchy retro-funk grooves with brass and quirky vocals. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="361" name="Elevate (a)" code="EDS 003 tk002" libraryid="1" albumid="11" albumartpath="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_003_Progressive_House/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Sample Magic / David Felton / Andrei Axinte" comment="Une montée synthétique en intro menant à un hymne dancefloor survitaminé." styleid="1" lengthseconds="248" time="4:08" samplefile="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_003_Progressive_House/EDS003_trk002_ELEVATE_(A)_Sample_Magic_David_Felton_Andrei_Axinte_Electronic_Dance_Series.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HOUSE, BEACH HOUSE, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, SPORT, EXERCICE, FITNESS, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, FORT, CONFIANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MONTÉE, ASCENDANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COURANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, MONTÉE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, VOIX TRAITÉES, MODIFIÉES, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PERIODE, MONTEE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEFILE DE MODE, ANNEES 2000, DEFILE, VOIX TRAITEES, ANNEES 20, MODIFIEES Une montée synthétique en intro menant à un hymne dancefloor survitaminé. eds 003 tk002 sample magic david felton andrei axinte elevate (a) eds 003 progressive house electronic dance series dance electro club electronica club electronica house beach house main activities settings fashion show sports exercise fitness tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio leisure lifestyle travel happy feel good strong confident uplifting uplifting rising ascending movement huge rising synth intro builds to high-energy dance floor anthem. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Electronic Dance Series" cae="00666407133"/>
    <item id="14607" name="The Bull Is Back (a)" code="WOM 106 tk002" libraryid="6" albumid="297" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_106_Urban_Underground/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Felix Roderick Tod / David Wesley Ayers" comment="Une bande son urban excentrique et joyeuse avec des vocales rétro et des saveurs jamaïquaines." styleid="28" lengthseconds="221" time="3:41" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_106_Urban_Underground/WOM106_trk002_THE_BULL_IS_BACK_(A)_Felix_Roderick_Tod_David_Wesley_Ayers_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, RETRO, HIP HOP, URBAIN, RAP, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ÉLECTRONIQUE, VOCAL, MASCULIN, ELECTRONIQUE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DECALE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE Une bande son urban excentrique et joyeuse avec des vocales rétro et des saveurs jamaïquaines. wom 106 tk002 felix roderick tod david wesley ayers the bull is back (a) wom 106 urban underground west one music hip-hop urban funk soul r&amp;b club electronica retro hip hop urban rap main activities settings city urban human environment movies crime detective mystery movies urban drama tv radio tv drama funny quirky happy upbeat tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) electronic vocals male quirky upbeat urban soundtrack with retro vocals and a jamaican flava. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="18200" name="Clap Your Hands (a)" code="WOM 189 tk006" libraryid="6" albumid="385" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_189_Dance_Punk/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jonny James / Parker Jones" comment="Féroce, filtré et funky. Une basse live dirty et grondante et des beats modernes bruts." styleid="1" lengthseconds="195" time="3:15" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_189_Dance_Punk/WOM189_trk006_CLAP_YOUR_HANDS_(A)_Jonny_James_Parker_Jones_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="6" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HOUSE, FRENCH HOUSE, FORT, CONFIANT, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, MÉCANIQUE, ROBOTIQUE, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, HOLLYWOOD, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE,, PERIODE, SERIEUX, MECANIQUE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETERMINE, DEFILE DE MODE, ANNEES 2000, DEFILE, ANNEES 20 Féroce, filtré et funky. Une basse live dirty et grondante et des beats modernes bruts. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 189 tk006 jonny james parker jones clap your hands (a) wom 189 dance punk west one music dance electro club electronica time period modern era 2000s main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) club electronica house french house strong confident happy happy happy playful peaceful contented serious determined movement rhythmic mechanical robotic glamorous luxurious activities fierce filtered and funky. dirty growling live bass and tough modern beats. main knees up, mess piano, cockney, east london, singalong, pub joanna, piano bar, piano-bar, live" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="15444" name="Flashback (a)" code="WOM 127 tk005" libraryid="6" albumid="321" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_127_Twisted_Electro_House/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Joshua Frederick Powell / Christopher William Hanson / Gary John Dedman / Kevin Mark Andrews" comment="Une bombe dancefloor avec une mélodie de synthé 80's et une voix robotique." styleid="1" lengthseconds="215" time="3:35" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_127_Twisted_Electro_House/WOM127_trk005_FLASHBACK_(A)_Joshua_Frederick_Powell_Christopher_William_Hanson_Gary_John_Dedman_Ke.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRO, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HOUSE, ELECTRO HOUSE, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, RETRO, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, FETE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, MÉCANIQUE, ROBOTIQUE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ÉLECTRONIQUE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 80, ELECTRONIQUE, PERIODE, MECANIQUE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ANNEES 2000, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 20, ANNEES 80 Une bombe dancefloor avec une mélodie de synthé 80's et une voix robotique. wom 127 tk005 joshua frederick powell christopher william hanson gary john dedman kevin mark andrews flashback (a) wom 127 twisted electro house west one music dance electro club electronica club electronica electro club electronica house electro house club electronica retro main activities settings city urban human environment activities settings party activities settings showbiz tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style happy upbeat upbeat floor killer with 80s synth melody and robotic vocal. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="22167" name="Sweet Swing Thing (a)" code="WOM 274 tk002" libraryid="6" albumid="476" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_274_Electro_Swing/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Sandor Mihaly Jozsa / Paul James Borg" comment="Des beats house battants fusionnés avec tout ce qui swingue. Avec des clarinettes, une trompette en sourdine, une guitare et des bribes de vocales accrocheuses." styleid="16" lengthseconds="162" time="2:42" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_274_Electro_Swing/WOM274_trk002_SWEET_SWING_THING_(A)_Sandor_Mihaly_Jozsa_Paul_James_Borg_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HOUSE, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, REMIXES, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, CUIVRES, TROMPETTE, CORNET, VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, VOIX TRAITÉES, MODIFIÉES,, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DECALE, DEFILE DE MODE, ANNEES 2000, DEFILE, VOIX TRAITEES, ANNEES 20, MODIFIEES Des beats house battants fusionnés avec tout ce qui swingue. Avec des clarinettes, une trompette en sourdine, une guitare et des bribes de vocales accrocheuses. wom 274 tk002 sandor mihaly jozsa paul james borg sweet swing thing (a) wom 274 electro swing west one music quirky club electronica time period modern era 2000s main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) club electronica house club electronica remixes happy feel good happy happy happy playful funny quirky activities settings fashion show tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style brass pumping house beats fused with all things swing. featuring clarinets muted trumpet guitar and catchy vocal snippets. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="20446" name="Pop (b)" code="WOM 234 tk017" libraryid="6" albumid="435" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_234_Electropop_Deluxe/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Tyler Van Den Berg" comment="Des guitares fuzz avec des synthés épais." styleid="1" lengthseconds="182" time="3:02" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_234_Electropop_Deluxe/WOM234_trk017_POP_(B)_Tyler_Van_Den_Berg_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="17" tracktotal="" search="POP, POP POUR ENFANTS, ENFANTS, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, EURO POP, POP, POP, PRÉ-ADOLESCENT, UNDERSCORE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, HOLLYWOOD, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PERIODE, PRE-ADOLESCENT, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEFILE DE MODE, ANNEES 2000, DEFILE, ANNEES 20 Des guitares fuzz avec des synthés épais. wom 234 tk017 tyler van den berg pop (b) wom 234 electropop deluxe west one music dance electro pop kiddie pop children club electronica euro pop pop pop tween underscore activities settings fashion show activities settings showbiz hollywood tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style happy upbeat tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) time period fuzz guitars meet chunky synths. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="22509" name="Losing My Attention (b)" code="WOM 282 tk021" libraryid="6" albumid="484" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_282_Planet_Pop/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Celetia Martin / Jonathan David Lipsey" comment="Imposant, assuré et funky. Entraînant, cool et plein d'attitude." styleid="7" lengthseconds="156" time="2:36" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_282_Planet_Pop/WOM282_trk021_LOSING_MY_ATTENTION_(B)_Celetia_Martin_Jonathan_David_Lipsey_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="21" tracktotal="" search="TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, POP, FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, SOUL CLASSIQUE, FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, SOUL CONTEMPORAINE, UNDERSCORE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEFILE DE MODE, ANNEES 2000, DEFILE, ANNEES 20 Imposant, assuré et funky. Entraînant, cool et plein d'attitude. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 282 tk021 celetia martin jonathan david lipsey losing my attention (b) wom 282 planet pop west one music pop pop funk soul r&amp;b classic soul funk soul r&amp;b contemporary soul underscore activities settings fashion show tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style happy upbeat tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) time period modern era 2000s big bold and funky. catchy cool and full of attitude. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="362" name="Lunar Eclipse" code="EDS 003 tk003" libraryid="1" albumid="11" albumartpath="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_003_Progressive_House/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Sample Magic / Colin Anthony Flynn / David Felton" comment="Une accroche synthétique tonique et répétitive se mue en un morceau club monstrueux." styleid="1" lengthseconds="243" time="4:03" samplefile="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_003_Progressive_House/EDS003_trk003_LUNAR_ECLIPSE_Sample_Magic_Colin_Anthony_Flynn_David_Felton_Electronic_Dance_Series.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HOUSE, BEACH HOUSE, PRINCIPAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, SPORT, EXERCICE, FITNESS, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, RÉPÉTITIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COURANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ANNEES 2000, REPETITIF, ANNEES 20, ELEMENTS Une accroche synthétique tonique et répétitive se mue en un morceau club monstrueux. eds 003 tk003 sample magic colin anthony flynn david felton lunar eclipse eds 003 progressive house electronic dance series dance electro club electronica club electronica house beach house main nature wildlife the elements land sun tropical seaside sports exercise fitness tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio sports uplifting euphoric uplifting uplifting repetitive uplifting synth hook explodes to a euphoric club monster. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Electronic Dance Series" cae="00666407133"/>
    <item id="22270" name="Flute Salad (a)" code="WOM 276 tk003" libraryid="6" albumid="478" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_276_Freestyle_Beats/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Russell Mcnamara" comment="Des accroches de flûtes samplées, des rythmes terriblement funky et des vocales d'homme expressives." styleid="1" lengthseconds="176" time="2:56" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_276_Freestyle_Beats/WOM276_trk003_FLUTE_SALAD_(A)_Russell_Mcnamara_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CLUB, ELECTRONICA, GROOVES, FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, SOUL CLASSIQUE, FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, SOUL CONTEMPORAINE, FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, NORTHERN SOUL, HEUREUX, ENJOUÉ, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, VOCAL, MASCULIN,, DECALE, ENJOUE Des accroches de flûtes samplées, des rythmes terriblement funky et des vocales d'homme expressives. wom 276 tk003 russell mcnamara flute salad (a) wom 276 freestyle beats west one music dance electro club electronica breakbeat main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) club electronica grooves funk soul r&amp;b classic soul funk soul r&amp;b contemporary soul funk soul r&amp;b northern soul happy lighthearted happy playful funny quirky tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure sampled flute hooks insanely funky grooves and soulful male vocals. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="387" name="Take Me Away" code="EDS 004 tk002" libraryid="1" albumid="12" albumartpath="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_004_Future_Disco/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Sample Magic / Colin Anthony Flynn / David Felton" comment="Un rythme disco sexy et des touches de synthés entraînants." styleid="1" lengthseconds="214" time="3:34" samplefile="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_004_Future_Disco/EDS004_trk002_TAKE_ME_AWAY_Sample_Magic_Colin_Anthony_Flynn_David_Felton_Electronic_Dance_Series.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 70, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLUB, ELECTRONICA, DISCO, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HOUSE, FRENCH HOUSE, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HOUSE, HANDBAG HOUSE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, SEXY, SEXY, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE,, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEFILE DE MODE, ANNEES 2000, 20E SIECLE, DEFILE, ANNEES 20, ANNEES 70, JOURNEE Un rythme disco sexy et des touches de synthés entraînants. eds 004 tk002 sample magic colin anthony flynn david felton take me away eds 004 future disco electronic dance series dance electro club electronica time period modern era 20th century 1970s time period modern era 2000s main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) club electronica disco club electronica house french house club electronica house handbag house happy feel good sexy sexy activities settings sexy disco groove with catchy synth touches. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Electronic Dance Series" cae="00666407133"/>
    <item id="2608" name="Glamour Bubble Breaks" code="RFM 031 tk001" libraryid="4" albumid="87" albumartpath="Music/Refuel Music/RFM_031_Ultimate_Archive_Killah_Funk_Collection/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Keith Andrew Roberts" comment="Version breakbeat et funky de &quot;Glamour Bubble&quot;. Remixé par Alexander S. Gray." styleid="8" lengthseconds="155" time="2:35" samplefile="Music/Refuel Music/RFM_031_Ultimate_Archive_Killah_Funk_Collection/RFM031_trk001_GLAMOUR_BUBBLE_BREAKS_Keith_Andrew_Roberts_Refuel_Music.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, REMIXES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, SEXY, COOL, FORT, CONFIANT, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 60, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 70, STYLE VINTAGE, ENREGISTREMENT D'ARCHIVE, PERIODE, 20E SIECLE, DETECTIVE, ANNEES 60, ANNEES 70, MYSTERE Version breakbeat et funky de &quot;Glamour Bubble&quot;. Remixé par Alexander S. Gray. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz rfm 031 tk001 keith andrew roberts glamour bubble breaks rfm 031 ultimate archive killah funk collection refuel music kitsch retro club electronica breakbeat club electronica remixes film score orchestral trailer funk soul r&amp;b main movies action adventure movies crime detective mystery movies espionage spy tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style happy feel good sexy funky breakbeat version of 'glamour bubble' remixed by alexander s. gray. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Refuel Music" cae="00617450359"/>
  </items>
</librarycollection>
