<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<librarycollection>
  <items>
    <item id="5415" name="From the Depths of Space (a)" code="TSH 052 tk054" libraryid="5" albumid="137" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_052_The_Mighty_Wurlitzer/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Leonard George Rawle" comment="Ambiance géniale de série B." styleid="17" lengthseconds="65" time="1:05" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_052_The_Mighty_Wurlitzer/TSH052_trk054_FROM_THE_DEPTHS_OF_SPACE_(A)_Leonard_George_Rawle_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="54" tracktotal="" search="KITSCH, RETRO, CHEESY, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, ESPACE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 50, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, FUTURISTE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, KITSCH, RETRO, CHEESY, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, STYLE VINTAGE, DROLE, MANIÉRÉ, DROLE, COMIQUE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, FILMS, SÉRIE B, FILMS, SCIENCE FICTION, CLAVIER, WURLITZER,, ELEMENTS SONORES, PERIODE, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), MANIERE, SERIE B, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 50, ELEMENTS Ambiance géniale de série B. tsh 052 tk054 leonard george rawle from the depths of space (a) tsh 052 the mighty wurlitzer the scoring house comedy kitsch retro cheesy sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds space time period modern era 20th century 1950s time period modern era futuristic main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) film score orchestral trailer kitsch retro cheesy sound elements atmospheres effects vintage style b-movie awesome space scenesetter. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="22310" name="New Moons" code="WOM 277 tk003" libraryid="6" albumid="479" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_277_Reconstruction_-_Textures/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Serein, chaleureux et attractif." styleid="12" lengthseconds="89" time="1:29" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_277_Reconstruction_-_Textures/WOM277_trk003_NEW_MOONS_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), RELIGIEUX, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, ZEN, MÉDITATION , TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, RELIGION &amp; ENVIRONNEMENTS RELIGIEUX,, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), MEDITATION, AERIEN, ELEMENTS Serein, chaleureux et attractif. wom 277 tk003 david ashton new moons wom 277 reconstruction - textures west one music atmospheres sound elements atmospheres main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) religious sound elements atmospheres peaceful dreamy peaceful peaceful peaceful zen meditation tender warm movement smooth aerial floating religion &amp; religious settings blissful warm and engaging. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="7038" name="Alien" code="TSH 024 tk034" libraryid="5" albumid="161" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_024_Conflict/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Everard Lawrence Wells / Robert John Foster" comment="Une atmosphère glaçante et perturbante." styleid="4" lengthseconds="67" time="1:07" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_024_Conflict/TSH024_trk034_ALIEN_Richard_Everard_Lawrence_Wells_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="34" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, SOUND DESIGN, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, ESPACE, INTERSIDÉRAL, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, ATMOSPHÈRE SCIENTIFIQUE, TROUBLANT, STÉRILE, TROUBLANT, FROID , TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, TROUBLANT, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, CRAINTIF, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, ÉTRANGE , TROUBLANT, SURNATUREL, TROUBLANT, BIZARRE, DRAMATIQUE, DANGEUREUX, EFFRAYANT, HORREUR, EFFRAYANT, MENAÇANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), SOUND DESIGN, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), STERILE, INQUIETANT, ETRANGE, MENACANT, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS, ATMOSPHERE SCIENTIFIQUE, INTERSIDERAL Une atmosphère glaçante et perturbante. tsh 024 tk034 richard everard lawrence wells robert john foster alien tsh 024 conflict the scoring house film score orchestral sound elements atmospheres sound design business corporate science technology film score orchestral trailer sound elements atmospheres main movies crime detective mystery movies horror thriller movies urban drama nature wildlife the elements sky space outer space science hostile disturbing soundscape. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="12637" name="The Force" code="WOM 063 tk009" libraryid="6" albumid="253" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_063_Fantasy_Adventure/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Bill Connor" comment="Les forces du bien et du mal s'affrontent dans une bataille intergalactique complexe." styleid="2" lengthseconds="133" time="2:13" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_063_Fantasy_Adventure/WOM063_trk009_THE_FORCE_Bill_Connor_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, MAL, TROUBLANT, SURNATUREL, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER,, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), INQUIETANT, EPIQUE Les forces du bien et du mal s'affrontent dans une bataille intergalactique complexe. wom 063 tk009 bill connor the force wom 063 fantasy adventure west one music trailer film score orchestral trailer main tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) disturbing eerie disturbing evil disturbing supernatural movies action drama movies epic movies fantasy adventure movies horror thriller complex intergalactic battle between the forces of good and evil. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="13796" name="Continuum (b)" code="WOM 088 tk022" libraryid="6" albumid="278" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_088_Forensic_Beats/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Tord Jungsten" comment="Un synthé nerveux et bizarre avec un effet." styleid="14" lengthseconds="67" time="1:07" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_088_Forensic_Beats/WOM088_trk022_CONTINUUM_(B)_Tord_Jungsten_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="22" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, AMBIENT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, LEFTFIELD, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, TRIP HOP, ALTERNATIF, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MER, SOUS-MARIN, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, BIZARRE, NERVEUX, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), SOUND DESIGN, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS Un synthé nerveux et bizarre avec un effet. wom 088 tk022 tord jungsten continuum (b) wom 088 forensic beats west one music drama club electronica ambient club electronica leftfield club electronica trip hop alternate movies crime detective mystery nature wildlife the elements sea underwater tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing weird edgy tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) edgy weird synth fx. alternative" waveformpath="" version="Alternative" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="3112" name="Darker Waters" code="TSH 008 tk003" libraryid="5" albumid="99" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_008_Ambient_Spirit/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Everard Lawrence Wells / Robert John Foster" comment="Un fond sonore anxieux et dérangeant avec des ponctuations graves." styleid="15" lengthseconds="74" time="1:14" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_008_Ambient_Spirit/TSH008_trk003_DARKER_WATERS_Richard_Everard_Lawrence_Wells_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, TROUBLANT, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, NERVEUX, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MER, SOUS-MARIN, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, ATMOSPHÈRE SCIENTIFIQUE,, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), INQUIETANT, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS, ATMOSPHERE SCIENTIFIQUE Un fond sonore anxieux et dérangeant avec des ponctuations graves. tsh 008 tk003 richard everard lawrence wells robert john foster darker waters tsh 008 ambient spirit the scoring house ambient chill sound elements atmospheres main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) business corporate science technology disturbing dark disturbing disturbing disturbing eerie disturbing mysterious edgy movies crime detective mystery tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama documentary edgy disturbing bed with low punctuations. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="26631" name="Into the Cosmos (a)" code="WOM 257 tk007" libraryid="6" albumid="571" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_257_Cinematic_Soundscapes/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Daniel Law Heath / James Brian Brasher" comment="Une superbe et captivante ouverture progresse doucement avec des tambours Taiko lointains." styleid="4" lengthseconds="173" time="2:53" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_257_Cinematic_Soundscapes/WOM257_trk007_INTO_THE_COSMOS_(A)_Daniel_Law_Heath_James_Brian_Brasher_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="WORLD BEAT, STYLES ETHNIQUES, GLOBAL, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, SÉRIEUX, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, BEAU, EVOLUTIF, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, DOCUMENTAIRE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, CHAUD, DÉSERT, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA,, SERIEUX, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS, DESERT, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Une superbe et captivante ouverture progresse doucement avec des tambours Taiko lointains. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede wom 257 tk007 daniel law heath james brian brasher into the cosmos (a) wom 257 cinematic soundscapes west one music film score orchestral world beat ethnic stylings global main tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) film score orchestral panoramic tender reflective serious disturbing mysterious beautiful building movies crime detective mystery documentary nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife beautiful captivating opening gently builds with distant taiko drums. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="24054" name="Axiom (a)" code="WOM 316 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="521" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_316_Cinematica/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Benson Taylor" comment="Paysage sonores éthérés et beats dubstep percutants avec de belles lignes de cordes." styleid="2" lengthseconds="199" time="3:19" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_316_Cinematica/WOM_316_trk001_AXIOM_(A)_Benson_Taylor_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, DUBSTEP, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, TV, RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, AGITÉ, TROUBLANT, TENDU, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, BEAU, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INSISTANT, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, AMERIQUE DU NORD, SERIEUX, ETATS-UNIS, AGITE, DETECTIVE, TELE REALITE, MYSTERE Paysage sonores éthérés et beats dubstep percutants avec de belles lignes de cordes. wom 316 tk001 benson taylor axiom (a) wom 316 cinematica west one music trailer film score orchestral trailer club electronica dubstep club electronica business corporate luxury main activities settings city urban human environment movies crime detective mystery movies espionage spy tv radio reality tv tv radio tv drama police legal ethereal soundscapes and snappy dubstep beats with beautiful string lines. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="17624" name="Solar Winds (a)" code="WOM 175 tk012" libraryid="6" albumid="371" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_175_Zero_Gravity/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Bill Connor" comment="Des synthés dérangeants et répétitifs avec des percussions profondes et pleines de pressentiments et des basses." styleid="12" lengthseconds="148" time="2:28" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_175_Zero_Gravity/WOM175_trk012_SOLAR_WINDS_(A)_Bill_Connor_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, FILMS, SCIENCE FICTION, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, AMBIANCES ET FONDS SONORES POUR PROJETS, TROUBLANT, STÉRILE, TROUBLANT, FROID , TROUBLANT, DÉSORIENTÉ, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, TROUBLANT, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, ÉTRANGE , TROUBLANT, SURNATUREL, TROUBLANT, BIZARRE, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), STERILE, DESORIENTE, INQUIETANT, ETRANGE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS Des synthés dérangeants et répétitifs avec des percussions profondes et pleines de pressentiments et des basses. wom 175 tk012 bill connor solar winds (a) wom 175 zero gravity west one music atmospheres sound elements atmospheres business corporate science technology film score orchestral trailer main documentary science technology movies crime detective mystery movies horror thriller movies science fiction science technology industry design beds disturbing barren disturbing repeating synths with deep foreboding percussion and bass. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="7119" name="The Eye and the Hurricane (a)" code="TSH 029 tk001" libraryid="5" albumid="164" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_029_Symphonic_Fantasia/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Arthur Rhodes" comment="Une aventure tourbillonnante, une section paisible à mi-morceau et une final étincelant." styleid="4" lengthseconds="305" time="5:05" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_029_Symphonic_Fantasia/TSH029_trk001_THE_EYE_AND_THE_HURRICANE_(A)_Simon_Arthur_Rhodes_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 90, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), PAISIBLE, TRANQUILLE, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, FILMS, SCIENCE FICTION, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA,, PERIODE, EPIQUE, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 90, ELEMENTS Une aventure tourbillonnante, une section paisible à mi-morceau et une final étincelant. tsh 029 tk001 simon arthur rhodes the eye and the hurricane (a) tsh 029 symphonic fantasia the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer time period modern era 20th century 1990s main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) peaceful tranquil movies action adventure movies epic movies fantasy adventure movies science fiction nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama whirlwind adventure tranquil middle section and dazzling finale. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="17330" name="Signs of Life (a)" code="WOM 169 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="364" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_169_Brave_New_World/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Patrick Thomas Hawes" comment="Atmosphérique et éthéré. Des fonds sonores suspendus avec des figures de harpes distantes et réverbérantes." styleid="12" lengthseconds="129" time="2:09" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_169_Brave_New_World/WOM169_trk001_SIGNS_OF_LIFE_(A)_Patrick_Thomas_Hawes_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, NEIGE, GLACE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MER, SOUS-MARIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, SÉRIEUX, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), AERIEN, ELEMENTS Atmosphérique et éthéré. Des fonds sonores suspendus avec des figures de harpes distantes et réverbérantes. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 169 tk001 patrick thomas hawes signs of life (a) wom 169 brave new world west one music atmospheres film score orchestral panoramic film score orchestral panoramic main nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife the elements land snow ice nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife nature wildlife the elements sea underwater nature atmospheric and ethereal. suspended string beds with distant reverberant harp figures. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="24399" name="All Seeing Eye (a)" code="WOM 322 tk003" libraryid="6" albumid="526" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_322_Cinematic_Drama/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Martin Tillmann" comment="Tension pulsante pour surveillance, enquete et cinematica sombre." styleid="14" lengthseconds="180" time="3:00" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_322_Cinematic_Drama/WOM322_trk003_ALL_SEEING_EYE_(A)_Martin_Tillmann_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, MODERNE, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, TROUBLANT, ANXIEUX, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, EFFRAYANT, MENAÇANT, SÉRIEUX, INQUIET, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, FORMATIONS GENERALES, SERIEUX, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, INQUIETANT, MENACANT, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE Tension pulsante pour surveillance, enquete et cinematica sombre. wom 322 tk003 martin tillmann all seeing eye (a) wom 322 cinematic drama west one music drama film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral documentary main movies crime detective mystery movies espionage spy movies human drama movies modern tv radio tv drama disturbing anxious disturbing dark disturbing eerie disturbing mysterious disturbing suspenseful pulsing tension for surveillance investigation and dark cinematica. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="18056" name="Strangers (a)" code="WOM 186 tk002" libraryid="6" albumid="382" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_186_Industrial_Ambience/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Rasmus Kunckel Nielsen" comment="De la musique d’alien étrange et merveilleuse avec une atmosphère euphorisante et industrieuse." styleid="15" lengthseconds="133" time="2:13" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_186_Industrial_Ambience/WOM186_trk002_STRANGERS_(A)_Rasmus_Kunckel_Nielsen_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS SONORES, SIFFLEMENT, CRÉPITEMENT, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, FUTURISTE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CLUB, ELECTRONICA, AMBIENT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FORMATION, INFORMATION, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TROUBLANT, DÉSORIENTÉ, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, ÉTRANGE , TROUBLANT, BIZARRE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INDUSTRIE, MACHINES, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, MÉCANIQUE, ROBOTIQUE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, AUTOMATISATION, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, AMBIANCES ET FONDS SONORES POUR PROJETS, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, ATMOSPHÈRE SCIENTIFIQUE,, ELEMENTS SONORES, PERIODE, ATMOSPHERES, MECANIQUE, DESORIENTE, ETRANGE, CREPITEMENT, ANNEES 2000, ANNEES 20, ELEMENTS, ATMOSPHERE SCIENTIFIQUE De la musique d’alien étrange et merveilleuse avec une atmosphère euphorisante et industrieuse. wom 186 tk002 rasmus kunckel nielsen strangers (a) wom 186 industrial ambience west one music ambient chill sound elements atmospheres sound effects hiss crackle time period modern era 2000s time period modern era futuristic main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) club electronica ambient club electronica business corporate science technology business corporate training information weird and wonderful alien music with an uplifting industrious atmosphere. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="22354" name="Breaking Dawn" code="WOM 277 tk047" libraryid="6" albumid="479" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_277_Reconstruction_-_Textures/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Des répétitions positives et décidées." styleid="12" lengthseconds="132" time="2:12" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_277_Reconstruction_-_Textures/WOM277_trk047_BREAKING_DAWN_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="47" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ENFANTS, CONTES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, CHEVAUCHER, ÉQUESTRE, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME,, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), PERIODES, EQUESTRE Des répétitions positives et décidées. wom 277 tk047 david ashton breaking dawn wom 277 reconstruction - textures west one music atmospheres children storytelling main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) children storytelling film score orchestral trailer uplifting positive movement rhythmic riding equestrian movies children storytelling movies fantasy adventure movies period historical costume drama positive and purposeful repetitions. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="6213" name="Science Mysteries" code="TSH 064A tk004" libraryid="5" albumid="146" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_064A_The_Observing_Eye/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Zac Jordan" comment="Bed de pulsations mystérieuses." styleid="12" lengthseconds="83" time="1:23" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_064A_The_Observing_Eye/TSH064A_trk004_SCIENCE_MYSTERIES_Zac_Jordan_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, PRINCIPAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, TROUBLANT, ANXIEUX, TROUBLANT, FLIPPANT, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, AGITÉ, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, SÉRIEUX, INQUIET, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, NUIT, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, ATMOSPHÈRE SCIENTIFIQUE, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, DRAME HOSPITALIER, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, ELEMENTS SONORES, FORMATIONS GENERALES, SERIEUX, ATMOSPHERES, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, AGITE, ELEMENTS, ATMOSPHERE SCIENTIFIQUE Bed de pulsations mystérieuses. tsh 064a tk004 zac jordan science mysteries tsh 064a the observing eye the scoring house atmospheres sound elements atmospheres general lineups electronic and acoustic main film score orchestral documentary disturbing anxious disturbing creepy disturbing dark disturbing mysterious disturbing restless disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense serious concerned movement mysterious pulsing bed. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="567" name="Forces of Darkness (a)" code="FEM 003 tk006" libraryid="2" albumid="17" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_003_Fantazium/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Toby Y. Chu" comment="Une inquiétante et dramatique envolée fantastique." styleid="2" lengthseconds="91" time="1:31" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_003_Fantazium/FEM003_trk006_FORCES_OF_DARKNESS_(A)_Toby_Y._Chu_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="6" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ENFANTS, CONTES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, BACK END, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, SURNATUREL, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, DANGEUREUX, EFFRAYANT, MENAÇANT, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, CONFIANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, CHOEUR, VOCAL, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 90, PERIODE, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), INQUIETANT, MENACANT, DETERMINE, EPIQUE, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 90 Une inquiétante et dramatique envolée fantastique. fem 003 tk006 toby y. chu forces of darkness (a) fem 003 fantazium fired earth music trailer film score orchestral trailer children storytelling film score orchestral panoramic main movies back end movies children storytelling movies epic movies fantasy adventure trailers trailer track disturbing eerie disturbing supernatural disturbing suspenseful disturbing an ominous and dramatic flight of fantasy. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
    <item id="8192" name="Drifting Away (a)" code="TSH 051 tk005" libraryid="5" albumid="177" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_051_Nearfield/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Everard Lawrence Wells / Robert John Foster" comment="Une nébuleuse de textures suspendues avec un violoncelle émergent." styleid="10" lengthseconds="127" time="2:07" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_051_Nearfield/TSH051_trk005_DRIFTING_AWAY_(A)_Richard_Everard_Lawrence_Wells_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, ZEN, MÉDITATION , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MER, SOUS-MARIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, DIVIN, CÉLESTE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, ESPACE, INTERSIDÉRAL, CORDES, VIOLONCELLE,, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), MEDITATION, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, CELESTE, INTERSIDERAL Une nébuleuse de textures suspendues avec un violoncelle émergent. tsh 051 tk005 richard everard lawrence wells robert john foster drifting away (a) tsh 051 nearfield the scoring house documentary sound elements atmospheres main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) peaceful dreamy peaceful peaceful peaceful zen meditation movement smooth aerial floating movement smooth aerial flying nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife nature wildlife the elements sea nebulous suspended textures with emerging cello. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="23406" name="Into the Wormhole" code="WOM 301 tk014" libraryid="6" albumid="507" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_301_Dark_Motion/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Christian Telford / Matthew St. Laurent / Galileo Seven / Koichi Sanchez-Imahashi / Nigel William Graham" comment="Textures electro d'un autre monde. Émouvant et troublant." styleid="14" lengthseconds="151" time="2:31" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_301_Dark_Motion/WOM301_trk014_INTO_THE_WORMHOLE_Christian_Telford_Matthew_St._Laurent_Galileo_Seven_Koichi_Sanchez-Imahashi_.mp3" track="14" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, PULSATION, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS Textures electro d'un autre monde. Émouvant et troublant. wom 301 tk014 christian telford matthew st. laurent galileo seven koichi sanchez-imahashi nigel william graham into the wormhole wom 301 dark motion west one music drama film score orchestral trailer sound elements atmospheres main documentary movies crime detective mystery movies human drama movies urban drama tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama sad depressing lonely sad depressing poignant sad depressing sad movement otherworldly electronic textures. haunting emotive. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="7123" name="Grand Spectacular (a)" code="TSH 029 tk005" libraryid="5" albumid="164" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_029_Symphonic_Fantasia/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Arthur Rhodes" comment="Une progression imposante ponctuée vers un climax explosif." styleid="4" lengthseconds="179" time="2:59" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_029_Symphonic_Fantasia/TSH029_trk005_GRAND_SPECTACULAR_(A)_Simon_Arthur_Rhodes_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, GUERRE, MILITAIRE, HISTORIQUE, SECONDE GUERRE MONDIALE, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, FILMS, GUERRE, TROUBLANT, TENDU, FORT, CONFIANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CUIVRES, CLAIRON, FANFARE, PÉRIODE, ÈRES CULTURELLES, SECONDE GUERRE MONDIALE (1939 - 1945), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 90, PERIODE, ERES CULTURELLES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), EPIQUE, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 90 Une progression imposante ponctuée vers un climax explosif. tsh 029 tk005 simon arthur rhodes grand spectacular (a) tsh 029 symphonic fantasia the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer main activities settings war military historical world war 2 movies epic movies fantasy adventure movies war disturbing tense strong confident tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) brass bugle fanfare time period cultural eras punctuated imposing build to explosive climax. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="26632" name="Above the Earth (a)" code="WOM 257 tk008" libraryid="6" albumid="571" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_257_Cinematic_Soundscapes/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Daniel Law Heath / James Brian Brasher" comment="Des phrases de piano lointaines et réverbérantes sur des cordes simples et expansives et des textures de synthé qui évoluent." styleid="4" lengthseconds="162" time="2:42" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_257_Cinematic_Soundscapes/WOM257_trk008_ABOVE_THE_EARTH_(A)_Daniel_Law_Heath_James_Brian_Brasher_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="8" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, MÉDICAL, SCIENCES DE LA VIE, ABSTRAIT, SIMPLE, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ELEMENTS, MEDICAL Des phrases de piano lointaines et réverbérantes sur des cordes simples et expansives et des textures de synthé qui évoluent. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 257 tk008 daniel law heath james brian brasher above the earth (a) wom 257 cinematic soundscapes west one music film score orchestral film score orchestral panoramic main documentary movies action adventure nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife science technology industry medical life science abstract simple disturbing mysterious peaceful distant reverberant piano phrases over simple expansive strings and evolving synth textures. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="17613" name="Orbital Moods (a)" code="WOM 175 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="371" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_175_Zero_Gravity/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Bill Connor" comment="Rêveur et optimiste. Des fonds sonores flottants de textures lumineuses progressent vers des percussions comme des battements de cœur et des mélodies délicates de célesta." styleid="12" lengthseconds="184" time="3:04" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_175_Zero_Gravity/WOM175_trk001_ORBITAL_MOODS_(A)_Bill_Connor_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, CLASSIQUE, STYLE MINIMALISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MER, SOUS-MARIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, AUBE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, ESPACE, INTERSIDÉRAL, TROUBLANT, DÉSORIENTÉ, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, TENDRE, DÉLICAT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, COOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, RALENTI, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLAVIER, CELESTE, EFFETS SONORES, HUMAIN, BATTEMENTS DE COEUR, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DESORIENTE, DELICAT, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, INTERSIDERAL Rêveur et optimiste. Des fonds sonores flottants de textures lumineuses progressent vers des percussions comme des battements de cœur et des mélodies délicates de célesta. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 175 tk001 bill connor orbital moods (a) wom 175 zero gravity west one music atmospheres sound elements atmospheres classical minimalist style business corporate science technology main documentary science technology nature wildlife the elements sea underwater nature wildlife the elements seasons time dawn nature wildlife the elements sky aerial clouds dream-like and optimistic. drifting beds of luminous textures build with heartbeat percussion and delicate celeste melodies. main delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="758" name="Battlefied: Milky Way (a)" code="FEM 013 tk006" libraryid="2" albumid="24" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_013_Bad_Boy_Trailer/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Enrico Cacace" comment="Une introduction électronique brouillée avec un rythme entrainant ouvrent cette piste Sci-Fi épique. Cuivres sombres et courses de chordes entrent à 00:32 par dessus un lit électronique sexy fait d'effets de bataille spatiale, le tout pour developper une fin d'action magistrale avec frappes et accoups." styleid="2" lengthseconds="100" time="1:40" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_013_Bad_Boy_Trailer/FEM013_trk006_BATTLEFIED_MILKY_WAY_(A)_Enrico_Cacace_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="6" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, ORCHESTRAL HYBRIDE , ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, SOUND DESIGN, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, BACK END, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, DRAMATIQUE, AGRESSIF, SEXY, SEXY, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, ÉPIQUE, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, IMPLACABLE, FORT, FORT, GLITCHY, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, DETERMINE, EPIQUE, ELEMENTS Une introduction électronique brouillée avec un rythme entrainant ouvrent cette piste Sci-Fi épique. Cuivres sombres et courses de chordes entrent à 00:32 par dessus un lit électronique sexy fait d'effets de bataille spatiale, le tout pour developper une fin d'action magistrale avec frappes et accoups. fem 013 tk006 enrico cacace battlefied: milky way (a) fem 013 bad boy trailer fired earth music trailer film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral orchestral hybrid sound elements atmospheres sound design main movies action adventure movies back end movies epic movies urban drama trailers trailer track disturbing dark dramatic aggressive sexy sexy strong confident glitchy electronic intro with catchy beat opens this sci-fi epic. dark brass and string runs layer in at 00:32 over this sexy electronic bed with space-wars effects coming together to develop to a huge action backend with stabs and hits. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
  </items>
</librarycollection>
