<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<librarycollection>
  <items>
    <item id="5420" name="Shock Horror (a)" code="TSH 052 tk059" libraryid="5" albumid="137" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_052_The_Mighty_Wurlitzer/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Leonard George Rawle" comment="Exclamation théâtrale dramatique." styleid="17" lengthseconds="25" time="0:25" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_052_The_Mighty_Wurlitzer/TSH052_trk059_SHOCK_HORROR_(A)_Leonard_George_Rawle_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="59" tracktotal="" search="KITSCH, RETRO, CHEESY, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, KITSCH, RETRO, CHEESY, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, DROLE, MANIÉRÉ, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, MÉLODRAMATIQUE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CLAVIER, WURLITZER, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 20, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 30, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 40, STYLE VINTAGE, PERIODE, MANIERE, MELODRAMATIQUE, DECALE, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 20, ANNEES 30, ANNEES 40 Exclamation théâtrale dramatique. tsh 052 tk059 leonard george rawle shock horror (a) tsh 052 the mighty wurlitzer the scoring house comedy kitsch retro cheesy film score orchestral trailer kitsch retro cheesy main activities settings showbiz funny campy funny comedic funny eccentric funny melodramatic funny quirky tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) keyboard organ wurlitzer time period modern era 20th century dramatic theatrical exclamation. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="5843" name="Marionette Memory (e)" code="TSH 056 tk180" libraryid="5" albumid="141" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_056_Delectable_Eclectica/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Bea Parks / Garo Nahoulakian / Oliver Charles Horton" comment="Valse hantée fantaisiste." styleid="16" lengthseconds="130" time="2:10" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_056_Delectable_Eclectica/TSH_056_trk180_MARIONETTE_MEMORY_(E)_Bea_Parks_Garo_Nahoulakian_Oliver_Charles_Horton_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="180" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, ENFANTS, CONTES, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, TEXTURE VOCALE, DANSE DE SALON, VALSE, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), INQUIETANT, DEPRIMANT, ELEMENTS Valse hantée fantaisiste. tsh 056 tk180 bea parks garo nahoulakian oliver charles horton marionette memory (e) tsh 056 delectable eclectica the scoring house quirky sound elements atmospheres children storytelling sound elements atmospheres main documentary movies children storytelling movies fantasy adventure disturbing eerie sad depressing tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) vocals vocal textures voice texture ballroom dance waltz haunting waltz time fantasy. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="26888" name="Peeping Tom (a)" code="WOM 317 tk012" libraryid="6" albumid="577" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_317_Weird_and_Wonderful/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Bill Connor" comment="Pizzicati insidieux de cordes pour affaires discrètes, jeux secrets et vies décalées." styleid="16" lengthseconds="115" time="1:55" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_317_Weird_and_Wonderful/WOM_317_trk012_PEEPING_TOM_(A)_Bill_Connor_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, ENFANTS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, ANIMATION, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, COMÉDIE, FILMS, FAMILIAL, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, MÉLODRAMATIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, DROLE, IRONIQUE, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, PIZZICATO, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, EXCENTRIQUE, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, INSECTE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, CORDES, CORDES PIZZICATO, MELODRAMATIQUE, ESPIEGLE, DECALE, IRREGULIER, COMEDIE, ELEGANT Pizzicati insidieux de cordes pour affaires discrètes, jeux secrets et vies décalées. wom 317 tk012 bill connor peeping tom (a) wom 317 weird and wonderful west one music quirky children storytelling children film score orchestral trailer main documentary movies animation movies children storytelling movies comedy movies family funny comedic funny eccentric funny melodramatic funny mischievous funny quirky funny wry scary ominous tender creeping pizzicato strings for furtive dealings secret games and quirky lives. dramedy. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="11738" name="Stigmata" code="WOM 047 tk016" libraryid="6" albumid="237" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_047_Big_Screen/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="James Anthony John Hannigan" comment="Un chœur évocateur avec des cordes et des cuivres dramatiques." styleid="2" lengthseconds="63" time="1:03" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_047_Big_Screen/WOM047_trk016_STIGMATA_James_Anthony_John_Hannigan_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="16" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO) Un chœur évocateur avec des cordes et des cuivres dramatiques. wom 047 tk016 james anthony john hannigan stigmata wom 047 big screen west one music trailer film score orchestral trailer main movies horror thriller movies human drama disturbing mysterious disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) classical and semi classical symphony orchestra evocative choir with dramatic strings and brass. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="6975" name="Secrets of the Past (a)" code="TSH 011 tk008" libraryid="5" albumid="160" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_011_Orchestral_Elements/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Bill Connor" comment="Un thème mystérieux et grandiose." styleid="4" lengthseconds="229" time="3:49" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_011_Orchestral_Elements/TSH011_trk008_SECRETS_OF_THE_PAST_(A)_Bill_Connor_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="8" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, MAGIE, ILLUSIONS, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SURNATUREL, MAGIQUE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), STYLE VINTAGE, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), INQUIETANT, PERIODES, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE Un thème mystérieux et grandiose. tsh 011 tk008 bill connor secrets of the past (a) tsh 011 orchestral elements the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer main activities settings magic illusions movies crime detective mystery movies horror thriller movies period historical costume drama trailers trailer track disturbing eerie disturbing mysterious disturbing supernatural magical tempo mysterious unfolding theme. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="568" name="Dark Fantasy (a)" code="FEM 003 tk007" libraryid="2" albumid="17" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_003_Fantazium/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Toby Y. Chu" comment="Une aventure magique sombre et bizarre aboutissant à un final dramatique avec des chœurs." styleid="2" lengthseconds="93" time="1:33" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_003_Fantazium/FEM003_trk007_DARK_FANTASY_(A)_Toby_Y._Chu_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ENFANTS, CONTES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ANIMATION, FILMS, BACK END, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, CRAINTIF, TROUBLANT, AGITÉ, TROUBLANT, SURNATUREL, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, DANGEUREUX, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, EFFRAYANT, MENAÇANT, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, CONFIANT, EVOLUTIF, MAGIQUE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, CHOEUR, VOCAL, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 90, PERIODE, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), INQUIETANT, AGITE, DECALE, MENACANT, DETERMINE, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 90, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Une aventure magique sombre et bizarre aboutissant à un final dramatique avec des chœurs. fem 003 tk007 toby y. chu dark fantasy (a) fem 003 fantazium fired earth music trailer film score orchestral trailer children storytelling film score orchestral panoramic main movies animation movies back end movies children storytelling movies fantasy adventure trailers trailer track disturbing dark disturbing eerie disturbing fearful disturbing restless dark quirky and magical adventure building throughout to a dramatic finale with choir. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
    <item id="12636" name="Sorcerer's Dance" code="WOM 063 tk008" libraryid="6" albumid="253" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_063_Fantasy_Adventure/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Bill Connor" comment="Une danse orchestrale fun et fantastique, avec un basson." styleid="2" lengthseconds="136" time="2:16" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_063_Fantasy_Adventure/WOM063_trk008_SORCERER'S_DANCE_Bill_Connor_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="8" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), HEUREUX, FUN, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, FAMILIAL, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, BOIS, BASSON,, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO) Une danse orchestrale fun et fantastique, avec un basson. wom 063 tk008 bill connor sorcerer's dance wom 063 fantasy adventure west one music trailer film score orchestral trailer main tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) happy fun movies children storytelling movies family movies fantasy adventure woodwinds bassoon fun fantastical orchestral dance featuring bassoon. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="6971" name="Watching You (a)" code="TSH 011 tk004" libraryid="5" albumid="160" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_011_Orchestral_Elements/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Bill Connor" comment="Mystérieuse et intrigante évocation amenée progressivement." styleid="4" lengthseconds="136" time="2:16" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_011_Orchestral_Elements/TSH011_trk004_WATCHING_YOU_(A)_Bill_Connor_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, CRAINTIF, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, EVOLUTIF, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Mystérieuse et intrigante évocation amenée progressivement. tsh 011 tk004 bill connor watching you (a) tsh 011 orchestral elements the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer main movies crime detective mystery movies horror thriller movies human drama tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing fearful disturbing mysterious disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense scary ominous building tempo intriguing mysterious evocation gradually building. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="5415" name="From the Depths of Space (a)" code="TSH 052 tk054" libraryid="5" albumid="137" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_052_The_Mighty_Wurlitzer/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Leonard George Rawle" comment="Ambiance géniale de série B." styleid="17" lengthseconds="65" time="1:05" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_052_The_Mighty_Wurlitzer/TSH052_trk054_FROM_THE_DEPTHS_OF_SPACE_(A)_Leonard_George_Rawle_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="54" tracktotal="" search="KITSCH, RETRO, CHEESY, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, ESPACE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 50, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, FUTURISTE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, KITSCH, RETRO, CHEESY, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, STYLE VINTAGE, DROLE, MANIÉRÉ, DROLE, COMIQUE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, FILMS, SÉRIE B, FILMS, SCIENCE FICTION, CLAVIER, WURLITZER,, ELEMENTS SONORES, PERIODE, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), MANIERE, SERIE B, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 50, ELEMENTS Ambiance géniale de série B. tsh 052 tk054 leonard george rawle from the depths of space (a) tsh 052 the mighty wurlitzer the scoring house comedy kitsch retro cheesy sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds space time period modern era 20th century 1950s time period modern era futuristic main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) film score orchestral trailer kitsch retro cheesy sound elements atmospheres effects vintage style b-movie awesome space scenesetter. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="20478" name="The Evil Ringmaster" code="WOM 235 tk013" libraryid="6" albumid="436" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_235_Circus/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Alistair Bruce Henry Friend / Ted Brett Barnes" comment="Le côté obscur de Monsieur Loyal." styleid="17" lengthseconds="131" time="2:11" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_235_Circus/WOM235_trk013_THE_EVIL_RINGMASTER_Alistair_Bruce_Henry_Friend_Ted_Brett_Barnes_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="13" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, CIRQUE, CARNAVAL, CIRQUE, TRADITIONNEL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, MAGIE, ILLUSIONS, SPECTACLE LIVE, THÉÂTRE, VAUDEVILLE, MUSIC HALL , FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, OCCASIONS SPÉCIALES, VACANCES, HALLOWEEN, TROUBLANT, DONNE LA CHAIR DE POULE, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, MÉLODRAMATIQUE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, MAGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, EXCENTRIQUE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), STYLE VINTAGE, OCCASIONS SPECIALES, MELODRAMATIQUE, DECALE, IRREGULIER, THEATRE Le côté obscur de Monsieur Loyal. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 235 tk013 alistair bruce henry friend ted brett barnes the evil ringmaster wom 235 circus west one music comedy children storytelling main activities settings circus carnival circus traditional activities settings magic illusions live entertainment theater vaudeville music hall movies children storytelling special occasions holidays halloween disturbing spooky funny comedic funny the sinister haunting other side of the ringmaster. main knees up, mess piano, cockney, east london, singalong, pub joanna, piano bar, piano-bar, live" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="4124" name="The Friendly Ghost (a)" code="TSH 025 tk002" libraryid="5" albumid="116" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_025_Tangled_Tales/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Marc Frederick Teitler" comment="Un thème effrayant avec un thérémine." styleid="20" lengthseconds="57" time="0:57" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_025_Tangled_Tales/TSH025_trk002_THE_FRIENDLY_GHOST_(A)_Marc_Frederick_Teitler_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, MÉLODRAMATIQUE, TROUBLANT, DONNE LA CHAIR DE POULE, MAGIQUE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, MAGIE, ILLUSIONS, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, INSTRUMENTS ÉLECTRONIQUES, THEREMIN,, ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ELECTRONIQUES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), MELODRAMATIQUE Un thème effrayant avec un thérémine. tsh 025 tk002 marc frederick teitler the friendly ghost (a) tsh 025 tangled tales the scoring house children children storytelling main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) film score orchestral trailer funny comedic funny melodramatic disturbing spooky magical activities settings magic illusions movies children storytelling electronic instruments theremin spooky theme featuring theremin. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="1326" name="Midnight Food Fight" code="FEM 008 tk004" libraryid="2" albumid="33" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_008_Spirited/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jeff Tymoschuk" comment="Ce qui s'annonçait comme un festin de minuit top secret devient une orchestration frénétique, rapide et tapageuse à l'ambiance tarte à la crème !" styleid="2" lengthseconds="119" time="1:59" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_008_Spirited/FEM008_trk004_MIDNIGHT_FOOD_FIGHT_Jeff_Tymoschuk_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, ENFANTS, MATERNELLE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, MARCHES, ORCHESTRE MILITAIRE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ANIMATION, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, FAMILIAL, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, INSENSÉ, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, DROLE, IDIOT, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, FORT, CONFIANT, TENDRE, INNOCENT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, POURSUITE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FRÉNÉSIE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, DÉFILÉ, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CUIVRES, BIG BAND, CUIVRES, FANFARE, MARCHE, INSENSE, ESPIEGLE, DECALE, FRENESIE, DEFILE Ce qui s'annonçait comme un festin de minuit top secret devient une orchestration frénétique, rapide et tapageuse à l'ambiance tarte à la crème ! fem 008 tk004 jeff tymoschuk midnight food fight fem 008 spirited fired earth music trailer children storytelling children pre school film score orchestral trailer marches military band main movies animation movies children storytelling movies family movies fantasy adventure trailers trailer track funny comedic funny eccentric funny madcap funny mischievous what starts out as a hush-hush midnight feast builds to frantic rambunctious fast-paced orchestral slapstick! main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
    <item id="7891" name="Hunters and Hunted (a)" code="TSH 004 tk026" libraryid="5" albumid="173" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_004_Natural_Wonders/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon David Chamberlain" comment="Un mouvement comme une poursuite menant à une fin paroxysmique et une sombre conclusion." styleid="26" lengthseconds="160" time="2:40" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_004_Natural_Wonders/TSH004_trk026_HUNTERS_AND_HUNTED_(A)_Simon_David_Chamberlain_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="26" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, DRAMATIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, POURSUITE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FRÉNÉSIE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COURANT, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, COMÉDIE, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE,, COMEDIE, FRENESIE, ELEMENTS Un mouvement comme une poursuite menant à une fin paroxysmique et une sombre conclusion. tsh 004 tk026 simon david chamberlain hunters and hunted (a) tsh 004 natural wonders the scoring house nature wildlife children storytelling main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) film score orchestral trailer dramatic movement rhythmic chase movement rhythmic frenzy movement rhythmic running movies action drama movies children storytelling movies comedy movies fantasy adventure nature chase like movement leading to a climactic end and sombre conclusion. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="17917" name="Haunted Fairytales (a)" code="WOM 182 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="378" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_182_Haunted_Fairytales/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Dan Graham" comment="Une introduction bizarre et évocatrice débouche sur un morceau t et dramatique à 0:52." styleid="2" lengthseconds="132" time="2:12" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_182_Haunted_Fairytales/WOM182_trk001_HAUNTED_FAIRYTALES_(A)_Dan_Graham_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, ENFANTS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ANIMATION, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, FAMILIAL, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, TROUBLANT, CRAINTIF, TROUBLANT, DONNE LA CHAIR DE POULE, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, MÉLODRAMATIQUE, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CHOEUR, CLAVIER, CELESTE, CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, VIOLONCELLE, CORDES, VIOLON , VOCAL, MELODRAMATIQUE Une introduction bizarre et évocatrice débouche sur un morceau t et dramatique à 0:52. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 182 tk001 dan graham haunted fairytales (a) wom 182 haunted fairytales west one music trailer children storytelling children film score orchestral trailer main movies animation movies children storytelling movies family movies fantasy adventure disturbing fearful disturbing spooky funny comedic funny melodramatic peaceful dreamy scary ominous tempo an intriguing and evocative introduction breaks into full dramatic score at 0:52. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="7934" name="Dungeon Doom" code="TSH 038 tk034" libraryid="5" albumid="174" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_038_Oddities/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Paul Reeves (Gb 2)" comment="Des figures de piano compliquées avec des interjections effrayantes de clarinette basse" styleid="17" lengthseconds="61" time="1:01" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_038_Oddities/TSH038_trk034_DUNGEON_DOOM_Paul_Reeves_(Gb_2)_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="34" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ANIMATION, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, TV, RADIO, DESSINS ANIMÉS, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, DONNE LA CHAIR DE POULE, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, MÉLODRAMATIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), BOIS, CLARINETTE BASSE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 50, STYLE VINTAGE, PERIODE, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), MELODRAMATIQUE, ESPIEGLE, 20E SIECLE, DETECTIVE, DESSINS ANIMES, ANNEES 50, MYSTERE Des figures de piano compliquées avec des interjections effrayantes de clarinette basse bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 038 tk034 paul reeves (gb 2) dungeon doom tsh 038 oddities the scoring house comedy film score orchestral trailer main movies animation movies crime detective mystery movies horror thriller tv radio cartoons disturbing mysterious disturbing spooky funny comedic funny melodramatic funny mischievous movement rhythmic stealthy tempo uneasy piano figure with spooky bass clarinet interjections. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="7388" name="Dream Dancers (a)" code="TSH 059 tk008" libraryid="5" albumid="168" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_059_Orchestral_Fantasia/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Arthur Rhodes" comment="Voix spectrales chantantes." styleid="4" lengthseconds="115" time="1:55" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_059_Orchestral_Fantasia/TSH_059_trk008_DREAM_DANCERS_(A)_Simon_Arthur_Rhodes_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="8" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, MAGIE, ILLUSIONS, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, DIVIN, CÉLESTE, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SURNATUREL, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, TENDRE, INNOCENT, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MAGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, CHANTONNANT, CLAVIER, PIANO, VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, TEXTURE VOCALE, INQUIETANT, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, CELESTE Voix spectrales chantantes. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 059 tk008 simon arthur rhodes dream dancers (a) tsh 059 orchestral fantasia the scoring house film score orchestral children storytelling business corporate luxury film score orchestral trailer main activities settings magic illusions movies children storytelling movies fantasy adventure nature wildlife the elements sky aerial clouds nature wildlife the elements sky heavenly celestial lilting spectral voices. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="563" name="Mischievous (a)" code="FEM 003 tk002" libraryid="2" albumid="17" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_003_Fantazium/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Toby Y. Chu" comment="Une aventure excitante et excentrique au rythme enlevé." styleid="2" lengthseconds="87" time="1:27" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_003_Fantazium/FEM003_trk002_MISCHIEVOUS_(A)_Toby_Y._Chu_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ENFANTS, CONTES, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ANIMATION, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, FAMILIAL, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, AGITÉ, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, EXCITANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, POURSUITE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CHOEUR, VOCAL, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 90, PERIODE, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), AGITE, DECALE, DETERMINE, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 90 Une aventure excitante et excentrique au rythme enlevé. fem 003 tk002 toby y. chu mischievous (a) fem 003 fantazium fired earth music trailer film score orchestral trailer children storytelling main movies animation movies children storytelling movies family movies fantasy adventure trailers trailer track disturbing mysterious disturbing restless funny quirky happy playful serious determined strong exciting fast paced quirky and exciting adventure. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
    <item id="26801" name="Strange Goings On (a)" code="WOM 248 tk011" libraryid="6" albumid="575" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_248_Dramedy/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Philip Hochstrate / Bill Connor" comment="Des bois mystérieux et des cordes pizzicati tendues." styleid="14" lengthseconds="147" time="2:27" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_248_Dramedy/WOM248_trk011_STRANGE_GOINGS_ON_(A)_Philip_Hochstrate_Bill_Connor_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="11" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, COMÉDIE, FILMS, COMÉDIE ROMANTIQUE, TV, RADIO, SITCOM, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, SEXY, GRIVOIS, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), CORDES, CORDES PIZZICATO, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), ESPIEGLE, DECALE, COMEDIE, COMEDIE ROMANTIQUE Des bois mystérieux et des cordes pizzicati tendues. wom 248 tk011 philip hochstrate bill connor strange goings on (a) wom 248 dramedy west one music drama film score orchestral trailer main movies children storytelling movies comedy movies romantic comedy tv radio sitcom disturbing mysterious disturbing tense funny comedic funny mischievous funny quirky happy playful sexy saucy tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) mysterious woodwinds and tense pizzicato strings. dramedy. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="7121" name="Phantasmagoria (a)" code="TSH 029 tk003" libraryid="5" albumid="164" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_029_Symphonic_Fantasia/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Arthur Rhodes" comment="Un mystère captivant, épisodique et magique." styleid="4" lengthseconds="291" time="4:51" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_029_Symphonic_Fantasia/TSH029_trk003_PHANTASMAGORIA_(A)_Simon_Arthur_Rhodes_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, MAGIE, ILLUSIONS, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, ANIMATION, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, JAILLIR, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 90, PERIODE, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 90 Un mystère captivant, épisodique et magique. tsh 029 tk003 simon arthur rhodes phantasmagoria (a) tsh 029 symphonic fantasia the scoring house film score orchestral children storytelling film score orchestral trailer main activities settings magic illusions movies action adventure movies animation movies children storytelling movies fantasy adventure uplifting soaring tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) time period modern era intriguing episodic magic and mystery. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
  </items>
</librarycollection>
