<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><librarycollection><items><item id="1171" name="Panic Stations, Planet Earth (g) (Low Dark Hit 1)" code="FEM 021 tk026" libraryid="2" albumid="33" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_021_Soundesign_Vol_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Russell A. McKamey" comment="Hit qui fait boom. Grave, sombre. Avec reverb qui crisse." styleid="2" lengthseconds="7" time="0:07" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_021_Soundesign_Vol_2/FEM_021_trk026_PANIC_STATIONS,_PLANET_EARTH_(G)_(LOW_DARK_HIT_1)_Russell_A._McKamey_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="26" tracktotal="" search="SOUND DESIGN, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, STING, TRAILERS, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, EFFRAYANT, EFFRAYANT, SOUND DESIGN, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, SONS ÉLECTRONIQUES, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, ESPACE, ELEMENTS SONORES, ELECTRONIQUE, ATMOSPHERES, INQUIETANT, SONS ELECTRONIQUES, ELEMENTS Hit qui fait boom. Grave, sombre. Avec reverb qui crisse. fem 021 tk026 russell a. mckamey panic stations planet earth (g) (low dark hit 1) fem 021 soundesign vol. 2 fired earth music trailer sound elements atmospheres sound design sound elements atmospheres effects sting trailers disturbing dark disturbing eerie scary ominous scary scary sound design sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds electronic sounds sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds space low dark booming hit with crunchy reverb. sound effect" waveformpath="" version="Sound Effect" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284" /><item id="1175" name="Panic Stations, Planet Earth (k) (Short Atmospheric Riser)" code="FEM 021 tk030" libraryid="2" albumid="33" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_021_Soundesign_Vol_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Russell A. McKamey" comment="Montée courte, tordue." styleid="2" lengthseconds="5" time="0:05" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_021_Soundesign_Vol_2/FEM_021_trk030_PANIC_STATIONS,_PLANET_EARTH_(K)_(SHORT_ATMOSPHERIC_RISER)_Russell_A._McKamey_Fired_Earth_Music.mp3" track="30" tracktotal="" search="SOUND DESIGN, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, STING, TRAILERS, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, EFFRAYANT, EFFRAYANT, MONTÉE, ASCENDANT, SOUND DESIGN, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, SONS ÉLECTRONIQUES, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, ESPACE, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, BALAYAGE, SOUFFLES, ELEMENTS SONORES, ELECTRONIQUE, MONTEE, ATMOSPHERES, INQUIETANT, SONS ELECTRONIQUES, ELEMENTS Montée courte, tordue. fem 021 tk030 russell a. mckamey panic stations planet earth (k) (short atmospheric riser) fem 021 soundesign vol. 2 fired earth music trailer sound elements atmospheres sound design sound elements atmospheres effects sting trailers disturbing dark disturbing eerie scary ominous scary scary rising ascending sound design sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds electronic sounds sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds space short warped rise. sound effect" waveformpath="" version="Sound Effect" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284" /><item id="1205" name="Edge of Humanity (r) (sci-fi blaze)" code="FEM 021 tk060" libraryid="2" albumid="33" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_021_Soundesign_Vol_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Russell A. McKamey" comment="Incendie explosif de sci-fi." styleid="2" lengthseconds="2" time="0:02" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_021_Soundesign_Vol_2/FEM_021_trk060_EDGE_OF_HUMANITY_(R)_(SCI-FI_BLAZE)_Russell_A._McKamey_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="60" tracktotal="" search="SOUND DESIGN, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, STING, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, FILMS, SCIENCE FICTION, TRAILERS, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, EFFRAYANT, HORREUR, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, SOUND DESIGN, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, SONS ÉLECTRONIQUES, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, ESPACE, ELEMENTS SONORES, ELECTRONIQUE, ATMOSPHERES, INQUIETANT, SONS ELECTRONIQUES, ELEMENTS Incendie explosif de sci-fi. fem 021 tk060 russell a. mckamey edge of humanity (r) (sci-fi blaze) fem 021 soundesign vol. 2 fired earth music trailer sound elements atmospheres sound design sound elements atmospheres effects sting activities settings futuristic movies science fiction trailers disturbing dark disturbing eerie scary horror scary ominous sound design sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds electronic sounds explosive sci-fi blaze. sound effect" waveformpath="" version="Sound Effect" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284" /><item id="21305" name="Alien Assault" code="WOM 229 tk044" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Une montée de rock hybride dirty." styleid="2" lengthseconds="25" time="0:25" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk044_ALIEN_ASSAULT_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="44" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, HARDCORE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, TROUBLANT, ÉTRANGE , TROUBLANT, BIZARRE, EFFRAYANT, HORREUR, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, POURSUITE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ETRANGE Une montée de rock hybride dirty. wom 229 tk044 david ashton alien assault wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer rock hardcore main movies action drama movies horror thriller disturbing strange disturbing weird scary horror movement rhythmic chase tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) dirty rock hybrid rise. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21301" name="End of the Universe" code="WOM 229 tk040" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Une atmosphère sombre et menaçante mène à une montée de l'ère spatiale." styleid="2" lengthseconds="25" time="0:25" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk040_END_OF_THE_UNIVERSE_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="40" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, ESPACE, EFFETS SONORES, HORREUR, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, ÉTRANGE , TROUBLANT, BIZARRE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, ESPACE, INTERSIDÉRAL,, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ETRANGE, ELEMENTS, INTERSIDERAL Une atmosphère sombre et menaçante mène à une montée de l'ère spatiale. wom 229 tk040 david ashton end of the universe wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds space sound effects horror main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) sound elements atmospheres effects disturbing dark disturbing strange disturbing weird nature wildlife the elements sky space outer space dark brooding atmosphere leads to space-age rise. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21292" name="The Necromancer" code="WOM 229 tk031" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Des cordes grandissantes et sinueuses mènent à une attaque." styleid="2" lengthseconds="24" time="0:24" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk031_THE_NECROMANCER_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="31" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, EFFETS SONORES, HORREUR, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, SURNATUREL, EFFRAYANT, HORREUR, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, MONTÉE, MONTÉE, ASCENDANT, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER,, ELEMENTS SONORES, MONTEE, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), INQUIETANT, ELEMENTS Des cordes grandissantes et sinueuses mènent à une attaque. wom 229 tk031 david ashton the necromancer wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects sound effects horror main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) disturbing eerie disturbing supernatural scary horror movement smooth rising rising ascending movies horror thriller rising twisting strings build to hit. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21308" name="Insanity Pursuit" code="WOM 229 tk047" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Des percussions furieuses progressant vers une montée." styleid="2" lengthseconds="24" time="0:24" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk047_INSANITY_PURSUIT_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="47" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, GUERRE, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, FORT, EVOLUTIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, POURSUITE, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Des percussions furieuses progressant vers une montée. wom 229 tk047 david ashton insanity pursuit wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer film score orchestral trailer main movies action adventure movies action drama movies war trailers trailer track strong building movement rhythmic chase tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) furious percussion building into rise. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21293" name="Nail Scraper" code="WOM 229 tk032" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Des cordes aiguës et crissantes." styleid="2" lengthseconds="21" time="0:21" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk032_NAIL_SCRAPER_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="32" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, EFFETS SONORES, HORREUR, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, SURNATUREL, EFFRAYANT, HORREUR, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER,, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), INQUIETANT, ELEMENTS Des cordes aiguës et crissantes. wom 229 tk032 david ashton nail scraper wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects sound effects horror main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) sound elements atmospheres effects disturbing eerie disturbing supernatural scary horror movies horror thriller high tortured strings. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21304" name="Particle Accelerator" code="WOM 229 tk043" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Une montée dans un style science-fiction." styleid="2" lengthseconds="20" time="0:20" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk043_PARTICLE_ACCELERATOR_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="43" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, ESPACE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 66 - 76 À L'AISE (ADAGIO), TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, ÉTRANGE , TROUBLANT, SURNATUREL, TROUBLANT, BIZARRE, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER,, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 66 - 76 A L'AISE (ADAGIO), INQUIETANT, ETRANGE, ELEMENTS Une montée dans un style science-fiction. wom 229 tk043 david ashton particle accelerator wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds space main tempo 66 - 76 medium slow (adagio) disturbing eerie disturbing strange disturbing supernatural disturbing weird movies horror thriller sci-fi-style rise. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21306" name="Fever Pitch" code="WOM 229 tk045" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Un mini morceau de bande-annonce, une attaque immense mène à une montée épique." styleid="2" lengthseconds="20" time="0:20" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk045_FEVER_PITCH_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="45" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, TROUBLANT, ÉTRANGE , TROUBLANT, BIZARRE, DRAMATIQUE, VIOLENT, EFFRAYANT, HORREUR, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, POURSUITE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ETRANGE, ELEMENTS Un mini morceau de bande-annonce, une attaque immense mène à une montée épique. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede wom 229 tk045 david ashton fever pitch wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects main movies action drama movies horror thriller disturbing strange disturbing weird dramatic violent scary horror movement rhythmic chase tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) mini-trailer cue huge hit leads to epic rise. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21299" name="Night Spiders" code="WOM 229 tk038" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Des effets pizzicati glaçants, avec une énorme montée orchestrale." styleid="2" lengthseconds="18" time="0:18" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk038_NIGHT_SPIDERS_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="38" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, EFFETS SONORES, HORREUR, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), TROUBLANT, FLIPPANT, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, ÉTRANGE , TROUBLANT, SURNATUREL, TROUBLANT, BIZARRE, EFFRAYANT, HORREUR, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER,, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, INQUIETANT, ETRANGE, ELEMENTS Des effets pizzicati glaçants, avec une énorme montée orchestrale. wom 229 tk038 david ashton night spiders wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects sound effects horror main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) disturbing creepy disturbing eerie disturbing strange disturbing supernatural disturbing weird scary horror movies horror thriller creepy pizzicato effects with huge orchestral rise. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21302" name="Future Chaos" code="WOM 229 tk041" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Un chaos électronique progressant." styleid="2" lengthseconds="15" time="0:15" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk041_FUTURE_CHAOS_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="41" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, TROUBLANT, ÉTRANGE , TROUBLANT, BIZARRE, EFFRAYANT, HORREUR, EVOLUTIF, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, ESPACE, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, ETRANGE, ELEMENTS, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Un chaos électronique progressant. wom 229 tk041 david ashton future chaos wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres sound elements atmospheres effects main movies horror thriller disturbing strange disturbing weird scary horror building tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds space building electronic chaos. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21298" name="Creepy Strings" code="WOM 229 tk037" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Une montée orchestrale qui fait froid dans le dos." styleid="2" lengthseconds="15" time="0:15" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk037_CREEPY_STRINGS_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="37" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, EFFRAYANT, HORREUR, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), EFFETS SONORES, HORREUR, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ELEMENTS Une montée orchestrale qui fait froid dans le dos. wom 229 tk037 david ashton creepy strings wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects sound elements atmospheres effects main movies horror thriller scary horror tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) sound effects horror spine-chilling orchestral rise. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21303" name="Rise of the Robots" code="WOM 229 tk042" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Une montée ressemblant à une machine." styleid="2" lengthseconds="14" time="0:14" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk042_RISE_OF_THE_ROBOTS_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="42" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, ESPACE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, ÉTRANGE , TROUBLANT, SURNATUREL, TROUBLANT, BIZARRE, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER,, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), INQUIETANT, ETRANGE, ELEMENTS Une montée ressemblant à une machine. wom 229 tk042 david ashton rise of the robots wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds space main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) sound elements atmospheres effects disturbing eerie disturbing strange disturbing supernatural disturbing weird scary ominous movies horror thriller machine-like rise. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21280" name="Soft Gong" code="WOM 229 tk019" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Un effet de gong." styleid="2" lengthseconds="14" time="0:14" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk019_SOFT_GONG_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="19" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, ÉLÉMENTS MUSICAUX, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FORT, ÉPIQUE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ETHNIQUE, PERCUSSION, GONG, PERCUSSION, GONGS, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), EPIQUE, ELEMENTS MUSICAUX, ELEMENTS Un effet de gong. wom 229 tk019 david ashton soft gong wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres music elements main movies epic strong epic tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) ethnic percussion gong percussion gongs gong effect. main delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21279" name="Enter the Place" code="WOM 229 tk018" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Un effet de gong." styleid="2" lengthseconds="14" time="0:14" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk018_ENTER_THE_PLACE_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="18" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FORT, ÉPIQUE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), ETHNIQUE, PERCUSSION, GONG, PERCUSSION, GONGS, EFFETS SONORES, EXPLOSIONS, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, EPIQUE, ELEMENTS Un effet de gong. wom 229 tk018 david ashton enter the place wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects sound elements atmospheres effects main movies epic strong epic tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) ethnic percussion gong percussion gongs sound effects explosions gong effect. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21297" name="Army of Strings" code="WOM 229 tk036" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Une montée orchestrale malsaine." styleid="2" lengthseconds="13" time="0:13" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk036_ARMY_OF_STRINGS_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="36" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, EFFRAYANT, HORREUR, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), EFFETS SONORES, HORREUR, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ELEMENTS Une montée orchestrale malsaine. wom 229 tk036 david ashton army of strings wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects sound elements atmospheres effects main movies horror thriller scary horror tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) sound effects horror twisted orchestral rise. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21321" name="Flyby" code="WOM 229 tk060" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Un effet de bande-annonce." styleid="2" lengthseconds="13" time="0:13" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk060_FLYBY_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="60" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, PRINCIPAL, TRAILERS, FORT, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), EFFETS SONORES, EXPLOSIONS, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, SONS ÉLECTRONIQUES, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, LASERS, ZAPS, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, ESPACE, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, BALAYAGE, SOUFFLES, ELEMENTS SONORES, ELECTRONIQUE, ATMOSPHERES, SONS ELECTRONIQUES, ELEMENTS Un effet de bande-annonce. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede wom 229 tk060 david ashton flyby wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects film score orchestral trailer sound elements atmospheres effects main trailers strong tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) sound effects explosions sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds electronic sounds sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds lasers trailer fx. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21296" name="Ghost Whispers" code="WOM 229 tk035" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Une atmosphère sonore malsaine d'horreur." styleid="2" lengthseconds="12" time="0:12" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk035_GHOST_WHISPERS_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="35" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, EFFRAYANT, HORREUR, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), EFFETS SONORES, HORREUR, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ELEMENTS Une atmosphère sonore malsaine d'horreur. wom 229 tk035 david ashton ghost whispers wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects sound elements atmospheres effects main movies horror thriller scary horror tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) sound effects horror twisted horror soundscape. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21284" name="Epic Reverse" code="WOM 229 tk023" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Un crescendo de cymbale devient une attaque." styleid="2" lengthseconds="11" time="0:11" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk023_EPIC_REVERSE_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="23" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, PRINCIPAL, TRAILERS, FORT, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), PERCUSSION, CYMBALES, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, ELEMENTS Un crescendo de cymbale devient une attaque. wom 229 tk023 david ashton epic reverse wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects main trailers strong tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) percussion cymbals cymbal swell into hit. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21294" name="Death Screams" code="WOM 229 tk033" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Un grondement sombre et menaçant et des cordes aiguës et sinueuses." styleid="2" lengthseconds="11" time="0:11" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk033_DEATH_SCREAMS_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="33" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, EFFETS SONORES, HORREUR, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, SURNATUREL, EFFRAYANT, HORREUR, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER,, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, INQUIETANT, ELEMENTS Un grondement sombre et menaçant et des cordes aiguës et sinueuses. wom 229 tk033 david ashton death screams wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects sound effects horror main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) sound elements atmospheres effects disturbing dark disturbing eerie disturbing supernatural scary horror scary ominous movies horror thriller dark ominous rumbles and high twisted strings. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21272" name="Earth Shaker" code="WOM 229 tk011" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Une attaque profonde de bande-annonce." styleid="2" lengthseconds="10" time="0:10" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk011_EARTH_SHAKER_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="11" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, TRAILERS, NEUTRE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), EFFETS SONORES, EXPLOSIONS, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ELEMENTS Une attaque profonde de bande-annonce. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede wom 229 tk011 david ashton earth shaker wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects film score orchestral trailer main trailers neutral tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) sound effects explosions deep trailer hit. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21315" name="Magical Swoosh" code="WOM 229 tk054" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Un léger swoosh." styleid="2" lengthseconds="10" time="0:10" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk054_MAGICAL_SWOOSH_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="54" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, MAGIE, ILLUSIONS, TENDRE, LÉGER, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, SONS ÉLECTRONIQUES, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, LASERS, ZAPS, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, BALAYAGE, SOUFFLES, EFFETS SONORES, HORREUR, EFFETS SONORES, NATURE, VENT, ELEMENTS SONORES, ELECTRONIQUE, ATMOSPHERES, LEGER, SONS ELECTRONIQUES, ELEMENTS Un léger swoosh. wom 229 tk054 david ashton magical swoosh wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects sound elements atmospheres effects main activities settings magic illusions tender light tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds electronic sounds sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds lasers zaps sound effects light swoosh. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21277" name="Epic Gongs" code="WOM 229 tk016" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Un effet de gong." styleid="2" lengthseconds="10" time="0:10" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk016_EPIC_GONGS_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="16" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FORT, ÉPIQUE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ETHNIQUE, PERCUSSION, GONG, PERCUSSION, GONGS, EFFETS SONORES, EXPLOSIONS, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), EPIQUE, ELEMENTS Un effet de gong. wom 229 tk016 david ashton epic gongs wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects sound elements atmospheres effects main movies epic strong epic tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) ethnic percussion gong percussion gongs sound effects explosions gong effect. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21318" name="Watery Swoosh" code="WOM 229 tk057" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Un léger swoosh." styleid="2" lengthseconds="10" time="0:10" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk057_WATERY_SWOOSH_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="57" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, MAGIE, ILLUSIONS, TENDRE, LÉGER, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, LASERS, ZAPS, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, BALAYAGE, SOUFFLES, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, LEGER, ELEMENTS Un léger swoosh. wom 229 tk057 david ashton watery swoosh wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects sound elements atmospheres effects main activities settings magic illusions tender light tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds lasers zaps sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds sweeps whooshes light swoosh. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21274" name="Reverse Boom" code="WOM 229 tk013" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Une attaque profonde de bande-annonce." styleid="2" lengthseconds="9" time="0:09" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk013_REVERSE_BOOM_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="13" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, PRINCIPAL, TRAILERS, NEUTRE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), EFFETS SONORES, EXPLOSIONS, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, ELEMENTS Une attaque profonde de bande-annonce. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede wom 229 tk013 david ashton reverse boom wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects film score orchestral trailer sound elements atmospheres effects main trailers neutral tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) sound effects explosions deep trailer hit. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21287" name="Epic Metal Strike" code="WOM 229 tk026" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Une attaque métallique de bande-annonce." styleid="2" lengthseconds="9" time="0:09" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk026_EPIC_METAL_STRIKE_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="26" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, PRINCIPAL, TRAILERS, FORT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), EFFETS SONORES, EXPLOSIONS, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ELEMENTS Une attaque métallique de bande-annonce. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede wom 229 tk026 david ashton epic metal strike wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects film score orchestral trailer sound elements atmospheres effects main trailers strong tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) sound effects explosions metallic trailer hit. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21288" name="Metal Impact" code="WOM 229 tk027" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Une attaque métallique de bande-annonce." styleid="2" lengthseconds="9" time="0:09" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk027_METAL_IMPACT_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="27" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, PRINCIPAL, TRAILERS, FORT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), EFFETS SONORES, EXPLOSIONS, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ELEMENTS Une attaque métallique de bande-annonce. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede wom 229 tk027 david ashton metal impact wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects film score orchestral trailer sound elements atmospheres effects main trailers strong tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) sound effects explosions metallic trailer hit. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21323" name="Fast Whip Reverb" code="WOM 229 tk062" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Un effet de bande-annonce." styleid="2" lengthseconds="9" time="0:09" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk062_FAST_WHIP_REVERB_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="62" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, PRINCIPAL, TRAILERS, FORT, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, SONS ÉLECTRONIQUES, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, LASERS, ZAPS, ELEMENTS SONORES, ELECTRONIQUE, ATMOSPHERES, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), SONS ELECTRONIQUES, ELEMENTS Un effet de bande-annonce. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede wom 229 tk062 david ashton fast whip reverb wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects film score orchestral trailer sound elements atmospheres effects main trailers strong tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds electronic sounds sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds lasers zaps trailer fx. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21278" name="Deep Wash" code="WOM 229 tk017" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Un effet de gong." styleid="2" lengthseconds="9" time="0:09" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk017_DEEP_WASH_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="17" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FORT, ÉPIQUE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), ETHNIQUE, PERCUSSION, GONG, PERCUSSION, GONGS, EFFETS SONORES, EXPLOSIONS, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, EPIQUE, ELEMENTS Un effet de gong. wom 229 tk017 david ashton deep wash wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects sound elements atmospheres effects main movies epic strong epic tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) ethnic percussion gong percussion gongs sound effects explosions gong effect. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21281" name="Gong Dream" code="WOM 229 tk020" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Un effet de gong." styleid="2" lengthseconds="9" time="0:09" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk020_GONG_DREAM_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="20" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, ÉLÉMENTS MUSICAUX, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, MAGIE, ILLUSIONS, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, ZEN, MÉDITATION , TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), ETHNIQUE, PERCUSSION, GONG, PERCUSSION, GONGS, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, ELEMENTS MUSICAUX, MEDITATION, ELEMENTS Un effet de gong. wom 229 tk020 david ashton gong dream wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres music elements main activities settings magic illusions peaceful dreamy peaceful zen meditation tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) ethnic percussion gong percussion gongs gong effect. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21316" name="Ethereal Swoosh" code="WOM 229 tk055" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Un léger swoosh." styleid="2" lengthseconds="9" time="0:09" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk055_ETHEREAL_SWOOSH_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="55" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, MAGIE, ILLUSIONS, TENDRE, LÉGER, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, SONS ÉLECTRONIQUES, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, LASERS, ZAPS, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, BALAYAGE, SOUFFLES, EFFETS SONORES, HORREUR, ELEMENTS SONORES, ELECTRONIQUE, ATMOSPHERES, LEGER, SONS ELECTRONIQUES, ELEMENTS Un léger swoosh. wom 229 tk055 david ashton ethereal swoosh wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects sound elements atmospheres effects main activities settings magic illusions tender light tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds electronic sounds sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds lasers zaps sound effects light swoosh. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21276" name="Super Boom" code="WOM 229 tk015" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Une attaque profonde de bande-annonce." styleid="2" lengthseconds="9" time="0:09" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk015_SUPER_BOOM_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="15" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, PRINCIPAL, TRAILERS, NEUTRE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), EFFETS SONORES, EXPLOSIONS, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ELEMENTS Une attaque profonde de bande-annonce. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede wom 229 tk015 david ashton super boom wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects film score orchestral trailer sound elements atmospheres effects main trailers neutral tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) sound effects explosions deep trailer hit. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21275" name="War Drums" code="WOM 229 tk014" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Une attaque profonde de bande-annonce." styleid="2" lengthseconds="8" time="0:08" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk014_WAR_DRUMS_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="14" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, PRINCIPAL, TRAILERS, NEUTRE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), EFFETS SONORES, EXPLOSIONS, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ELEMENTS Une attaque profonde de bande-annonce. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede wom 229 tk014 david ashton war drums wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects film score orchestral trailer sound elements atmospheres effects main trailers neutral tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) sound effects explosions deep trailer hit. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21262" name="Epic Destruction" code="WOM 229 tk001" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Une attaque épique de bande-annonce." styleid="2" lengthseconds="8" time="0:08" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk001_EPIC_DESTRUCTION_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FORT, ÉPIQUE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), EFFETS SONORES, EXPLOSIONS, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, EPIQUE, ELEMENTS Une attaque épique de bande-annonce. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede wom 229 tk001 david ashton epic destruction wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects film score orchestral trailer main movies epic strong epic tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) sound effects explosions epic trailer hit. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21273" name="Distant War" code="WOM 229 tk012" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Une attaque profonde de bande-annonce." styleid="2" lengthseconds="8" time="0:08" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk012_DISTANT_WAR_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, ÉLÉMENTS MUSICAUX, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, TRAILERS, NEUTRE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, ELEMENTS MUSICAUX, ELEMENTS Une attaque profonde de bande-annonce. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede wom 229 tk012 david ashton distant war wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres music elements film score orchestral trailer main trailers neutral tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) deep trailer hit. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21263" name="Strike of the Gods" code="WOM 229 tk002" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Une attaque épique de bande-annonce." styleid="2" lengthseconds="8" time="0:08" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk002_STRIKE_OF_THE_GODS_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, EFFETS SONORES, EXPLOSIONS, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, FORT, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, ÉPIQUE,, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), EPIQUE, ELEMENTS Une attaque épique de bande-annonce. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede wom 229 tk002 david ashton strike of the gods wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects sound effects explosions main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) film score orchestral trailer sound elements atmospheres effects strong epic movies epic epic trailer hit. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21290" name="Prison Door" code="WOM 229 tk029" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Une attaque métallique de bande-annonce." styleid="2" lengthseconds="8" time="0:08" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk029_PRISON_DOOR_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="29" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, PRINCIPAL, TRAILERS, FORT, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), EFFETS SONORES, PORTE, EFFETS SONORES, EXPLOSIONS, EFFETS SONORES, NATURE, TONNERRE, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), ELEMENTS Une attaque métallique de bande-annonce. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede wom 229 tk029 david ashton prison door wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects film score orchestral trailer sound elements atmospheres effects main trailers strong tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) sound effects door sound effects explosions sound effects nature thunder metallic trailer hit. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21282" name="Monster Crash" code="WOM 229 tk021" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Cymbale." styleid="2" lengthseconds="8" time="0:08" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk021_MONSTER_CRASH_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="21" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, PRINCIPAL, TRAILERS, FORT, FORT, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), PERCUSSION, CYMBALES, EFFETS SONORES, EXPLOSIONS, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), ELEMENTS Cymbale. wom 229 tk021 david ashton monster crash wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects sound elements atmospheres effects main trailers strong strong tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) percussion cymbals sound effects explosions cymbal. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21266" name="Hell's Orchestra" code="WOM 229 tk005" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Une attaque épique de bande-annonce." styleid="2" lengthseconds="7" time="0:07" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk005_HELL'S_ORCHESTRA_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, EFFETS SONORES, HORREUR, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, FORT, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, ÉPIQUE,, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), EPIQUE, ELEMENTS Une attaque épique de bande-annonce. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede wom 229 tk005 david ashton hell's orchestra wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects sound effects horror main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) film score orchestral trailer strong epic movies epic epic trailer hit. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21295" name="Knife Attack" code="WOM 229 tk034" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Une atmosphère sonore malsaine d'horreur." styleid="2" lengthseconds="7" time="0:07" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk034_KNIFE_ATTACK_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="34" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, EFFRAYANT, HORREUR, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), EFFETS SONORES, HORREUR, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), ELEMENTS Une atmosphère sonore malsaine d'horreur. wom 229 tk034 david ashton knife attack wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects sound elements atmospheres effects main movies horror thriller scary horror tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) sound effects horror twisted horror soundscape. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21267" name="Wall of Toms" code="WOM 229 tk006" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Une batterie épique de bande-annonce." styleid="2" lengthseconds="7" time="0:07" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk006_WALL_OF_TOMS_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="6" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, EFFETS SONORES, HORREUR, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, FORT, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, ÉPIQUE,, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), EPIQUE, ELEMENTS Une batterie épique de bande-annonce. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede wom 229 tk006 david ashton wall of toms wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects sound effects horror main tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) film score orchestral trailer sound elements atmospheres effects strong epic movies epic epic trailer drums. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21269" name="Gran Casa" code="WOM 229 tk008" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Une batterie épique de bande-annonce." styleid="2" lengthseconds="7" time="0:07" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk008_GRAN_CASA_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="8" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, EFFETS SONORES, HORREUR, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, FORT, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, ÉPIQUE,, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), EPIQUE, ELEMENTS Une batterie épique de bande-annonce. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede wom 229 tk008 david ashton gran casa wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects sound effects horror main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) film score orchestral trailer strong epic movies epic epic trailer drums. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21312" name="Zombie Swipe" code="WOM 229 tk051" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Un effet d'horreur." styleid="2" lengthseconds="7" time="0:07" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk051_ZOMBIE_SWIPE_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="51" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, EFFRAYANT, HORREUR, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, ÉLANCEMENT, EFFETS SONORES, ANIMATION, ÉVÈNEMENT, LIEU EN ARRIÈRE-PLAN, BATAILLE À L'ÉPÉE, EFFETS SONORES, HORREUR, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, IRREGULIER, EVENEMENT, ELANCEMENT, LIEU EN ARRIERE-PLAN, ELEMENTS, BATAILLE A L'EPEE Un effet d'horreur. wom 229 tk051 david ashton zombie swipe wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects sound elements atmospheres effects main movies horror thriller scary horror movement irregular stabbing sound effects background activity event location sword fight sound effects horror horror fx. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21270" name="Tribal Ensemble" code="WOM 229 tk009" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Une batterie épique de bande-annonce." styleid="2" lengthseconds="7" time="0:07" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk009_TRIBAL_ENSEMBLE_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, EFFETS SONORES, HORREUR, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, FORT, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, ÉPIQUE,, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), EPIQUE, ELEMENTS Une batterie épique de bande-annonce. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede wom 229 tk009 david ashton tribal ensemble wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects sound effects horror main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) film score orchestral trailer strong epic movies epic epic trailer drums. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21264" name="The Deity" code="WOM 229 tk003" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Une attaque épique de bande-annonce." styleid="2" lengthseconds="7" time="0:07" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk003_THE_DEITY_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, EFFETS SONORES, EXPLOSIONS, EFFETS SONORES, HORREUR, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, FORT, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, ÉPIQUE,, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), EPIQUE, ELEMENTS Une attaque épique de bande-annonce. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede wom 229 tk003 david ashton the deity wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects sound effects explosions sound effects horror main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) film score orchestral trailer strong epic movies epic epic trailer hit. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21283" name="Cymbal Attack" code="WOM 229 tk022" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Cymbale courte." styleid="2" lengthseconds="6" time="0:06" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk022_CYMBAL_ATTACK_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="22" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, ÉLÉMENTS MUSICAUX, PRINCIPAL, TRAILERS, FORT, FORT, PERCUSSION, CYMBALES, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, ELEMENTS MUSICAUX, ELEMENTS Cymbale courte. wom 229 tk022 david ashton cymbal attack wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres music elements main trailers strong strong percussion cymbals short cymbal. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21285" name="Short Reverse" code="WOM 229 tk024" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Un crescendo de cymbale court." styleid="2" lengthseconds="6" time="0:06" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk024_SHORT_REVERSE_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="24" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, PRINCIPAL, TRAILERS, FORT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PERCUSSION, CYMBALES, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ELEMENTS Un crescendo de cymbale court. wom 229 tk024 david ashton short reverse wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects main trailers strong tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) percussion cymbals short cymbal swell into hit. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21300" name="Fast Rise" code="WOM 229 tk039" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Des effets orchestraux." styleid="2" lengthseconds="6" time="0:06" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk039_FAST_RISE_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="39" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, EFFRAYANT, HORREUR, EFFETS SONORES, HORREUR, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, ELEMENTS Des effets orchestraux. wom 229 tk039 david ashton fast rise wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects sound elements atmospheres effects main movies horror thriller scary horror sound effects horror orchestral effects. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21319" name="Fast Swipe" code="WOM 229 tk058" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Un effet de bande-annonce." styleid="2" lengthseconds="6" time="0:06" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk058_FAST_SWIPE_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="58" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, PRINCIPAL, TRAILERS, FORT, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, LASERS, ZAPS, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, BALAYAGE, SOUFFLES, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, ELEMENTS Un effet de bande-annonce. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede wom 229 tk058 david ashton fast swipe wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects film score orchestral trailer sound elements atmospheres effects main trailers strong sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds lasers zaps sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds sweeps whooshes trailer fx. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21268" name="Taikos" code="WOM 229 tk007" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Une batterie épique de bande-annonce." styleid="2" lengthseconds="6" time="0:06" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk007_TAIKOS_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, EFFETS SONORES, HORREUR, ASIE, ASIE DE L'EST, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, FORT, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, ETHNIQUE, PERCUSSION, TAMBOUR TAIKO, BATTERIE,, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), EPIQUE, ELEMENTS Une batterie épique de bande-annonce. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede wom 229 tk007 david ashton taikos wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects sound effects horror asia east asia main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) film score orchestral trailer strong epic movies epic ethnic percussion taiko drum drums epic trailer drums. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21286" name="Sharp Cymbal" code="WOM 229 tk025" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Cymbale." styleid="2" lengthseconds="6" time="0:06" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk025_SHARP_CYMBAL_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="25" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, PRINCIPAL, TRAILERS, FORT, PERCUSSION, CYMBALES, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, ELEMENTS Cymbale. wom 229 tk025 david ashton sharp cymbal wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects main trailers strong percussion cymbals cymbal. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21311" name="Eye Driller" code="WOM 229 tk050" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Un effet d'horreur." styleid="2" lengthseconds="6" time="0:06" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk050_EYE_DRILLER_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="50" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, EFFRAYANT, HORREUR, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, ÉLANCEMENT, EFFETS SONORES, ANIMATION, ÉVÈNEMENT, LIEU EN ARRIÈRE-PLAN, BATAILLE À L'ÉPÉE, EFFETS SONORES, HORREUR, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, IRREGULIER, EVENEMENT, ELANCEMENT, LIEU EN ARRIERE-PLAN, ELEMENTS, BATAILLE A L'EPEE Un effet d'horreur. wom 229 tk050 david ashton eye driller wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects main movies horror thriller scary horror movement irregular stabbing sound effects background activity event location sword fight sound effects horror horror fx. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21291" name="Metal Attack" code="WOM 229 tk030" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Une attaque métallique légère de bande-annonce." styleid="2" lengthseconds="6" time="0:06" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk030_METAL_ATTACK_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="30" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, PRINCIPAL, TRAILERS, FORT, TENDRE, LÉGER, EFFETS SONORES, ANIMATION, ÉVÈNEMENT, LIEU EN ARRIÈRE-PLAN, BATAILLE À L'ÉPÉE, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, LEGER, EVENEMENT, LIEU EN ARRIERE-PLAN, ELEMENTS, BATAILLE A L'EPEE Une attaque métallique légère de bande-annonce. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede wom 229 tk030 david ashton metal attack wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects film score orchestral trailer sound elements atmospheres effects main trailers strong tender light sound effects background activity event location sword fight light metallic trailer hit. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21313" name="Electron Crossing" code="WOM 229 tk052" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Un effet électronique." styleid="2" lengthseconds="6" time="0:06" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk052_ELECTRON_CROSSING_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="52" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, PRINCIPAL, TRAILERS, TROUBLANT, DONNE LA CHAIR DE POULE, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, ÉLANCEMENT, EFFETS SONORES, ANIMATION, ÉVÈNEMENT, LIEU EN ARRIÈRE-PLAN, BATAILLE À L'ÉPÉE, EFFETS SONORES, HORREUR, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, IRREGULIER, EVENEMENT, ELANCEMENT, LIEU EN ARRIERE-PLAN, ELEMENTS, BATAILLE A L'EPEE Un effet électronique. wom 229 tk052 david ashton electron crossing wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects sound elements atmospheres effects main trailers disturbing spooky movement irregular stabbing sound effects background activity event location sword fight sound effects horror electronic fx. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21322" name="Fast Whip" code="WOM 229 tk061" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Un effet de bande-annonce." styleid="2" lengthseconds="6" time="0:06" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk061_FAST_WHIP_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="61" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, PRINCIPAL, TRAILERS, FORT, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, SONS ÉLECTRONIQUES, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, LASERS, ZAPS, ELEMENTS SONORES, ELECTRONIQUE, ATMOSPHERES, SONS ELECTRONIQUES, ELEMENTS Un effet de bande-annonce. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede wom 229 tk061 david ashton fast whip wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects film score orchestral trailer sound elements atmospheres effects main trailers strong sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds electronic sounds sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds lasers zaps trailer fx. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21317" name="Airy Swoosh" code="WOM 229 tk056" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Un léger swoosh." styleid="2" lengthseconds="6" time="0:06" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk056_AIRY_SWOOSH_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="56" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, MAGIE, ILLUSIONS, TENDRE, LÉGER, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, LASERS, ZAPS, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, BALAYAGE, SOUFFLES, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, LEGER, ELEMENTS Un léger swoosh. wom 229 tk056 david ashton airy swoosh wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects sound elements atmospheres effects main activities settings magic illusions tender light sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds lasers zaps sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds sweeps whooshes light swoosh. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21271" name="Timpani" code="WOM 229 tk010" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Une batterie épique de bande-annonce." styleid="2" lengthseconds="6" time="0:06" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk010_TIMPANI_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="10" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, ÉLÉMENTS MUSICAUX, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FORT, ÉPIQUE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), EPIQUE, ELEMENTS MUSICAUX, ELEMENTS Une batterie épique de bande-annonce. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede wom 229 tk010 david ashton timpani wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres music elements film score orchestral trailer main movies epic strong epic tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) epic trailer drums. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21320" name="Fast Swipe Reverb" code="WOM 229 tk059" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Un effet de bande-annonce." styleid="2" lengthseconds="6" time="0:06" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk059_FAST_SWIPE_REVERB_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="59" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, PRINCIPAL, TRAILERS, FORT, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, LASERS, ZAPS, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, BALAYAGE, SOUFFLES, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), ELEMENTS Un effet de bande-annonce. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede wom 229 tk059 david ashton fast swipe reverb wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects film score orchestral trailer sound elements atmospheres effects main trailers strong tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds lasers zaps sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds sweeps whooshes trailer fx. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21314" name="Electro Glitch" code="WOM 229 tk053" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Un effet électronique." styleid="2" lengthseconds="5" time="0:05" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk053_ELECTRO_GLITCH_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="53" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, PRINCIPAL, TRAILERS, DRAMATIQUE, VIOLENT, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, ÉLANCEMENT, EFFETS SONORES, ANIMATION, ÉVÈNEMENT, LIEU EN ARRIÈRE-PLAN, BATAILLE À L'ÉPÉE, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, SONS ÉLECTRONIQUES, EFFETS SONORES, HORREUR, ELEMENTS SONORES, ELECTRONIQUE, ATMOSPHERES, IRREGULIER, EVENEMENT, ELANCEMENT, LIEU EN ARRIERE-PLAN, SONS ELECTRONIQUES, ELEMENTS, BATAILLE A L'EPEE Un effet électronique. wom 229 tk053 david ashton electro glitch wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects sound elements atmospheres effects main trailers dramatic violent movement irregular stabbing sound effects background activity event location sword fight sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds electronic sounds sound effects horror electronic fx. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21265" name="Stake Through the Heart" code="WOM 229 tk004" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Une attaque épique de bande-annonce avec un aspect métallique." styleid="2" lengthseconds="5" time="0:05" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk004_STAKE_THROUGH_THE_HEART_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, EFFETS SONORES, HORREUR, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, FORT, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, ÉPIQUE,, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), EPIQUE, ELEMENTS Une attaque épique de bande-annonce avec un aspect métallique. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede wom 229 tk004 david ashton stake through the heart wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects sound effects horror main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) film score orchestral trailer strong epic movies epic epic trailer hit with metallic edge. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21289" name="Clashing Swords" code="WOM 229 tk028" libraryid="7" albumid="446" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Un effet métallique." styleid="2" lengthseconds="5" time="0:05" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_229_Reconstruction_-_Trailers/WOM229_trk028_CLASHING_SWORDS_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="28" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, PRINCIPAL, TRAILERS, FORT, EFFETS SONORES, ANIMATION, ÉVÈNEMENT, LIEU EN ARRIÈRE-PLAN, BATAILLE À L'ÉPÉE, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, EVENEMENT, LIEU EN ARRIERE-PLAN, ELEMENTS, BATAILLE A L'EPEE Un effet métallique. wom 229 tk028 david ashton clashing swords wom 229 reconstruction - trailers west one music trailer sound elements atmospheres effects sound elements atmospheres effects main trailers strong sound effects background activity event location sword fight metallic effect. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="1321" name="Submerged (d) (Hit 2)" code="FEM 021 tk176" libraryid="2" albumid="33" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_021_Soundesign_Vol_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Russell A. McKamey" comment="Hit simple pour action ou sci-fi." styleid="2" lengthseconds="2" time="0:02" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_021_Soundesign_Vol_2/FEM_021_trk176_SUBMERGED_(D)_(HIT_2)_Russell_A._McKamey_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="176" tracktotal="" search="SOUND DESIGN, TRAILER, ROCK, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, STING, FILMS, SCIENCE FICTION, TRAILERS, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, FORT, FORT, SOUND DESIGN, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, SONS ÉLECTRONIQUES, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, ESPACE, ELEMENTS SONORES, ELECTRONIQUE, ATMOSPHERES, INQUIETANT, SONS ELECTRONIQUES, ELEMENTS Hit simple pour action ou sci-fi. fem 021 tk176 russell a. mckamey submerged (d) (hit 2) fem 021 soundesign vol. 2 fired earth music trailer sound elements atmospheres sound design rock sound elements atmospheres effects sting movies science fiction trailers disturbing eerie strong strong sound design sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds electronic sounds sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds space simple action or sci-fi hit. sound effect" waveformpath="" version="Sound Effect" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284" /><item id="27670" name="The Big Story (d)" code="WOM 354 tk059" libraryid="7" albumid="585" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_354_24_Hour_News/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jay Price" comment="Business. Sting plein d'excitation pour actualités. Avec cordes énergiques et piano." styleid="30" lengthseconds="3" time="0:03" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_354_24_Hour_News/WOM_354_trk059_THE_BIG_STORY_(D)_Jay_Price_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="59" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, COMMUNICATION, ACTUALITÉS, ACTUALITES, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, PUISSANCE, ÉNERGIE, ENERGIE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, REVELER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, LIAISON, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, NOUVELLES BUSINESS, ACTUALITES, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, NOUVELLES LÉGÈRES, ACTUALITES, NOUVELLES LEGERES, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, BEDS POUR ACTUALITÉS, ACTUALITES, BEDS POUR ACTUALITES, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, TRAFIC, MÉTÉO, ACTUALITES, ETE, METEO, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, DETERMINE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, FORMATIONS GENERALES, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, CLAVIER, PIANO Business. Sting plein d'excitation pour actualités. Avec cordes énergiques et piano. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 354 tk059 jay price the big story (d) wom 354 24 hour news west one music news current affairs business corporate communication news business corporate beds business corporate bright optimistic business corporate motivational business corporate power energy business corporate reveal launch film score orchestral documentary link activities settings city urban business: exciting news sting with energetic strings and piano. link" waveformpath="" version="Link" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="28354" name="Cuban Calypso (f)" code="WOM 372 tk136" libraryid="7" albumid="598" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_372_Quirky_Vintage_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Paul Reeves (PRS)" comment="Calypso décontractée." styleid="8" lengthseconds="3" time="0:03" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_372_Quirky_Vintage_2/WOM_372_trk136_CUBAN_CALYPSO_(F)_Paul_Reeves_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="136" tracktotal="" search="JAZZ, JAZZ, JAZZ, BIG BAND, JAZZ, SWING, STING, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FETE, COCKTAIL, VACANCES, DE SAISON, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, ELEMENTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, ÉTÉ, ELEMENTS, ETE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, DECALE, HEUREUX, JOYEUX, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, FUN, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, PAISIBLE, NONCHALANT, PAISIBLE, LYRIQUE, PAISIBLE, DÉTENDU, DETENDU, PAISIBLE, TRANQUILLE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, MÉLODIQUE, LYRIQUE, MELODIQUE, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ENSEMBLE DE JAZZ, GROUPE DE JAZZ, FORMATIONS GENERALES, CUIVRES, TROMPETTE, CORNET, BOIS, CLARINETTE Calypso décontractée. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 372 tk136 paul reeves (prs) cuban calypso (f) wom 372 quirky vintage 2 west one music kitsch retro jazz jazz big band jazz swing sting activities settings party cocktail holiday seasonal nature wildlife the elements land sun tropical seaside nature wildlife the elements seasons time summer tv radio leisure lifestyle travel funny quirky happy cheerful happy easy-going calypso. sting dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="428434750" /><item id="1277" name="Siren of the Damned (r) (Robot Pulse 2)" code="FEM 021 tk132" libraryid="2" albumid="33" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_021_Soundesign_Vol_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Russell A. McKamey" comment="Pulsation métallique rapide." styleid="2" lengthseconds="3" time="0:03" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_021_Soundesign_Vol_2/FEM_021_trk132_SIREN_OF_THE_DAMNED_(R)_(ROBOT_PULSE_2)_Russell_A._McKamey_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="132" tracktotal="" search="SOUND DESIGN, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, STING, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, FILMS, SCIENCE FICTION, TRAILERS, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, EFFRAYANT, HORREUR, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, MÉCANIQUE, ROBOTIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, PULSATION, SOUND DESIGN, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, SONS ÉLECTRONIQUES, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, ESPACE, ELEMENTS SONORES, ELECTRONIQUE, ATMOSPHERES, MECANIQUE, INQUIETANT, SONS ELECTRONIQUES, ELEMENTS Pulsation métallique rapide. fem 021 tk132 russell a. mckamey siren of the damned (r) (robot pulse 2) fem 021 soundesign vol. 2 fired earth music trailer sound elements atmospheres sound design sound elements atmospheres effects sting activities settings futuristic movies science fiction trailers disturbing dark disturbing eerie scary horror scary ominous movement rhythmic mechanical robotic movement rhythmic pulsing fast metallic pulse. sound effect" waveformpath="" version="Sound Effect" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284" /><item id="28349" name="Mystery Cat (f)" code="WOM 372 tk131" libraryid="7" albumid="598" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_372_Quirky_Vintage_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Paul Reeves (PRS)" comment="Fanfaronnade onctueuse et sophistiquée." styleid="8" lengthseconds="3" time="0:03" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_372_Quirky_Vintage_2/WOM_372_trk131_MYSTERY_CAT_(F)_Paul_Reeves_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="131" tracktotal="" search="JAZZ, JAZZ, JAZZ, BIG BAND, JAZZ, SWING, STING, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FETE, COCKTAIL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FETE, HAUTE SOCIÉTÉ, HAUTE SOCIETE, SPECTACLE LIVE, THÉÂTRE, CABARET, THEATRE, SPECTACLE LIVE, THÉÂTRE, COMÉDIE MUSICALE, BROADWAY, THEATRE, COMEDIE, COMEDIE MUSICALE, FILMS, COMÉDIE, TARTE A LA CRÈME, COMEDIE, TARTE A LA CREME, FILMS, COMÉDIE MUSICALE, COMEDIE, COMEDIE MUSICALE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, HUMORISTIQUE, DROLE, ESPIÈGLE, ESPIEGLE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, DECALE, DROLE, FANTASQUE, HEUREUX, FUN, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, MÉLODIQUE, LYRIQUE, MELODIQUE, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ENSEMBLE DE JAZZ, GROUPE DE JAZZ, FORMATIONS GENERALES, CUIVRES, TROMPETTE, CORNET, BOIS, CLARINETTE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 20, PERIODE, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 20, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 30, PERIODE, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 30, STYLE VINTAGE Fanfaronnade onctueuse et sophistiquée. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 372 tk131 paul reeves (prs) mystery cat (f) wom 372 quirky vintage 2 west one music kitsch retro jazz jazz big band jazz swing sting activities settings party cocktail activities settings party upscale society live entertainment theater cabaret live entertainment theater musicals broadway movies comedy slapstick movies musical funny eccentric funny humorous funny smooth sophisticated swagger. sting dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel knees up, mess piano, cockney, east london, singalong, pub joanna, piano bar, piano-bar, live" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="428434750" /><item id="28356" name="Quirky Two Step (h)" code="WOM 372 tk138" libraryid="7" albumid="598" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_372_Quirky_Vintage_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Paul Reeves (PRS)" comment="Swing big band, gai et entrainant." styleid="8" lengthseconds="3" time="0:03" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_372_Quirky_Vintage_2/WOM_372_trk138_QUIRKY_TWO_STEP_(H)_Paul_Reeves_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="138" tracktotal="" search="JAZZ, JAZZ, JAZZ, BIG BAND, JAZZ, SWING, STING, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FETE, COCKTAIL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FETE, HAUTE SOCIÉTÉ, HAUTE SOCIETE, SPECTACLE LIVE, THÉÂTRE, CABARET, THEATRE, SPECTACLE LIVE, THÉÂTRE, COMÉDIE MUSICALE, BROADWAY, THEATRE, COMEDIE, COMEDIE MUSICALE, FILMS, COMÉDIE, TARTE A LA CRÈME, COMEDIE, TARTE A LA CREME, FILMS, COMÉDIE MUSICALE, COMEDIE, COMEDIE MUSICALE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, HUMORISTIQUE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, DECALE, DROLE, FANTASQUE, HEUREUX, BONDISSANT, HEUREUX, JOYEUX, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, GUILLERET, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, DETERMINE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, MÉLODIQUE, LYRIQUE, MELODIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, BONDISSANT, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ORCHESTRE DE DANSE TRADITIONNELLE, FORMATIONS GENERALES, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ENSEMBLE DE JAZZ, GROUPE DE JAZZ, FORMATIONS GENERALES, BOIS, CLARINETTE, DANSE DE SALON, CHARLESTON, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 20, PERIODE, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 20, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 30, PERIODE, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 30, STYLE VINTAGE Swing big band, gai et entrainant. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 372 tk138 paul reeves (prs) quirky two step (h) wom 372 quirky vintage 2 west one music kitsch retro jazz jazz big band jazz swing sting activities settings party cocktail activities settings party upscale society live entertainment theater cabaret live entertainment theater musicals broadway movies comedy slapstick movies musical funny eccentric funny humorous funny lively big-band swing. sting dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel knees up, mess piano, cockney, east london, singalong, pub joanna, piano bar, piano-bar, live" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="428434750" /><item id="28352" name="Sophisticated Ladies (f)" code="WOM 372 tk134" libraryid="7" albumid="598" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_372_Quirky_Vintage_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Paul Reeves (PRS)" comment="Swing big band plein de malice." styleid="8" lengthseconds="4" time="0:04" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_372_Quirky_Vintage_2/WOM_372_trk134_SOPHISTICATED_LADIES_(F)_Paul_Reeves_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="134" tracktotal="" search="JAZZ, JAZZ, JAZZ, BIG BAND, JAZZ, SWING, STING, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FETE, COCKTAIL, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FETE, HAUTE SOCIÉTÉ, HAUTE SOCIETE, SPECTACLE LIVE, THÉÂTRE, CABARET, THEATRE, SPECTACLE LIVE, THÉÂTRE, COMÉDIE MUSICALE, BROADWAY, THEATRE, COMEDIE, COMEDIE MUSICALE, SPECTACLE LIVE, THÉÂTRE, SE JOUER DE, ATTISER UNE RIVALITÉ, THEATRE, ATTISER UNE RIVALITE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, FILMS, COMÉDIE MUSICALE, COMEDIE, COMEDIE MUSICALE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, DECALE, DROLE, FANTASQUE, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, DETERMINE, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, ENERGIQUE, FORT, EXCITANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MÉLODIQUE, LYRIQUE, MELODIQUE, SOPHISTIQUÉ, CLASSE, SOPHISTIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, BONDISSANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ORCHESTRE DE DANSE TRADITIONNELLE, FORMATIONS GENERALES, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ENSEMBLE DE JAZZ, GROUPE DE JAZZ, FORMATIONS GENERALES, CUIVRES, TROMBONE, CUIVRES, TROMPETTE, CORNET, BATTERIE, BATTERIE, BATTERIE, TOMS, CLAVIER, PIANO, BOIS, CLARINETTE, BOIS, SAXOPHONE, DANSE DE SALON, QUICKSTEP, DANSE DE SALON, SWING, JITTERBUG, JIVE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 20, PERIODE, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 20, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 30, PERIODE, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 30, STYLE VINTAGE Swing big band plein de malice. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 372 tk134 paul reeves (prs) sophisticated ladies (f) wom 372 quirky vintage 2 west one music kitsch retro jazz jazz big band jazz swing sting activities settings party cocktail activities settings party upscale society live entertainment theater cabaret live entertainment theater musicals broadway live entertainment theater play on play off movies crime detective mystery cheeky big band swing. sting dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel knees up, mess piano, cockney, east london, singalong, pub joanna, piano bar, piano-bar, live" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="428434750" /><item id="1327" name="Submerged (j) (Pulse 1)" code="FEM 021 tk182" libraryid="2" albumid="33" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_021_Soundesign_Vol_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Russell A. McKamey" comment="Pulsation surnaturelle, inquiétante." styleid="2" lengthseconds="4" time="0:04" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_021_Soundesign_Vol_2/FEM_021_trk182_SUBMERGED_(J)_(PULSE_1)_Russell_A._McKamey_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="182" tracktotal="" search="SOUND DESIGN, TRAILER, ROCK, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, STING, FILMS, SCIENCE FICTION, TRAILERS, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, ÉTRANGE , TROUBLANT, BIZARRE, EFFRAYANT, FAIRE PEUR, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, SOUND DESIGN, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, SONS ÉLECTRONIQUES, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, ESPACE, ELEMENTS SONORES, ELECTRONIQUE, ATMOSPHERES, INQUIETANT, ETRANGE, SONS ELECTRONIQUES, ELEMENTS Pulsation surnaturelle, inquiétante. fem 021 tk182 russell a. mckamey submerged (j) (pulse 1) fem 021 soundesign vol. 2 fired earth music trailer sound elements atmospheres sound design rock sound elements atmospheres effects sting movies science fiction trailers disturbing eerie disturbing strange disturbing weird scary frightening scary ominous sound design sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds electronic sounds eerie supernatural pulse. sound effect" waveformpath="" version="Sound Effect" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284" /><item id="1249" name="Start Em Up (i) (Dub Synth Moan)" code="FEM 021 tk104" libraryid="2" albumid="33" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_021_Soundesign_Vol_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Russell A. McKamey" comment="Gémissement de synthé dub, pour sci-fi action." styleid="2" lengthseconds="4" time="0:04" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_021_Soundesign_Vol_2/FEM_021_trk104_START_EM_UP_(I)_(DUB_SYNTH_MOAN)_Russell_A._McKamey_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="104" tracktotal="" search="SOUND DESIGN, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, STING, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, FILMS, SCIENCE FICTION, TRAILERS, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, ÉTRANGE , TROUBLANT, BIZARRE, EFFRAYANT, HORREUR, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, EFFRAYANT, EFFRAYANT, SOUND DESIGN, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, SONS ÉLECTRONIQUES, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, ESPACE, ELEMENTS SONORES, ELECTRONIQUE, ATMOSPHERES, INQUIETANT, ETRANGE, SONS ELECTRONIQUES, ELEMENTS Gémissement de synthé dub, pour sci-fi action. fem 021 tk104 russell a. mckamey start em up (i) (dub synth moan) fem 021 soundesign vol. 2 fired earth music trailer sound elements atmospheres sound design sound elements atmospheres effects sting activities settings futuristic movies horror thriller movies science fiction trailers disturbing dark disturbing eerie disturbing strange disturbing weird scary horror scary ominous scary sci-fi action dub synth moan. sound effect" waveformpath="" version="Sound Effect" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284" /><item id="1298" name="The Super Race (d) (Hit 2)" code="FEM 021 tk153" libraryid="2" albumid="33" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_021_Soundesign_Vol_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Russell A. McKamey" comment="Hit sci-fi." styleid="2" lengthseconds="4" time="0:04" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_021_Soundesign_Vol_2/FEM_021_trk153_THE_SUPER_RACE_(D)_(HIT_2)_Russell_A._McKamey_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="153" tracktotal="" search="SOUND DESIGN, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, STING, TRAILERS, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, ÉTRANGE , TROUBLANT, BIZARRE, SOUND DESIGN, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, SONS ÉLECTRONIQUES, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, ESPACE, ELEMENTS SONORES, ELECTRONIQUE, ATMOSPHERES, INQUIETANT, ETRANGE, SONS ELECTRONIQUES, ELEMENTS Hit sci-fi. fem 021 tk153 russell a. mckamey the super race (d) (hit 2) fem 021 soundesign vol. 2 fired earth music trailer sound elements atmospheres sound design sound elements atmospheres effects sting trailers disturbing eerie disturbing strange disturbing weird sound design sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds electronic sounds sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds space sci-fi hit. sound effect" waveformpath="" version="Sound Effect" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284" /><item id="13560" name="Dig In (f)" code="WOM 054 tk085" libraryid="7" albumid="264" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_054_Jazznotes/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Henry Lowther / Ronnie Creviss" comment="Du free jazz frénétique avec une basse et une batterie qui groovent." styleid="19" lengthseconds="5" time="0:05" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_054_Jazznotes/WOM054_trk085_DIG_IN_(F)_Henry_Lowther_Ronnie_Creviss_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="85" tracktotal="" search="JAZZ, BEBOP, JAZZ, MODERN JAZZ, STING, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ENSEMBLE DE JAZZ, GROUPE DE JAZZ, CUIVRES, TROMPETTE, CORNET, BOIS, SAXOPHONE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, FORMATIONS GENERALES, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO) Du free jazz frénétique avec une basse et une batterie qui groovent. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 054 tk085 henry lowther ronnie creviss dig in (f) wom 054 jazznotes west one music jazz jazz bebop jazz modern jazz sting documentary biographical historical the arts happy upbeat tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) general lineups jazz ensemble jazz band brass trumpet cornet woodwinds saxophone time period modern era frenetic free jazz with grooving bass and drums. sting dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="30125" name="Secret Affairs (d)" code="WOM 359 tk078" libraryid="7" albumid="630" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_359_Modern_Dramedy/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Thomas Greenberg (PRS)" comment="Intrigue et enquete: amours clandestines. Avec vives guitares, celesta et beats hip-hop discrets. Pour dramedy." styleid="16" lengthseconds="5" time="0:05" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_359_Modern_Dramedy/WOM_359_trk078_SECRET_AFFAIRS_(D)_Thomas_Greenberg_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="78" tracktotal="" search="LATIN, HIP HOP, URBAIN, STING, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, CRIME, DƒTECTIVE, MYSTéRE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TƒLƒ RƒALITƒ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SITCOM, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SOAP OPERA, TELENOVELA, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, DROLE, ESPIéGLE, ESPIEGLE, DROLE, DƒCALƒ, DECALE, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, ENJOUƒ, ENJOUE, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, NEUTRE, TENDRE, LƒGER, LEGER, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, PIZZICATO, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, BATTERIE, BOITE Ë RYTHMES, BATTERIE ƒLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, CLAVIER, CELESTE, CLAVIER, PIANO, PERCUSSION, MARIMBA, CORDES, GUITARE, ƒLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE Intrigue et enquete: amours clandestines. Avec vives guitares, celesta et beats hip-hop discrets. Pour dramedy. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 359 tk078 thomas greenberg (prs) secret affairs (d) wom 359 modern dramedy west one music quirky latin sting neutral pizzicato documentary funny quirky happy bright tender light hip hop urban happy playful western piano tender romantic western celeste western marimba funny mischievous happy lighthearted disturbing mysterious western guitar electric movies intrigue &amp; investigation: surreptitious lovers. featuring bright guitars celeste and sparse hip hop beats. dramedy. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="428434750" /><item id="30127" name="Sneaking Around (d)" code="WOM 359 tk080" libraryid="7" albumid="630" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_359_Modern_Dramedy/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Thomas Greenberg (PRS)" comment="Intrigue et enquete: détective undercover. Guitares et célesta furtifs sont alliés à des beats hip-hop. Pour dramedy." styleid="16" lengthseconds="5" time="0:05" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_359_Modern_Dramedy/WOM_359_trk080_SNEAKING_AROUND_(D)_Thomas_Greenberg_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="80" tracktotal="" search="LATIN, HIP HOP, URBAIN, STING, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, CRIME, DƒTECTIVE, MYSTéRE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TƒLƒ RƒALITƒ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SITCOM, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SOAP OPERA, TELENOVELA, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, DROLE, ESPIéGLE, ESPIEGLE, DROLE, DƒCALƒ, DECALE, HEUREUX, ENJOUƒ, ENJOUE, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, NEUTRE, SƒRIEUX, SƒRIEUX, SERIEUX, TENDRE, LƒGER, LEGER, PIZZICATO, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, BATTERIE, BOITE Ë RYTHMES, BATTERIE ƒLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, CLAVIER, CELESTE, CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, GUITARE, ƒLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE Intrigue et enquete: détective undercover. Guitares et célesta furtifs sont alliés à des beats hip-hop. Pour dramedy. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 359 tk080 thomas greenberg (prs) sneaking around (d) wom 359 modern dramedy west one music quirky latin sting neutral pizzicato documentary funny quirky tender light hip hop urban happy playful western piano serious serious western celeste funny mischievous happy lighthearted disturbing mysterious western guitar electric movies detective mystery movement rhythmic intrigue &amp; investigation: undercover detective. covert guitars and celeste join with hip hop beats. dramedy. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="428434750" /><item id="15316" name="Goodbye Bavent (b)" code="WOM 091 tk040" libraryid="7" albumid="300" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_091_Electro_Rock/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Caspar John Valentine Kedros / Scott Doran" comment="Une étrangeté au tempo moyen, cool et lo-fi." styleid="6" lengthseconds="5" time="0:05" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_091_Electro_Rock/WOM091_trk040_GOODBYE_BAVENT_(B)_Caspar_John_Valentine_Kedros_Scott_Doran_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="40" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRO, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, LO-FI, POP, POP, SYNTH POP, ROCK, STING, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), GROUPE DE ROCK, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO) Une étrangeté au tempo moyen, cool et lo-fi. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 091 tk040 caspar john valentine kedros scott doran goodbye bavent (b) wom 091 electro rock west one music pop club electronica electro club electronica club electronica lo fi pop pop synth pop rock sting activities settings city urban human environment tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style uplifting positive tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) cool lo fi mid tempo quirky. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="1167" name="Panic Stations, Planet Earth (c) (Low Thriller Hit)" code="FEM 021 tk022" libraryid="2" albumid="33" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_021_Soundesign_Vol_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Russell A. McKamey" comment="Profond hit de thriller." styleid="2" lengthseconds="5" time="0:05" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_021_Soundesign_Vol_2/FEM_021_trk022_PANIC_STATIONS,_PLANET_EARTH_(C)_(LOW_THRILLER_HIT)_Russell_A._McKamey_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="22" tracktotal="" search="SOUND DESIGN, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, STING, TRAILERS, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, EFFRAYANT, EFFRAYANT, SOUND DESIGN, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, SONS ÉLECTRONIQUES, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, ESPACE, ELEMENTS SONORES, ELECTRONIQUE, ATMOSPHERES, INQUIETANT, SONS ELECTRONIQUES, ELEMENTS Profond hit de thriller. fem 021 tk022 russell a. mckamey panic stations planet earth (c) (low thriller hit) fem 021 soundesign vol. 2 fired earth music trailer sound elements atmospheres sound design sound elements atmospheres effects sting trailers disturbing dark disturbing eerie scary ominous scary scary sound design sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds electronic sounds sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds space deep thriller hit. sound effect" waveformpath="" version="Sound Effect" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284" /><item id="18788" name="25 to Life (c)" code="WOM 173 tk048" libraryid="7" albumid="387" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_173_Hip-Hop_Metal_Union/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Aaron Urquhart / Joachim Svare / Galileo Seven" comment="Un paysage sonore de hip hop urbain." styleid="29" lengthseconds="5" time="0:05" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_173_Hip-Hop_Metal_Union/WOM173_trk048_25_TO_LIFE_(C)_Aaron_Urquhart_Joachim_Svare_Galileo_Seven_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="48" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, LIAISON, TEMPO, 66 - 76 À L'AISE (ADAGIO), HIP HOP, URBAIN, HIP HOP, ROCK, NU METAL, ROCK, RAP ROCK, FORT, CONFIANT, TENDRE, SONGEUR, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, AGRESSIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, SPORT, SPORTS EXTREMES,, PERIODE, SERIEUX, 66 - 76 A L'AISE (ADAGIO), DETERMINE, ANNEES 2000, ANNEES 20 Un paysage sonore de hip hop urbain. wom 173 tk048 aaron urquhart joachim svare galileo seven 25 to life (c) wom 173 hip-hop metal union west one music hip-hop urban club electronica time period modern era 2000s link tempo 66 - 76 medium slow (adagio) hip hop urban hip hop rock nu metal rock rap rock strong confident tender reflective serious determined disturbing tense dramatic aggressive movement rhythmic driving movement rhythmic urban hip hop soundscape. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="30117" name="Playing it Cool (d)" code="WOM 359 tk070" libraryid="7" albumid="630" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_359_Modern_Dramedy/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Thomas Greenberg (PRS)" comment="Positif et entrainant: beats à la fois sexy et classe, avec guitares, celesta et glockenspiel. Pour dramedy." styleid="16" lengthseconds="5" time="0:05" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_359_Modern_Dramedy/WOM_359_trk070_PLAYING_IT_COOL_(D)_Thomas_Greenberg_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="70" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, INDIE, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HOUSE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FORMATION, INFORMATION, POP, POP, UNDERSCORE, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, DOCUMENTAIRE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TƒLƒ RƒALITƒ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SITCOM, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SOAP OPERA, TELENOVELA, DROLE, DƒCALƒ, DECALE, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, SEXY, COOL, SEXY, SEXY, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, ƒNERGIQUE, ENERGIQUE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, BONDISSANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, BATTERIE, BOITE Ë RYTHMES, BATTERIE ƒLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ƒLECTRONIQUES, ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ELECTRONIQUES, CLAVIER, CELESTE, PERCUSSION, MARIMBA, PERCUSSION, XYLOPHONE, GLOCKENSPIEL, CORDES, GUITARE, ƒLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE, CORDES, CORDES PIZZICATO Positif et entrainant: beats à la fois sexy et classe, avec guitares, celesta et glockenspiel. Pour dramedy. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 359 tk070 thomas greenberg (prs) playing it cool (d) wom 359 modern dramedy west one music quirky pop pop sexy cool sexy sexy rock indie underscore documentary happy happy tender warm funny quirky happy bright happy upbeat happy playful happy feel good western celeste western marimba strong confident strong energetic uplifting positive uplifting uplifting positive &amp; upbeat: sexy and stylish beats with guitars celeste and glockenspiel. dramedy. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="428434750" /><item id="18790" name="Stoney Watkins (c)" code="WOM 173 tk050" libraryid="7" albumid="387" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_173_Hip-Hop_Metal_Union/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Aaron Urquhart / Joachim Svare / Galileo Seven" comment="Un remix de rock hip hop." styleid="29" lengthseconds="5" time="0:05" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_173_Hip-Hop_Metal_Union/WOM173_trk050_STONEY_WATKINS_(C)_Aaron_Urquhart_Joachim_Svare_Galileo_Seven_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="50" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, NU METAL, LIAISON, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), FORT, CONFIANT, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, TROUBLANT, CRAINTIF, DRAMATIQUE, AGRESSIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, REMIX, TV, RADIO, SPORT, SPORT, SPORTS EXTREMES,, SERIEUX, DETERMINE Un remix de rock hip hop. wom 173 tk050 aaron urquhart joachim svare galileo seven stoney watkins (c) wom 173 hip-hop metal union west one music hip-hop urban rock nu metal link tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) strong confident serious determined disturbing fearful dramatic aggressive movement rhythmic driving movement rhythmic rugged remix tv radio sports sports extreme sports rock hip hop remix. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="11092" name="Push (b)" code="WOM 005 tk052" libraryid="7" albumid="215" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_005_Weekender_(Dance)/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Tom Ambler" comment="De l'action analogique massive." styleid="1" lengthseconds="5" time="0:05" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_005_Weekender_(Dance)/WOM005_trk052_PUSH_(B)_Tom_Ambler_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="52" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BIG BEAT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, STING, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ÉLECTRONIQUE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 90, ELECTRONIQUE, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEFILE DE MODE, ANNEES 2000, 20E SIECLE, DEFILE, ANNEES 20, ANNEES 90 De l'action analogique massive. wom 005 tk052 tom ambler push (b) wom 005 weekender (dance) west one music dance electro club electronica club electronica big beat club electronica breakbeat sting activities settings fashion show activities settings showbiz tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden happy upbeat tempo fat analogue action. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="1286" name="Ascendance (c) (Action Guitar Riff 1)" code="FEM 021 tk141" libraryid="2" albumid="33" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_021_Soundesign_Vol_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Russell A. McKamey" comment="Cool riff d'action." styleid="2" lengthseconds="5" time="0:05" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_021_Soundesign_Vol_2/FEM_021_trk141_ASCENDANCE_(C)_(ACTION_GUITAR_RIFF_1)_Russell_A._McKamey_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="141" tracktotal="" search="SOUND DESIGN, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, STING, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, TRAILERS, DRAMATIQUE, AGRESSIF, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, FORT, SOUND DESIGN, CORDES, GUITARE, DISTORSION, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, SONS ÉLECTRONIQUES, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, ESPACE, ELEMENTS SONORES, ELECTRONIQUE, ATMOSPHERES, DETERMINE, SONS ELECTRONIQUES, ELEMENTS Cool riff d'action. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz fem 021 tk141 russell a. mckamey ascendance (c) (action guitar riff 1) fem 021 soundesign vol. 2 fired earth music trailer sound elements atmospheres sound design sound elements atmospheres effects sting movies action adventure trailers dramatic aggressive strong determined strong strong sound design strings guitar distorted electric sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds electronic sounds cool action riff. sound effect" waveformpath="" version="Sound Effect" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284" /><item id="2847" name="Iron Horse (c)" code="NRF 017 tk032" libraryid="3" albumid="64" albumartpath="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_017_Troublemaker/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Mitchell Ray Marlow (SESAC)" comment="Rock nerveux plein de guitares et bourré d'attitude." styleid="5" lengthseconds="5" time="0:05" samplefile="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_017_Troublemaker/NRF_017_trk032_IRON_HORSE_(C)_Mitchell_Ray_Marlow_(SESAC)_Noise_Refinery.mp3" track="32" tracktotal="" search="BLUES, BLUES ROCK, ROCK, HARD ROCK, ROCK, ROCK, STING, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, BAR, BAR À COCKTAILS, RESTAURANT, RESTOROUTE, BAR DE BIKERS, BAR A COCKTAILS, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, ROAD TRIP, FILMS, ROAD MOVIE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, DRAMATIQUE, AGRESSIF, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, SEXY, COOL, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, COURAGEUX, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, DETERMINE, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, ENERGIQUE, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, FORT, COOL, NERVEUX, QUI A DU CRAN, MACHO, ARROGANCE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, GROUPE DE ROCK, BATTERIE, BATTERIE, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, AMERIQUE DU NORD, ETATS-UNIS Rock nerveux plein de guitares et bourré d'attitude. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live nrf 017 tk032 mitchell ray marlow (sesac) iron horse (c) nrf 017 troublemaker noise refinery rock rock band western drum kit dramatic aggressive dramatic intense sexy cool strong confident strong courageous strong determined strong energetic strong powerful strong strong activities &amp; settings roadhouse biker bar activities &amp; settings road trip movies road movie tv edgy guitar rock featuring a truckload of attitude. sting dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="Noise Refinery" cae="00719510644" /><item id="30115" name="Pick Me Up (d)" code="WOM 359 tk068" libraryid="7" albumid="630" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_359_Modern_Dramedy/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Thomas Greenberg (PRS)" comment="Positif et entrainant: enlevé, attrayant, avec synthés qui donnent la peche, guitares et beats urbains. Pour dramedy." styleid="16" lengthseconds="5" time="0:05" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_359_Modern_Dramedy/WOM_359_trk068_PICK_ME_UP_(D)_Thomas_Greenberg_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="68" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, INDIE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FORMATION, INFORMATION, POP, POP, STING, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, DOCUMENTAIRE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, SANTƒ, BIEN-æTRE, BIEN-ETRE, SANTE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TƒLƒ RƒALITƒ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SITCOM, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SOAP OPERA, TELENOVELA, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, FESTIF, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, SEXY, COOL, SEXY, SEXY, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, ƒNERGIQUE, ENERGIQUE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, BATTERIE, BOITE Ë RYTHMES, BATTERIE ƒLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ƒLECTRONIQUES, ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ELECTRONIQUES, CORDES, GUITARE, ƒLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE Positif et entrainant: enlevé, attrayant, avec synthés qui donnent la peche, guitares et beats urbains. Pour dramedy. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 359 tk068 thomas greenberg (prs) pick me up (d) wom 359 modern dramedy west one music quirky sting pop pop sexy cool sexy sexy rock indie documentary happy happy tender warm happy bright happy upbeat happy feel good strong confident strong energetic happy celebratory uplifting positive uplifting uplifting uplifting optimistic glamorous luxurious uplifting positive &amp; upbeat: upbeat and seductive with feelgood synths guitars and urban beats. dramedy. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="428434750" /><item id="30123" name="Dirty Secrets (d)" code="WOM 359 tk076" libraryid="7" albumid="630" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_359_Modern_Dramedy/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Thomas Greenberg (PRS)" comment="Intrigue et enquete: déplacements furtifs en ville. Des beats urbains se joignent à des guitares et des synthés. Pour dramedy." styleid="16" lengthseconds="5" time="0:05" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_359_Modern_Dramedy/WOM_359_trk076_DIRTY_SECRETS_(D)_Thomas_Greenberg_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="76" tracktotal="" search="HIP HOP, URBAIN, STING, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, CRIME, DƒTECTIVE, MYSTéRE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TƒLƒ RƒALITƒ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SITCOM, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SOAP OPERA, TELENOVELA, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, ESPIéGLE, ESPIEGLE, DROLE, DƒCALƒ, DECALE, SƒRIEUX, DƒTERMINƒ, SERIEUX, DETERMINE, SƒRIEUX, SƒRIEUX, SERIEUX, TENDRE, LƒGER, LEGER, PIZZICATO, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, BATTERIE, BOITE Ë RYTHMES, BATTERIE ƒLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, CORDES, GUITARE, ƒLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE Intrigue et enquete: déplacements furtifs en ville. Des beats urbains se joignent à des guitares et des synthés. Pour dramedy. wom 359 tk076 thomas greenberg (prs) dirty secrets (d) wom 359 modern dramedy west one music quirky sting pizzicato documentary funny quirky tender light funny comedic hip hop urban serious serious funny mischievous serious determined disturbing mysterious disturbing suspenseful western guitar electric movies detective mystery movement rhythmic stealthy tv intrigue &amp; investigation: sneaking around town. urban beats join with guitars and synths. dramedy. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="428434750" /><item id="27671" name="The Big Story (e)" code="WOM 354 tk060" libraryid="7" albumid="585" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_354_24_Hour_News/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jay Price" comment="Business. Sting plein d'excitation pour actualités. Avec cordes énergiques et piano." styleid="30" lengthseconds="5" time="0:05" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_354_24_Hour_News/WOM_354_trk060_THE_BIG_STORY_(E)_Jay_Price_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="60" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, COMMUNICATION, ACTUALITÉS, ACTUALITES, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, PUISSANCE, ÉNERGIE, ENERGIE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, REVELER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, LIAISON, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, NOUVELLES BUSINESS, ACTUALITES, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, NOUVELLES LÉGÈRES, ACTUALITES, NOUVELLES LEGERES, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, BEDS POUR ACTUALITÉS, ACTUALITES, BEDS POUR ACTUALITES, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, TRAFIC, MÉTÉO, ACTUALITES, ETE, METEO, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, DETERMINE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, FORMATIONS GENERALES, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, CLAVIER, PIANO Business. Sting plein d'excitation pour actualités. Avec cordes énergiques et piano. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 354 tk060 jay price the big story (e) wom 354 24 hour news west one music news current affairs business corporate communication news business corporate beds business corporate bright optimistic business corporate motivational business corporate power energy business corporate reveal launch film score orchestral documentary link activities settings city urban business: exciting news sting with energetic strings and piano. link" waveformpath="" version="Link" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="1356" name="Earth to Mars (q) (Bass Effect 2)" code="FEM 021 tk211" libraryid="2" albumid="33" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_021_Soundesign_Vol_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Russell A. McKamey" comment="Robuste effet de basse sci-fi." styleid="2" lengthseconds="5" time="0:05" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_021_Soundesign_Vol_2/FEM_021_trk211_EARTH_TO_MARS_(Q)_(BASS_EFFECT_2)_Russell_A._McKamey_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="211" tracktotal="" search="SOUND DESIGN, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, STING, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, FILMS, SCIENCE FICTION, TRAILERS, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, ÉTRANGE , TROUBLANT, BIZARRE, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, SOUND DESIGN, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, SONS ÉLECTRONIQUES, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, ESPACE, ELEMENTS SONORES, ELECTRONIQUE, ATMOSPHERES, INQUIETANT, ETRANGE, SONS ELECTRONIQUES, ELEMENTS Robuste effet de basse sci-fi. fem 021 tk211 russell a. mckamey earth to mars (q) (bass effect 2) fem 021 soundesign vol. 2 fired earth music trailer sound elements atmospheres sound design sound elements atmospheres effects sting activities settings futuristic movies science fiction trailers disturbing eerie disturbing strange disturbing weird scary ominous sound design sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds tough sci-fi bass effect. sound effect" waveformpath="" version="Sound Effect" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284" /><item id="13559" name="Dig In (e)" code="WOM 054 tk084" libraryid="7" albumid="264" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_054_Jazznotes/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Henry Lowther / Ronnie Creviss" comment="Du free jazz frénétique avec une basse et une batterie qui groovent." styleid="19" lengthseconds="5" time="0:05" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_054_Jazznotes/WOM054_trk084_DIG_IN_(E)_Henry_Lowther_Ronnie_Creviss_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="84" tracktotal="" search="JAZZ, BEBOP, JAZZ, MODERN JAZZ, STING, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ENSEMBLE DE JAZZ, GROUPE DE JAZZ, CUIVRES, TROMPETTE, CORNET, BOIS, SAXOPHONE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, FORMATIONS GENERALES, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO) Du free jazz frénétique avec une basse et une batterie qui groovent. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 054 tk084 henry lowther ronnie creviss dig in (e) wom 054 jazznotes west one music jazz jazz bebop jazz modern jazz sting documentary biographical historical the arts happy upbeat tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) general lineups jazz ensemble jazz band brass trumpet cornet woodwinds saxophone time period modern era frenetic free jazz with grooving bass and drums. sting dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="28351" name="Un Petit Baiser (h)" code="WOM 372 tk133" libraryid="7" albumid="598" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_372_Quirky_Vintage_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Paul Reeves (PRS)" comment="Chanson française douce et innocente." styleid="8" lengthseconds="6" time="0:06" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_372_Quirky_Vintage_2/WOM_372_trk133_UN_PETIT_BAISER_(H)_Paul_Reeves_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="133" tracktotal="" search="JAZZ, JAZZ, JAZZ, SWING, STING, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FETE, HAUTE SOCIÉTÉ, HAUTE SOCIETE, FILMS, ANIMATION, FILMS, IDYLLE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, DECALE, DROLE, FANTASQUE, HEUREUX, BONDISSANT, HEUREUX, JOYEUX, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, FUN, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, GUILLERET, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, TENDRE, INNOCENT, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, TENDRE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, MÉLODIQUE, LYRIQUE, MELODIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, BONDISSANT, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ENSEMBLE DE JAZZ, GROUPE DE JAZZ, FORMATIONS GENERALES, CLAVIER, ACCORDÉON, CONCERTINA, ACCORDEON, BOIS, CLARINETTE, BOIS, SAXOPHONE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 20, PERIODE, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 20, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 30, PERIODE, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 30, STYLE VINTAGE, AVEC PAROLES Chanson française douce et innocente. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 372 tk133 paul reeves (prs) un petit baiser (h) wom 372 quirky vintage 2 west one music kitsch retro jazz jazz swing sting activities settings party upscale society movies animation movies romance funny eccentric funny quirky funny whimsical happy bouncy happy cheerful happy feel good happy fun happy happy happy perky happy playful happy upbeat tender innocent sweet innocent french song. sting dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="428434750" /><item id="18442" name="Busy Build" code="WOM 166 tk037" libraryid="7" albumid="379" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_166_Immersion/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jared Nathan Sweetman / Paul James Borg" comment="Une ponctuation de design sonore." styleid="13" lengthseconds="6" time="0:06" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_166_Immersion/WOM166_trk037_BUSY_BUILD_Jared_Nathan_Sweetman_Paul_James_Borg_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="37" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, SOUND DESIGN, CLASSIQUE, STYLE MINIMALISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, ESPACE, INTERSIDÉRAL, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, AUTOMATISATION, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, AMBIANCES ET FONDS SONORES POUR PROJETS, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, ATMOSPHÈRE SCIENTIFIQUE, TROUBLANT, ÉTRANGE , TROUBLANT, BIZARRE, TEMPO, 66 - 76 À L'AISE (ADAGIO), SOUND DESIGN, EFFETS SONORES, SIFFLEMENT, CRÉPITEMENT, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 66 - 76 A L'AISE (ADAGIO), ETRANGE, CREPITEMENT, ELEMENTS, ATMOSPHERE SCIENTIFIQUE, INTERSIDERAL Une ponctuation de design sonore. wom 166 tk037 jared nathan sweetman paul james borg busy build wom 166 immersion west one music atmospheres sound elements atmospheres sound design classical minimalist style business corporate science technology sound elements atmospheres main documentary science technology nature wildlife the elements sky space outer space science technology industry automation science sound design sting. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="28484" name="Candy Kicks (d)" code="WOM 378 tk079" libraryid="7" albumid="600" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_378_Dive_Bar_Rock/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jez Miller (PRS)" comment="Sting d'indie rock garage palpitant." styleid="5" lengthseconds="6" time="0:06" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_378_Dive_Bar_Rock/WOM_378_trk079_CANDY_KICKS_(D)_Jez_Miller_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="79" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, ROCK, ROCK, GARAGE ROCK, ROCK, INDIE, STING, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, BAR, BAR À COCKTAILS, RESTAURANT, RESTOROUTE, BAR DE BIKERS, BAR A COCKTAILS, FILMS, ROAD MOVIE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, PRÉ-ADOLESCENTS, PRE-ADOLESCENT, PRE-ADOLESCENTS, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, HEUREUX, BRUYANT, HEUREUX, BONDISSANT, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, FESTIF, HEUREUX, EXCITÉ, EXCITE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, FUN, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, DETERMINE, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, ENERGIQUE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, IMPLACABLE, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, GROUPE DE ROCK, BATTERIE, BATTERIE, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE Sting d'indie rock garage palpitant. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 378 tk079 jez miller (prs) candy kicks (d) wom 378 dive bar rock west one music rock rock garage rock indie sting bar roadhouse biker bar movies road movie tv radio children youth tv tweens reality tv sports happy boisterous bouncy bright celebratory excited feel good fun upbeat strong confident determined energetic exciting powerful relentless exciting garage indie rock sting. sting dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="30109" name="Hit the Strip (d)" code="WOM 359 tk062" libraryid="7" albumid="630" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_359_Modern_Dramedy/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Thomas Greenberg (PRS)" comment="Positif et entrainant: sexy et sur de soi avec guitares qui crissent et synthés. Pour dramedy." styleid="16" lengthseconds="6" time="0:06" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_359_Modern_Dramedy/WOM_359_trk062_HIT_THE_STRIP_(D)_Thomas_Greenberg_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="62" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, INDIE, HIP HOP, URBAIN, HIP HOP, STING, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, DOCUMENTAIRE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TƒLƒ RƒALITƒ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SITCOM, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SOAP OPERA, TELENOVELA, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, SEXY, COOL, SEXY, SEXY, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DƒTERMINƒ, DETERMINE, FORT, ƒNERGIQUE, ENERGIQUE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MACHO, ARROGANCE, BATTERIE, BOITE Ë RYTHMES, BATTERIE ƒLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ƒLECTRONIQUES, ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ELECTRONIQUES, CORDES, GUITARE, ƒLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE Positif et entrainant: sexy et sur de soi avec guitares qui crissent et synthés. Pour dramedy. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 359 tk062 thomas greenberg (prs) hit the strip (d) wom 359 modern dramedy west one music quirky sting sexy cool sexy sexy rock indie documentary happy upbeat strong strong macho swagger strong exciting strong confident strong energetic strong determined uplifting positive glamorous luxurious hip hop urban hip hop western guitar electric activities &amp; settings positive &amp; upbeat: sexy and confident with crunchy guitars and synths. dramedy. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="428434750" /><item id="18792" name="Thug Paradise (c)" code="WOM 173 tk052" libraryid="7" albumid="387" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_173_Hip-Hop_Metal_Union/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Aaron Urquhart / Joachim Svare / Galileo Seven" comment="Des rythmes lourds avec des beats graves et denses." styleid="29" lengthseconds="6" time="0:06" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_173_Hip-Hop_Metal_Union/WOM173_trk052_THUG_PARADISE_(C)_Aaron_Urquhart_Joachim_Svare_Galileo_Seven_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="52" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, NU METAL, LIAISON, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ROCK, RAP ROCK, FORT, CONFIANT, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, DRAMATIQUE, AGRESSIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, SPORT, SPORTS EXTREMES,, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETERMINE Des rythmes lourds avec des beats graves et denses. wom 173 tk052 aaron urquhart joachim svare galileo seven thug paradise (c) wom 173 hip-hop metal union west one music hip-hop urban rock nu metal link tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) rock rap rock strong confident serious determined dramatic aggressive movement rhythmic driving movement rhythmic rugged tv radio sports sports extreme sports heavy downbeat grooves. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="27678" name="World of Smiles (d)" code="WOM 354 tk067" libraryid="7" albumid="585" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_354_24_Hour_News/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jay Price" comment="Voyage! Sting pour un voyage de reve, avec piano positif et sons électroniques." styleid="30" lengthseconds="6" time="0:06" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_354_24_Hour_News/WOM_354_trk067_WORLD_OF_SMILES_(D)_Jay_Price_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="67" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FORMATION, INFORMATION, LIAISON, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, ELEMENTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, SOLEIL, CHALEUR, ELEMENTS, ETE, METEO, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, SANTÉ, BIEN-ÊTRE, BIEN-ETRE, SANTE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, NOUVELLES LÉGÈRES, ACTUALITES, NOUVELLES LEGERES, PAISIBLE, CALME, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, NONCHALANT, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, DÉTENDU, DETENDU, PAISIBLE, APAISANT, PAISIBLE, SPIRITUEL, PAISIBLE, ZEN, MÉDITATION, MEDITATION, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, LÉGER, LEGER, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, CLAVIER, PIANO Voyage! Sting pour un voyage de reve, avec piano positif et sons électroniques. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 354 tk067 jay price world of smiles (d) wom 354 24 hour news west one music news current affairs business corporate luxury business corporate beds business corporate training information link business corporate nature wildlife the elements land sun tropical seaside nature wildlife the elements weather sun heat tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio travel: aspirational travel sting with positive piano and electronics. link" waveformpath="" version="Link" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="14248" name="Pick Up and Get Ready (c)" code="WOM 066 tk063" libraryid="7" albumid="276" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_066_Modern_Lifestyle/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Camrin Brown" comment="Un groove funk, 70's et contagieux." styleid="12" lengthseconds="6" time="0:06" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_066_Modern_Lifestyle/WOM066_trk063_PICK_UP_AND_GET_READY_(C)_Camrin_Brown_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="63" tracktotal="" search="JAZZ, JAZZ FUNK, ROCK, FUNK ROCK, STING, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CUIVRES, SECTION DE CUIVRES, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 70, PERIODE, DEFILE DE MODE, 20E SIECLE, DEFILE, ANNEES 70 Un groove funk, 70's et contagieux. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 066 tk063 camrin brown pick up and get ready (c) wom 066 modern lifestyle west one music corporate business jazz jazz funk rock funk rock sting activities settings fashion show tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style happy feel good tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) brass brass section time period modern era 20th century 1970s infectious 70s funk groove. sting dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="29073" name="Cute Corner (d)" code="WOM 391 tk105" libraryid="7" albumid="610" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_391_Something_Simple_Acoustic/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Thomas Greenberg (PRS)" comment="Sting positif et encourageant." styleid="16" lengthseconds="6" time="0:06" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_391_Something_Simple_Acoustic/WOM_391_trk105_CUTE_CORNER_(D)_Thomas_Greenberg_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="105" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, ENFANTS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BUSINESS, POP CORPORATE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, POP, POP POUR ENFANTS, STING, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, ENFANTS, MATERNELLE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VACANCES, DE SAISON, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, SANTÉ, BIEN-ÊTRE, BIEN-ETRE, SANTE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, JOURNEE, HEUREUX, BONDISSANT, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, FESTIF, HEUREUX, JOYEUX, HEUREUX, EXCITÉ, EXCITE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, JOYEUX, HEUREUX, ENJOUÉ, ENJOUE, HEUREUX, GUILLERET, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, INNOCENT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, ACOUSTIQUE, ENFANTIN, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, BONDISSANT, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ACOUSTIQUE, FORMATIONS GENERALES, BATTERIE, BATTERIE, CLAVIER, PIANO, PERCUSSION, XYLOPHONE, GLOCKENSPIEL, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN MÉTAL, CORDES EN METAL, CORDES, UKULELE, EFFETS SONORES, HUMAIN, APPLAUDISSEMENTS Sting positif et encourageant. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 391 tk105 thomas greenberg (prs) cute corner (d) wom 391 something simple acoustic west one music quirky general lineups acoustic western drum kit western piano western xylophone glockenspiel western guitar acoustic steel string western ukulele happy bouncy happy bright happy celebratory happy cheerful happy excited happy feel good happy happy happy joyous happy positive and uplifting sting. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="14470" name="Hey Camboso Roll (c)" code="WOM 072 tk050" libraryid="7" albumid="281" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_072_Essential_R&amp;B/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Mr Camboso" comment="Des beats entraînants et fluides roulent sous des basses retentissantes et des guitares synthés." styleid="31" lengthseconds="6" time="0:06" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_072_Essential_R&amp;B/WOM072_trk050_HEY_CAMBOSO_ROLL_(C)_Mr_Camboso_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="50" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, R &amp; B CLASSIQUE, HIP HOP, URBAIN, HIP HOP, POP, R&amp;B CONTEMPORAIN, POP, STING, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, HOLLYWOOD, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, HEUREUX, JOYEUX, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ÉLECTRONIQUE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 90, ELECTRONIQUE, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEFILE DE MODE, ANNEES 2000, 20E SIECLE, DEFILE, ANNEES 20, ANNEES 90 Des beats entraînants et fluides roulent sous des basses retentissantes et des guitares synthés. wom 072 tk050 mr camboso hey camboso roll (c) wom 072 essential r&amp;b west one music r&amp;b soul club electronica funk soul r&amp;b classic r&amp;b hip hop urban hip hop pop contemporary r&amp;b pop sting activities settings city urban human environment activities settings fashion show activities settings showbiz hollywood tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio rolling head nodding beats and synth guitars. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="2359" name="Antithesis (c)" code="NRF 007 tk032" libraryid="3" albumid="52" albumartpath="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_007_Radio_Ready/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Dan Diaz" comment="Groove indie rock nerveux avec des touches de dubstep." styleid="5" lengthseconds="6" time="0:06" samplefile="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_007_Radio_Ready/NRF_007_trk032_ANTITHESIS_(C)_Dan_Diaz_Noise_Refinery.mp3" track="32" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, GROUPE DE ROCK, STING, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, DUB, ROCK, ROCK ALTERNATIF, ROCK, INDIE, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EMBLÉMATIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, COOL, NERVEUX, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, JEUX VIDÉOS, SPORT, SPORTS EXTREMES, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, JEUX VIDEOS, DETERMINE, EMBLEMATIQUE, ELECTRIQUE Groove indie rock nerveux avec des touches de dubstep. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz nrf 007 tk032 dan diaz antithesis (c) nrf 007 radio ready noise refinery rock rock rock band sting club electronica dub rock alternative rock rock indie strong confident strong determined strong powerful strong strong uplifting anthemic uplifting motivational movement rhythmic driving cool edgy activities settings city urban human environment edgy indie rock groove with dubstep elements. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="Noise Refinery" cae="00719510644" /><item id="14687" name="Come Together (e)" code="WOM 076 tk059" libraryid="7" albumid="285" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_076_Feelgood_Light_Pop/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Clifford Eric Haywood / Thomas Garrad-Cole" comment="De la pop rock vive et enjouée." styleid="12" lengthseconds="6" time="0:06" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_076_Feelgood_Light_Pop/WOM076_trk059_COME_TOGETHER_(E)_Clifford_Eric_Haywood_Thomas_Garrad-Cole_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="59" tracktotal="" search="POP, POP, PRÉ-ADOLESCENT, RELIGIEUX, CHRÉTIEN, PROTESTANT, CHANSONS GOSPEL, NEGRO SPIRITUALS, STING, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, SOLEIL, CHALEUR, TV, RADIO, JEU, QUIZZ, SPECTACLE DE VARIÉTÉS, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), GROUPE DE ROCK, CORDES, GUITARE, BOTTLENECK, SLIDE, PRE-ADOLESCENT, CHRETIEN, ELEMENTS, METEO, SPECTACLE DE VARIETES, ETE De la pop rock vive et enjouée. wom 076 tk059 clifford eric haywood thomas garrad-cole come together (e) wom 076 feelgood light pop west one music corporate business pop pop tween religious christian protestant gospel songs spirituals sting nature wildlife the elements land sun tropical seaside nature wildlife the elements weather sun heat tv radio game quiz variety show tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden happy bright n breezy pop rock. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="29115" name="Feeling True (d)" code="WOM 391 tk147" libraryid="7" albumid="610" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_391_Something_Simple_Acoustic/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Thomas Greenberg (PRS)" comment="Sting plein d'émotion et de nostalgie." styleid="16" lengthseconds="6" time="0:06" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_391_Something_Simple_Acoustic/WOM_391_trk147_FEELING_TRUE_(D)_Thomas_Greenberg_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="147" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, ENFANTS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, STING, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, ENFANTS, MATERNELLE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VACANCES, DE SAISON, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, SANTÉ, BIEN-ÊTRE, BIEN-ETRE, SANTE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, JOURNEE, HEUREUX, VIF, PAISIBLE, CALME, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, APAISANT, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, INNOCENT, TENDRE, AFFECTUEUX, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TENDRE, TENDRE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, ACOUSTIQUE, ENFANTIN, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, BONDISSANT, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ACOUSTIQUE, FORMATIONS GENERALES, CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN MÉTAL, CORDES EN METAL, CORDES, UKULELE Sting plein d'émotion et de nostalgie. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 391 tk147 thomas greenberg (prs) feeling true (d) wom 391 something simple acoustic west one music quirky general lineups acoustic western piano western guitar acoustic steel string western ukulele happy bright peaceful calm peaceful contented peaceful peaceful peaceful soothing tender hopeful tender innocent tender loving tender nostalgic tender romantic tender emotive and nostalgic sting. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="2366" name="The Price We Pay (c)" code="NRF 007 tk039" libraryid="3" albumid="52" albumartpath="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_007_Radio_Ready/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Siddhartha Menon, Mitchell R. Marlow" comment="Indie rock plein de caractère, avec une sensation de retour aux années 80." styleid="5" lengthseconds="6" time="0:06" samplefile="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_007_Radio_Ready/NRF_007_trk039_THE_PRICE_WE_PAY_(C)_Siddhartha_Menon,_Mitchell_R._Marlow_Noise_Refinery.mp3" track="39" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, GROUPE DE ROCK, STING, ROCK, ROCK ALTERNATIF, ROCK, INDIE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, FUN, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EMBLÉMATIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, COOL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, JEUX VIDÉOS, SPORT, SPORTS EXTREMES, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, JEUX VIDEOS, ENERGIQUE, EMBLEMATIQUE, ELECTRIQUE Indie rock plein de caractère, avec une sensation de retour aux années 80. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live nrf 007 tk039 siddhartha menon mitchell r. marlow the price we pay (c) nrf 007 radio ready noise refinery rock rock rock band sting rock alternative rock rock indie happy feel good happy fun happy upbeat strong energetic strong strong uplifting anthemic uplifting positive uplifting uplifting movement rhythmic driving cool activities settings city urban human environment vibey indie rock with retro throwback 80s feel. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="Noise Refinery" cae="00719510644" /><item id="2853" name="Broken Highway (c)" code="NRF 017 tk038" libraryid="3" albumid="64" albumartpath="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_017_Troublemaker/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Mitchell Ray Marlow (SESAC)" comment="Blues rock grincheux." styleid="5" lengthseconds="6" time="0:06" samplefile="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_017_Troublemaker/NRF_017_trk038_BROKEN_HIGHWAY_(C)_Mitchell_Ray_Marlow_(SESAC)_Noise_Refinery.mp3" track="38" tracktotal="" search="BLUES, BLUES ROCK, ROCK, HARD ROCK, ROCK, ROCK, STING, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, BAR, BAR À COCKTAILS, RESTAURANT, RESTOROUTE, BAR DE BIKERS, BAR A COCKTAILS, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, ROAD TRIP, FILMS, ROAD MOVIE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, NUIT, PAISIBLE, INTROSPECTIF, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, MÉLANCOLIE, DEPRIMANT, MELANCOLIE, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, SERIEUX, SÉRIEUX, ATTENTIONNÉ, SERIEUX, ATTENTIONNE, SEXY, COOL, TENDRE, SONGEUR, COOL, NERVEUX, QUI A DU CRAN, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, GROUPE DE ROCK, BATTERIE, BATTERIE, CLAVIER, ORGUE, ÉLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN MÉTAL, CORDES EN METAL, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, AMERIQUE DU NORD, ETATS-UNIS Blues rock grincheux. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live nrf 017 tk038 mitchell ray marlow (sesac) broken highway (c) nrf 017 troublemaker noise refinery rock rock band western drum kit western organ electric western guitar acoustic steel string peaceful introspective sad depressing melancholy serious serious serious thoughtful sexy cool tender reflective activities &amp; settings roadhouse biker bar activities &amp; settings road trip moody blues rock. sting dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="Noise Refinery" cae="00719510644" /><item id="14481" name="U the New Original (c)" code="WOM 072 tk061" libraryid="7" albumid="281" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_072_Essential_R&amp;B/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="P La Flava" comment="Des beats de hip hop old school qui swinguent." styleid="31" lengthseconds="6" time="0:06" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_072_Essential_R&amp;B/WOM072_trk061_U_THE_NEW_ORIGINAL_(C)_P_La_Flava_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="61" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, HIP HOP, URBAIN, HIP HOP, POP, STING, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, FETE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, SEXY, COOL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), ÉLECTRONIQUE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 80, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 90, ELECTRONIQUE, PERIODE, ANNEES 2000, 20E SIECLE, TELE REALITE, ANNEES 20, ANNEES 80, ANNEES 90 Des beats de hip hop old school qui swinguent. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 072 tk061 p la flava u the new original (c) wom 072 essential r&amp;b west one music r&amp;b soul club electronica funk soul r&amp;b hip hop urban hip hop pop sting activities settings city urban human environment activities settings party activities settings showbiz tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio reality tv sexy cool tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) old school hip hop swing beats. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="2319" name="My Girl (c)" code="NRF 009 tk033" libraryid="3" albumid="51" albumartpath="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_009_Spring_Break/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Siddhartha Menon" comment="Pop rock inoubliable, avec guitare." styleid="5" lengthseconds="6" time="0:06" samplefile="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_009_Spring_Break/NRF_009_trk033_MY_GIRL_(C)_Siddhartha_Menon_Noise_Refinery.mp3" track="33" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, ROCK, POP, POP, STING, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FETE, SOIRÉE, SOIREE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, PRÉ-ADOLESCENTS, PRE-ADOLESCENT, PRE-ADOLESCENTS, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, FUN, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, ENERGIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EMBLÉMATIQUE, EMBLEMATIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, GROUPE DE ROCK, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE Pop rock inoubliable, avec guitare. nrf 009 tk033 siddhartha menon my girl (c) nrf 009 spring break noise refinery rock rock pop sting activities settings city urban human environment activities settings party house party tv radio children youth tv tweens tv radio reality tv happy bright happy fun happy upbeat strong energetic uplifting anthemic uplifting motivational uplifting super-anthemic pop rock featuring guitar. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="Noise Refinery" cae="00719510644" /><item id="12326" name="Trickster (b)" code="WOM 031 tk055" libraryid="7" albumid="241" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_031_Attitude/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Steve Ruff" comment="Un beat break ambient et profond." styleid="29" lengthseconds="6" time="0:06" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_031_Attitude/WOM031_trk055_TRICKSTER_(B)_Steve_Ruff_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="55" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BIG BEAT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CHEMICAL BEATS, STING, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, ABSTRAIT, ABSTRAIT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ÉLECTRONIQUE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, ELECTRONIQUE, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ANNEES 2000, ANNEES 20 Un beat break ambient et profond. wom 031 tk055 steve ruff trickster (b) wom 031 attitude west one music hip-hop urban club electronica club electronica big beat club electronica breakbeat club electronica chemical beats sting activities settings city urban human environment activities settings futuristic business corporate documentary science technology science technology industry deep ambient break beat. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="28451" name="Flame Grilled (d)" code="WOM 378 tk046" libraryid="7" albumid="600" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_378_Dive_Bar_Rock/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jez Miller (PRS)" comment="Sting de thrash rock bourré d'adrénaline." styleid="5" lengthseconds="6" time="0:06" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_378_Dive_Bar_Rock/WOM_378_trk046_FLAME_GRILLED_(D)_Jez_Miller_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="46" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, ROCK, ROCK, ROCK CLASSIQUE, ROCK, PUNK METAL, ROCK, SPEED METAL, TRASH METAL, STING, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, BAR, BAR À COCKTAILS, RESTAURANT, RESTOROUTE, BAR DE BIKERS, BAR A COCKTAILS, FILMS, ROAD MOVIE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, DRAMATIQUE, AGRESSIF, DRAMATIQUE, DANGEUREUX, DRAMATIQUE, FOUGUEUX, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, HEUREUX, BRUYANT, HEUREUX, EXCITÉ, EXCITE, HEUREUX, FUN, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, SEXY, COCHON, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, DETERMINE, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, ENERGIQUE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, IMPLACABLE, FORT, FORT, MACHO, ARROGANCE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, GROUPE DE ROCK, BATTERIE, BATTERIE, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE Sting de thrash rock bourré d'adrénaline. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 378 tk046 jez miller (prs) flame grilled (d) wom 378 dive bar rock west one music rock rock classic rock punk metal speed metal thrash metal sting bar roadhouse biker bar movies road movie tv radio reality tv sports dramatic aggressive dangerous fiery intense happy boisterous excited fun upbeat sexy sleazy strong confident determined energetic exciting adrenalized thrash rock sting. sting dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="27674" name="Celebrity Culture (d)" code="WOM 354 tk063" libraryid="7" albumid="585" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_354_24_Hour_News/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jay Price" comment="Divertissement. Sting showbiz pour actualités avec cuivres funky et scratch." styleid="30" lengthseconds="6" time="0:06" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_354_24_Hour_News/WOM_354_trk063_CELEBRITY_CULTURE_(D)_Jay_Price_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="63" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, COMMUNICATION, ACTUALITÉS, ACTUALITES, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BUSINESS, POP CORPORATE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, REVELER, KITSCH, RETRO, KITSCH, CHEESY, LIAISON, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, DETERMINE, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, ENERGIQUE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, FORT, FORT, TRIOMPHAL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, CUIVRES, SECTION DE CUIVRES, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, FORMATIONS GENERALES, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, CLAVIER, PIANO Divertissement. Sting showbiz pour actualités avec cuivres funky et scratch. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 354 tk063 jay price celebrity culture (d) wom 354 24 hour news west one music news current affairs business corporate communication news business corporate bright optimistic business corporate corporate pop business corporate luxury business corporate motivational business corporate reveal launch kitsch retro cheesy link activities settings city urban entertainment: showbiz news sting with funky brass and dj scratches. link" waveformpath="" version="Link" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="30129" name="Eccentric Ways (d)" code="WOM 359 tk082" libraryid="7" albumid="630" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_359_Modern_Dramedy/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Thomas Greenberg (PRS)" comment="Intrigue et enquete: furtivité et discrétion. Guitares simples et piano avec beats électroniques dans un style militaire. Pour dramedy." styleid="16" lengthseconds="6" time="0:06" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_359_Modern_Dramedy/WOM_359_trk082_ECCENTRIC_WAYS_(D)_Thomas_Greenberg_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="82" tracktotal="" search="LATIN, HIP HOP, URBAIN, STING, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, CRIME, DƒTECTIVE, MYSTéRE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TƒLƒ RƒALITƒ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SITCOM, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SOAP OPERA, TELENOVELA, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, ESPIéGLE, ESPIEGLE, DROLE, DƒCALƒ, DECALE, HEUREUX, ENJOUƒ, ENJOUE, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, NEUTRE, SƒRIEUX, SƒRIEUX, SERIEUX, TENDRE, LƒGER, LEGER, PIZZICATO, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, BATTERIE, BOITE Ë RYTHMES, BATTERIE ƒLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, GUITARE, ƒLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE Intrigue et enquete: furtivité et discrétion. Guitares simples et piano avec beats électroniques dans un style militaire. Pour dramedy. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 359 tk082 thomas greenberg (prs) eccentric ways (d) wom 359 modern dramedy west one music quirky latin sting neutral pizzicato documentary funny quirky tender light hip hop urban funny comedic happy playful western piano funny eccentric serious serious funny mischievous happy lighthearted disturbing mysterious western guitar electric movies detective mystery intrigue &amp; investigation: sneaky and stealthy. simple guitars and piano with electronic military-style beats. dramedy. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="428434750" /><item id="1288" name="Ascendance (e) (Scream Synth)" code="FEM 021 tk143" libraryid="2" albumid="33" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_021_Soundesign_Vol_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Russell A. McKamey" comment="Effet au synthé: hurlement sci-fi." styleid="2" lengthseconds="6" time="0:06" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_021_Soundesign_Vol_2/FEM_021_trk143_ASCENDANCE_(E)_(SCREAM_SYNTH)_Russell_A._McKamey_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="143" tracktotal="" search="SOUND DESIGN, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, STING, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, TRAILERS, DRAMATIQUE, AGRESSIF, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, FORT, SOUND DESIGN, CORDES, GUITARE, DISTORSION, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, SONS ÉLECTRONIQUES, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, ESPACE, EFFETS SONORES, HUMAIN, HURLEMENT, ELEMENTS SONORES, ELECTRONIQUE, ATMOSPHERES, DETERMINE, SONS ELECTRONIQUES, ELEMENTS Effet au synthé: hurlement sci-fi. fem 021 tk143 russell a. mckamey ascendance (e) (scream synth) fem 021 soundesign vol. 2 fired earth music trailer sound elements atmospheres sound design sound elements atmospheres effects sting movies action adventure trailers dramatic aggressive strong determined strong strong sound design strings guitar distorted electric sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds electronic sounds screaming sci-fi synth effect. sound effect" waveformpath="" version="Sound Effect" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284" /><item id="2852" name="Vigilante (c)" code="NRF 017 tk037" libraryid="3" albumid="64" albumartpath="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_017_Troublemaker/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Robert Anthony Navarro (ASCAP)" comment="Rock de biker je-m'en-foutiste et explosif, avec un effet shuffle." styleid="5" lengthseconds="6" time="0:06" samplefile="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_017_Troublemaker/NRF_017_trk037_VIGILANTE_(C)_Robert_Anthony_Navarro_(ASCAP)_Noise_Refinery.mp3" track="37" tracktotal="" search="BLUES, BLUES ROCK, ROCK, ROCK, STING, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, BAR, BAR À COCKTAILS, RESTAURANT, RESTOROUTE, BAR DE BIKERS, BAR A COCKTAILS, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, ROAD TRIP, FILMS, ROAD MOVIE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, NUIT, DRAMATIQUE, FOUGUEUX, SEXY, COOL, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, COURAGEUX, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, DETERMINE, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, ENERGIQUE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, IMPLACABLE, FORT, FORT, COOL, NERVEUX, QUI A DU CRAN, MACHO, ARROGANCE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, TRAINER LES PIEDS, GROUPE DE ROCK, BATTERIE, BATTERIE, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, AMERIQUE DU NORD, ETATS-UNIS Rock de biker je-m'en-foutiste et explosif, avec un effet shuffle. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live nrf 017 tk037 robert anthony navarro (ascap) vigilante (c) nrf 017 troublemaker noise refinery rock rock band western drum kit dramatic fiery sexy cool strong confident strong courageous strong determined strong energetic strong exciting strong relentless strong strong activities &amp; settings roadhouse biker bar activities &amp; settings road trip movies road movie tv high-octane devil-may-care motorcycle rock with shuffle feel. sting dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="Noise Refinery" cae="00719510644" /><item id="27665" name="Big Society (d)" code="WOM 354 tk054" libraryid="7" albumid="585" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_354_24_Hour_News/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jay Price" comment="Politique. Sting sérieux et dramatique pour actualités. Avec orchestre live." styleid="30" lengthseconds="7" time="0:07" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_354_24_Hour_News/WOM_354_trk054_BIG_SOCIETY_(D)_Jay_Price_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="54" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, COMMUNICATION, ACTUALITÉS, ACTUALITES, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, PRESTIGE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, LIAISON, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, FLASH INFO, BULLETIN, ACTUALITES, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, BEDS POUR ACTUALITÉS, ACTUALITES, BEDS POUR ACTUALITES, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, POLITIQUE, ACTUALITES, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, DRAMATIQUE, PASSIONNÉ, PASSIONNE, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, SERIEUX, DETERMINE, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, SERIEUX, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, DETERMINE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, FORT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, FORMATIONS GENERALES, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, CLAVIER, PIANO Politique. Sting sérieux et dramatique pour actualités. Avec orchestre live. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 354 tk054 jay price big society (d) wom 354 24 hour news west one music news current affairs business corporate communication news business corporate motivational business corporate prestige film score orchestral documentary link activities settings city urban human environment business corporate science technology industry tv radio news and current affairs politics: serious and dramatic news sting featuring live orchestra. link knees up, mess piano, cockney, east london, singalong, pub joanna, piano bar, piano-bar, live" waveformpath="" version="Link" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="27666" name="Great Debate (d)" code="WOM 354 tk055" libraryid="7" albumid="585" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_354_24_Hour_News/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jay Price" comment="Politique. Sting intellectuel pour actualités avec piano et cordes puissantes." styleid="30" lengthseconds="7" time="0:07" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_354_24_Hour_News/WOM_354_trk055_GREAT_DEBATE_(D)_Jay_Price_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="55" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, COMMUNICATION, ACTUALITÉS, ACTUALITES, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, PUISSANCE, ÉNERGIE, ENERGIE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, LIAISON, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, FLASH INFO, BULLETIN, ACTUALITES, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, NOUVELLES BUSINESS, ACTUALITES, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, JOURNALISME D'INVESTIGATION, ACTUALITES, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, BEDS POUR ACTUALITÉS, ACTUALITES, BEDS POUR ACTUALITES, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, POLITIQUE, ACTUALITES, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, DRAMATIQUE, PASSIONNÉ, PASSIONNE, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, SERIEUX, DETERMINE, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, SERIEUX, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, DETERMINE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, IMPLACABLE, FORT, FORT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, FORMATIONS GENERALES, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, CLAVIER, PIANO Politique. Sting intellectuel pour actualités avec piano et cordes puissantes. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 354 tk055 jay price great debate (d) wom 354 24 hour news west one music news current affairs business corporate communication news business corporate motivational business corporate power energy film score orchestral documentary link activities settings city urban human environment business corporate science technology industry tv radio news and current affairs politics: intellectual news sting with piano and driving strings. link" waveformpath="" version="Link" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="2854" name="Thicker Than Water (c)" code="NRF 017 tk039" libraryid="3" albumid="64" albumartpath="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_017_Troublemaker/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Mitchell Ray Marlow (SESAC)" comment="Rock plein de guitares. Tempo moyen." styleid="5" lengthseconds="7" time="0:07" samplefile="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_017_Troublemaker/NRF_017_trk039_THICKER_THAN_WATER_(C)_Mitchell_Ray_Marlow_(SESAC)_Noise_Refinery.mp3" track="39" tracktotal="" search="BLUES, BLUES ROCK, ROCK, HARD ROCK, ROCK, ROCK, ROCK, ROCK SUDISTE, STING, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, BAR, BAR À COCKTAILS, RESTAURANT, RESTOROUTE, BAR DE BIKERS, BAR A COCKTAILS, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, ROAD TRIP, FILMS, ROAD MOVIE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, NUIT, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, SERIEUX, DETERMINE, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, SERIEUX, SEXY, COOL, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, FORT, COOL, NERVEUX, QUI A DU CRAN, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, GROUPE DE ROCK, BATTERIE, BATTERIE, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, AMERIQUE DU NORD, ETATS-UNIS Rock plein de guitares. Tempo moyen. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live nrf 017 tk039 mitchell ray marlow (sesac) thicker than water (c) nrf 017 troublemaker noise refinery rock rock band western drum kit western guitar electric dramatic intense serious determined serious serious sexy cool strong confident strong strong activities &amp; settings roadhouse biker bar activities &amp; settings road trip movies road movie tv radio program formats sports tv medium tempo guitar rock. sting dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="Noise Refinery" cae="00719510644" /><item id="2719" name="Twilight Lullaby (c)" code="NRF 015 tk032" libraryid="3" albumid="61" albumartpath="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_015_Shadow_Substance/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Robert Anthony Navarro (ASCAP)" comment="Valse de cirque évocatrice." styleid="3" lengthseconds="7" time="0:07" samplefile="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_015_Shadow_Substance/NRF_015_trk032_TWILIGHT_LULLABY_(C)_Robert_Anthony_Navarro_(ASCAP)_Noise_Refinery.mp3" track="32" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, POP, POP, ROCK, INDIE, ROCK, ROCK, STING, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, ROAD TRIP, FILMS, FILMS INDÉPENDANTS, FILMS INDEPENDANTS, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, PAISIBLE, NONCHALANT, PAISIBLE, DÉTENDU, DETENDU, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, GROUPE DE ROCK Valse de cirque évocatrice. nrf 015 tk032 robert anthony navarro (ascap) twilight lullaby (c) nrf 015 shadow &amp; substance noise refinery film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral documentary pop rock indie rock sting activities settings city urban human environment activities settings road trip movies indie films tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden tv radio leisure lifestyle gentle impressionistic nocturne featuring dulcitone and backwards textures. sting delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="Noise Refinery" cae="00719510644" /><item id="1239" name="We Are Not Alone (h) (sci-fi Bass Drop)" code="FEM 021 tk094" libraryid="2" albumid="33" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_021_Soundesign_Vol_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Russell A. McKamey" comment="Drop de basse sci-fi." styleid="2" lengthseconds="7" time="0:07" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_021_Soundesign_Vol_2/FEM_021_trk094_WE_ARE_NOT_ALONE_(H)_(SCI-FI_BASS_DROP)_Russell_A._McKamey_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="94" tracktotal="" search="SOUND DESIGN, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, STING, TRAILERS, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, EFFRAYANT, EFFRAYANT, CHUTE, DESCENTE, SOUND DESIGN, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, SONS ÉLECTRONIQUES, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, ESPACE, ELEMENTS SONORES, ELECTRONIQUE, ATMOSPHERES, INQUIETANT, SONS ELECTRONIQUES, ELEMENTS Drop de basse sci-fi. fem 021 tk094 russell a. mckamey we are not alone (h) (sci-fi bass drop) fem 021 soundesign vol. 2 fired earth music trailer sound elements atmospheres sound design sound elements atmospheres effects sting trailers disturbing dark disturbing eerie scary ominous scary scary falling descending sound design sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds electronic sounds sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds sci-fi bass drop. sound effect" waveformpath="" version="Sound Effect" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284" /><item id="11524" name="U Go First (e)" code="WOM 014 tk062" libraryid="7" albumid="224" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_014_Refresh/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Matthew Cang" comment="Du funk ensoleillé et paresseux." styleid="12" lengthseconds="7" time="0:07" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_014_Refresh/WOM014_trk062_U_GO_FIRST_(E)_Matthew_Cang_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="62" tracktotal="" search="POP, STING, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, JAM BAND, FORMATIONS GENERALES, JOURNEE Du funk ensoleillé et paresseux. wom 014 tk062 matthew cang u go first (e) wom 014 refresh west one music corporate business pop sting business corporate tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden tv radio talkshow entertainment daytime happy feel good uplifting positive tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) general lineups jam band lazy sunshine funk. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="30093" name="Trouble in Paradise (d)" code="WOM 359 tk046" libraryid="7" albumid="630" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_359_Modern_Dramedy/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Thomas Greenberg (PRS)" comment="Excentrique et malicieux: guitares décalées avec beats bizzarres, percussions et piano. Pour dramedy." styleid="16" lengthseconds="7" time="0:07" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_359_Modern_Dramedy/WOM_359_trk046_TROUBLE_IN_PARADISE_(D)_Thomas_Greenberg_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="46" tracktotal="" search="HIP HOP, URBAIN, STING, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, DOCUMENTAIRE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TƒLƒ RƒALITƒ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SITCOM, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SOAP OPERA, TELENOVELA, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, ESPIéGLE, ESPIEGLE, DROLE, DƒCALƒ, DECALE, HEUREUX, ENJOUƒ, ENJOUE, HEUREUX, GUILLERET, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, SEXY, COOL, SEXY, CHARMEUR, SEXY, SEXY, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, FORT, COOL, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, PIZZICATO, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, FURTIF, BATTERIE, BOITE Ë RYTHMES, BATTERIE ƒLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, BOITE A RYTHMES, BATTERIE ELECTRONIQUE, CLAVIER, PIANO, AUTRE, INHABITUEL, PERCUSSION CORPORELLE, CORDES, GUITARE, ƒLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE Excentrique et malicieux: guitares décalées avec beats bizzarres, percussions et piano. Pour dramedy. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 359 tk046 thomas greenberg (prs) trouble in paradise (d) wom 359 modern dramedy west one music quirky cool sting sexy cool sexy sexy pizzicato happy perky documentary funny quirky hip hop urban western piano funny comedic happy playful strong strong funny eccentric sexy flirtatious strong confident funny mischievous happy lighthearted glamorous luxurious western mischievous &amp; oddball: off-the-wall guitars meet quirky beats percussion and piano. dramedy. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="428434750" /><item id="14474" name="Action Clip 2 Blaze (d)" code="WOM 072 tk054" libraryid="7" albumid="281" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_072_Essential_R&amp;B/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Mr Camboso" comment="Des cuivres lourds et gonflés à bloc avec un gros beat rock solide." styleid="31" lengthseconds="7" time="0:07" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_072_Essential_R&amp;B/WOM072_trk054_ACTION_CLIP_2_BLAZE_(D)_Mr_Camboso_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="54" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, R &amp; B CLASSIQUE, HIP HOP, URBAIN, HIP HOP, POP, R&amp;B CONTEMPORAIN, STING, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, FORT, ÉPIQUE, FORT, FORT, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), ÉLECTRONIQUE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 90, ELECTRONIQUE, PERIODE, EPIQUE, ANNEES 2000, 20E SIECLE, DETECTIVE, ANNEES 20, ANNEES 90, MYSTERE Des cuivres lourds et gonflés à bloc avec un gros beat rock solide. wom 072 tk054 mr camboso action clip 2 blaze (d) wom 072 essential r&amp;b west one music r&amp;b soul club electronica funk soul r&amp;b classic r&amp;b hip hop urban hip hop pop contemporary r&amp;b sting activities settings city urban human environment movies action drama movies crime detective mystery movies espionage spy movies horror thriller strong epic strong strong tempo heavyweight pumping brass with a rock solid fat beat. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="14471" name="Twistin' Like U Know (c)" code="WOM 072 tk051" libraryid="7" albumid="281" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_072_Essential_R&amp;B/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Camrin Brown" comment="Du R&amp;B pétillant et de la pop Soul." styleid="31" lengthseconds="7" time="0:07" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_072_Essential_R&amp;B/WOM072_trk051_TWISTIN'_LIKE_U_KNOW_(C)_Camrin_Brown_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="51" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, R &amp; B CLASSIQUE, POP, R&amp;B CONTEMPORAIN, POP, STING, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, FETE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, ÉTINCELANT, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), ÉLECTRONIQUE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, ELECTRONIQUE, PERIODE, ETINCELANT, ANNEES 2000, TELE REALITE, ANNEES 20 Du R&amp;B pétillant et de la pop Soul. wom 072 tk051 camrin brown twistin' like u know (c) wom 072 essential r&amp;b west one music r&amp;b soul club electronica funk soul r&amp;b classic r&amp;b pop contemporary r&amp;b pop sting activities settings party tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio reality tv happy feel good sparkling tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) electronic time period modern era 2000s sparkling r&amp;b and soul pop. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="2803" name="Bisou Bisou (c)" code="NRF 010 tk037" libraryid="3" albumid="63" albumartpath="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_010_Push/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Chani Krich (ASCAP) / Nathan Beale (ASCAP)" comment="Jazz décalé hyper relax avec guitares, céleste, theremin et percussion." styleid="6" lengthseconds="7" time="0:07" samplefile="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_010_Push/NRF_010_trk037_BISOU_BISOU_(C)_Chani_Krich_(ASCAP)_Nathan_Beale_(ASCAP)_Noise_Refinery.mp3" track="37" tracktotal="" search="JAZZ, JAZZ, EASY LISTENING, LOUNGE, STING, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, BAR, BAR À COCKTAILS, RESTAURANT, BAR À COCKTAILS, BAR, BAR A COCKTAILS, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, FILMS, IDYLLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, DROLE, MANIÉRÉ, MANIERE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, DECALE, HEUREUX, FUN, HEUREUX, ENJOUÉ, ENJOUE, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, SEXY, CHARMEUR, SEXY, GRIVOIS, SEXY, SÉDUISANT, SEDUISANT, SEXY, SENSUEL, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, AFFECTUEUX, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, TRAINER LES PIEDS, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, TRIO JAZZ, FORMATIONS GENERALES, INSTRUMENTS ÉLECTRONIQUES, THEREMIN, ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ELECTRONIQUES, CLAVIER, CELESTE, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN NYLON Jazz décalé hyper relax avec guitares, céleste, theremin et percussion. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live nrf 010 tk037 chani krich (ascap) nathan beale (ascap) bisou bisou (c) nrf 010 push noise refinery pop jazz easy listening lounge sting activities settings bar cocktail lounge restaurant cocktail lounge bar activities settings city urban human environment movies romance tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio quirky laid-back jazz with guitars celesta theramin and percussion. link dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Link" publisher="Noise Refinery" cae="00719510644" /><item id="2361" name="Tomorrowland (c)" code="NRF 007 tk034" libraryid="3" albumid="52" albumartpath="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_007_Radio_Ready/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Robert Navarro" comment="Indie rock positif avec guitares reveuses." styleid="5" lengthseconds="7" time="0:07" samplefile="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_007_Radio_Ready/NRF_007_trk034_TOMORROWLAND_(C)_Robert_Navarro_Noise_Refinery.mp3" track="34" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, GROUPE DE ROCK, STING, POP, ROCK, ROCK ALTERNATIF, ROCK, INDIE, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, FUN, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EMBLÉMATIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, COOL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, ROAD TRIP, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, ENERGIQUE, EMBLEMATIQUE, ELECTRIQUE Indie rock positif avec guitares reveuses. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz nrf 007 tk034 robert navarro tomorrowland (c) nrf 007 radio ready noise refinery rock rock rock band sting pop rock alternative rock rock indie happy bright happy feel good happy fun happy upbeat strong energetic strong strong uplifting anthemic uplifting positive uplifting uplifting movement rhythmic driving cool activities settings road trip tv positive indie rock with dreamy guitars. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="Noise Refinery" cae="00719510644" /><item id="29077" name="Travel Happy (d)" code="WOM 391 tk109" libraryid="7" albumid="610" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_391_Something_Simple_Acoustic/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Thomas Greenberg (PRS)" comment="Sting positif et encourageant." styleid="16" lengthseconds="7" time="0:07" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_391_Something_Simple_Acoustic/WOM_391_trk109_TRAVEL_HAPPY_(D)_Thomas_Greenberg_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="109" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, ENFANTS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BUSINESS, POP CORPORATE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, POP, POP POUR ENFANTS, STING, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, ENFANTS, MATERNELLE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VACANCES, DE SAISON, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, SANTÉ, BIEN-ÊTRE, BIEN-ETRE, SANTE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, JOURNEE, HEUREUX, BONDISSANT, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, FESTIF, HEUREUX, JOYEUX, HEUREUX, EXCITÉ, EXCITE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, JOYEUX, HEUREUX, ENJOUÉ, ENJOUE, HEUREUX, GUILLERET, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, INNOCENT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, ACOUSTIQUE, ENFANTIN, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, BONDISSANT, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ACOUSTIQUE, FORMATIONS GENERALES, BATTERIE, BATTERIE, CLAVIER, PIANO, PERCUSSION, XYLOPHONE, GLOCKENSPIEL, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN MÉTAL, CORDES EN METAL, CORDES, UKULELE, EFFETS SONORES, HUMAIN, APPLAUDISSEMENTS Sting positif et encourageant. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 391 tk109 thomas greenberg (prs) travel happy (d) wom 391 something simple acoustic west one music quirky general lineups acoustic western drum kit western piano western xylophone glockenspiel western guitar acoustic steel string western ukulele happy bouncy happy bright happy celebratory happy cheerful happy excited happy feel good happy happy happy joyous happy positive and uplifting sting. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="13267" name="Reach for the Stars (b)" code="WOM 049 tk042" libraryid="7" albumid="259" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_049_USA/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Daryl Neil Alexander Griffith" comment="Une fermeture grandiose en fanfare." styleid="18" lengthseconds="7" time="0:07" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_049_USA/WOM049_trk042_REACH_FOR_THE_STARS_(B)_Daryl_Neil_Alexander_Griffith_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="42" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, STING, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, PATRIOTIQUE, FORT EN ÉMOTIONS, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, AMERIQUE DU NORD, FORT EN EMOTIONS, ETATS-UNIS, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ELEMENTS Une fermeture grandiose en fanfare. wom 049 tk042 daryl neil alexander griffith reach for the stars (b) wom 049 usa west one music world film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic sting movies fantasy adventure nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama trailers trailer track uplifting patriotic sweeping tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) grand closing fanfare. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="28630" name="Hipster (d)" code="WOM 181A tk046" libraryid="7" albumid="602" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_181A_The_Lifestyle_Lounge/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Joachim Svare (ASCAP) / Galileo Seven (ASCAP) / Kim S. Hansen (BMI)" comment="Du lounge 60’s stylé fusionné avec des breaks modernes et des cuivres fatals." styleid="12" lengthseconds="7" time="0:07" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_181A_The_Lifestyle_Lounge/WOM_181A_trk046_HIPSTER_(D)_Joachim_Svare_(ASCAP)_Galileo_Seven_(ASCAP)_Kim_S._Hansen_(BMI)_West_One_Musi.mp3" track="46" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BIG BEAT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, LIQUID FUNK, JAZZ, JAZZ FUNK, STING, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, BAR, BAR À COCKTAILS, RESTAURANT, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, LAS VEGAS, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, ENJOUÉ, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DECALE, ENJOUE, DETERMINE, DEFILE DE MODE, DEFILE, BAR A COCKTAILS Du lounge 60’s stylé fusionné avec des breaks modernes et des cuivres fatals. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 181a tk046 joachim svare (ascap) galileo seven (ascap) kim s. hansen (bmi) hipster (d) wom 181a the lifestyle lounge west one music corporate business glitz style daytime tv super-stylin' 60s lounge fused with modern breaks and killer horns. sting dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="13868" name="Eleven Heaven (d)" code="WOM 059 tk064" libraryid="7" albumid="269" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_059_Free-Running/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Billy Handsome / Jeff Coates" comment="Un thème rock enjoué qui donne la pêche." styleid="12" lengthseconds="7" time="0:07" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_059_Free-Running/WOM059_trk064_ELEVEN_HEAVEN_(D)_Billy_Handsome_Jeff_Coates_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="64" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, POP, LIAISON, TV, RADIO, SPORT, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO) Un thème rock enjoué qui donne la pêche. wom 059 tk064 billy handsome jeff coates eleven heaven (d) wom 059 free-running west one music corporate business rock pop link tv radio sports happy feel good happy upbeat tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) upbeat feel good theme. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="2766" name="Pocket Full Of Sunshine (c)" code="NRF 018 tk039" libraryid="3" albumid="62" albumartpath="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_018_Soleil/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Michael W. Thompson (BMI)" comment="Paysage sonore pop rock fun, avec un groove de triangle." styleid="6" lengthseconds="7" time="0:07" samplefile="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_018_Soleil/NRF_018_trk039_POCKET_FULL_OF_SUNSHINE_(C)_Michael_W._Thompson_(BMI)_Noise_Refinery.mp3" track="39" tracktotal="" search="POP, POP, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, ROCK, ROCK, STING, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, SOLEIL, CHALEUR, ELEMENTS, ETE, METEO, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, JOURNEE, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, JOYEUX, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, FUN, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, GROOVY, PERCUSSIF, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN MÉTAL, CORDES EN METAL, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE, VOCAL, FÉMININ, FÉMININ, FEMININ, VOCAL, MASCULIN, MASCULIN Paysage sonore pop rock fun, avec un groove de triangle. nrf 018 tk039 michael w. thompson (bmi) pocket full of sunshine (c) nrf 018 soleil noise refinery pop western guitar acoustic steel string western guitar electric vocals female female vocals male male happy bright happy cheerful happy feel good happy fun happy happy happy playful happy upbeat tender hopeful tender warm uplifting motivational uplifting optimistic fun pop rock soundscape featuring triangle groove . sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="Noise Refinery" cae="00719510644" /><item id="29129" name="Light and Breezy (d)" code="WOM 391 tk161" libraryid="7" albumid="610" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_391_Something_Simple_Acoustic/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Thomas Greenberg (PRS)" comment="Sting plein d'émotion et de nostalgie." styleid="16" lengthseconds="7" time="0:07" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_391_Something_Simple_Acoustic/WOM_391_trk161_LIGHT_AND_BREEZY_(D)_Thomas_Greenberg_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="161" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, ENFANTS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, STING, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, ENFANTS, MATERNELLE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VACANCES, DE SAISON, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, SANTÉ, BIEN-ÊTRE, BIEN-ETRE, SANTE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, JOURNEE, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, ENJOUÉ, ENJOUE, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, INNOCENT, TENDRE, AFFECTUEUX, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TENDRE, TENDRE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, ACOUSTIQUE, BEAU, ENFANTIN, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ACOUSTIQUE, FORMATIONS GENERALES, CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, VIOLONCELLE, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN MÉTAL, CORDES EN METAL, CORDES, CORDES PIZZICATO, BOIS, CLARINETTE, EFFETS SONORES, HUMAIN, APPLAUDISSEMENTS Sting plein d'émotion et de nostalgie. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 391 tk161 thomas greenberg (prs) light and breezy (d) wom 391 something simple acoustic west one music quirky general lineups acoustic western piano western cello western guitar acoustic steel string western pizzicato strings western clarinet happy bright happy lighthearted tender hopeful tender innocent tender loving tender nostalgic tender reflective tender romantic tender emotive and nostalgic sting. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="28482" name="Rum Runner (d)" code="WOM 378 tk077" libraryid="7" albumid="600" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_378_Dive_Bar_Rock/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jez Miller (PRS)" comment="Sting de surf rock fanfaronnant." styleid="5" lengthseconds="8" time="0:08" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_378_Dive_Bar_Rock/WOM_378_trk077_RUM_RUNNER_(D)_Jez_Miller_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="77" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, ROCK, ROCK, SURF ROCK, STING, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, BAR, BAR À COCKTAILS, RESTAURANT, RESTOROUTE, BAR DE BIKERS, BAR A COCKTAILS, FILMS, ROAD MOVIE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, DRAMATIQUE, PASSIONNÉ, PASSIONNE, HEUREUX, EXCITÉ, EXCITE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, FUN, HEUREUX, GUILLERET, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, SEXY, COOL, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, EXCITANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, MACHO, ARROGANCE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, GROUPE DE ROCK, BATTERIE, BATTERIE, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 70, PERIODE, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 70 Sting de surf rock fanfaronnant. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 378 tk077 jez miller (prs) rum runner (d) wom 378 dive bar rock west one music rock rock surf rock sting bar roadhouse biker bar movies road movie tv radio youth tv reality tv sports dramatic passionate happy excited feel good fun perky upbeat sexy cool strong confident exciting uplifting positive macho swagger movement rhythmic rugged rock band swaggering surf rock sting. sting dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="13885" name="Freewheelin' (b)" code="WOM 059 tk081" libraryid="7" albumid="269" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_059_Free-Running/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Billy Handsome / Jeff Coates" comment="Du rock d'action grunge." styleid="12" lengthseconds="8" time="0:08" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_059_Free-Running/WOM059_trk081_FREEWHEELIN'_(B)_Billy_Handsome_Jeff_Coates_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="81" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, LIAISON, TV, RADIO, SPORT, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, CRADE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO) Du rock d'action grunge. wom 059 tk081 billy handsome jeff coates freewheelin' (b) wom 059 free-running west one music corporate business rock link tv radio sports happy feel good grungy tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) grungy rock action. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="28461" name="Big Mouth (d)" code="WOM 378 tk056" libraryid="7" albumid="600" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_378_Dive_Bar_Rock/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jez Miller (PRS)" comment="Sting de rock pur et dur, avec grosses guitares et batterie cogneuse." styleid="5" lengthseconds="8" time="0:08" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_378_Dive_Bar_Rock/WOM_378_trk056_BIG_MOUTH_(D)_Jez_Miller_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="56" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, ROCK, ROCK, ROCK CLASSIQUE, STING, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, BAR, BAR À COCKTAILS, RESTAURANT, RESTOROUTE, BAR DE BIKERS, BAR A COCKTAILS, FILMS, ROAD MOVIE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, SPORT, DRAMATIQUE, AGRESSIF, DRAMATIQUE, DANGEUREUX, DRAMATIQUE, FOUGUEUX, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, HEUREUX, EXCITÉ, EXCITE, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, SEXY, COCHON, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, DETERMINE, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, ENERGIQUE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, IMPLACABLE, FORT, FORT, MACHO, ARROGANCE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, GROUPE DE ROCK, BATTERIE, BATTERIE, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE Sting de rock pur et dur, avec grosses guitares et batterie cogneuse. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 378 tk056 jez miller (prs) big mouth (d) wom 378 dive bar rock west one music rock rock classic rock sting bar roadhouse biker bar movies road movie tv radio reality tv sports dramatic aggressive dangerous fiery intense happy excited upbeat sexy sleazy strong confident determined energetic exciting powerful relentless macho swagger movement rhythmic deep-fried rock sting. sting dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="13886" name="Freewheelin' (c)" code="WOM 059 tk082" libraryid="7" albumid="269" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_059_Free-Running/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Billy Handsome / Jeff Coates" comment="Du rock d'action, énergique et enlevé." styleid="12" lengthseconds="8" time="0:08" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_059_Free-Running/WOM059_trk082_FREEWHEELIN'_(C)_Billy_Handsome_Jeff_Coates_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="82" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, LIAISON, TV, RADIO, SPORT, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, CRADE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO) Du rock d'action, énergique et enlevé. wom 059 tk082 billy handsome jeff coates freewheelin' (c) wom 059 free-running west one music corporate business rock link tv radio sports happy feel good grungy tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) up and energetic rock action. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="21139" name="On the Hour (f)" code="WOM 225 tk063" libraryid="7" albumid="442" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_225_News_Themes/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jay Price" comment="Des informations élégantes et modernes." styleid="30" lengthseconds="8" time="0:08" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_225_News_Themes/WOM225_trk063_ON_THE_HOUR_(F)_Jay_Price_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="63" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, COMMUNICATION, ACTUALITÉS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, COMMUNICATION, ACTUALITÉS, STING, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, FLASH INFO, BULLETIN, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, NOUVELLES BUSINESS, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, JOURNALISME D'INVESTIGATION, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, BEDS POUR ACTUALITÉS, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, POLITIQUE, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, IMPLACABLE, SOPHISTIQUÉ, GLOSSY, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), SOPHISTIQUE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETERMINE, ACTUALITES, BEDS POUR ACTUALITES Des informations élégantes et modernes. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz wom 225 tk063 jay price on the hour (f) wom 225 news themes west one music news current affairs business corporate communication news business corporate communication news sting tv radio news and current affairs breaking news bulletin tv radio news and current affairs business news tv radio news and current affairs investigative reporting tv radio slick modern news. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="19404" name="Rodeo Drive (c)" code="WOM 188 tk045" libraryid="7" albumid="402" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_188_Feelgood_Light_Pop_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Clifford Eric Haywood / Thomas Garrad-Cole" comment="De la pop classique estivale et enjouée." styleid="6" lengthseconds="8" time="0:08" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_188_Feelgood_Light_Pop_2/WOM188_trk045_RODEO_DRIVE_(C)_Clifford_Eric_Haywood_Thomas_Garrad-Cole_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="45" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 90, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, LIAISON, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, POP CORPORATE, POP, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, BATTERIE, CLAVIER, ORGUE, ÉLECTRIQUE, CLAVIER, PIANO, ÉLECTRIQUE,, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ANNEES 2000, 20E SIECLE, ELECTRIQUE, ANNEES 20, ANNEES 90, JOURNEE De la pop classique estivale et enjouée. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 188 tk045 clifford eric haywood thomas garrad-cole rodeo drive (c) wom 188 feelgood light pop 2 west one music pop business corporate time period modern era 20th century 1990s time period modern era 2000s link tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) business corporate corporate pop pop happy bright happy feel good happy happy peaceful contented tender warm glamorous luxurious business bright and breezy classic summertime pop. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="19407" name="Shifting Sands (c)" code="WOM 188 tk048" libraryid="7" albumid="402" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_188_Feelgood_Light_Pop_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Clifford Eric Haywood / Thomas Garrad-Cole" comment="Chaleureux, rassurant et euphorisant." styleid="6" lengthseconds="8" time="0:08" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_188_Feelgood_Light_Pop_2/WOM188_trk048_SHIFTING_SANDS_(C)_Clifford_Eric_Haywood_Thomas_Garrad-Cole_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="48" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LIAISON, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, POP, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, CLAVIER, ORGUE, ÉLECTRIQUE, CLAVIER, PIANO, CLAVIER, PIANO, ÉLECTRIQUE,, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), ELECTRIQUE, JOURNEE Chaleureux, rassurant et euphorisant. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 188 tk048 clifford eric haywood thomas garrad-cole shifting sands (c) wom 188 feelgood light pop 2 west one music pop business corporate link tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) business corporate luxury pop uplifting uplifting happy playful peaceful contented tender warm glamorous luxurious business corporate tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden tv radio talkshow warm reassuring and uplifting. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="1282" name="Siren of the Damned (w) (Action Drum Groove)" code="FEM 021 tk137" libraryid="2" albumid="33" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_021_Soundesign_Vol_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Russell A. McKamey" comment="Groove de batterie pour séquence action." styleid="2" lengthseconds="8" time="0:08" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_021_Soundesign_Vol_2/FEM_021_trk137_SIREN_OF_THE_DAMNED_(W)_(ACTION_DRUM_GROOVE)_Russell_A._McKamey_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="137" tracktotal="" search="SOUND DESIGN, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, STING, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, SCIENCE FICTION, TRAILERS, DRAMATIQUE, AGRESSIF, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, FORT, FORT, SOUND DESIGN, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, SONS ÉLECTRONIQUES, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, ESPACE, ELEMENTS SONORES, ELECTRONIQUE, ATMOSPHERES, SONS ELECTRONIQUES, ELEMENTS Groove de batterie pour séquence action. fem 021 tk137 russell a. mckamey siren of the damned (w) (action drum groove) fem 021 soundesign vol. 2 fired earth music trailer sound elements atmospheres sound design sound elements atmospheres effects sting activities settings futuristic movies action adventure movies science fiction trailers dramatic aggressive dramatic intense scary ominous strong strong sound design sound effects fantasy action drum groove. sound effect" waveformpath="" version="Sound Effect" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284" /><item id="2162" name="Coral Forests (c)" code="NRF 011 tk035" libraryid="3" albumid="47" albumartpath="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_011_Majestic/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Christian Telford / Nigel William Graham / Kenneth E. Belcher" comment="Sting" styleid="3" lengthseconds="8" time="0:08" samplefile="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_011_Majestic/NRF_011_trk035_CORAL_FORESTS_(C)_Christian_Telford_Nigel_William_Graham_Kenneth_E._Belcher_Noise_Refinery.mp3" track="35" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, STING, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, FAMILIAL, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, ELEMENTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, ELEMENTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ELEMENTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, ELEMENTS, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, ENERGIQUE, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, MAJESTUEUX, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, JAILLIR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, BEAU, EVOLUTIF, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, OCCUPÉ, OCCUPE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, POURSUITE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COURANT, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN NYLON Sting bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live nrf 011 tk035 christian telford nigel william graham kenneth e. belcher coral forests (c) nrf 011 majestic noise refinery film score orchestral film score orchestral documentary film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic film score orchestral pastoral sting movies children storytelling movies family movies romance nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife sting. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="Noise Refinery" cae="00719510644" /><item id="2718" name="Altered Perception (c)" code="NRF 015 tk031" libraryid="3" albumid="61" albumartpath="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_015_Shadow_Substance/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Robert Anthony Navarro (ASCAP)" comment="Nocturne impressioniste douce avec dulcitone et textures à l'envers." styleid="3" lengthseconds="8" time="0:08" samplefile="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_015_Shadow_Substance/NRF_015_trk031_ALTERED_PERCEPTION_(C)_Robert_Anthony_Navarro_(ASCAP)_Noise_Refinery.mp3" track="31" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, POP, POP, ROCK, INDIE, UNDERSCORE, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, ROAD TRIP, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, FILMS INDÉPENDANTS, FILMS INDEPENDANTS, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, PAISIBLE, NONCHALANT, PAISIBLE, DÉTENDU, DETENDU, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT Nocturne impressioniste douce avec dulcitone et textures à l'envers. nrf 015 tk031 robert anthony navarro (ascap) altered perception (c) nrf 015 shadow &amp; substance noise refinery film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral documentary pop rock indie underscore activities settings road trip documentary biographical historical the arts movies indie films tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden tv radio leisure lifestyle travel mellow rock soundscape featuring swirling guitar textures. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="Noise Refinery" cae="00719510644" /><item id="2815" name="Clearer 2 (d)" code="NRF 010 tk049" libraryid="3" albumid="63" albumartpath="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_010_Push/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Antonia Jennifer Swann (SOCAN)" comment="Super catchy Indie Pop with kinetic keyboards. Alternative Mix." styleid="6" lengthseconds="8" time="0:08" samplefile="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_010_Push/NRF_010_trk049_CLEARER_2_(D)_Antonia_Jennifer_Swann_(SOCAN)_Noise_Refinery.mp3" track="49" tracktotal="" search="nrf 010 tk049 antonia jennifer swann (socan) clearer 2 (d) nrf 010 push noise refinery pop pop tween sting activities settings city urban human environment tv radio children youth tv tweens leisure lifestyle fashion style reality tv happy bouncy feel good fun upbeat uplifting anthemic inspirational motivational positive movement rhythmic general lineups super catchy indie pop with kinetic keyboards. alternative mix. link" waveformpath="" version="Link" /><item id="2323" name="Miracle (c)" code="NRF 009 tk037" libraryid="3" albumid="51" albumartpath="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_009_Spring_Break/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Siddhartha Menon" comment="Balade pop rock épique avec de puissantes guitares et une émotion non feinte." styleid="5" lengthseconds="8" time="0:08" samplefile="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_009_Spring_Break/NRF_009_trk037_MIRACLE_(C)_Siddhartha_Menon_Noise_Refinery.mp3" track="37" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, ROCK, POP, POP, STING, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FETE, SOIRÉE, SOIREE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, PRÉ-ADOLESCENTS, PRE-ADOLESCENT, PRE-ADOLESCENTS, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, COEUR BRISÉ, DEPRIMANT, COEUR BRISE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, DEPRIMANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, MÉLANCOLIE, DEPRIMANT, MELANCOLIE, SÉRIEUX, ÉMOUVANT, SERIEUX, EMOUVANT, TENDRE, SONGEUR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EMBLÉMATIQUE, EMBLEMATIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, GROUPE DE ROCK, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE Balade pop rock épique avec de puissantes guitares et une émotion non feinte. nrf 009 tk037 siddhartha menon miracle (c) nrf 009 spring break noise refinery rock rock pop sting activities settings city urban human environment activities settings party house party tv radio children youth tv tweens tv radio reality tv sad depressing heartbroken sad depressing lonely sad depressing melancholy serious emotional tender reflective epic pop rock ballad featuring powerful guitars and serious emotion. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="Noise Refinery" cae="00719510644" /><item id="2681" name="Mimosa (c)" code="NRF 016 tk034" libraryid="3" albumid="60" albumartpath="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_016_Elle/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Koichi C. Sanchez-Imahashi (ASCAP), Kenneth E. Belcher (ASCAP)" comment="Sting" styleid="6" lengthseconds="9" time="0:09" samplefile="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_016_Elle/NRF_016_trk034_MIMOSA_(C)_Koichi_C._Sanchez-Imahashi_(ASCAP),_Kenneth_E._Belcher_(ASCAP)_Noise_Refinery.mp3" track="34" tracktotal="" search="POP, POP, STING, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FILMS, FILMS INDÉPENDANTS, FILMS INDEPENDANTS, FILMS, IDYLLE, FILMS, COMÉDIE ROMANTIQUE, COMEDIE, COMEDIE ROMANTIQUE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, SANTÉ, BIEN-ÊTRE, BIEN-ETRE, SANTE, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, LÉGER, LEGER, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, DOUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, DIVIN, SOPHISTIQUÉ, CLASSE, SOPHISTIQUE, ÉTINCELANT, ETINCELANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ÉLECTRONIQUES, ELECTRONIQUE, INSTRUMENTS ELECTRONIQUES Sting sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz nrf 016 tk034 koichi c. sanchez-imahashi (ascap) kenneth e. belcher (ascap) mimosa (c) nrf 016 elle noise refinery pop sting pop pop heavenly sparkling happy happy tender soft happy bright tender light happy playful tender hopeful movies romance happy feel good tender romantic peaceful peaceful peaceful contented uplifting positive movies indie films business corporate uplifting sting sting delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="Noise Refinery" cae="00719510644" /><item id="2284" name="Apparent Motion (c)" code="NRF 013 tk037" libraryid="3" albumid="50" albumartpath="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_013_Fractals/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Mauricio Yazigi (BMI)" comment="Sting." styleid="3" lengthseconds="9" time="0:09" samplefile="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_013_Fractals/NRF_013_trk037_APPARENT_MOTION_(C)_Mauricio_Yazigi_(BMI)_Noise_Refinery.mp3" track="37" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, ORCHESTRAL HYBRIDE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, TRAILER, STING, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, INQUIETANT, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, AGITÉ, AGITE, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, EFFRAYANT, MENAÇANT, MENACANT, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, SÉRIEUX, INQUIET, SERIEUX, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, SERIEUX, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, DETERMINE, FORT, FORT, EVOLUTIF, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, PULSATION, ÉLECTRONIQUE, ELECTRONIQUE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES Sting. nrf 013 tk037 mauricio yazigi (bmi) apparent motion (c) nrf 013 fractals noise refinery film score orchestral film score orchestral orchestral hybrid film score orchestral documentary film score orchestral trailer sting activities settings city urban human environment movies crime detective mystery movies espionage spy movies human drama movies urban drama tv radio tv drama sting. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="Noise Refinery" cae="719510644" /><item id="2646" name="Con Of Man (c)" code="NRF 014 tk039" libraryid="3" albumid="59" albumartpath="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_014_Humanity/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Christian Telford (ASCAP), Matthew St. Laurent (ASCAP)" comment="Sting" styleid="3" lengthseconds="9" time="0:09" samplefile="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_014_Humanity/NRF_014_trk039_CON_OF_MAN_(C)_Christian_Telford_(ASCAP),_Matthew_St._Laurent_(ASCAP)_Noise_Refinery.mp3" track="39" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, STING, FILMS, FAMILIAL, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, PERIODE, PERIODES, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, ELEMENTS, DRAMATIQUE, PASSIONNÉ, PASSIONNE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, MÉLANCOLIE, DEPRIMANT, MELANCOLIE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, LUGUBRE, DEPRIMANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, DEPRIMANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, DEPRIMANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRAGIQUE, DEPRIMANT, SÉRIEUX, DIGNE, SERIEUX, SÉRIEUX, ÉMOUVANT, SERIEUX, EMOUVANT, SÉRIEUX, NOBLE, SERIEUX, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, SERIEUX, SÉRIEUX, ATTENTIONNÉ, SERIEUX, ATTENTIONNE, FORT, MAJESTUEUX, FORT, PUISSANT, BEAU, EVOLUTIF, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, MONTÉE, MONTEE, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE DE CHAMBRE, PETIT ORCHESTRE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, BOIS, SECTION DE BOIS, CLAVIER, PIANO Sting bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live nrf 014 tk039 christian telford (ascap) matthew st. laurent (ascap) con of man (c) nrf 014 humanity noise refinery film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral documentary film score orchestral panoramic sting movies family movies human drama movies period historical costume drama movies romance nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama dramatic passionate sad sting sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="Noise Refinery" cae="00719510644" /><item id="2246" name="Majesty of the Unknown (c)" code="NRF 012 tk039" libraryid="3" albumid="49" albumartpath="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_012_Celestial/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Matthew St. Laurent (ASCAP), Koichi C. Sanchez-Imahashi (ASCAP), Luc Johansson (ASCAP)" comment="Sting." styleid="3" lengthseconds="9" time="0:09" samplefile="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_012_Celestial/NRF_012_trk039_MAJESTY_OF_THE_UNKNOWN_(C)_Matthew_St._Laurent_(ASCAP),_Koichi_C._Sanchez-Imahashi_(ASCAP),_Luc_Johans.mp3" track="39" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, ORCHESTRAL HYBRIDE, STING, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, CRIME, DƒTECTIVE, MYSTéRE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, FILMS, MODERNE, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ƒLƒMENTS, CIEL, ESPACE, INTERSIDƒRAL, ELEMENTS, INTERSIDERAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ƒLƒMENTS, MƒTƒO, TEMPETES, TONNERRE, VENT, OURAGANS, ELEMENTS, METEO, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, CRAINTIF, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, DANGEUREUX, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DƒTERMINƒ, DETERMINE, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, IMPLACABLE, FORT, FORT, EVOLUTIF, MONTEE, MONTƒE, EVOLUTION, MONTƒE, ASCENDANT, MONTEE, CUIVRES, SECTION DE CUIVRES, FORMATIONS GƒNƒRALES, ƒLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, FORMATIONS GENERALES, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, CORDES, GUITARE, ƒLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE Sting. nrf 012 tk039 matthew st. laurent (ascap) koichi c. sanchez-imahashi (ascap) luc johansson (ascap) majesty of the unknown (c) nrf 012 celestial noise refinery film score orchestral film score orchestral documentary film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral orchestral hybrid sting movies action drama movies crime detective mystery movies horror thriller movies modern movies urban drama nature wildlife the elements sky space outer space sting sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="Noise Refinery" cae="719510644" /><item id="13796" name="Life-Cycle (b)" code="WOM 058 tk053" libraryid="7" albumid="268" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_058_Irresistible/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Graham Donald Harry Preskett" comment="Un thème orchestral planant." styleid="32" lengthseconds="9" time="0:09" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_058_Irresistible/WOM058_trk053_LIFE-CYCLE_(B)_Graham_Donald_Harry_Preskett_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="53" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, LIAISON, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, JAILLIR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL,, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ELEMENTS Un thème orchestral planant. wom 058 tk053 graham donald harry preskett life-cycle (b) wom 058 irresistible west one music romantic film score orchestral pastoral link tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) film score orchestral pastoral uplifting soaring tender romantic nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral soaring orchestra theme. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="15311" name="Beast (b)" code="WOM 091 tk035" libraryid="7" albumid="300" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_091_Electro_Rock/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Caspar John Valentine Kedros / Scott Doran" comment="Une ponctuation pétillante et tapageuse au tempo moyen avec des beats chimiques." styleid="6" lengthseconds="9" time="0:09" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_091_Electro_Rock/WOM091_trk035_BEAST_(B)_Caspar_John_Valentine_Kedros_Scott_Doran_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="35" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CHEMICAL BEATS, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRO, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HOUSE, ELECTRO HOUSE, POP, SYNTH POP, STING, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), ÉLECTRONIQUE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 80, ELECTRONIQUE, PERIODE, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 80 Une ponctuation pétillante et tapageuse au tempo moyen avec des beats chimiques. wom 091 tk035 caspar john valentine kedros scott doran beast (b) wom 091 electro rock west one music pop club electronica chemical beats club electronica electro club electronica house electro house pop synth pop sting activities settings city urban human environment activities settings showbiz tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style uplifting kicking mid tempo fuzzed up sting with chemical beats. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="2642" name="A Fond Remembrance (c)" code="NRF 014 tk035" libraryid="3" albumid="59" albumartpath="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_014_Humanity/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Christian Telford (ASCAP), Matthew St. Laurent (ASCAP)" comment="Sting" styleid="3" lengthseconds="9" time="0:09" samplefile="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_014_Humanity/NRF_014_trk035_A_FOND_REMEMBRANCE_(C)_Christian_Telford_(ASCAP),_Matthew_St._Laurent_(ASCAP)_Noise_Refinery.mp3" track="35" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, STING, FILMS, FAMILIAL, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, PERIODE, PERIODES, FILMS, IDYLLE, DRAMATIQUE, PASSIONNÉ, PASSIONNE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, DOUX-AMER, DEPRIMANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, DEPRIMANT, SÉRIEUX, DIGNE, SERIEUX, SÉRIEUX, ÉMOUVANT, SERIEUX, EMOUVANT, SÉRIEUX, NOBLE, SERIEUX, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, SERIEUX, SÉRIEUX, ATTENTIONNÉ, SERIEUX, ATTENTIONNE, TENDRE, DÉLICAT, DELICAT, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, AFFECTUEUX, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, TENDRE, BEAU, EVOLUTIF, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT, ELEGANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE DE CHAMBRE, PETIT ORCHESTRE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, CLAVIER, PIANO Sting bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live nrf 014 tk035 christian telford (ascap) matthew st. laurent (ascap) a fond remembrance (c) nrf 014 humanity noise refinery film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral documentary film score orchestral panoramic sting movies family movies human drama movies period historical costume drama movies romance dramatic passionate sad depressing bittersweet sad depressing poignant serious sting sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="Noise Refinery" cae="00719510644" /><item id="13797" name="Life-Cycle (c)" code="WOM 058 tk054" libraryid="7" albumid="268" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_058_Irresistible/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Graham Donald Harry Preskett" comment="Un thème orchestral planant." styleid="32" lengthseconds="9" time="0:09" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_058_Irresistible/WOM058_trk054_LIFE-CYCLE_(C)_Graham_Donald_Harry_Preskett_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="54" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, STING, FILMS, FAMILIAL, FILMS, IDYLLE, FILMS, COMÉDIE ROMANTIQUE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, OCCASIONS SPÉCIALES, ÉVÈNEMENTS, CERÉMONIEL, CÉRÉMONIE ROYALE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, PATRIOTIQUE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, AMERIQUE DU NORD, OCCASIONS SPECIALES, ETATS-UNIS, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), COMEDIE, COMEDIE ROMANTIQUE, EVENEMENTS, EVENEMENT, CEREMONIEL, ELEMENTS, CEREMONIE ROYALE Un thème orchestral planant. wom 058 tk054 graham donald harry preskett life-cycle (c) wom 058 irresistible west one music romantic film score orchestral trailer sting movies family movies romance movies romantic comedy nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral special occasions events ceremonial royal ceremony uplifting patriotic tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) soaring orchestra theme. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="2727" name="Vespertine Elegy (c)" code="NRF 015 tk040" libraryid="3" albumid="61" albumartpath="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_015_Shadow_Substance/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Robert Anthony Navarro (ASCAP)" comment="Musique d'ambiance au tempo lent avec guitares à l'envers, Rhodes et éléments électroniques." styleid="3" lengthseconds="10" time="0:10" samplefile="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_015_Shadow_Substance/NRF_015_trk040_VESPERTINE_ELEGY_(C)_Robert_Anthony_Navarro_(ASCAP)_Noise_Refinery.mp3" track="40" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, POP, POP, ROCK, INDIE, STING, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, ROAD TRIP, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, FILMS INDÉPENDANTS, FILMS INDEPENDANTS, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, PAISIBLE, NONCHALANT, PAISIBLE, DÉTENDU, DETENDU, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT Musique d'ambiance au tempo lent avec guitares à l'envers, Rhodes et éléments électroniques. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz nrf 015 tk040 robert anthony navarro (ascap) vespertine elegy (c) nrf 015 shadow &amp; substance noise refinery film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral documentary pop rock indie sting activities settings road trip documentary biographical historical the arts movies indie films tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden tv radio leisure lifestyle travel down-tempo mood music featuring backwards guitars rhodes piano and electronic elements. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="Noise Refinery" cae="00719510644" /><item id="2763" name="Clear Skies Ahead (c)" code="NRF 018 tk036" libraryid="3" albumid="62" albumartpath="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_018_Soleil/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Michael W. Thompson (BMI)" comment="Des guitares pensives, songeuses ouvrent la voie à un chorus inoubliable qui surgit." styleid="6" lengthseconds="10" time="0:10" samplefile="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_018_Soleil/NRF_018_trk036_CLEAR_SKIES_AHEAD_(C)_Michael_W._Thompson_(BMI)_Noise_Refinery.mp3" track="36" tracktotal="" search="POP, POP, STING, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, SOLEIL, CHALEUR, ELEMENTS, ETE, METEO, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, SANTÉ, BIEN-ÊTRE, BIEN-ETRE, SANTE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, JOURNEE, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, DOUX-AMER, DEPRIMANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, MÉLANCOLIE, DEPRIMANT, MELANCOLIE, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, SERIEUX, SÉRIEUX, ATTENTIONNÉ, SERIEUX, ATTENTIONNE, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN MÉTAL, CORDES EN METAL, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE, VOCAL, FÉMININ, FÉMININ, FEMININ, VOCAL, MASCULIN, MASCULIN Des guitares pensives, songeuses ouvrent la voie à un chorus inoubliable qui surgit. nrf 018 tk036 michael w. thompson (bmi) clear skies ahead (c) nrf 018 soleil noise refinery pop western guitar acoustic steel string western guitar electric vocals female female vocals male male peaceful dreamy sad depressing bittersweet sad depressing melancholy serious serious serious thoughtful tender hopeful tender nostalgic tender reflective tender thoughtful reflective guitars pave the way for an anthemic chorus reveal. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="Noise Refinery" cae="00719510644" /><item id="2724" name="The Conjuring (c)" code="NRF 015 tk037" libraryid="3" albumid="61" albumartpath="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_015_Shadow_Substance/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Robert Anthony Navarro (ASCAP)" comment="Groove blues animé, avec drone au tambura, cigar box guitare, percussions ethniques et textures renversées." styleid="3" lengthseconds="10" time="0:10" samplefile="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_015_Shadow_Substance/NRF_015_trk037_THE_CONJURING_(C)_Robert_Anthony_Navarro_(ASCAP)_Noise_Refinery.mp3" track="37" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, TRAILER, BLUES, BLUES, ROCK, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, ROCK, ROCK, ROCK, ROCK SUDISTE, STING, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, ROAD TRIP, FILMS, FILMS INDÉPENDANTS, FILMS INDEPENDANTS, FILMS, ROAD MOVIE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, CHAUD, DÉSERT, DESERT, ELEMENTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, ELEMENTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, ELEMENTS, NEUTRE, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, SERIEUX, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, DETERMINE, MACHO, ARROGANCE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT Groove blues animé, avec drone au tambura, cigar box guitare, percussions ethniques et textures renversées. nrf 015 tk037 robert anthony navarro (ascap) the conjuring (c) nrf 015 shadow &amp; substance noise refinery film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer blues rock film score orchestral documentary rock rock southern rock sting activities settings road trip movies indie films movies road movie nature wildlife the elements land hot desert nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama vibey blues groove featuring tambura drone cigar box guitar ethnic percussion and backwards textures. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="Noise Refinery" cae="00719510644" /><item id="2242" name="The Moons Surface (c)" code="NRF 012 tk035" libraryid="3" albumid="49" albumartpath="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_012_Celestial/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Matthew St. Laurent (ASCAP), Koichi C. Sanchez-Imahashi (ASCAP), Luc Johansson (ASCAP)" comment="Sting." styleid="3" lengthseconds="10" time="0:10" samplefile="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_012_Celestial/NRF_012_trk035_THE_MOONS_SURFACE_(C)_Matthew_St._Laurent_(ASCAP),_Koichi_C._Sanchez-Imahashi_(ASCAP),_Luc_Johansson_(.mp3" track="35" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, ORCHESTRAL HYBRIDE, STING, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, FILMS, CRIME, DƒTECTIVE, MYSTéRE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ƒLƒMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, ELEMENTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ƒLƒMENTS, CIEL, ESPACE, INTERSIDƒRAL, ELEMENTS, INTERSIDERAL, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ACTUALITƒS, JOURNALISME D'INVESTIGATION, ACTUALITES, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, AGITƒ, AGITE, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, DRAMATIQUE, PASSIONNƒ, PASSIONNE, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DƒTERMINƒ, DETERMINE, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, IMPLACABLE, FORT, FORT, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, EVOLUTIF, MONTEE, MONTƒE, EVOLUTION, PIZZICATO, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, PULSATION, FORMATIONS GƒNƒRALES, ƒLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, FORMATIONS GENERALES, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, PERCUSSION, MARIMBA, CORDES, GUITARE, ƒLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE Sting. nrf 012 tk035 matthew st. laurent (ascap) koichi c. sanchez-imahashi (ascap) luc johansson (ascap) the moons surface (c) nrf 012 celestial noise refinery film score orchestral film score orchestral documentary film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral orchestral hybrid sting activities settings futuristic documentary science technology movies crime detective mystery movies human drama movies urban drama nature wildlife the elements sting sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="Noise Refinery" cae="719510644" /><item id="2800" name="Clearer (c)" code="NRF 010 tk034" libraryid="3" albumid="63" albumartpath="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_010_Push/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Antonia J. Swann ()" comment="Indie pop super catchy." styleid="6" lengthseconds="10" time="0:10" samplefile="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_010_Push/NRF_010_trk034_CLEARER_(C)_Antonia_J._Swann_()_Noise_Refinery.mp3" track="34" tracktotal="" search="POP, POP, POP, PRÉ-ADOLESCENT, PRE-ADOLESCENT, ROCK, INDIE, STING, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, PRÉ-ADOLESCENTS, PRE-ADOLESCENT, PRE-ADOLESCENTS, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, JOURNEE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EMBLÉMATIQUE, EMBLEMATIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, FORMATIONS GENERALES, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, GROUPE DE ROCK Indie pop super catchy. nrf 010 tk034 antonia j. swann () clearer (c) nrf 010 push noise refinery pop pop pop tween rock indie sting activities settings city urban human environment tv radio children youth tv tweens tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio reality tv super catchy indie pop with kinetic keyboards. link" waveformpath="" version="Link" publisher="Noise Refinery" cae="00719510644" /><item id="2605" name="The Waking Hour (c)" code="NRF 008 tk038" libraryid="3" albumid="58" albumartpath="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_008_Lumos/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Christian Telford, Koichi C. Sanchez-Imahashi, Shinnosuke Miyazawa, Kenneth E. Belcher" comment="Sting." styleid="3" lengthseconds="10" time="0:10" samplefile="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_008_Lumos/NRF_008_trk038_THE_WAKING_HOUR_(C)_Christian_Telford,_Koichi_C._Sanchez-Imahashi,_Shinnosuke_Miyazawa,_Kenneth_E._Belcher.mp3" track="38" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, STING, FILMS, ART ET ESSAI, FILMS, FAMILIAL, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, FILMS INDÉPENDANTS, FILMS, IDYLLE, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, DRAME FAMILIAL, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, AFFECTUEUX, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, BEAU, EVOLUTIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, PULSATION, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, GROUPES VOCAUX, CHOEUR, CHOEURS MIXTES, CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN NYLON, FORMATIONS GENERALES, FILMS INDEPENDANTS, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Sting. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live nrf 008 tk038 christian telford koichi c. sanchez-imahashi shinnosuke miyazawa kenneth e. belcher the waking hour (c) nrf 008 lumos noise refinery film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral documentary film score orchestral panoramic sting movies art house movies family movies human drama movies indie films movies romance tv radio tv drama family drama tender hopeful tender loving tender nostalgic tender sting. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="Noise Refinery" cae="00719510644" /><item id="2759" name="Home At Last (c)" code="NRF 018 tk032" libraryid="3" albumid="62" albumartpath="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_018_Soleil/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Michael W. Thompson (BMI)" comment="Mal du pays garanti avec des guitares chaleureuses et floues, un groove insulaire ultra relax et une bonne dose de nostalgie." styleid="6" lengthseconds="10" time="0:10" samplefile="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_018_Soleil/NRF_018_trk032_HOME_AT_LAST_(C)_Michael_W._Thompson_(BMI)_Noise_Refinery.mp3" track="32" tracktotal="" search="POP, POP, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, STING, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, SOLEIL, CHALEUR, ELEMENTS, ETE, METEO, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TELE REALITE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, JOURNEE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, ENJOUÉ, ENJOUE, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN MÉTAL, CORDES EN METAL, VOCAL, FÉMININ, FÉMININ, FEMININ, VOCAL, MASCULIN, MASCULIN Mal du pays garanti avec des guitares chaleureuses et floues, un groove insulaire ultra relax et une bonne dose de nostalgie. nrf 018 tk032 michael w. thompson (bmi) home at last (c) nrf 018 soleil noise refinery pop western guitar acoustic steel string vocals female female vocals male male happy feel good happy happy happy lighthearted tender hopeful tender nostalgic tender reflective tender sentimental tender warm uplifting positive uplifting uplifting business corporate nature warm and fuzzy guitars a relaxed island groove and enough nostalgia to make you homesick. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="Noise Refinery" cae="00719510644" /><item id="2722" name="Everlasting Sky (c)" code="NRF 015 tk035" libraryid="3" albumid="61" albumartpath="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_015_Shadow_Substance/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Robert Anthony Navarro (ASCAP)" comment="Valse lounge retro avec guitares à l'envers." styleid="3" lengthseconds="11" time="0:11" samplefile="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_015_Shadow_Substance/NRF_015_trk035_EVERLASTING_SKY_(C)_Robert_Anthony_Navarro_(ASCAP)_Noise_Refinery.mp3" track="35" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, KITSCH, RETRO, RETRO, STING, FILMS, ART ET ESSAI, FILMS, FILMS INDÉPENDANTS, FILMS INDEPENDANTS, FILMS, ROAD MOVIE, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, FORMATS DE PROGRAMMES RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, DOUX-AMER, DEPRIMANT, SÉRIEUX, ATTENTIONNÉ, SERIEUX, ATTENTIONNE, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, GENTIL, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, DOUX, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT Valse lounge retro avec guitares à l'envers. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz nrf 015 tk035 robert anthony navarro (ascap) everlasting sky (c) nrf 015 shadow &amp; substance noise refinery film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral documentary kitsch retro sting movies art house movies indie films movies road movie tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden tv radio leisure lifestyle travel peaceful dreamy sad depressing bittersweet retro lounge waltz featuring backwards guitars. sting dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="Noise Refinery" cae="00719510644" /><item id="12574" name="Upstanding (d)" code="WOM 037 tk053" libraryid="7" albumid="247" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_037_American_Dream/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Graham Donald Harry Preskett" comment="Intrépide, cérémonial et fier." styleid="30" lengthseconds="11" time="0:11" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_037_American_Dream/WOM037_trk053_UPSTANDING_(D)_Graham_Donald_Harry_Preskett_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="53" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, STING, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, FIER, TV, RADIO, SITCOM, TV, RADIO, SOAP OPERA, TELENOVELA, OCCASIONS SPÉCIALES, ÉVÈNEMENTS, CERÉMONIEL, CÉRÉMONIE ROYALE,, AMERIQUE DU NORD, OCCASIONS SPECIALES, ETATS-UNIS, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), EVENEMENTS, EVENEMENT, CEREMONIEL, CEREMONIE ROYALE Intrépide, cérémonial et fier. wom 037 tk053 graham donald harry preskett upstanding (d) wom 037 american dream west one music news current affairs film score orchestral trailer north america usa sting tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) uplifting proud tv radio sitcom tv radio soap opera telenovela special occasions events ceremonial royal ceremony bold ceremonial and proud. sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" /><item id="1210" name="Edge of Humanity (w) (Bass Drum Droove 2)" code="FEM 021 tk065" libraryid="2" albumid="33" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_021_Soundesign_Vol_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Russell A. McKamey" comment="Groove de grosse caisse, cool et énergique." styleid="2" lengthseconds="11" time="0:11" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_021_Soundesign_Vol_2/FEM_021_trk065_EDGE_OF_HUMANITY_(W)_(BASS_DRUM_DROOVE_2)_Russell_A._McKamey_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="65" tracktotal="" search="SOUND DESIGN, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, STING, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, FILMS, SCIENCE FICTION, TRAILERS, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, FORT, CONFIANT, SOUND DESIGN, BATTERIE, GROSSE CAISSE, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, SONS ÉLECTRONIQUES, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, ESPACE, ELEMENTS SONORES, ELECTRONIQUE, ATMOSPHERES, SONS ELECTRONIQUES, ELEMENTS Groove de grosse caisse, cool et énergique. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz fem 021 tk065 russell a. mckamey edge of humanity (w) (bass drum droove 2) fem 021 soundesign vol. 2 fired earth music trailer sound elements atmospheres sound design sound elements atmospheres effects sting activities settings futuristic movies science fiction trailers disturbing dark strong confident sound design drums bass drum sound effects fantasy sci fi sounds electronic sounds sound effects cool energetic bass drum groove. sound effect" waveformpath="" version="Sound Effect" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284" /><item id="1262" name="Start Em Up (v) (Bass Groove 2)" code="FEM 021 tk117" libraryid="2" albumid="33" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_021_Soundesign_Vol_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Russell A. McKamey" comment="Groove déformé de synthétiseur et basse." styleid="2" lengthseconds="11" time="0:11" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_021_Soundesign_Vol_2/FEM_021_trk117_START_EM_UP_(V)_(BASS_GROOVE_2)_Russell_A._McKamey_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="117" tracktotal="" search="SOUND DESIGN, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, STING, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, FILMS, SCIENCE FICTION, TRAILERS, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, EFFRAYANT, HORREUR, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, SOUND DESIGN, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, SONS ÉLECTRONIQUES, EFFETS SONORES, FANTASTIQUE, SONS POUR SCIENCE-FICTION, ESPACE, ELEMENTS SONORES, ELECTRONIQUE, ATMOSPHERES, INQUIETANT, SONS ELECTRONIQUES, ELEMENTS Groove déformé de synthétiseur et basse. fem 021 tk117 russell a. mckamey start em up (v) (bass groove 2) fem 021 soundesign vol. 2 fired earth music trailer sound elements atmospheres sound design sound elements atmospheres effects sting activities settings futuristic movies horror thriller movies science fiction trailers disturbing dark disturbing eerie scary horror scary ominous sound design sound effects fantasy warped bass and synth groove. sound effect" waveformpath="" version="Sound Effect" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284" /><item id="2238" name="Gravitational Collapse (c)" code="NRF 012 tk031" libraryid="3" albumid="49" albumartpath="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_012_Celestial/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Matthew St. Laurent (ASCAP), Koichi C. Sanchez-Imahashi (ASCAP), Luc Johansson (ASCAP)" comment="Sting." styleid="3" lengthseconds="13" time="0:13" samplefile="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_012_Celestial/NRF_012_trk031_GRAVITATIONAL_COLLAPSE_(C)_Matthew_St._Laurent_(ASCAP),_Koichi_C._Sanchez-Imahashi_(ASCAP),_Luc_Johans.mp3" track="31" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, ORCHESTRAL HYBRIDE, STING, SITUATIONS ET ENVIRONNEMENTS, FUTURISTE, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, FILMS, CRIME, DƒTECTIVE, MYSTéRE, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ƒLƒMENTS, CIEL, ESPACE, INTERSIDƒRAL, ELEMENTS, INTERSIDERAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ƒLƒMENTS, MƒTƒO, TEMPETES, TONNERRE, VENT, OURAGANS, ELEMENTS, METEO, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DƒTERMINƒ, DETERMINE, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, IMPLACABLE, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EVOLUTIF, MONTEE, MONTƒE, EVOLUTION, FORMATIONS GƒNƒRALES, ƒLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, FORMATIONS GENERALES, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, GROUPES VOCAUX, CHOEUR, CHOEURS MIXTES, CORDES, GUITARE, ƒLECTRIQUE, ELECTRIQUE Sting. nrf 012 tk031 matthew st. laurent (ascap) koichi c. sanchez-imahashi (ascap) luc johansson (ascap) gravitational collapse (c) nrf 012 celestial noise refinery film score orchestral film score orchestral documentary film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral orchestral hybrid sting activities settings futuristic documentary science technology movies crime detective mystery movies espionage spy movies horror thriller nature wildlife sting sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="Noise Refinery" cae="719510644" /><item id="2239" name="Floating Among the Stars (c)" code="NRF 012 tk032" libraryid="3" albumid="49" albumartpath="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_012_Celestial/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Matthew St. Laurent (ASCAP), Koichi C. Sanchez-Imahashi (ASCAP), Luc Johansson (ASCAP)" comment="Sting." styleid="3" lengthseconds="15" time="0:15" samplefile="Music/Noise Refinery/NRF_012_Celestial/NRF_012_trk032_FLOATING_AMONG_THE_STARS_(C)_Matthew_St._Laurent_(ASCAP),_Koichi_C._Sanchez-Imahashi_(ASCAP),_Luc_Joha.mp3" track="32" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, ORCHESTRAL HYBRIDE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, STING, FILMS, FAMILIAL, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ƒLƒMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, ELEMENTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ƒLƒMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ELEMENTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ƒLƒMENTS, CIEL, AƒRIEN, NUAGES, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ƒLƒMENTS, CIEL, ESPACE, INTERSIDƒRAL, ELEMENTS, INTERSIDERAL, SƒRIEUX, ƒMOUVANT, SERIEUX, EMOUVANT, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DƒTERMINƒ, DETERMINE, FORT, MAJESTUEUX, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, FORT, FORT, TRIOMPHAL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, IMPRESSIONANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, FIER, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EVOLUTIF, MONTEE, MONTƒE, EVOLUTION, MONTƒE, ASCENDANT, MONTEE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AƒRIEN, EN VOL, AERIEN, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ƒLƒGANT, ELEGANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, CUIVRES, SECTION DE CUIVRES, FORMATIONS GƒNƒRALES, ƒLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, FORMATIONS GENERALES, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, GROUPES VOCAUX, CHOEUR, CHOEURS MIXTES, CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN NYLON Sting. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live nrf 012 tk032 matthew st. laurent (ascap) koichi c. sanchez-imahashi (ascap) luc johansson (ascap) floating among the stars (c) nrf 012 celestial noise refinery film score orchestral film score orchestral documentary film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral orchestral hybrid film score orchestral panoramic sting movies family movies human drama movies romance nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife the elements sting sting" waveformpath="" version="Sting" publisher="Noise Refinery" cae="719510644" /><item id="6902" name="Art and Invention (b)" code="TSH 067 tk064" libraryid="6" albumid="155" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_067_Inspiring_Innovation/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Everard Lawrence Wells / Robert John Foster" comment="Liaison de cordes." styleid="12" lengthseconds="9" time="0:09" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_067_Inspiring_Innovation/TSH067_trk064_ART_AND_INVENTION_(B)_Richard_Everard_Lawrence_Wells_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_H.mp3" track="64" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, PRESTIGE , CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, LIAISON, CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIÈCLE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, COMMUNICATION, ACTUALITÉS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, PUISSANCE, ÉNERGIE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, PATRIOTIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, FIER, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UN TRAIN, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, ART, ANTIQUITÉS, BOIS, CLARINETTE, BOIS, SAXOPHONE, SAXOPHONE ALTO, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIECLE, 20E SIECLE, ACTUALITES, ENERGIE, ANTIQUITES Liaison de cordes. tsh 067 tk064 richard everard lawrence wells robert john foster art and invention (b) tsh 067 inspiring innovation the scoring house corporate business business corporate prestige strings string section link classical 20th century classical style business corporate bright optimistic business corporate communication news business corporate luxury business corporate power energy uplifting inspirational uplifting motivational string driven link. link" waveformpath="" version="Link" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" /><item id="6924" name="Growing Together (b)" code="TSH 067 tk086" libraryid="6" albumid="155" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_067_Inspiring_Innovation/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Barnaby J Robson" comment="Liaison positive et chargée d'espoir." styleid="12" lengthseconds="5" time="0:05" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_067_Inspiring_Innovation/TSH067_trk086_GROWING_TOGETHER_(B)_Barnaby_J_Robson_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="86" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, PRESTIGE , FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, LIAISON, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, PATRIOTIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, FIER, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, JAILLIR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MÉLODIQUE, LYRIQUE, SOPHISTIQUÉ, CLASSE, ÉTINCELANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, NOËL, STYLE DE NOËL, ATMOSPHÈRES, VACANCES, DE SAISON, TV, RADIO, SPORT, CLAVIER, PIANO, FORMATIONS GENERALES, MELODIQUE, SOPHISTIQUE, ETINCELANT, NOEL, ATMOSPHERES, STYLE DE NOEL, AERIEN, ELEGANT Liaison positive et chargée d'espoir. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 067 tk086 barnaby j robson growing together (b) tsh 067 inspiring innovation the scoring house corporate business business corporate prestige general lineups acoustic strings string section link business corporate bright optimistic business corporate luxury business corporate motivational uplifting inspirational uplifting motivational uplifting optimistic uplifting patriotic uplifting expectant positive link. link" waveformpath="" version="Link" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" /><item id="6900" name="Hands Across the World (g)" code="TSH 067 tk062" libraryid="6" albumid="155" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_067_Inspiring_Innovation/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Barnaby J Robson" comment="Liaison exaltante." styleid="12" lengthseconds="9" time="0:09" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_067_Inspiring_Innovation/TSH067_trk062_HANDS_ACROSS_THE_WORLD_(G)_Barnaby_J_Robson_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="62" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, PRESTIGE , FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, LIAISON, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, PATRIOTIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, FIER, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, JAILLIR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, MÉLODIQUE, LYRIQUE, SOPHISTIQUÉ, CLASSE, ÉTINCELANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, TV, RADIO, SPORT, CLAVIER, PIANO, FORMATIONS GENERALES, MELODIQUE, SOPHISTIQUE, ETINCELANT, AERIEN, ELEGANT, ELEMENTS Liaison exaltante. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 067 tk062 barnaby j robson hands across the world (g) tsh 067 inspiring innovation the scoring house corporate business business corporate prestige general lineups acoustic strings string section link business corporate bright optimistic business corporate luxury business corporate motivational uplifting inspirational uplifting motivational uplifting optimistic uplifting patriotic uplifting uplifting link. link" waveformpath="" version="Link" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" /><item id="6887" name="Soft Flight (f)" code="TSH 067 tk049" libraryid="6" albumid="155" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_067_Inspiring_Innovation/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Barnaby J Robson" comment="Liaison chaleureuse, ambitieuse." styleid="12" lengthseconds="5" time="0:05" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_067_Inspiring_Innovation/TSH067_trk049_SOFT_FLIGHT_(F)_Barnaby_J_Robson_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="49" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, PRESTIGE , FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, LIAISON, CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIÈCLE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, PATRIOTIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, FIER, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, JAILLIR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MÉLODIQUE, LYRIQUE, SOPHISTIQUÉ, CLASSE, ÉTINCELANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, NOËL, STYLE DE NOËL, ATMOSPHÈRES, VACANCES, DE SAISON, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, CUIVRES, COR, COR D'HARMONIE, FORMATIONS GENERALES, MELODIQUE, SOPHISTIQUE, ETINCELANT, NOEL, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIECLE, ATMOSPHERES, STYLE DE NOEL, 20E SIECLE, AERIEN, ELEGANT Liaison chaleureuse, ambitieuse. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz tsh 067 tk049 barnaby j robson soft flight (f) tsh 067 inspiring innovation the scoring house corporate business business corporate prestige general lineups acoustic strings string section link classical 20th century classical style business corporate bright optimistic business corporate luxury business corporate motivational uplifting inspirational uplifting motivational uplifting warm aspirational link. link delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Link" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" /><item id="6879" name="Top Flight (e)" code="TSH 067 tk041" libraryid="6" albumid="155" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_067_Inspiring_Innovation/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Barnaby J Robson" comment="Liaison ambitieuse et positive." styleid="12" lengthseconds="6" time="0:06" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_067_Inspiring_Innovation/TSH067_trk041_TOP_FLIGHT_(E)_Barnaby_J_Robson_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="41" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, PRESTIGE , FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, LIAISON, CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIÈCLE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, PATRIOTIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, FIER, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, JAILLIR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MÉLODIQUE, LYRIQUE, SOPHISTIQUÉ, CLASSE, ÉTINCELANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, NOËL, STYLE DE NOËL, ATMOSPHÈRES, VACANCES, DE SAISON, TV, RADIO, SPORT, CLAVIER, PIANO, FORMATIONS GENERALES, MELODIQUE, SOPHISTIQUE, ETINCELANT, NOEL, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIECLE, ATMOSPHERES, STYLE DE NOEL, 20E SIECLE, AERIEN, ELEGANT Liaison ambitieuse et positive. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 067 tk041 barnaby j robson top flight (e) tsh 067 inspiring innovation the scoring house corporate business business corporate prestige general lineups acoustic strings string section link classical 20th century classical style business corporate bright optimistic business corporate luxury business corporate motivational uplifting inspirational uplifting motivational uplifting positive aspirational link. link" waveformpath="" version="Link" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" /><item id="6877" name="Top Flight (c)" code="TSH 067 tk039" libraryid="6" albumid="155" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_067_Inspiring_Innovation/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Barnaby J Robson" comment="Liaison ambitieuse et positive." styleid="12" lengthseconds="5" time="0:05" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_067_Inspiring_Innovation/TSH067_trk039_TOP_FLIGHT_(C)_Barnaby_J_Robson_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="39" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, PRESTIGE , FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, LIAISON, CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIÈCLE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, PATRIOTIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, FIER, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, JAILLIR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MÉLODIQUE, LYRIQUE, SOPHISTIQUÉ, CLASSE, ÉTINCELANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, NOËL, STYLE DE NOËL, ATMOSPHÈRES, VACANCES, DE SAISON, TV, RADIO, SPORT, CLAVIER, PIANO, FORMATIONS GENERALES, MELODIQUE, SOPHISTIQUE, ETINCELANT, NOEL, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIECLE, ATMOSPHERES, STYLE DE NOEL, 20E SIECLE, AERIEN, ELEGANT Liaison ambitieuse et positive. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 067 tk039 barnaby j robson top flight (c) tsh 067 inspiring innovation the scoring house corporate business business corporate prestige general lineups acoustic strings string section link classical 20th century classical style business corporate bright optimistic business corporate luxury business corporate motivational uplifting inspirational uplifting motivational uplifting positive aspirational link. link" waveformpath="" version="Link" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" /><item id="6937" name="Touching Lives (e)" code="TSH 067 tk099" libraryid="6" albumid="155" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_067_Inspiring_Innovation/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Barnaby J Robson" comment="Liaison visionnaire et attentionnée." styleid="12" lengthseconds="8" time="0:08" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_067_Inspiring_Innovation/TSH067_trk099_TOUCHING_LIVES_(E)_Barnaby_J_Robson_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="99" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, LIAISON, ENFANTS, BERCEUSE, ENFANTS, CONTES, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, COMMUNICATION, ACTUALITÉS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, INNOCENT, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, TENDRE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, BEAU, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FILMS, FAMILIAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, CLAVIER, PIANO, FORMATIONS GENERALES, ACTUALITES, ELEMENTS Liaison visionnaire et attentionnée. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 067 tk099 barnaby j robson touching lives (e) tsh 067 inspiring innovation the scoring house corporate business business corporate bright optimistic general lineups acoustic strings string section link children lullaby children storytelling business corporate communication news business corporate luxury film score orchestral documentary tender hopeful tender innocent tender caring visionary link. link" waveformpath="" version="Link" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382" /></items></librarycollection>