<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<librarycollection>
  <items>
    <item id="2680" name="All in a Dream" code="RFM 035 tk001" libraryid="4" albumid="91" albumartpath="Music/Refuel Music/RFM_035_Ultimate_Archive_Lounge_Collection/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Robert Farnon" comment="Remix rêveur et ambiant de 'Dream Lovers', remixé par Alexander S. Gray." styleid="8" lengthseconds="151" time="2:31" samplefile="Music/Refuel Music/RFM_035_Ultimate_Archive_Lounge_Collection/RFM_035_trk001_ALL_IN_A_DREAM_Robert_Farnon_Refuel_Music.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, AMBIENT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, REMIXES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, AUBE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, SOLEIL, CHALEUR, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, DÉTENDU, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, COOL, DIVIN, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), REMIX, ENREGISTREMENT D'ARCHIVE, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETENDU, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, METEO, ETE Remix rêveur et ambiant de 'Dream Lovers', remixé par Alexander S. Gray. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz rfm 035 tk001 robert farnon all in a dream rfm 035 ultimate archive lounge collection refuel music kitsch retro sound elements atmospheres club electronica ambient club electronica club electronica remixes film score orchestral trailer sound elements atmospheres main nature wildlife the elements land sun tropical seaside nature wildlife the elements seasons time dawn nature dreamy ambient remix of 'dream lovers' remixed by alexander s. gray. main dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Refuel Music" cae="00617450359"/>
    <item id="25682" name="Lets Get Started (a)" code="WOM 345 tk006" libraryid="6" albumid="550" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_345_Electro_Indie_Alternative/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Toby Hulbert" comment="Indie East Coast brut avec batterie pechue, guitares lo-fi, synthétiseurs et chant masculin accrocheur." styleid="34" lengthseconds="182" time="3:02" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_345_Electro_Indie_Alternative/WOM_345_trk006_LETS_GET_STARTED_(A)_Toby_Hulbert_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="6" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, INDIE, ROCK, ROCK ALTERNATIF, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, FORT, FORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EMBLÉMATIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EVOLUTIF, COOL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, GROUPE DE ROCK, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, VOCAL, MASCULIN, MASCULIN, FORMATIONS GENERALES, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, DETERMINE, ENERGIQUE, EMBLEMATIQUE, ELECTRIQUE, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Indie East Coast brut avec batterie pechue, guitares lo-fi, synthétiseurs et chant masculin accrocheur. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 345 tk006 toby hulbert lets get started (a) wom 345 electro indie alternative west one music indie rock indie rock alternative rock main activities settings city urban human environment tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio sports happy bright happy feel good strong confident strong raw east coast indie with punchy drums lo-fi guitars synths and hooky male vocals. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="17958" name="Miami Fever (a)" code="WOM 183 tk006" libraryid="6" albumid="379" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_183_Classic_Disco/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Alex Wilson" comment="Des vibrations réconfortantes et ensoleillées en provenance direct de l’archipel des Keys. Avec un piano et des cuivres au style latino." styleid="1" lengthseconds="141" time="2:21" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_183_Classic_Disco/WOM183_trk006_MIAMI_FEVER_(A)_Alex_Wilson_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="6" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, DISCO, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, LAS VEGAS, TV, RADIO, JEU, QUIZZ, SPECTACLE DE VARIÉTÉS, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, NUIT, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, SEXY, SEXY, FORT, CONFIANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CUIVRES, COR, COR D'HARMONIE, CUIVRES, TROMBONE, CUIVRES, TROMPETTE, CORNET, BATTERIE, CORDES, BASSE, BASSE ÉLECTRIQUE, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, CORDES, GUITARE, WAH WAH, CORDES, VIOLON , PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 70, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 80, PERIODE, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETERMINE, 20E SIECLE, ELECTRIQUE, BASSE ELECTRIQUE, ANNEES 70, ANNEES 80, SPECTACLE DE VARIETES, ETE Des vibrations réconfortantes et ensoleillées en provenance direct de l’archipel des Keys. Avec un piano et des cuivres au style latino. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 183 tk006 alex wilson miami fever (a) wom 183 classic disco west one music dance electro club electronica disco club electronica main activities settings showbiz las vegas tv radio game quiz variety show tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio talkshow entertainment late night happy happy serious determined sexy sexy strong confident uplifting feelgood sunshine vibes straight from the keys. with latin-style piano and horns. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="4243" name="Reaching Up (a)" code="TSH 030 tk003" libraryid="5" albumid="119" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_030_Outlook_Sunny/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Peter Simon Beckmann" comment="Un progression tonique et sympathique." styleid="11" lengthseconds="123" time="2:03" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_030_Outlook_Sunny/TSH030_trk003_REACHING_UP_(A)_Peter_Simon_Beckmann_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, ENFANTS, MATERNELLE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FORMATION, INFORMATION, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, ENFANTS, MATERNELLE, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, MATERNELLE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UN TRAIN, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), JOURNEE Un progression tonique et sympathique. tsh 030 tk003 peter simon beckmann reaching up (a) tsh 030 outlook sunny the scoring house corporate business children children pre school business corporate beds business corporate bright optimistic business corporate motivational business corporate training information main activities settings children pre school tv radio children youth tv pre school tv radio leisure easy-going uplifting progress. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="19726" name="Super-Sol (a)" code="WOM 221A tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="420" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_221A_Big_Chill_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Caspar John Valentine Kedros / Scott Doran" comment="Laissez-vous absorber par le soleil de ce morceau euphorisant et décontracté." styleid="15" lengthseconds="146" time="2:26" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_221A_Big_Chill_2/WOM221A_trk001_SUPER-SOL_(A)_Caspar_John_Valentine_Kedros_Scott_Doran_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CHILL OUT, DOWNTEMPO, PRINCIPAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), ELEMENTS, JOURNEE Laissez-vous absorber par le soleil de ce morceau euphorisant et décontracté. wom 221a tk001 caspar john valentine kedros scott doran super-sol (a) wom 221a big chill 2 west one music ambient chill club electronica chill out downtempo main nature wildlife the elements land sun tropical seaside tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio talkshow entertainment daytime just soak up the sun. uplifting and chilled. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="22960" name="Young Guns (a)" code="WOM 291 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="496" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_291_Go_Go_Indie/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Wesley Ayers" comment="Indé euphorique et significatif." styleid="34" lengthseconds="184" time="3:04" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_291_Go_Go_Indie/WOM_291_trk001_YOUNG_GUNS_(A)_David_Wesley_Ayers_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="POP, POP POUR ENFANTS, ENFANTS, ROCK, INDIE, PRINCIPAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, SPORT, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), ELEMENTS, JOURNEE Indé euphorique et significatif. wom 291 tk001 david wesley ayers young guns (a) wom 291 go go indie west one music indie pop kiddie pop children rock indie main nature wildlife the elements land sun tropical seaside sports tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio talkshow entertainment daytime happy feel good uplifting euphoric movement rhythmic driving euphoric life-affirming indie. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="2357" name="Honolulu Dreamer" code="RFM 011 tk004" libraryid="4" albumid="67" albumartpath="Music/Refuel Music/RFM_011_Aloha/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Len Fillis" comment="Humeur rêveuse et sereine. Authentique enregistrement d'époque." styleid="8" lengthseconds="141" time="2:21" samplefile="Music/Refuel Music/RFM_011_Aloha/RFM011_trk004_HONOLULU_DREAMER_Len_Fillis_Refuel_Music.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="KITSCH, RETRO, PRINCIPAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, JUNGLE, TROPICAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, TRANQUILLE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, HAWAÏ, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 60, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 70, STYLE VINTAGE, ENREGISTREMENT D'ARCHIVE, AMERIQUE DU NORD, PERIODE, ETATS-UNIS, HAWAI, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 60, ANNEES 70, ELEMENTS Humeur rêveuse et sereine. Authentique enregistrement d'époque. rfm 011 tk004 len fillis honolulu dreamer rfm 011 aloha refuel music kitsch retro kitsch retro main nature wildlife the elements land jungle tropical nature wildlife the elements land sun tropical seaside tv radio leisure lifestyle travel peaceful dreamy peaceful tranquil tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) north america usa hawaii time period dreamy tranquil mood. authentic period recording. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Refuel Music" cae="00617450359"/>
    <item id="23495" name="Solar Ray Gun (a)" code="WOM 303 tk012" libraryid="6" albumid="509" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_303_Commercial_Dance/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Charlie Tenku / Jamie Paul Reddington / Emre Ramazanoglu" comment="House commerciale avec une touche de disco. Accrocheur, classe et qui met de bonne humeur." styleid="1" lengthseconds="164" time="2:44" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_303_Commercial_Dance/WOM303_trk012_SOLAR_RAY_GUN_(A)_Charlie_Tenku_Jamie_Paul_Reddington_Emre_Ramazanoglu_West_One_Music_Lim.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRO, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRO, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HOUSE, POP, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, NUIT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), TWIST, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEFILE DE MODE, DEFILE House commerciale avec une touche de disco. Accrocheur, classe et qui met de bonne humeur. wom 303 tk012 charlie tenku jamie paul reddington emre ramazanoglu solar ray gun (a) wom 303 commercial dance west one music dance electro club electronica electro club electronica electro club electronica house pop main activities settings fashion show activities settings showbiz tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio talkshow entertainment late night uplifting commercial house with a disco twist catchy stylish feelgood. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="16645" name="In the Sunshine" code="WOM 155 tk011" libraryid="6" albumid="350" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_155_Dub_&amp;_Breakbeat_Sessions_2/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Justin John Shearn / Itchy Kid" comment="Une guitare acoustique douce et un piano avec des breaks jazzy." styleid="1" lengthseconds="178" time="2:58" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_155_Dub_&amp;_Breakbeat_Sessions_2/WOM155_trk011_IN_THE_SUNSHINE_Justin_John_Shearn_Itchy_Kid_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="11" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, BREAKBEAT, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, GROOVES, PRINCIPAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, SOLEIL, CHALEUR, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, ACOUSTIQUE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), AERIEN, ELEMENTS, METEO, ETE Une guitare acoustique douce et un piano avec des breaks jazzy. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 155 tk011 justin john shearn itchy kid in the sunshine wom 155 dub &amp; breakbeat sessions 2 west one music dance electro club electronica breakbeat club electronica club electronica grooves main nature wildlife the elements land sun tropical seaside nature wildlife the elements sky aerial clouds nature wildlife the elements weather sun heat tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home gentle acoustic guitar and piano with jazzy breaks. main delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="2674" name="Tropical Blend" code="RFM 034 tk013" libraryid="4" albumid="90" albumartpath="Music/Refuel Music/RFM_034_Ultimate_Archive_Kitsch_Collection/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Burnell Leonard Whibley" comment="Les rythmes épicés d'Amérique Latine. Enregistrement authentique d'époque." styleid="8" lengthseconds="139" time="2:19" samplefile="Music/Refuel Music/RFM_034_Ultimate_Archive_Kitsch_Collection/RFM034_trk013_TROPICAL_BLEND_Burnell_Leonard_Whibley_Refuel_Music.mp3" track="13" tracktotal="" search="KITSCH, RETRO, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 60, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 70, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), KITSCH, RETRO, STYLE VINTAGE, ENREGISTREMENT D'ARCHIVE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, HUMORISTIQUE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE,, PERIODE, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 60, ANNEES 70 Les rythmes épicés d'Amérique Latine. Enregistrement authentique d'époque. rfm 034 tk013 burnell leonard whibley tropical blend rfm 034 ultimate archive kitsch collection refuel music kitsch retro kitsch retro time period modern era 20th century 1960s time period modern era 20th century 1970s main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) kitsch retro vintage style archival recording happy feel good funny comedic funny humorous tv radio leisure lifestyle travel spicy latin american rhythms. authentic period recording. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Refuel Music" cae="00617450359"/>
    <item id="25491" name="Sun Street (b)" code="WOM 340 tk054" libraryid="6" albumid="545" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_340_Acoustic_Delights/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Alistair Bruce Henry Friend, Ted Brett Barnes" comment="Ensoleillé et léger, avec rythmes de batterie africains et guitares acoustiques." styleid="13" lengthseconds="117" time="1:57" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_340_Acoustic_Delights/WOM340_trk054_SUN_STREET_(B)_Alistair_Bruce_Henry_Friend,_Ted_Brett_Barnes_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="54" tracktotal="" search="POP, CUIVRES, ENSEMBLE DE CUIVRES, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ACOUSTIQUE, AFRIQUE, AMÉRIQUE LATINE, CARAÏBES, ANTILLES, AMÉRIQUE LATINE, AMÉRIQUE DU SUD, BRÉSIL, UNDERSCORE, WORLD BEAT, STYLES ETHNIQUES, INFLUENCE AFRICAINE, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, FESTIF, HEUREUX, JOYEUX, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, FUN, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, ENJOUÉ, HEUREUX, GUILLERET, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, PAISIBLE, NONCHALANT, PAISIBLE, LYRIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, BONDISSANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, CHANTONNANT, ACOUSTIQUE, VACANCES, DE SAISON, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, SOLEIL, CHALEUR, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, CUIVRES, BUGLE, CUIVRES, TROMPETTE, CORNET, BATTERIE, BATTERIE, INHABITUEL, PERCUSSION DE BRIC ET DE BROC, OBJETS TROUVÉS, SHAKER, CORDES, BASSE, BASSE ÉLECTRIQUE, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN NYLON, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, FORMATIONS GENERALES, AMERIQUE LATINE, CARAIBES, AMERIQUE DU SUD, ENJOUE, BRESIL, ELECTRIQUE, BASSE ELECTRIQUE, ELEMENTS, OBJETS TROUVES, METEO, ETE Ensoleillé et léger, avec rythmes de batterie africains et guitares acoustiques. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede wom 340 tk054 alistair bruce henry friend ted brett barnes sun street (b) wom 340 acoustic delights west one music acoustic pop brass brass ensemble general lineups acoustic africa latin america caribbean west indies latin america south america brazil underscore world beat ethnic stylings african influenced happy bright happy celebratory happy cheerful happy feel good happy fun happy happy sunny and bright featuring afro drum rhythms and acoustic guitars. underscore" waveformpath="" version="Underscore" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="21978" name="You Make Me Smile (b)" code="WOM 269 tk015" libraryid="6" albumid="471" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_269_Hitlist/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Tyler Van Den Berg / Kevin Ronnie Mcpherson" comment="Du new wave/R&amp;B qui se met au gospel. Vibrant, euphorique et terriblement entraînant." styleid="7" lengthseconds="152" time="2:32" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_269_Hitlist/WOM269_trk015_YOU_MAKE_ME_SMILE_(B)_Tyler_Van_Den_Berg_Kevin_Ronnie_Mcpherson_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="15" tracktotal="" search="TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, POP, POP POUR ENFANTS, FUNK, SOUL, R&amp;B, SOUL CONTEMPORAINE, POP, R&amp;B CONTEMPORAIN, POP, RELIGIEUX, CHRÉTIEN, PROTESTANT, CHANSONS GOSPEL, NEGRO SPIRITUALS, UNDERSCORE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CHRETIEN, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEFILE DE MODE, DEFILE Du new wave/R&amp;B qui se met au gospel. Vibrant, euphorique et terriblement entraînant. wom 269 tk015 tyler van den berg kevin ronnie mcpherson you make me smile (b) wom 269 hitlist west one music pop pop kiddie pop funk soul r&amp;b contemporary soul pop contemporary r&amp;b pop religious christian protestant gospel songs spirituals underscore activities settings fashion show tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio talkshow nu-wave r&amp;b goes gospel. vibrant euphoric and catchy as hell. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="13220" name="Upbeat Bashment (a)" code="WOM 075 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="265" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_075_Reggae_&amp;_Ska/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Irieman" comment="Des vibration estivales fun et fruitées." styleid="32" lengthseconds="200" time="3:20" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_075_Reggae_&amp;_Ska/WOM075_trk001_UPBEAT_BASHMENT_(A)_Irieman_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="DANSE ETHNIQUE, STYLE POP, REGGAE, AMÉRIQUE LATINE, CARAÏBES, ANTILLES, JAMAIQUE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), HEUREUX, FUN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, ÉTÉ,, AMERIQUE LATINE, CARAIBES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ELEMENTS, ETE Des vibration estivales fun et fruitées. wom 075 tk001 irieman upbeat bashment (a) wom 075 reggae &amp; ska west one music reggae ethnic dance pop style reggae latin america caribbean west indies jamaica main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) happy fun nature wildlife the elements seasons time summer fun 'n' fruity summer vibe. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="23738" name="Something Good (b)" code="WOM 309 tk017" libraryid="6" albumid="514" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_309_Indie_Organica/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="John-Paul Jones" comment="Audacieuses guitares infusées de soleil et batterie entrainante. Édifiant et inspirant." styleid="34" lengthseconds="145" time="2:25" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_309_Indie_Organica/WOM_309_trk017_SOMETHING_GOOD_(B)_John-Paul_Jones_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="17" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, POP CORPORATE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, ROCK, INDIE, ALTERNATIF, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, SPORT, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ELECTRIQUE, ELEMENTS Audacieuses guitares infusées de soleil et batterie entrainante. Édifiant et inspirant. wom 309 tk017 john-paul jones something good (b) wom 309 indie organica west one music indie business corporate corporate pop business corporate motivational rock indie alternate business corporate nature wildlife the elements land sun tropical seaside sports tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio sports strong prestigious uplifting motivational uplifting bold sunshine-soaked guitars and driving drums. uplifting and inspiring. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="80" name="Loop Wash (a)" code="EDS 007 tk002" libraryid="1" albumid="3" albumartpath="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_007_Chillwave_Glo-fi/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Israel Medina / Sample Magic / David Felton" comment="Électronica chaleureux, euphorique et évolutif. Accompagné de textures vocales." styleid="1" lengthseconds="239" time="3:59" samplefile="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_007_Chillwave_Glo-fi/EDS_007_trk002_LOOP_WASH_(A)_Israel_Medina_Sample_Magic_David_Felton_Electronic_Dance_Series.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CHILL OUT, DOWNTEMPO, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, ELECTRO, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HOUSE, ELECTRO HOUSE, DANSE ETHNIQUE, STYLE POP, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, SOLEIL, CHALEUR, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, COOL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, TEXTURE VOCALE, MOYEN-ORIENT, DEFILE DE MODE, DEFILE, ELEMENTS, METEO, ETE Électronica chaleureux, euphorique et évolutif. Accompagné de textures vocales. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz eds 007 tk002 israel medina sample magic david felton loop wash (a) eds 007 chillwave &amp; glo-fi electronic dance series dance electro club electronica chill out downtempo club electronica club electronica club electronica electro club electronica club electronica house electro house ethnic dance pop style main activities settings fashion show nature wildlife the elements land sun tropical seaside warm evolving and euphoric electronica. featuring voice textures. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Electronic Dance Series" cae="00666407133"/>
    <item id="19554" name="Children of the Sun (b)" code="WOM 216 tk013" libraryid="6" albumid="415" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_216_Catch_the_Sun/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Ian Mccutcheon" comment="Du surf-rock cool et rétro. Avec des batements de mains, des cloches et une pedal steel guitare habile." styleid="6" lengthseconds="162" time="2:42" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_216_Catch_the_Sun/WOM216_trk013_CHILDREN_OF_THE_SUN_(B)_Ian_Mccutcheon_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="13" tracktotal="" search="POP, ROCK, ROCK 'N' ROLL, UNDERSCORE, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, SOPHISTIQUÉ, GLOSSY, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 50, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 60, PERIODE, SOPHISTIQUE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 50, ANNEES 60 Du surf-rock cool et rétro. Avec des batements de mains, des cloches et une pedal steel guitare habile. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 216 tk013 ian mccutcheon children of the sun (b) wom 216 catch the sun west one music rock pop rock rock &amp; roll underscore tv radio children youth tv happy upbeat slick glossy tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) time period modern era 20th century 1950s time period modern era 20th century 1960s super-cool retro surf-rock. with handclaps bells and slick pedal steel. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="5410" name="Seaside Ballroom" code="TSH 052 tk049" libraryid="5" albumid="137" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_052_The_Mighty_Wurlitzer/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Leonard George Rawle" comment="Interpretation exhuberante et animée de 'I Do Like to be Beside the Seaside'." styleid="17" lengthseconds="47" time="0:47" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_052_The_Mighty_Wurlitzer/TSH052_trk049_SEASIDE_BALLROOM_Leonard_George_Rawle_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="49" tracktotal="" search="KITSCH, RETRO, CHEESY, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, ANGLETERRE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 30, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 40, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 50, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), KITSCH, RETRO, CHEESY, STYLE VINTAGE, HEUREUX, BRUYANT ET JOYEUX, DROLE, MANIÉRÉ, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, CLAVIER, WURLITZER,, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), MANIERE, DECALE, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 30, ANNEES 40, ANNEES 50, ELEMENTS Interpretation exhuberante et animée de 'I Do Like to be Beside the Seaside'. tsh 052 tk049 leonard george rawle seaside ballroom tsh 052 the mighty wurlitzer the scoring house comedy kitsch retro cheesy europe northern europe england time period modern era 20th century 1930s time period modern era 20th century 1940s time period modern era 20th century 1950s main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) kitsch retro cheesy vintage style happy rollicking funny rollicking rendition of i do like to be beside the seaside. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="6617" name="Summer in My Soul (a)" code="TSH 069 tk001" libraryid="5" albumid="153" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_069_Live_Life_Happy/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Glyn Michael Owen" comment="Thème heureux et accrocheur." styleid="10" lengthseconds="83" time="1:23" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_069_Live_Life_Happy/TSH_069_trk001_SUMMER_IN_MY_SOUL_(A)_Glyn_Michael_Owen_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="POP, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ACOUSTIQUE, PRINCIPAL, ENFANTS, MATERNELLE, POP, POP POUR ENFANTS, HEUREUX, BONDISSANT, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, JOYEUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, ACOUSTIQUE, ENFANTIN, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, ENFANTS, MATERNELLE, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, MATERNELLE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, FORMATIONS GENERALES, JOURNEE Thème heureux et accrocheur. tsh 069 tk001 glyn michael owen summer in my soul (a) tsh 069 live life happy the scoring house documentary pop general lineups acoustic main children pre school pop kiddie pop happy bouncy happy bright happy cheerful happy happy happy upbeat acoustic childlike activities settings children pre school tv radio children youth tv pre school tv radio leisure lifestyle food happy catchy theme. main knees up, mess piano, cockney, east london, singalong, pub joanna, piano bar, piano-bar, live" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="109" name="Dubfire (a)" code="EDS 008 tk002" libraryid="1" albumid="4" albumartpath="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_008_Extreme_Dubstep/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Samuel Rupert Cole Sutton / Alexander David Bachell" comment="Un dub-style rebondissant avec une énorme basse et des samples de reggae retardés." styleid="1" lengthseconds="140" time="2:20" samplefile="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_008_Extreme_Dubstep/EDS_008_trk002_DUBFIRE_(A)_Samuel_Rupert_Cole_Sutton_Alexander_David_Bachell_Electronic_Dance_Series.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, DUBSTEP, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, DUB, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, VILLE, URBAIN, ENVIRONNEMENT HUMAIN, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, SHOWBIZ, HOLLYWOOD, SPORT, SPORTS EXTREMES, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, EXCITANT, FORT, PUISSANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, NERVEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INDUSTRIE, MACHINES, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, ÉLECTRONIQUE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, ELECTRONIQUE, PERIODE, ANNEES 2000, ANNEES 20 Un dub-style rebondissant avec une énorme basse et des samples de reggae retardés. eds 008 tk002 samuel rupert cole sutton alexander david bachell dubfire (a) eds 008 extreme dubstep electronic dance series dance electro club electronica dubstep club electronica dub main activities settings city urban human environment activities settings showbiz hollywood sports extreme sports tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio sports strong confident strong exciting strong powerful jump-up dub styles with phat boomin’ bass and delayed reggae samples. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Electronic Dance Series" cae="00666407133"/>
    <item id="5774" name="Whistling Worker (g)" code="TSH 056 tk111" libraryid="5" albumid="141" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_056_Delectable_Eclectica/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Bea Parks / Garo Nahoulakian / Alexander Mayor" comment="Amusement rapide et joyeux accompagné de sifflements." styleid="16" lengthseconds="126" time="2:06" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_056_Delectable_Eclectica/TSH_056_trk111_WHISTLING_WORKER_(G)_Bea_Parks_Garo_Nahoulakian_Alexander_Mayor_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="111" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, ENFANTS, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, ENFANTS, MATERNELLE, DROLE, COMIQUE, DROLE, EXCENTRIQUE, DROLE, DÉCALÉ, HEUREUX, JOYEUX, HEUREUX, FUN, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, ENJOUÉ, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, DÉFILÉ, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), VOCAL, SIFFLEMENT, EFFETS SONORES, HUMAIN, SIFFLEMENT, MARCHE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DECALE, ENJOUE, DEFILE Amusement rapide et joyeux accompagné de sifflements. tsh 056 tk111 bea parks garo nahoulakian alexander mayor whistling worker (g) tsh 056 delectable eclectica the scoring house quirky children children main activities settings children pre school funny comedic funny eccentric funny quirky happy cheerful happy fun happy happy happy lighthearted happy upbeat movement rhythmic marching tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) vocals whistling sound effects human cheerful upbeat fun featuring whistling. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="26883" name="An English Summer (a)" code="WOM 317 tk007" libraryid="6" albumid="577" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_317_Weird_and_Wonderful/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Bill Connor" comment="Délicat et majestueux, pour manigances de gens très comme il faut." styleid="16" lengthseconds="121" time="2:01" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_317_Weird_and_Wonderful/WOM_317_trk007_AN_ENGLISH_SUMMER_(A)_Bill_Connor_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="TENNIS, WIMBLEDON, CENTRE COURT, SPORTS, ENFANTS, CONTES, ENFANTS, MATERNELLE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, ENFANTS, MATERNELLE, NOËL, ENFANTS, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, FAMILIAL, HEUREUX, ENJOUÉ, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, DÉTENDU, TENDRE, DÉLICAT, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, INNOCENT, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, PIZZICATO, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, CORDES, CORDES PIZZICATO, NOEL, ENJOUE, DETENDU, DELICAT Délicat et majestueux, pour manigances de gens très comme il faut. wom 317 tk007 bill connor an english summer (a) wom 317 weird and wonderful west one music quirky children storytelling children pre school film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral pastoral main activities settings children pre school christmas children documentary movies children storytelling movies family happy lighthearted happy playful peaceful delicate and stately for prim and proper goings-on. dramedy. main delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="13981" name="Summer Love-In (a)" code="WOM 092 tk015" libraryid="6" albumid="282" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_092_Jazzadelica/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Damian John Hand / Charles James Nicholas Casey" comment="Des flûtes espiègles enjouées et légères et des vibrations positives." styleid="16" lengthseconds="131" time="2:11" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_092_Jazzadelica/WOM092_trk015_SUMMER_LOVE-IN_(A)_Damian_John_Hand_Charles_James_Nicholas_Casey_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="15" tracktotal="" search="JAZZ, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 60, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), JAZZ, STYLE VINTAGE, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, SITCOM, BOIS, FLUTE,, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 60 Des flûtes espiègles enjouées et légères et des vibrations positives. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 092 tk015 damian john hand charles james nicholas casey summer love-in (a) wom 092 jazzadelica west one music quirky jazz time period modern era 20th century 1960s main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) jazz vintage style happy playful happy upbeat tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio sitcom woodwinds flute playful upbeat poppy flutes and good vibes. main dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="227" name="Counting Stars (a)" code="EDS 011 tk002" libraryid="1" albumid="7" albumartpath="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_011_Mainroom_House/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Francois Oxford / Oscar Hill / Justin Black" comment="House chaleureuse et séduisante avec synthés stylés. Un titre funky pour tard dans la nuit." styleid="1" lengthseconds="185" time="3:05" samplefile="Music/Electronic Dance Series/EDS_011_Mainroom_House/EDS_011_trk002_COUNTING_STARS_(A)_Francois_Oxford_Oscar_Hill_Justin_Black_Electronic_Dance_Series.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HOUSE, ELECTRO HOUSE, ÉLECTRONIQUE, PRINCIPAL, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, CLUB, ELECTRONICA, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, ELECTRONIQUE, ENERGIQUE, ELEMENTS House chaleureuse et séduisante avec synthés stylés. Un titre funky pour tard dans la nuit. eds 011 tk002 francois oxford oscar hill justin black counting stars (a) eds 011 mainroom house electronic dance series dance electro club electronica house electro house electronic main club electronica club electronica happy bright happy feel good strong energetic uplifting motivational uplifting positive uplifting uplifting movement rhythmic driving nature wildlife the elements land sun tropical warm and seductive house track with stylish synths. a funky late night mover. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Electronic Dance Series" cae="00666407133"/>
    <item id="22234" name="Walking in the Sun (b)" code="WOM 275 tk015" libraryid="6" albumid="477" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_275_Acoustic_Pop/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Rob Rewes" comment="De la pop rock acoustique chaleureuse, optimiste et ensoleillée." styleid="7" lengthseconds="191" time="3:11" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_275_Acoustic_Pop/WOM275_trk015_WALKING_IN_THE_SUN_(B)_Rob_Rewes_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="15" tracktotal="" search="POP, POP POUR ENFANTS, ENFANTS, POP, UNDERSCORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, SOLEIL, CHALEUR, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, ENJOUÉ, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, ACOUSTIQUE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, ANNÉES 2000, PERIODE, ENJOUE, ANNEES 2000, ANNEES 20, ELEMENTS, METEO, JOURNEE, ETE De la pop rock acoustique chaleureuse, optimiste et ensoleillée. wom 275 tk015 rob rewes walking in the sun (b) wom 275 acoustic pop west one music pop pop kiddie pop children pop underscore nature wildlife the elements land sun tropical seaside nature wildlife the elements weather sun heat tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio talkshow entertainment daytime warm optimistic sun-kissed acoustic pop-rock. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="2331" name="Neapolitana" code="RFM 009 tk002" libraryid="4" albumid="65" albumartpath="Music/Refuel Music/RFM_009_Life_in_the_Sun/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Tony Osborne (Gb 1)" comment="Rythmes d'été joyeux. Authentique enregistrement d'époque." styleid="8" lengthseconds="141" time="2:21" samplefile="Music/Refuel Music/RFM_009_Life_in_the_Sun/RFM009_trk002_NEAPOLITANA_Tony_Osborne_(Gb_1)_Refuel_Music.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="EASY LISTENING, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, COMÉDIE, CHEESY, KITSCH, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, ÉTÉ, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 60, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 70, STYLE VINTAGE, ENREGISTREMENT D'ARCHIVE, PERIODE, COMEDIE, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 60, ANNEES 70, ELEMENTS, ETE Rythmes d'été joyeux. Authentique enregistrement d'époque. rfm 009 tk002 tony osborne (gb 1) neapolitana rfm 009 life in the sun refuel music kitsch retro easy listening main movies comedy cheesy kitsch nature wildlife the elements land sun tropical seaside nature wildlife the elements seasons time summer tv radio leisure lifestyle travel happy feel good happy upbeat tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) time period modern era joyful summer rhythms. authentic period recording. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="Refuel Music" cae="00617450359"/>
  </items>
</librarycollection>
