<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<librarycollection>
  <items>
    <item id="12337" name="Magical Moments (a)" code="WOM 058 tk003" libraryid="6" albumid="248" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_058_Irresistible/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Graham Donald Harry Preskett" comment="Un opéra gracieux et étincelant. Sensible et émotionnel." styleid="31" lengthseconds="145" time="2:25" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_058_Irresistible/WOM058_trk003_MAGICAL_MOMENTS_(A)_Graham_Donald_Harry_Preskett_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, TENDRE, GRACIEUX, SÉRIEUX, ÉMOUVANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, ÉTINCELANT, FILMS, IDYLLE, FILMS, COMÉDIE ROMANTIQUE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL,, AMERIQUE DU NORD, SERIEUX, ETINCELANT, ETATS-UNIS, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), EMOUVANT, COMEDIE, COMEDIE ROMANTIQUE, ELEMENTS Un opéra gracieux et étincelant. Sensible et émotionnel. wom 058 tk003 graham donald harry preskett magical moments (a) wom 058 irresistible west one music romantic film score orchestral trailer classical and semi classical symphony orchestra north america usa main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral pastoral tender graceful serious emotional movement smooth graceful sparkling movies graceful sparkling orchestra. sensitive and emotional. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="26638" name="Curved Light" code="WOM 012 tk011" libraryid="6" albumid="572" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_012_Clarity/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Paul Reeves (Gb 2)" comment="Une valse simple et crystalline évoquant l'innocence et la tranquilité." styleid="4" lengthseconds="138" time="2:18" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_012_Clarity/WOM012_trk011_CURVED_LIGHT_Paul_Reeves_(Gb_2)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="11" tracktotal="" search="CLASSIQUE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 66 - 76 À L'AISE (ADAGIO), CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIÈCLE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, ABSTRAIT, SIMPLE, DANSE DE SALON, VALSE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, IDYLLE, CLAVIER, PIANO,, PERIODE, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIECLE, 66 - 76 A L'AISE (ADAGIO), DEPRIMANT, 20E SIECLE Une valse simple et crystalline évoquant l'innocence et la tranquilité. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 012 tk011 paul reeves (gb 2) curved light wom 012 clarity west one music film score orchestral classical time period modern era 20th century main tempo 66 - 76 medium slow (adagio) classical 20th century classical style film score orchestral trailer tender nostalgic tender romantic sad depressing poignant sad depressing sad abstract simple ballroom dance waltz movies simple transparent waltz depicting innocence and tranquillity. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="6909" name="Touch the Sky (a)" code="TSH 001 tk006" libraryid="5" albumid="158" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_001_Cinematic_Adventures/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Un prélude étincelant vers une virée aventureuse et aérienne et une conclusion tumultueuse ." styleid="4" lengthseconds="175" time="2:55" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_001_Cinematic_Adventures/TSH001_trk006_TOUCH_THE_SKY_(A)_Richard_Allen_Harvey_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="6" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, NAVIGATION, PIRATES, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, FILMS, SCIENCE FICTION, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, TITRE POUR TRAILER, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, AVENTUREUX, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, PATRIOTIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, FORME CLASSIQUE, PRÉLUDE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 80, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 90, PÉRIODE, PRÉ-20E SIÈCLE, 19E SIÈCLE, AMERIQUE DU NORD, PERIODE, SERIEUX, ETATS-UNIS, PRE-20E SIECLE, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), DETERMINE, PRELUDE, 20E SIECLE, 19E SIECLE, AERIEN, ANNEES 80, ANNEES 90, ELEMENTS Un prélude étincelant vers une virée aventureuse et aérienne et une conclusion tumultueuse . tsh 001 tk006 richard allen harvey touch the sky (a) tsh 001 cinematic adventures the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer main activities settings seafaring pirates movies action adventure movies fantasy adventure movies science fiction nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama trailer track serious determined strong adventurous tender hopeful shimmering prelude to an adventurous aerial joyride and tumultuous conclusion. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="3763" name="Circle of Life (a)" code="TSH 018 tk005" libraryid="5" albumid="109" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_018_Say_it_With_Style/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Gwilym Raymond Simcock / Curtis Frederick Schwartz" comment="Un thème chaleureux et méditatif évoluant graduellement, pour piano solo." styleid="19" lengthseconds="256" time="4:16" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_018_Say_it_With_Style/TSH018_trk005_CIRCLE_OF_LIFE_(A)_Gwilym_Raymond_Simcock_Curtis_Frederick_Schwartz_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FORMATION, INFORMATION, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EVOLUTIF, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLAVIER, PIANO, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, REVELER, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Un thème chaleureux et méditatif évoluant graduellement, pour piano solo. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 018 tk005 gwilym raymond simcock curtis frederick schwartz circle of life (a) tsh 018 say it with style the scoring house jazz business corporate bright optimistic business corporate luxury business corporate reveal launch business corporate training information film score orchestral trailer main business corporate documentary movies human drama tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home warm reflective theme gradually evolving. main dinner, jazz, cocktail, lounge, cocktail lounge, bar, hotel" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="6210" name="A Fragile Balance" code="TSH 064A tk001" libraryid="5" albumid="146" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_064A_The_Observing_Eye/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Zac Jordan" comment="Observations chaleureuses et introspectives." styleid="12" lengthseconds="127" time="2:07" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_064A_The_Observing_Eye/TSH064A_trk001_A_FRAGILE_BALANCE_Zac_Jordan_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, PRINCIPAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, PAISIBLE, CALME, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TENDRE, DÉLICAT, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, SONGEUR, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, RALENTI, BEAU, ÉTINCELANT, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, DIVIN, CÉLESTE, CLAVIER, PIANO, ELEMENTS SONORES, FORMATIONS GENERALES, ETINCELANT, ATMOSPHERES, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, DELICAT, AERIEN, ELEGANT, ELEMENTS, CELESTE Observations chaleureuses et introspectives. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 064a tk001 zac jordan a fragile balance tsh 064a the observing eye the scoring house atmospheres sound elements atmospheres general lineups electronic and acoustic main film score orchestral documentary peaceful calm peaceful dreamy peaceful peaceful tender delicate tender intimate tender reflective movement smooth aerial floating movement smooth elegant movement warm introspective observations. main delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="18296" name="Arco Noir (a)" code="WOM 192 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="388" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_192_Strings_of_Sorrow/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Une intéraction lyrique entre des solos de violon et de violoncelle sur un underscore de cordes pulsant et doux." styleid="14" lengthseconds="173" time="2:53" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_192_Strings_of_Sorrow/WOM192_trk001_ARCO_NOIR_(A)_Richard_Allen_Harvey_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, FILM NOIR, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, PAISIBLE, LYRIQUE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRAGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, MÉLODIQUE, LYRIQUE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CORDES, VIOLONCELLE, CORDES, VIOLON, MELODIQUE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE Une intéraction lyrique entre des solos de violon et de violoncelle sur un underscore de cordes pulsant et doux. wom 192 tk001 richard allen harvey arco noir (a) wom 192 strings of sorrow west one music drama film score orchestral trailer main documentary movies crime detective mystery movies film noir movies human drama disturbing mysterious peaceful lyrical sad depressing poignant sad depressing sad sad depressing tragic tender reflective tender sentimental melodic lyrical interplay between violin and cello solos over a pulsating gentle string underscore. main delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="7388" name="Dream Dancers (a)" code="TSH 059 tk008" libraryid="5" albumid="168" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_059_Orchestral_Fantasia/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Arthur Rhodes" comment="Voix spectrales chantantes." styleid="4" lengthseconds="115" time="1:55" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_059_Orchestral_Fantasia/TSH_059_trk008_DREAM_DANCERS_(A)_Simon_Arthur_Rhodes_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="8" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, MAGIE, ILLUSIONS, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, DIVIN, CÉLESTE, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SURNATUREL, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, TENDRE, INNOCENT, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MAGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, CHANTONNANT, CLAVIER, PIANO, VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, TEXTURE VOCALE, INQUIETANT, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, CELESTE Voix spectrales chantantes. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 059 tk008 simon arthur rhodes dream dancers (a) tsh 059 orchestral fantasia the scoring house film score orchestral children storytelling business corporate luxury film score orchestral trailer main activities settings magic illusions movies children storytelling movies fantasy adventure nature wildlife the elements sky aerial clouds nature wildlife the elements sky heavenly celestial lilting spectral voices. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="26953" name="Out on the Ice (a)" code="WOM 321 tk012" libraryid="6" albumid="578" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_321_Light_Bright_and_Playful/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Mike Reed / Tom Howe" comment="Piano délicat et pizzicati de cordes. Décalé et joueur." styleid="10" lengthseconds="120" time="2:00" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_321_Light_Bright_and_Playful/WOM321_trk012_OUT_ON_THE_ICE_(A)_Mike_Reed_Tom_Howe_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, ENFANTS, MATERNELLE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, FAMILIAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, HEUREUX, VIF, HEUREUX, ENJOUÉ, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, INNOCENT, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, ÉTINCELANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN MÉTAL, CORDES, CORDES PIZZICATO, ETINCELANT, ENJOUE, ELEMENTS, CORDES EN METAL Piano délicat et pizzicati de cordes. Décalé et joueur. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 321 tk012 mike reed tom howe out on the ice (a) wom 321 light bright and playful west one music documentary children storytelling children pre school film score orchestral documentary main movies children storytelling movies family nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife tv radio leisure lifestyle food delicate piano and pizzicato strings. quirky and playful. dramedy. main delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="7947" name="Time Reflections" code="TSH 038 tk047" libraryid="5" albumid="174" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_038_Oddities/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Paul Reeves (Gb 2)" comment="Un piano doux pour dépeindre le temps et l'espace." styleid="17" lengthseconds="60" time="1:00" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_038_Oddities/TSH038_trk047_TIME_REFLECTIONS_Paul_Reeves_(Gb_2)_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="47" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), SOLO, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, NOËL, STYLE DE NOËL, ATMOSPHÈRES, CLAVIER, PIANO,, ELEMENTS SONORES, NOEL, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), STYLE DE NOEL, ELEMENTS Un piano doux pour dépeindre le temps et l'espace. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 038 tk047 paul reeves (gb 2) time reflections tsh 038 oddities the scoring house comedy sound elements atmospheres main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) solo peaceful dreamy peaceful peaceful tender nostalgic tender reflective tender romantic christmas christmas stylings atmospheres keyboard piano gentle piano depicting time and space. main delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="17991" name="A Winter Land (a)" code="WOM 184 tk003" libraryid="6" albumid="380" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_184_Family_Fantasy/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Paul Reeves (Gb 2)" comment="Une valse délicate qui grandit à travers des scènes magiques menant à un climax grisant." styleid="2" lengthseconds="173" time="2:53" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_184_Family_Fantasy/WOM184_trk003_A_WINTER_LAND_(A)_Paul_Reeves_(Gb_2)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, ENFANTS, CLASSIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, NOËL, ENFANTS, FILMS, ANIMATION, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, FORT, EXALTANT, TENDRE, DÉLICAT, TENDRE, INNOCENT, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MAGIQUE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CHOEUR, CUIVRES, COR, COR D'HARMONIE, CLAVIER, CELESTE, CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, VIOLONCELLE, CORDES, HARPE, CORDES, VIOLON , BOIS, FLUTE, VOCAL, DANSE DE SALON, VALSE, NOEL, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DELICAT Une valse délicate qui grandit à travers des scènes magiques menant à un climax grisant. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 184 tk003 paul reeves (gb 2) a winter land (a) wom 184 family fantasy west one music trailer children storytelling children classical film score orchestral trailer main christmas children movies animation movies children storytelling movies fantasy adventure trailers trailer track happy playful peaceful contented peaceful dreamy peaceful peaceful strong a delicate waltz expanding through magical scenes to an exhilarating climax. main delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="4866" name="Starry Night" code="TSH 044 tk012" libraryid="5" albumid="129" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_044_My_American_Story/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Francis Richard Shaw" comment="Etablissez la scene avec cette piste miroitante, intriguante et déscriptive." styleid="23" lengthseconds="48" time="0:48" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_044_My_American_Story/TSH_044_trk012_STARRY_NIGHT_Francis_Richard_Shaw_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 66 - 76 À L'AISE (ADAGIO), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, DRAMATIQUE, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, HIVER,, AMERIQUE DU NORD, ETATS-UNIS, 66 - 76 A L'AISE (ADAGIO), DEPRIMANT, ELEMENTS Etablissez la scene avec cette piste miroitante, intriguante et déscriptive. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede tsh 044 tk012 francis richard shaw starry night tsh 044 my american story the scoring house country folk film score orchestral trailer classical and semi classical symphony orchestra north america usa main tempo 66 - 76 medium slow (adagio) film score orchestral pastoral sad depressing sad dramatic movies fantasy adventure nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama shimmering intriguing descriptive scene setter. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="4045" name="Family Photos (a)" code="TSH 022 tk010" libraryid="5" albumid="114" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_022_Human_Stories/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Michael Price / Laurence Love Greed" comment="Un thème doux et évocateur de piano et cordes." styleid="10" lengthseconds="137" time="2:17" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_022_Human_Stories/TSH022_trk010_FAMILY_PHOTOS_(A)_Michael_Price_Laurence_Love_Greed_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="10" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, AUTOMNE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, RALENTI, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, CLAVIER, PIANO, DEPRIMANT, AERIEN, ELEGANT, ELEMENTS Un thème doux et évocateur de piano et cordes. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 022 tk010 michael price laurence love greed family photos (a) tsh 022 human stories the scoring house documentary film score orchestral pastoral main documentary movies human drama nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral nature wildlife the elements seasons time autumn nature wildlife the elements sky aerial clouds peaceful dreamy peaceful peaceful sad gentle evocative theme for piano and strings. main delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="26639" name="Echoes" code="WOM 012 tk012" libraryid="6" albumid="572" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_012_Clarity/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Daryl Neil Alexander Griffith" comment="Un morceau optimiste et fort." styleid="4" lengthseconds="155" time="2:35" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_012_Clarity/WOM012_trk012_ECHOES_Daryl_Neil_Alexander_Griffith_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="CLASSIQUE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIÈCLE, CLASSIQUE, STYLE MINIMALISTE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, FORT, PUISSANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, FILMS, FAMILIAL, FILMS, IDYLLE,, PERIODE, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIECLE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), 20E SIECLE, ACCELERE Un morceau optimiste et fort. wom 012 tk012 daryl neil alexander griffith echoes wom 012 clarity west one music film score orchestral classical time period modern era 20th century main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) classical 20th century classical style classical minimalist style film score orchestral trailer strong powerful uplifting optimistic movement rhythmic speeded up time lapse movies family movies optimistic and powerful piece. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="26481" name="Heavenly Creatures (a)" code="WOM 304 tk007" libraryid="6" albumid="568" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_304_Emotive_Minimalism/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Captivant et magique. Des cordes enveloppants et inspirantes et de douces guitares se développent tout au long de ce morceau. Avec chant féminin sans paroles." styleid="4" lengthseconds="177" time="2:57" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_304_Emotive_Minimalism/WOM304_trk007_HEAVENLY_CREATURES_(A)_Richard_Allen_Harvey_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, ANGLETERRE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE, CLASSIQUE, STYLE MINIMALISTE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, MAGIQUE, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, TEXTURE VOCALE,, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), 20E SIECLE, AERIEN, ELEMENTS Captivant et magique. Des cordes enveloppants et inspirantes et de douces guitares se développent tout au long de ce morceau. Avec chant féminin sans paroles. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 304 tk007 richard allen harvey heavenly creatures (a) wom 304 emotive minimalism west one music film score orchestral classical classical styling classical and semi classical symphony orchestra europe northern europe england time period modern era 20th century main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) classical classical styling classical minimalist style film score orchestral panoramic film score captivating and magical. rich inspiring strings and gentle guitars evolve throughout. featuring wordless female vocal. main delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="4605" name="New Light" code="TSH 035 tk001" libraryid="5" albumid="125" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_035_A_Winner_is_Born/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Mark Lasker" comment="Des textures délicates et frémissantes." styleid="22" lengthseconds="71" time="1:11" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_035_A_Winner_is_Born/TSH035_trk001_NEW_LIGHT_Mark_Lasker_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FORMATION, INFORMATION, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, SOLEIL, CHALEUR, SPORT, JEUX OLYMPIQUES, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, NOUVELLES LÉGÈRES, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, BEDS POUR ACTUALITÉS, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, TENDRE, DÉLICAT, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, RALENTI, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DELICAT, ACTUALITES, ELEMENTS, NOUVELLES LEGERES, BEDS POUR ACTUALITES, METEO, ETE Des textures délicates et frémissantes. tsh 035 tk001 mark lasker new light tsh 035 a winner is born the scoring house sport business corporate beds business corporate bright optimistic business corporate luxury business corporate motivational business corporate training information main documentary nature wildlife the elements weather sun heat sports olympics tv radio news and current affairs shimmering delicate textures. main delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="5843" name="Marionette Memory (e)" code="TSH 056 tk180" libraryid="5" albumid="141" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_056_Delectable_Eclectica/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Bea Parks / Garo Nahoulakian / Oliver Charles Horton" comment="Valse hantée fantaisiste." styleid="16" lengthseconds="130" time="2:10" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_056_Delectable_Eclectica/TSH_056_trk180_MARIONETTE_MEMORY_(E)_Bea_Parks_Garo_Nahoulakian_Oliver_Charles_Horton_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="180" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, ENFANTS, CONTES, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, TEXTURE VOCALE, DANSE DE SALON, VALSE, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), INQUIETANT, DEPRIMANT, ELEMENTS Valse hantée fantaisiste. tsh 056 tk180 bea parks garo nahoulakian oliver charles horton marionette memory (e) tsh 056 delectable eclectica the scoring house quirky sound elements atmospheres children storytelling sound elements atmospheres main documentary movies children storytelling movies fantasy adventure disturbing eerie sad depressing tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) vocals vocal textures voice texture ballroom dance waltz haunting waltz time fantasy. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="24404" name="In Aeternum (a)" code="WOM 322 tk008" libraryid="6" albumid="526" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_322_Cinematic_Drama/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Martin Tillmann" comment="Motifs répétés de violoncelle, marimba et piano. Sincère et charmant." styleid="14" lengthseconds="144" time="2:24" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_322_Cinematic_Drama/WOM322_trk008_IN_AETERNUM_(A)_Martin_Tillmann_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="8" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, MODERNE, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, DRAME FAMILIAL, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, DRAME HOSPITALIER, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, MÉLANCOLIE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, SÉRIEUX, ÉMOUVANT, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, ATTENTIONNÉ, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, RÉPÉTITIF, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ACOUSTIQUE, CLAVIER, PIANO, PERCUSSION, MARIMBA, CORDES, VIOLONCELLE, FORMATIONS GENERALES, SERIEUX, DEPRIMANT, EMOUVANT, ATTENTIONNE, MELANCOLIE, REPETITIF Motifs répétés de violoncelle, marimba et piano. Sincère et charmant. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 322 tk008 martin tillmann in aeternum (a) wom 322 cinematic drama west one music drama film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral documentary main movies human drama movies modern tv radio tv drama family drama tv radio tv drama medical drama tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama sad depressing lonely sad depressing melancholy sad repeating cello marimba and piano patterns. sincere and engaging. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="6292" name="Life Journeys" code="TSH 065A tk024" libraryid="5" albumid="148" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_065A_The_Piano_Book/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Ostinati fluides, expressifs." styleid="25" lengthseconds="185" time="3:05" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_065A_The_Piano_Book/TSH065A_trk024_LIFE_JOURNEYS_Richard_Allen_Harvey_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="24" tracktotal="" search="CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIÈCLE, PRINCIPAL, ENFANTS, CONTES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, INNOCENT, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, BEAU, MÉLODIQUE, LYRIQUE, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, CLAVIER, PIANO, SOLO, MELODIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIECLE, DEPRIMANT, 20E SIECLE, ELEMENTS Ostinati fluides, expressifs. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 065a tk024 richard allen harvey life journeys tsh 065a the piano book the scoring house classical opera classical 20th century classical style main children storytelling film score orchestral documentary film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral pastoral peaceful peaceful sad depressing poignant sad depressing sad tender hopeful tender innocent tender intimate expressive flowing ostinati. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="20910" name="The Ragged Waltz (a)" code="WOM 246 tk012" libraryid="6" albumid="447" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_246_Atmospheric_Guitar/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Dan Cassady" comment="Des mélodies de guitare lyrique avec un design sonore distant et rêveur." styleid="12" lengthseconds="157" time="2:37" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_246_Atmospheric_Guitar/WOM246_trk012_THE_RAGGED_WALTZ_(A)_Dan_Cassady_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="EASY LISTENING, NEW AGE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, SOUND DESIGN, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, LYRIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, RALENTI, MÉLODIQUE, LYRIQUE, DOCUMENTAIRE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE,, ELEMENTS SONORES, MELODIQUE, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), AERIEN, ELEGANT, ELECTRIQUE, ELEMENTS Des mélodies de guitare lyrique avec un design sonore distant et rêveur. wom 246 tk012 dan cassady the ragged waltz (a) wom 246 atmospheric guitar west one music atmospheres easy listening new age main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) sound elements atmospheres sound design peaceful dreamy peaceful lyrical tender reflective movement smooth aerial flying movement smooth elegant movement smooth flowing movement smooth graceful movement smooth lyrical guitar melodies with distant dreamy sound design. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="15299" name="Ice Dance (a)" code="WOM 124 tk005" libraryid="6" albumid="318" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_124_Life_in_Motion/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Paul Reeves (Gb 2)" comment="Une valse rassurante qui s'étend vers un monde magique." styleid="26" lengthseconds="127" time="2:07" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_124_Life_in_Motion/WOM124_trk005_ICE_DANCE_(A)_Paul_Reeves_(Gb_2)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIÈCLE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, NOËL, STYLE DE NOËL, ATMOSPHÈRES, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, HIVER, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, MAGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, DANSE DE SALON, VALSE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, PERIODE, NOEL, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIECLE, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), STYLE DE NOEL, 20E SIECLE, AERIEN, ELEGANT, ELEMENTS Une valse rassurante qui s'étend vers un monde magique. wom 124 tk005 paul reeves (gb 2) ice dance (a) wom 124 life in motion west one music nature wildlife children storytelling classical 20th century classical style film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic main christmas christmas stylings atmospheres movies children storytelling nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife reassuring waltz expanding into a magical world. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="23739" name="Winter Swell (b)" code="WOM 309 tk018" libraryid="6" albumid="514" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_309_Indie_Organica/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="John-Paul Jones" comment="Une répetition de piano rigide et percussions électro, construction constante." styleid="34" lengthseconds="114" time="1:54" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_309_Indie_Organica/WOM_309_trk018_WINTER_SWELL_(B)_John-Paul_Jones_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="18" tracktotal="" search="ROCK, INDIE, WORLD BEAT, STYLES ETHNIQUES, ALTERNATIF, DOCUMENTAIRE, SPORT, TV, RADIO, SPORT, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, EVOLUTIF, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), AERIEN, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Une répetition de piano rigide et percussions électro, construction constante. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 309 tk018 john-paul jones winter swell (b) wom 309 indie organica west one music indie rock indie world beat ethnic stylings alternate documentary sports tv radio sports strong prestigious building movement smooth aerial flying tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) stark repeating piano and electro percussion building throughout. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="3465" name="A Winter Chorale (a)" code="TSH 014A tk011" libraryid="5" albumid="104" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_014A_Smile-_A_Most_Cheerful_Earful/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Une évocation sincère et chaleureuse." styleid="17" lengthseconds="134" time="2:14" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_014A_Smile-_A_Most_Cheerful_Earful/TSH_014A_trk011_A_WINTER_CHORALE_(A)_Richard_Allen_Harvey_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="11" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, MUSIQUE DE CHAMBRE, ENSEMBLE CLASSIQUE, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, ANGLETERRE, PÉRIODE, ÈRES CULTURELLES, PERIODES DE LA MUSIQUE CLASSIQUE, MOYEN AGE (477 - 1420), PÉRIODE, ÈRES CULTURELLES, PERIODES DE LA MUSIQUE CLASSIQUE, RENAISSANCE (1420 - 1600), PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, SÉRIEUX, DIGNE, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL,, PERIODE, SERIEUX, ERES CULTURELLES, PERIODES, ELEMENTS Une évocation sincère et chaleureuse. tsh 014a tk011 richard allen harvey a winter chorale (a) tsh 014a smile: a most cheerful earful the scoring house comedy children children pre school main activities settings children pre school movies animation tv radio cartoons tv radio children youth tv pre school tv radio leisure lifestyle travel funny comedic funny eccentric funny humorous funny quirky funny wry tender innocent warm heartfelt evocation. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="28021" name="Arctic Fun (a)" code="WOM 241A tk008" libraryid="6" albumid="598" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_241A_Natural_World_Landscapes/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Matt Norman (PRS)" comment="Une guitare acoustique enjouée et des textures de synthé évoquent de tendres paysages hivernaux." styleid="26" lengthseconds="135" time="2:15" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_241A_Natural_World_Landscapes/WOM_241A_trk008_ARCTIC_FUN_(A)_Matt_Norman_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="8" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, NOËL, STYLE DE NOËL, ATMOSPHÈRES, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, NEIGE, GLACE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, HEUREUX, JOUEUR, TENDRE, INNOCENT, ACOUSTIQUE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), NOEL, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), STYLE DE NOEL, ELEMENTS Une guitare acoustique enjouée et des textures de synthé évoquent de tendres paysages hivernaux. wom 241a tk008 matt norman (prs) arctic fun (a) wom 241a natural world: landscapes west one music nature wildlife volcanos nature wildlife planet earth natural world landscape exploration countryside deserts geology playful acoustic guitar and synth textures evoke gentle winter scenes. main delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="7122" name="Nirvana (a)" code="TSH 029 tk004" libraryid="5" albumid="164" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_029_Symphonic_Fantasia/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Arthur Rhodes" comment="Serein, enveloppant, flottant." styleid="4" lengthseconds="199" time="3:19" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_029_Symphonic_Fantasia/TSH029_trk004_NIRVANA_(A)_Simon_Arthur_Rhodes_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, ESPACE, INTERSIDÉRAL, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, SEREIN, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, RALENTI, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, CLAVIER, PIANO, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, DEPRIMANT, ACCELERE, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, INTERSIDERAL Serein, enveloppant, flottant. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 029 tk004 simon arthur rhodes nirvana (a) tsh 029 symphonic fantasia the scoring house film score orchestral sound elements atmospheres film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic main movies romance nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife nature wildlife the elements sky aerial clouds nature serene immersive drifting. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="6461" name="Building Futures (a)" code="TSH 067 tk013" libraryid="5" albumid="151" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_067_Inspiring_Innovation/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Barnaby J Robson" comment="Progression chantante, exaltante." styleid="11" lengthseconds="132" time="2:12" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_067_Inspiring_Innovation/TSH067_trk013_BUILDING_FUTURES_(A)_Barnaby_J_Robson_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="13" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, PRESTIGE , FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, PRINCIPAL, CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIÈCLE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, INSPIRANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, POSITIF, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, FIER, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, JAILLIR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, GRACIEUX, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MÉLODIQUE, LYRIQUE, SOPHISTIQUÉ, CLASSE, ÉTINCELANT, DANSE DE SALON, VALSE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, NOËL, STYLE DE NOËL, ATMOSPHÈRES, VACANCES, DE SAISON, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, FILMS, FAMILIAL, CLAVIER, PIANO, FORMATIONS GENERALES, MELODIQUE, SOPHISTIQUE, ETINCELANT, NOEL, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIECLE, ATMOSPHERES, STYLE DE NOEL, 20E SIECLE, AERIEN, ELEGANT Progression chantante, exaltante. sophistiqué, musique de fond, musique d'ambiance, lounge, jazz bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 067 tk013 barnaby j robson building futures (a) tsh 067 inspiring innovation the scoring house corporate business business corporate prestige general lineups acoustic strings string section main classical 20th century classical style business corporate bright optimistic business corporate luxury business corporate motivational uplifting inspirational uplifting motivational uplifting lilting uplifting progression. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
  </items>
</librarycollection>
