<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<librarycollection>
  <items>
    <item id="7345" name="The Last Post (a)" code="TSH 042 tk051" libraryid="5" albumid="167" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_042_A_Soldier's_Story/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Trad / Barnaby J Robson" comment="Un arrangement lancinant pour trompette, alto et violoncelle." styleid="4" lengthseconds="135" time="2:15" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_042_A_Soldier's_Story/TSH042_trk051_THE_LAST_POST_(A)_Trad_Barnaby_J_Robson_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="51" tracktotal="" search="CLASSIQUE, ARRANGEMENT CLASSIQUE, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, GUERRE, MILITAIRE, HISTORIQUE, PREMIERE GUERRE MONDIALE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, GUERRE, MILITAIRE, HISTORIQUE, SECONDE GUERRE MONDIALE, OCCASIONS SPÉCIALES, ÉVÈNEMENTS, FUNÉRAILLES, SÉRIEUX, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CUIVRES, CLAIRON, CUIVRES, TROMPETTE, CORNET, CORDES, VIOLONCELLE, CORDES, VIOLE, ARRANGEMENT, FANFARE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, 1900 - 1919, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 40, PERIODE, SERIEUX, OCCASIONS SPECIALES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), EVENEMENTS, EVENEMENT, 20E SIECLE, FUNERAILLES, ANNEES 40 Un arrangement lancinant pour trompette, alto et violoncelle. tsh 042 tk051 trad barnaby j robson the last post (a) tsh 042 a soldier's story the scoring house film score orchestral classical classical arrangement main activities settings war military historical world war 1 activities settings war military historical world war 2 special occasions events funeral serious tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) brass bugle brass trumpet cornet strings cello haunting arrangement for trumpet viola and cello. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="8226" name="No Return" code="TSH 051 tk039" libraryid="5" albumid="177" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_051_Nearfield/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Everard Lawrence Wells / Robert John Foster" comment="Violoncelle et piano poignants." styleid="10" lengthseconds="130" time="2:10" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_051_Nearfield/TSH051_trk039_NO_RETURN_Richard_Everard_Lawrence_Wells_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="39" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, SÉRIEUX, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CORDES, VIOLONCELLE, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, ELEMENTS Violoncelle et piano poignants. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 051 tk039 richard everard lawrence wells robert john foster no return tsh 051 nearfield the scoring house documentary film score orchestral documentary main documentary movies human drama nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife sad depressing lonely sad depressing poignant sad depressing sad serious tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) strings cello poignant cello and piano. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="26629" name="Elysian Fields (a)" code="WOM 257 tk005" libraryid="6" albumid="571" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_257_Cinematic_Soundscapes/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Michael Dale Simon / Daniel Law Heath / James Brian Brasher" comment="Le voyage vers la vie après la mort. Naturellement beau et serein." styleid="4" lengthseconds="159" time="2:39" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_257_Cinematic_Soundscapes/WOM257_trk005_ELYSIAN_FIELDS_(A)_Michael_Dale_Simon_Daniel_Law_Heath_James_Brian_Brasher_West_One_Music_L.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, MÉDICAL, SCIENCES DE LA VIE, PAISIBLE, SEREIN, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, SÉRIEUX, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, BEAU, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), SERIEUX, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), DEPRIMANT, ELEMENTS, MEDICAL Le voyage vers la vie après la mort. Naturellement beau et serein. wom 257 tk005 michael dale simon daniel law heath james brian brasher elysian fields (a) wom 257 cinematic soundscapes west one music film score orchestral film score orchestral documentary main documentary movies human drama nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife science technology industry medical life science peaceful serene sad depressing poignant sad depressing sad serious tender nostalgic tender reflective the journey to the afterlife. effortlessly beautiful and serene. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="8192" name="Drifting Away (a)" code="TSH 051 tk005" libraryid="5" albumid="177" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_051_Nearfield/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Everard Lawrence Wells / Robert John Foster" comment="Une nébuleuse de textures suspendues avec un violoncelle émergent." styleid="10" lengthseconds="127" time="2:07" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_051_Nearfield/TSH051_trk005_DRIFTING_AWAY_(A)_Richard_Everard_Lawrence_Wells_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, ZEN, MÉDITATION , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MER, SOUS-MARIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, DIVIN, CÉLESTE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, ESPACE, INTERSIDÉRAL, CORDES, VIOLONCELLE,, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), MEDITATION, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, CELESTE, INTERSIDERAL Une nébuleuse de textures suspendues avec un violoncelle émergent. tsh 051 tk005 richard everard lawrence wells robert john foster drifting away (a) tsh 051 nearfield the scoring house documentary sound elements atmospheres main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) peaceful dreamy peaceful peaceful peaceful zen meditation movement smooth aerial floating movement smooth aerial flying nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife nature wildlife the elements sea nebulous suspended textures with emerging cello. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="18309" name="Lost Hope" code="WOM 192 tk014" libraryid="6" albumid="388" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_192_Strings_of_Sorrow/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Des mélodies sombres et maussades sur des motifs de cordes basses répétées." styleid="14" lengthseconds="213" time="3:33" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_192_Strings_of_Sorrow/WOM192_trk014_LOST_HOPE_Richard_Allen_Harvey_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="14" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRAGIQUE, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, CORDES, VIOLONCELLE, CORDES, VIOLON ,, ELEMENTS SONORES, SERIEUX, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, ELEMENTS Des mélodies sombres et maussades sur des motifs de cordes basses répétées. wom 192 tk014 richard allen harvey lost hope wom 192 strings of sorrow west one music drama sound elements atmospheres main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) film score orchestral trailer tender reflective sad depressing poignant sad depressing sad sad depressing tragic serious serious disturbing dark movies human drama strings cello strings violin dark brooding melodies over repeating low string motifs. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="26376" name="Last Rites (a)" code="WOM 209 tk012" libraryid="6" albumid="565" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_209_Absolution/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Toby Y. Chu" comment="Sombre, lugubre et méditatif. Des mélodies de simple guitare acoustique mènent à des textures de cordes émouvantes." styleid="4" lengthseconds="147" time="2:27" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_209_Absolution/WOM209_trk012_LAST_RITES_(A)_Toby_Y._Chu_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), TITRE POUR TRAILER, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, DÉTENDU, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRAGIQUE, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, ABSTRAIT, SIMPLE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, FILMS, ART ET ESSAI, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, TRAILERS, DOCUMENTAIRE, CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE,, SERIEUX, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), DETENDU, DEPRIMANT, ACCELERE, AERIEN, DETECTIVE, ELECTRIQUE, MYSTERE Sombre, lugubre et méditatif. Des mélodies de simple guitare acoustique mènent à des textures de cordes émouvantes. wom 209 tk012 toby y. chu last rites (a) wom 209 absolution west one music film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer main tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) trailer track peaceful dreamy peaceful peaceful peaceful relaxed tender reflective tender sentimental sad depressing poignant sad depressing sad sad depressing tragic serious serious disturbing dark sombre and reflective. simple atmospheric guitar melodies lead to emotive string textures. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="4056" name="Sad Memories" code="TSH 022 tk021" libraryid="5" albumid="114" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_022_Human_Stories/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Michael Price" comment="Un thème méditatif et poignant au violoncelle et au piano. Même thématique que &quot;Memories in Sepia&quot;." styleid="10" lengthseconds="139" time="2:19" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_022_Human_Stories/TSH022_trk021_SAD_MEMORIES_Michael_Price_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="21" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CORDES, VIOLONCELLE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT Un thème méditatif et poignant au violoncelle et au piano. Même thématique que &quot;Memories in Sepia&quot;. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 022 tk021 michael price sad memories tsh 022 human stories the scoring house documentary film score orchestral documentary main documentary movies human drama sad depressing lonely sad depressing poignant sad depressing sad tender nostalgic tender reflective tender romantic tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) strings cello poignant reflective theme for cello and piano. thematic to 'memories in sepia'. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="4625" name="Personal Reflections" code="TSH 035 tk021" libraryid="5" albumid="125" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_035_A_Winner_is_Born/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Mark Lasker" comment="Une atmosphère d'introspection évoluant lentement." styleid="22" lengthseconds="133" time="2:13" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_035_A_Winner_is_Born/TSH035_trk021_PERSONAL_REFLECTIONS_Mark_Lasker_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="21" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, NEIGE, GLACE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MER, SOUS-MARIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, TROUBLANT, STÉRILE, TROUBLANT, FROID , TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, ÉTRANGE , TROUBLANT, BIZARRE, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, INTROSPECTIF, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRAGIQUE, SÉRIEUX, TENDRE, SONGEUR, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), ELEMENTS SONORES, SERIEUX, ATMOSPHERES, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), STERILE, INQUIETANT, ETRANGE, DEPRIMANT, AERIEN, ELEMENTS Une atmosphère d'introspection évoluant lentement. tsh 035 tk021 mark lasker personal reflections tsh 035 a winner is born the scoring house sport sound elements atmospheres main movies human drama nature wildlife the elements land snow ice nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife nature wildlife the elements sea underwater nature wildlife the elements sky aerial clouds disturbing barren disturbing cold introspective slowly evolving atmosphere. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="5952" name="The Hours (a)" code="TSH 058 tk010" libraryid="5" albumid="143" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_058_Ultimate_Piano/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Will Simcock / Curtis Frederick Schwartz" comment="Humeure, contemplative et émotionelle pour solo de piano." styleid="10" lengthseconds="173" time="2:53" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_058_Ultimate_Piano/TSH_058_trk010_THE_HOURS_(A)_Will_Simcock_Curtis_Frederick_Schwartz_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="10" tracktotal="" search="CLASSIQUE, STYLE MINIMALISTE, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, OCCASIONS SPÉCIALES, ÉVÈNEMENTS, FUNÉRAILLES, TROUBLANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, SÉRIEUX, ÉMOUVANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLAVIER, PIANO, SOLO, SERIEUX, OCCASIONS SPECIALES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, EMOUVANT, EVENEMENTS, EVENEMENT, FUNERAILLES, ELEMENTS Humeure, contemplative et émotionelle pour solo de piano. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 058 tk010 will simcock curtis frederick schwartz the hours (a) tsh 058 ultimate piano the scoring house documentary classical minimalist style main documentary movies human drama nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife special occasions events funeral disturbing sad depressing lonely sad depressing poignant sad depressing sad serious emotional movement rhythmic clock like contemplative emotional mood for solo piano. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="26488" name="Peaceful Perfection (a)" code="WOM 304 tk014" libraryid="6" albumid="568" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_304_Emotive_Minimalism/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Piano léger et mélodies éblouissantes de cordes solo, avec un accompagnement subtil." styleid="4" lengthseconds="229" time="3:49" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_304_Emotive_Minimalism/WOM304_trk014_PEACEFUL_PERFECTION_(A)_Richard_Allen_Harvey_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="14" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, CONTES, ENFANTS, CONTES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ENFANTS, CONTES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, AUTOMNE, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TENDRE, INNOCENT, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, ANGLETERRE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), AERIEN, ELEMENTS Piano léger et mélodies éblouissantes de cordes solo, avec un accompagnement subtil. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 304 tk014 richard allen harvey peaceful perfection (a) wom 304 emotive minimalism west one music film score orchestral children storytelling children storytelling film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic film score orchestral pastoral main movies children storytelling nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife the elements land rural gentle piano and stunning solo string melodies with subtle backing. main delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="7072" name="Celestial Journeys (b)" code="TSH 026A tk011" libraryid="5" albumid="162" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_026A_Dimensions/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Dave Hewson / Alexander Balanescu" comment="L'imagerie légère et nébuleuse de l'errance, au violon et au piano." styleid="4" lengthseconds="125" time="2:05" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_026A_Dimensions/TSH026A_trk011_CELESTIAL_JOURNEYS_(B)_Dave_Hewson_Alexander_Balanescu_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="11" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, ALTERNATIF, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, DIVIN, CÉLESTE, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TENDRE, LÉGER, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, CORDES, VIOLON, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), LEGER, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, CELESTE L'imagerie légère et nébuleuse de l'errance, au violon et au piano. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 026a tk011 dave hewson alexander balanescu celestial journeys (b) tsh 026a dimensions the scoring house film score orchestral sound elements atmospheres film score orchestral pastoral alternate nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife nature wildlife the elements sky light nebulous drifting imagery for violin and piano. alternative" waveformpath="" version="Alternative" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="26303" name="The Last Farewell (a)" code="WOM 177 tk012" libraryid="6" albumid="563" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_177_Reflections/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Déchirant et tendre. Des cordes légères et fragiles soutiennent des mélodies chaleureuses de piano." styleid="4" lengthseconds="155" time="2:35" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_177_Reflections/WOM177_trk012_THE_LAST_FAREWELL_(A)_Richard_Allen_Harvey_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, MÉDICAL, SCIENCES DE LA VIE, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRAGIQUE, TENDRE, LÉGER, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TENDRE, TENDRE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, VIOLON, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, LEGER, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, MEDICAL Déchirant et tendre. Des cordes légères et fragiles soutiennent des mélodies chaleureuses de piano. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 177 tk012 richard allen harvey the last farewell (a) wom 177 reflections west one music film score orchestral business corporate beds business corporate science technology film score orchestral trailer main business corporate documentary movies human drama nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife science technology industry medical life science disturbing mysterious heart-rending and tender. light fragile strings support warm piano melodies. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="18311" name="Final Tragedy" code="WOM 192 tk016" libraryid="6" albumid="388" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_192_Strings_of_Sorrow/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Lent et sombre. Des mélodies lugubres et mélancoliques sur des textures riches et puissantes." styleid="14" lengthseconds="243" time="4:03" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_192_Strings_of_Sorrow/WOM192_trk016_FINAL_TRAGEDY_Richard_Allen_Harvey_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="16" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, GUERRE, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, LUGUBRE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRAGIQUE, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, FORT, PUISSANT, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), CORDES, VIOLONCELLE, CORDES, VIOLON, ELEMENTS SONORES, SERIEUX, ATMOSPHERES, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), DEPRIMANT, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS Lent et sombre. Des mélodies lugubres et mélancoliques sur des textures riches et puissantes. wom 192 tk016 richard allen harvey final tragedy wom 192 strings of sorrow west one music drama sound elements atmospheres film score orchestral trailer main documentary movies crime detective mystery movies horror thriller movies human drama movies war disturbing dark disturbing mysterious sad depressing mournful sad depressing poignant sad depressing sad sad slow and sombre. dark mournful melodies over rich powerful textures. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="6910" name="The Last Salute (a)" code="TSH 001 tk007" libraryid="5" albumid="158" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_001_Cinematic_Adventures/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Un thème poignant et respectueux avec un développement orchestral guindé et des voix de sopranos tendres qui se lamentent." styleid="4" lengthseconds="224" time="3:44" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_001_Cinematic_Adventures/TSH001_trk007_THE_LAST_SALUTE_(A)_Richard_Allen_Harvey_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, GUERRE, MILITAIRE, HISTORIQUE, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, FILMS, GUERRE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, SÉRIEUX, DIGNE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TENDRE, TENDRE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, PATRIOTIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, PÉRIODE, PRÉ-20E SIÈCLE, 19E SIÈCLE, AMERIQUE DU NORD, PERIODE, SERIEUX, ETATS-UNIS, PRE-20E SIECLE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, DETERMINE, PERIODES, 20E SIECLE, 19E SIECLE Un thème poignant et respectueux avec un développement orchestral guindé et des voix de sopranos tendres qui se lamentent. tsh 001 tk007 richard allen harvey the last salute (a) tsh 001 cinematic adventures the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic main activities settings war military historical documentary biographical historical the arts movies human drama movies period historical costume drama movies war sad depressing poignant sad depressing sad poignant and respectful theme with dignified orchestral development and mourning tender sopranos. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="7344" name="The Fallen (c)" code="TSH 042 tk050" libraryid="5" albumid="167" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_042_A_Soldier's_Story/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Barnaby J Robson" comment="Un morceau poignant et solitaire pour planter le décor." styleid="4" lengthseconds="46" time="0:46" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_042_A_Soldier's_Story/TSH042_trk050_THE_FALLEN_(C)_Barnaby_J_Robson_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="50" tracktotal="" search="CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE, ALTERNATIF, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, GUERRE, MILITAIRE, GUERRE GÉNÉRALE, SCÈNES DE COMBAT, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, GUERRE, MILITAIRE, HISTORIQUE, PREMIERE GUERRE MONDIALE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, SÉRIEUX, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, 1900 - 1919, PERIODE, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, 20E SIECLE, GUERRE GENERALE, SCENES DE COMBAT Un morceau poignant et solitaire pour planter le décor. tsh 042 tk050 barnaby j robson the fallen (c) tsh 042 a soldier's story the scoring house film score orchestral classical classical styling alternate activities settings war military general war battle scenes activities settings war military historical world war 1 sad depressing poignant serious tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) time period modern era 20th century 1900 - 1919 poignant solitary scene-setter. alternative" waveformpath="" version="Alternative" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="6966" name="Epitaph" code="TSH 006 tk034" libraryid="5" albumid="159" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_006_Destiny/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Graham Donald Harry Preskett" comment="Une poignante complainte avec une voix solo et des cordes." styleid="4" lengthseconds="50" time="0:50" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_006_Destiny/TSH006_trk034_EPITAPH_Graham_Donald_Harry_Preskett_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="34" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, CHOEUR, CHOEUR FÉMININ, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRAGIQUE, SÉRIEUX, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, GUERRE, MILITAIRE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, OCCASIONS SPÉCIALES, ÉVÈNEMENTS, FUNÉRAILLES, VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, TEXTURE VOCALE,, PERIODE, SERIEUX, OCCASIONS SPECIALES, CHOEUR FEMININ, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, PERIODES, EVENEMENTS, FEMININ, EVENEMENT, DETECTIVE, FUNERAILLES, MYSTERE Une poignante complainte avec une voix solo et des cordes. tsh 006 tk034 graham donald harry preskett epitaph tsh 006 destiny the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer chorus female chorus main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) sad depressing poignant sad depressing tragic serious disturbing mysterious activities settings war military movies crime detective mystery movies human drama movies period historical poignant lament featuring solo voice and strings. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="22308" name="Fields of Wonder" code="WOM 277 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="479" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_277_Reconstruction_-_Textures/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Spirales glorieuses de lumière chatoyante." styleid="12" lengthseconds="90" time="1:30" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_277_Reconstruction_-_Textures/WOM277_trk001_FIELDS_OF_WONDER_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, DÉTENDU, TENDRE, LÉGER, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, DIVIN, CÉLESTE,, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), DETENDU, LEGER, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, CELESTE Spirales glorieuses de lumière chatoyante. wom 277 tk001 david ashton fields of wonder wom 277 reconstruction - textures west one music atmospheres sound elements atmospheres classical and semi classical symphony orchestra main tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) film score orchestral panoramic sound elements atmospheres peaceful dreamy peaceful peaceful peaceful relaxed tender light movement smooth aerial floating glorious swirls of shimmering light. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="23572" name="Pride of Nations (a)" code="WOM 306 tk012" libraryid="6" albumid="511" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_306_Success_Stories/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Paul Reeves (Gb 2)" comment="Thème émouvant représentant la fierté et la réussite. L'introduction à la clarinette se développe en un thème complet." styleid="11" lengthseconds="150" time="2:30" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_306_Success_Stories/WOM_306_trk012_PRIDE_OF_NATIONS_(A)_Paul_Reeves_(Gb_2)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="CLASSIQUE, CLASSIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, FAMILIAL, FILMS, WESTERN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, PATRIOTIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, FIER, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, PÉRIODE, PRÉ-20E SIÈCLE, 19E SIÈCLE, AMERIQUE DU NORD, PERIODE, ETATS-UNIS, PRE-20E SIECLE, 20E SIECLE, 19E SIECLE, ELEMENTS Thème émouvant représentant la fierté et la réussite. L'introduction à la clarinette se développe en un thème complet. wom 306 tk012 paul reeves (gb 2) pride of nations (a) wom 306 success stories west one music corporate business classical classical film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic main documentary biographical historical the arts movies family movies western nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside emotive theme depicting pride and achievement. solo clarinet introduction develops to full theme. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="18627" name="Strength and Honour (c)" code="WOM 198 tk024" libraryid="6" albumid="394" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_198_Homecoming_Heroes/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Patrick Thomas Hawes" comment="Une ouverture élégante et pastorale progresse vers un final expansif de grande envergure." styleid="14" lengthseconds="104" time="1:44" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_198_Homecoming_Heroes/WOM198_trk024_STRENGTH_AND_HONOUR_(C)_Patrick_Thomas_Hawes_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="24" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, ALTERNATIF, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, FILMS, IDYLLE, FILMS, GUERRE, OCCASIONS SPÉCIALES, ÉVÈNEMENTS, CERÉMONIEL, CÉRÉMONIE ROYALE, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, CONFIANT, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, PATRIOTIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, FORT EN ÉMOTIONS, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, PERIODE, SERIEUX, FORT EN EMOTIONS, OCCASIONS SPECIALES, DETERMINE, PERIODES, EVENEMENTS, EVENEMENT, ELEGANT, CEREMONIEL, CEREMONIE ROYALE Une ouverture élégante et pastorale progresse vers un final expansif de grande envergure. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede wom 198 tk024 patrick thomas hawes strength and honour (c) wom 198 homecoming heroes west one music drama film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic film score orchestral pastoral alternate movies period historical costume drama movies romance movies war special occasions events ceremonial royal ceremony trailers trailer track peaceful contented serious elegant pastoral opening builds to an expansive sweeping finale. alternative" waveformpath="" version="Alternative" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="26174" name="A New Beginning" code="WOM 098 tk013" libraryid="6" albumid="560" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_098_Emotive_Orchestral/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Bill Connor" comment="Un orchestre à cordes euphorisant et plein d'aspirations." styleid="4" lengthseconds="64" time="1:04" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_098_Emotive_Orchestral/WOM098_trk013_A_NEW_BEGINNING_Bill_Connor_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="13" tracktotal="" search="CLASSIQUE, CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIÈCLE, CLASSIQUE, STYLE MINIMALISTE, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FILMS, FAMILIAL, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CORDES, ORCHESTRE À CORDES, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, PERIODE, SERIEUX, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIECLE, A CORDES, ORCHESTRE A CORDES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETERMINE, PERIODES, 20E SIECLE Un orchestre à cordes euphorisant et plein d'aspirations. wom 098 tk013 bill connor a new beginning wom 098 emotive orchestral west one music film score orchestral classical classical 20th century classical style classical minimalist style main business corporate movies family movies fantasy adventure movies period historical costume drama serious determined tender romantic uplifting uplifting tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) strings aspirational and uplifting string orchestra. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="18623" name="The Final Journey (c)" code="WOM 198 tk020" libraryid="6" albumid="394" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_198_Homecoming_Heroes/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Patrick Thomas Hawes" comment="Des cordes enveloppantes et des cuivres exaltants." styleid="14" lengthseconds="125" time="2:05" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_198_Homecoming_Heroes/WOM198_trk020_THE_FINAL_JOURNEY_(C)_Patrick_Thomas_Hawes_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="20" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ALTERNATIF, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, OCCASIONS SPÉCIALES, ÉVÈNEMENTS, CERÉMONIEL, CÉRÉMONIE ROYALE, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, FORT, CONFIANT, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, PATRIOTIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, FORT EN ÉMOTIONS, TEMPO, 66 - 76 À L'AISE (ADAGIO), PÉRIODE, CIVILISATIONS ANCIENNES, ROME ANTIQUE (500 AV. J-C - 476 AP. J-C), PERIODE, FORT EN EMOTIONS, OCCASIONS SPECIALES, 66 - 76 A L'AISE (ADAGIO), EPIQUE, PERIODES, EVENEMENTS, EVENEMENT, CEREMONIEL, CEREMONIE ROYALE Des cordes enveloppantes et des cuivres exaltants. wom 198 tk020 patrick thomas hawes the final journey (c) wom 198 homecoming heroes west one music drama film score orchestral trailer alternate movies action adventure movies epic movies fantasy adventure movies period historical costume drama special occasions events ceremonial royal ceremony peaceful contented strong confident tender reflective tender warm uplifting rich strings and rousing brass. alternative" waveformpath="" version="Alternative" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="19409" name="Pride of the Nation (a)" code="WOM 213 tk009" libraryid="6" albumid="412" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_213_Classical_Evolutions/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Patrick Thomas Hawes" comment="Des cordes luxueuses, des cuivres nobles et de superbes bois constituent ce thème patriotique exaltant." styleid="25" lengthseconds="128" time="2:08" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_213_Classical_Evolutions/WOM213_trk009_PRIDE_OF_THE_NATION_(A)_Patrick_Thomas_Hawes_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="CLASSIQUE, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, ANGLETERRE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, PATRIOTIQUE, SÉRIEUX, DIGNE, SÉRIEUX, NOBLE, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, ART, ANTIQUITÉS, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, OCCASIONS SPÉCIALES, ÉVÈNEMENTS, CERÉMONIEL, CÉRÉMONIE ROYALE,, PERIODE, SERIEUX, OCCASIONS SPECIALES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), PERIODES, EVENEMENTS, EVENEMENT, CEREMONIEL, ELEMENTS, CEREMONIE ROYALE, ANTIQUITES Des cordes luxueuses, des cuivres nobles et de superbes bois constituent ce thème patriotique exaltant. wom 213 tk009 patrick thomas hawes pride of the nation (a) wom 213 classical evolutions west one music classical opera classical europe northern europe england main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) classical classical styling film score orchestral trailer uplifting patriotic serious dignified serious noble movies period historical costume drama tv radio leisure lifestyle arts antiques rich strings noble brass and gorgeous woodwind feature in this patriotic rousing theme. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="28024" name="Great Wilderness (c)" code="WOM 241A tk011" libraryid="6" albumid="598" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_241A_Natural_World_Landscapes/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Matt Norman (PRS)" comment="Un thème puissant de grande envergure. Versions sans percussions." styleid="26" lengthseconds="115" time="1:55" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_241A_Natural_World_Landscapes/WOM_241A_trk011_GREAT_WILDERNESS_(C)_Matt_Norman_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="11" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, UNDERSCORE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, FORT, PUISSANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, PATRIOTIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, FORT EN ÉMOTIONS, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA,, PERIODE, FORT EN EMOTIONS, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), EPIQUE, PERIODES, ELEMENTS Un thème puissant de grande envergure. Versions sans percussions. wom 241a tk011 matt norman (prs) great wilderness (c) wom 241a natural world: landscapes west one music nature wildlife volcanos nature wildlife planet earth natural world landscape exploration countryside deserts geology powerful sweeping theme. version without percussion. underscore" waveformpath="" version="Underscore" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="17137" name="Summer Sunrise (a)" code="WOM 165 tk002" libraryid="6" albumid="360" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_165_The_Pastoral_Album/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Patrick Thomas Hawes" comment="Optimiste et calme. Des cordes et des cuivres expansifs avec des phrases de flûte, harpe et guitare acoustique." styleid="26" lengthseconds="146" time="2:26" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_165_The_Pastoral_Album/WOM165_trk002_SUMMER_SUNRISE_(A)_Patrick_Thomas_Hawes_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="CLASSIQUE, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, PAISIBLE, CALME, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, ACOUSTIQUE, FILMS, IDYLLE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, PRINTEMPS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, ÉTÉ,, ELEMENTS, ETE Optimiste et calme. Des cordes et des cuivres expansifs avec des phrases de flûte, harpe et guitare acoustique. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 165 tk002 patrick thomas hawes summer sunrise (a) wom 165 the pastoral album west one music nature wildlife classical classical and semi classical symphony orchestra main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral pastoral uplifting optimistic peaceful calm tender romantic tender warm acoustic movies romance tv radio leisure lifestyle optimistic and calm. expansive strings and brass with flute harp and acoustic guitar phrases. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="16447" name="Return of the Hero" code="WOM 150 tk016" libraryid="6" albumid="345" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_150_Epic_Journeys/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Un retour au pays épique et grandiose." styleid="14" lengthseconds="222" time="3:42" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_150_Epic_Journeys/WOM150_trk016_RETURN_OF_THE_HERO_Richard_Allen_Harvey_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="16" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, FORT, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, OCCASIONS SPÉCIALES, ÉVÈNEMENTS, FUNÉRAILLES,, PERIODE, OCCASIONS SPECIALES, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), EPIQUE, PERIODES, EVENEMENTS, EVENEMENT, FUNERAILLES Un retour au pays épique et grandiose. wom 150 tk016 richard allen harvey return of the hero wom 150 epic journeys west one music drama film score orchestral trailer main tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) film score orchestral trailer strong epic movies epic movies period historical costume drama special occasions events funeral epic grand homecoming. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="18617" name="After the Victory (c)" code="WOM 198 tk014" libraryid="6" albumid="394" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_198_Homecoming_Heroes/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Patrick Thomas Hawes" comment="Des cordes chaleureuses et des cuivres généreux mènent à un climax vibrant." styleid="14" lengthseconds="129" time="2:09" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_198_Homecoming_Heroes/WOM198_trk014_AFTER_THE_VICTORY_(C)_Patrick_Thomas_Hawes_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="14" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, ALTERNATIF, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, FILMS, GUERRE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, OCCASIONS SPÉCIALES, ÉVÈNEMENTS, CERÉMONIEL, CÉRÉMONIE ROYALE, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, FORT, CONFIANT, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, PATRIOTIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, JAILLIR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, PERIODE, OCCASIONS SPECIALES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), PERIODES, EVENEMENTS, EVENEMENT, CEREMONIEL, ELEMENTS, CEREMONIE ROYALE Des cordes chaleureuses et des cuivres généreux mènent à un climax vibrant. wom 198 tk014 patrick thomas hawes after the victory (c) wom 198 homecoming heroes west one music drama film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic alternate movies period historical costume drama movies war nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama special occasions events ceremonial royal ceremony trailers trailer track peaceful contented warm strings and rich brass build to a stirring climax. alternative" waveformpath="" version="Alternative" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="469" name="Absolute Magnitude (b)" code="FEM 007 tk016" libraryid="2" albumid="14" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_007_Ultimatum/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jesper Kyd" comment="Une bande-annonce orchestrale épique et envoûtante. Une ouverture émouvante conduit à un thème vaillant avec des percussions massives." styleid="2" lengthseconds="132" time="2:12" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_007_Ultimatum/FEM007_trk016_ABSOLUTE_MAGNITUDE_(B)_Jesper_Kyd_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="16" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, ALTERNATIF, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, DRAMATIQUE, PASSIONNÉ, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, ÉPIQUE, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EVOLUTIF, FORT EN ÉMOTIONS, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), PÉRIODE, CIVILISATIONS ANCIENNES, ROME ANTIQUE (500 AV. J-C - 476 AP. J-C), PERIODE, FORT EN EMOTIONS, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), PASSIONNE, DEPRIMANT, EPIQUE, PERIODES, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Une bande-annonce orchestrale épique et envoûtante. Une ouverture émouvante conduit à un thème vaillant avec des percussions massives. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede fem 007 tk016 jesper kyd absolute magnitude (b) fem 007 ultimatum fired earth music trailer film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic alternate movies action adventure movies epic movies period historical costume drama nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama trailers trailer track disturbing tense dramatic intense dramatic sweeping epic orchestral trailer cue. emotive opening leads into valiant theme with huge percussion. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
    <item id="6907" name="The High Plains (a)" code="TSH 001 tk004" libraryid="5" albumid="158" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_001_Cinematic_Adventures/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Des figures méditatives au piano et des cordes luxueuses, menant à un développement épique et panoramique et une reprise profonde." styleid="4" lengthseconds="253" time="4:13" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_001_Cinematic_Adventures/TSH001_trk004_THE_HIGH_PLAINS_(A)_Richard_Allen_Harvey_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, SÉRIEUX, ATTENTIONNÉ, FORT, ÉPIQUE, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, PATRIOTIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EVOLUTIF, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, PÉRIODE, PRÉ-20E SIÈCLE, 19E SIÈCLE, AMERIQUE DU NORD, PERIODE, SERIEUX, ETATS-UNIS, PRE-20E SIECLE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, ATTENTIONNE, EPIQUE, 20E SIECLE, 19E SIECLE, ELEMENTS, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Des figures méditatives au piano et des cordes luxueuses, menant à un développement épique et panoramique et une reprise profonde. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 001 tk004 richard allen harvey the high plains (a) tsh 001 cinematic adventures the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic main documentary biographical historical the arts movies human drama movies romance nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama trailers trailer track sad depressing poignant sad depressing sad pensive piano figures to expansive strings building to epic panoramic development and thoughtful reprise. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="7132" name="Our Beautiful World" code="TSH 029 tk014" libraryid="5" albumid="164" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_029_Symphonic_Fantasia/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Arthur Rhodes" comment="Un thème spacieux, majestueux et sincère avec une conclusion calme." styleid="4" lengthseconds="112" time="1:52" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_029_Symphonic_Fantasia/TSH029_trk014_OUR_BEAUTIFUL_WORLD_Simon_Arthur_Rhodes_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="14" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MER, PAYSAGE MARIN, DRAMATIQUE, PAISIBLE, CALME, FORT, MAJESTUEUX, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, ANGLETERRE, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, AMERIQUE DU NORD, ETATS-UNIS, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), AERIEN, ELEMENTS Un thème spacieux, majestueux et sincère avec une conclusion calme. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz tsh 029 tk014 simon arthur rhodes our beautiful world tsh 029 symphonic fantasia the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic main documentary biographical historical the arts movies fantasy adventure nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral nature wildlife broad majestic heart-felt theme with calm conclusion. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="6987" name="Forged by Nature" code="TSH 011 tk020" libraryid="5" albumid="160" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_011_Orchestral_Elements/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Bill Connor" comment="Un thème puissant montant en flèche, thématique pour Places of Heart (a)." styleid="4" lengthseconds="98" time="1:38" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_011_Orchestral_Elements/TSH011_trk020_FORGED_BY_NATURE_Bill_Connor_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="20" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, FORT, PUISSANT, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, FLASH INFO, BULLETIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA,, PERIODE, PERIODES, ACTUALITES, ELEMENTS Un thème puissant montant en flèche, thématique pour Places of Heart (a). tsh 011 tk020 bill connor forged by nature tsh 011 orchestral elements the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer classical and semi classical symphony orchestra main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) film score orchestral panoramic strong powerful movies period historical costume drama tv radio news and current affairs breaking news bulletin nature wildlife powerful surging theme thematic to places of the heart (a). main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="4400" name="Attack Formation" code="TSH 032A tk021" libraryid="5" albumid="121" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_032A_Big_Bang_Percussion/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="John Gregory Knowles" comment="Des motifs incessants de tambour militaire." styleid="2" lengthseconds="107" time="1:47" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_032A_Big_Bang_Percussion/TSH032A_trk021_ATTACK_FORMATION_John_Gregory_Knowles_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="21" tracktotal="" search="MARCHES, ORCHESTRE MILITAIRE, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, GUERRE, MILITAIRE, GUERRE GÉNÉRALE, SCÈNES DE COMBAT, FORT, IMPLACABLE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, DÉFILÉ, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COURANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 40, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), 20E SIECLE, DEFILE, ANNEES 40, GUERRE GENERALE, SCENES DE COMBAT Des motifs incessants de tambour militaire. tsh 032a tk021 john gregory knowles attack formation tsh 032a big bang percussion the scoring house trailer marches military band main activities settings war military general war battle scenes strong relentless movement rhythmic marching movement rhythmic running tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) time period modern era 20th century 1940s relentless military drum patterns. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="13672" name="The Power and the Glory (b)" code="WOM 085 tk022" libraryid="6" albumid="275" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_085_Epic_Action_Trailers/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Dan Graham" comment="Une introduction au style militaire menaçant, progressant au fil du morceau." styleid="2" lengthseconds="108" time="1:48" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_085_Epic_Action_Trailers/WOM085_trk022_THE_POWER_AND_THE_GLORY_(B)_Dan_Graham_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="22" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ALTERNATIF, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, ACTION, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, EVOLUTIF, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), CORDES, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Une introduction au style militaire menaçant, progressant au fil du morceau. wom 085 tk022 dan graham the power and the glory (b) wom 085 epic action trailers west one music trailer film score orchestral trailer alternate movies action adventure movies action drama trailers trailer track scary ominous building tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) strings ominous military style introduction building throughout. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="674" name="Centaurus (b)" code="FEM 009 tk020" libraryid="2" albumid="21" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_009_Immortality/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Ryan Amon" comment="Des percussions et cordes pour démarrer ce morceau de bande-annonce énergique qui rappelle la cavalerie en partance pour la bataille et conduit à un final puissant." styleid="2" lengthseconds="105" time="1:45" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_009_Immortality/FEM009_trk020_CENTAURUS_(B)_Ryan_Amon_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="20" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, ALTERNATIF, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, BACK END, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, GUERRE, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, AGRESSIF, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, PATRIOTIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EVOLUTIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, DÉFILÉ, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, CHEVAUCHER, ÉQUESTRE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, PÉRIODE, CIVILISATIONS ANCIENNES, ROME ANTIQUE (500 AV. J-C - 476 AP. J-C), PÉRIODE, ÈRES CULTURELLES, GUERRE DE SÉCESSION (1861 - 1865), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, PERIODE, SERIEUX, ERES CULTURELLES, DETERMINE, ENERGIQUE, EPIQUE, GUERRE DE SECESSION (1861 - 1865), 20E SIECLE, DEFILE, EQUESTRE, GUERRE DE SECESSION, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Des percussions et cordes pour démarrer ce morceau de bande-annonce énergique qui rappelle la cavalerie en partance pour la bataille et conduit à un final puissant. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede fem 009 tk020 ryan amon centaurus (b) fem 009 immortality fired earth music trailer film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic alternate movies action adventure movies back end movies epic movies war trailers trailer track disturbing tense dramatic aggressive scary ominous serious determined serious serious strong confident strong percussion and strings open this energetic trailer cue reminiscent of cavalry going into battle building to all-powerful back end. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
    <item id="28017" name="Rugged Landscapes (a)" code="WOM 241A tk004" libraryid="6" albumid="598" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_241A_Natural_World_Landscapes/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Matt Norman (PRS)" comment="Intrépide et dramatique, avec des motifs de cordes stridents, des percussions puissantes et des mélodies de cuivres vibrantes." styleid="26" lengthseconds="133" time="2:13" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_241A_Natural_World_Landscapes/WOM_241A_trk004_RUGGED_LANDSCAPES_(A)_Matt_Norman_(PRS)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, TRAILERS, TV, RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, TENDU, FORT, PUISSANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), TELE REALITE, ELEMENTS Intrépide et dramatique, avec des motifs de cordes stridents, des percussions puissantes et des mélodies de cuivres vibrantes. wom 241a tk004 matt norman (prs) rugged landscapes (a) wom 241a natural world: landscapes west one music nature wildlife volcanos nature wildlife planet earth natural world landscape exploration countryside deserts geology bold and dramatic featuring strident string motifs powerful percussion and stirring brass melodies. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="7032" name="March of History" code="TSH 024 tk028" libraryid="5" albumid="161" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_024_Conflict/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Everard Lawrence Wells / Robert John Foster" comment="Une progression mesurée et puissante." styleid="4" lengthseconds="140" time="2:20" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_024_Conflict/TSH024_trk028_MARCH_OF_HISTORY_Richard_Everard_Lawrence_Wells_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="28" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), FORT, PUISSANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INSISTANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, DÉFILÉ, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, GUERRE, MILITAIRE, HISTORIQUE, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, FILMS, GUERRE,, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), PERIODES, DEFILE Une progression mesurée et puissante. tsh 024 tk028 richard everard lawrence wells robert john foster march of history tsh 024 conflict the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) strong powerful movement rhythmic insistent movement rhythmic marching activities settings war military historical movies period historical costume drama movies war measured powerful build. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="18633" name="Rules of Engagement (b)" code="WOM 198 tk030" libraryid="6" albumid="394" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_198_Homecoming_Heroes/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Patrick Thomas Hawes" comment="En route pour la bataille. Tension grandissante, accompagnée de tambours tribaux." styleid="14" lengthseconds="93" time="1:33" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_198_Homecoming_Heroes/WOM198_trk030_RULES_OF_ENGAGEMENT_(B)_Patrick_Thomas_Hawes_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="30" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ALTERNATIF, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, FORT, CONFIANT, EVOLUTIF, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETERMINE, EPIQUE, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION En route pour la bataille. Tension grandissante, accompagnée de tambours tribaux. wom 198 tk030 patrick thomas hawes rules of engagement (b) wom 198 homecoming heroes west one music drama film score orchestral trailer alternate movies action adventure movies action drama movies epic movies fantasy adventure trailers trailer track scary ominous serious determined serious serious strong confident building tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) the road to battle. building in tension featuring big tribal drums. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="16438" name="Let the Battle Commence" code="WOM 150 tk007" libraryid="6" albumid="345" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_150_Epic_Journeys/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Un thème d'action intense et dramatique." styleid="14" lengthseconds="253" time="4:13" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_150_Epic_Journeys/WOM150_trk007_LET_THE_BATTLE_COMMENCE_Richard_Allen_Harvey_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, FILMS, GUERRE,, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), EPIQUE, PERIODES Un thème d'action intense et dramatique. wom 150 tk007 richard allen harvey let the battle commence wom 150 epic journeys west one music drama film score orchestral trailer main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) dramatic intense movies action adventure movies action drama movies epic movies period historical costume drama movies war dramatic intense action theme. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="7041" name="Epic Battle (b)" code="TSH 024 tk037" libraryid="5" albumid="161" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_024_Conflict/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Everard Lawrence Wells / Robert John Foster" comment="Une tension profonde et menaçante." styleid="4" lengthseconds="71" time="1:11" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_024_Conflict/TSH024_trk037_EPIC_BATTLE_(B)_Richard_Everard_Lawrence_Wells_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="37" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, UNDERSCORE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, GUERRE, MILITAIRE, HISTORIQUE, ANCIEN, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, GUERRE, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, FORT, HÉROIQUE, FORT, IMPLACABLE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PÉRIODE, CIVILISATIONS ANCIENNES, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), EPIQUE, HEROIQUE Une tension profonde et menaçante. tsh 024 tk037 richard everard lawrence wells robert john foster epic battle (b) tsh 024 conflict the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer underscore activities settings war military historical ancient movies action drama movies epic movies war trailers trailer track strong heroic strong relentless tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) time period ancient civilizations deep ominous tension. underscore" waveformpath="" version="Underscore" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="18628" name="Battle Draws Near (b)" code="WOM 198 tk025" libraryid="6" albumid="394" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_198_Homecoming_Heroes/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Patrick Thomas Hawes" comment="Tendu et dramatique, avec de puissantes percussions." styleid="14" lengthseconds="91" time="1:31" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_198_Homecoming_Heroes/WOM198_trk025_BATTLE_DRAWS_NEAR_(B)_Patrick_Thomas_Hawes_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="25" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ALTERNATIF, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, TENDU, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, PUISSANT, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), PÉRIODE, CIVILISATIONS ANCIENNES, ROME ANTIQUE (500 AV. J-C - 476 AP. J-C), PERIODE, SERIEUX, DETERMINE, EPIQUE Tendu et dramatique, avec de puissantes percussions. wom 198 tk025 patrick thomas hawes battle draws near (b) wom 198 homecoming heroes west one music drama film score orchestral trailer alternate movies action adventure movies action drama movies epic movies fantasy adventure trailers trailer track disturbing tense scary ominous serious determined strong confident strong powerful tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) time period tense and dramatic with powerful bold percussion. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="7005" name="The Invaders" code="TSH 024 tk001" libraryid="5" albumid="161" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_024_Conflict/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Everard Lawrence Wells / Robert John Foster" comment="Une avancée puissante et résolue." styleid="4" lengthseconds="135" time="2:15" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_024_Conflict/TSH024_trk001_THE_INVADERS_Richard_Everard_Lawrence_Wells_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, GUERRE, MILITAIRE, HISTORIQUE, ANCIEN, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, FILMS, GUERRE, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, PUISSANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PÉRIODE, CIVILISATIONS ANCIENNES, ROME ANTIQUE (500 AV. J-C - 476 AP. J-C), PERIODE, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETERMINE, EPIQUE, PERIODES Une avancée puissante et résolue. tsh 024 tk001 richard everard lawrence wells robert john foster the invaders tsh 024 conflict the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer main activities settings war military historical ancient movies epic movies period historical costume drama movies war trailers trailer track scary ominous serious determined strong determined strong powerful tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) powerful determined advance. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="6950" name="The Final Conflict (a)" code="TSH 006 tk018" libraryid="5" albumid="159" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_006_Destiny/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Graham Donald Harry Preskett" comment="Une introduction menaçante menant à une progression dramatique vers une conclusion solennelle." styleid="4" lengthseconds="189" time="3:09" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_006_Destiny/TSH006_trk018_THE_FINAL_CONFLICT_(A)_Graham_Donald_Harry_Preskett_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="18" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, GUERRE, MILITAIRE, GUERRE GÉNÉRALE, SCÈNES DE COMBAT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRAGIQUE, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, SÉRIEUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EMBLÉMATIQUE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PÉRIODE, ÈRES CULTURELLES, GUERRE DE SÉCESSION (1861 - 1865), PERIODE, SERIEUX, ERES CULTURELLES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, GUERRE DE SECESSION (1861 - 1865), EMBLEMATIQUE, GUERRE GENERALE, SCENES DE COMBAT, GUERRE DE SECESSION Une introduction menaçante menant à une progression dramatique vers une conclusion solennelle. tsh 006 tk018 graham donald harry preskett the final conflict (a) tsh 006 destiny the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer main activities settings war military general war battle scenes sad depressing poignant sad depressing sad sad depressing tragic scary ominous serious uplifting anthemic tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) time period cultural eras ominous introduction to dramatic build and anthemic conclusion. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="465" name="Precession (b)" code="FEM 007 tk012" libraryid="2" albumid="14" albumartpath="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_007_Ultimatum/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jesper Kyd" comment="Une bande-annonce épique. Des cordes dark plantent le décor d'un morceau percussif avec des crescendos de cuivres." styleid="2" lengthseconds="112" time="1:52" samplefile="Music/Fired Earth Music/FEM_007_Ultimatum/FEM007_trk012_PRECESSION_(B)_Jesper_Kyd_Fired_Earth_Music_Limited.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, ALTERNATIF, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, BACK END, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, AGRESSIF, DRAMATIQUE, DANGEUREUX, DRAMATIQUE, VIOLENT, EFFRAYANT, MENAÇANT, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, SÉRIEUX, DÉTERMINÉ, FORT, CONFIANT, FORT, ÉPIQUE, EVOLUTIF, PERCUSSIF, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PÉRIODE, CIVILISATIONS ANCIENNES, ROME ANTIQUE (500 AV. J-C - 476 AP. J-C), PERIODE, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), MENACANT, DETERMINE, EPIQUE, PERIODES, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Une bande-annonce épique. Des cordes dark plantent le décor d'un morceau percussif avec des crescendos de cuivres. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede fem 007 tk012 jesper kyd precession (b) fem 007 ultimatum fired earth music trailer film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic alternate movies action adventure movies back end movies epic movies period historical costume drama trailers trailer track disturbing dark disturbing tense dramatic aggressive dramatic dangerous dramatic epic trailer cue. dark strings set up for giant percussive cue with brass swells. without vocal" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="Fired Earth Music Limited" cae="00615215284"/>
    <item id="7203" name="Field of Battle (a)" code="TSH 037A tk019" libraryid="5" albumid="165" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_037A_Unfolding_History/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Robert John Foster" comment="Des formations militaires puissantes." styleid="4" lengthseconds="151" time="2:31" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_037A_Unfolding_History/TSH037A_trk019_FIELD_OF_BATTLE_(A)_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="19" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PÉRIODE, CIVILISATIONS ANCIENNES, ROME ANTIQUE (500 AV. J-C - 476 AP. J-C), PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), FORT, PUISSANT, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, GUERRE, MILITAIRE, HISTORIQUE, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, FILMS, GUERRE,, PERIODE, PERIODES Des formations militaires puissantes. tsh 037a tk019 robert john foster field of battle (a) tsh 037a unfolding history the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer time period ancient civilizations ancient rome (500 bc - 476 ad) main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) strong powerful activities settings war military historical movies period historical costume drama movies war powerful military formations. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="7024" name="Machines Of War" code="TSH 024 tk020" libraryid="5" albumid="161" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_024_Conflict/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Everard Lawrence Wells / Robert John Foster" comment="Une avancée militaire vigoureuse." styleid="4" lengthseconds="143" time="2:23" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_024_Conflict/TSH024_trk020_MACHINES_OF_WAR_Richard_Everard_Lawrence_Wells_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="20" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, FILMS, GUERRE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), EPIQUE Une avancée militaire vigoureuse. tsh 024 tk020 richard everard lawrence wells robert john foster machines of war tsh 024 conflict the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer main movies action adventure movies epic movies fantasy adventure movies war tv radio sports strong prestigious movement rhythmic driving movement rhythmic rugged tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) forceful military advance. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="7208" name="Gregorian Echoes" code="TSH 037A tk024" libraryid="5" albumid="165" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_037A_Unfolding_History/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Robert John Foster" comment="Des voix monastiques et atmosphériques." styleid="4" lengthseconds="130" time="2:10" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_037A_Unfolding_History/TSH037A_trk024_GREGORIAN_ECHOES_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="24" tracktotal="" search="RELIGIEUX, RELIGIEUX, CHRÉTIEN, CATHOLIQUE, PRINCIPAL, RELIGION &amp; ENVIRONNEMENTS RELIGIEUX, SÉRIEUX, SACRÉ, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), VOCAL, TEXTURES VOCALES, CHANT, GÉNÉRIQUE, FORME CLASSIQUE, CHANT GRÉGORIEN, PÉRIODE, CIVILISATIONS ANCIENNES, PERIODE, SERIEUX, CHRETIEN, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), SACRE, CHANT GREGORIEN, GENERIQUE Des voix monastiques et atmosphériques. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 037a tk024 robert john foster gregorian echoes tsh 037a unfolding history the scoring house film score orchestral religious religious christian catholic main religion &amp; religious settings serious sacred tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) vocals vocal textures chanting generic classical form gregorian chant time period ancient civilizations atmospheric monastic voices. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="24407" name="Shadowlands (a)" code="WOM 322 tk011" libraryid="6" albumid="526" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_322_Cinematic_Drama/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Martin Tillmann" comment="Drones de mauvais augure et sound design troublant, évolutif." styleid="14" lengthseconds="154" time="2:34" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_322_Cinematic_Drama/WOM322_trk011_SHADOWLANDS_(A)_Martin_Tillmann_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="11" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, DRONES, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, SOUND DESIGN, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, TROUBLANT, ANXIEUX, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, EFFRAYANT, MENAÇANT, SÉRIEUX, INQUIET, SÉRIEUX, ÉMOUVANT, SÉRIEUX, SOLENNEL, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, CORDES, VIOLONCELLE, ELEMENTS SONORES, FORMATIONS GENERALES, SERIEUX, ATMOSPHERES, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, MENACANT, EMOUVANT, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS Drones de mauvais augure et sound design troublant, évolutif. wom 322 tk011 martin tillmann shadowlands (a) wom 322 cinematic drama west one music drama film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral documentary sound elements atmospheres sound elements atmospheres drones sound elements atmospheres sound design main movies crime detective mystery movies espionage spy movies human drama movies urban drama tv radio ominous drones and unnerving evolving sound design. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="8202" name="Pulsing Threat (a)" code="TSH 051 tk015" libraryid="5" albumid="177" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_051_Nearfield/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Everard Lawrence Wells / Robert John Foster" comment="Courrants sous-jacents sombres et insidieux." styleid="10" lengthseconds="111" time="1:51" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_051_Nearfield/TSH051_trk015_PULSING_THREAT_(A)_Richard_Everard_Lawrence_Wells_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="15" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, TV, RADIO, ACTUALITÉS, JOURNALISME D'INVESTIGATION, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, SÉRIEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, PULSATION, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETECTIVE, ACTUALITES, MYSTERE Courrants sous-jacents sombres et insidieux. tsh 051 tk015 richard everard lawrence wells robert john foster pulsing threat (a) tsh 051 nearfield the scoring house documentary business corporate science technology main documentary science technology movies crime detective mystery science technology industry tv radio news and current affairs investigative reporting tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing dark serious movement dark insidious undercurrents. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="26669" name="Mist" code="WOM 012 tk004" libraryid="6" albumid="572" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_012_Clarity/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Daryl Neil Alexander Griffith" comment="Un motif de piano simple et méditatif avec des cordes suspendues." styleid="4" lengthseconds="156" time="2:36" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_012_Clarity/WOM012_trk004_MIST_Daryl_Neil_Alexander_Griffith_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="CLASSIQUE, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIÈCLE, CLASSIQUE, STYLE MINIMALISTE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, ABSTRAIT, SIMPLE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, DOCUMENTAIRE, CLAVIER, PIANO,, PERIODE, STYLE CLASSIQUE DU 20E SIECLE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, 20E SIECLE Un motif de piano simple et méditatif avec des cordes suspendues. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 012 tk004 daryl neil alexander griffith mist wom 012 clarity west one music film score orchestral classical time period modern era 20th century main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) classical 20th century classical style classical minimalist style film score orchestral trailer tender reflective sad depressing poignant sad depressing sad abstract simple movies human drama simple reflective piano pattern with suspended strings. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="2814" name="Waiting and Watching" code="TSH 003 tk001" libraryid="5" albumid="94" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_003_Deeper_Minimal/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Robert John Foster" comment="Fond sonore raffiné et plein de suspense." styleid="12" lengthseconds="72" time="1:12" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_003_Deeper_Minimal/TSH003_trk001_WAITING_AND_WATCHING_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, CHAUD, DÉSERT, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, ESPACE, INTERSIDÉRAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, FROID, STÉRILE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MÉTÉO, SOLEIL, CHALEUR, TROUBLANT, STÉRILE, TROUBLANT, FROID , TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SURNATUREL, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), EFFETS SONORES, SIFFLEMENT, CRÉPITEMENT, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), STERILE, INQUIETANT, CREPITEMENT, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS, METEO, DESERT, ETE, INTERSIDERAL Fond sonore raffiné et plein de suspense. tsh 003 tk001 robert john foster waiting and watching tsh 003 deeper minimal the scoring house atmospheres sound elements atmospheres business corporate science technology main movies crime detective mystery nature wildlife the elements land hot desert nature wildlife the elements sky space outer space nature wildlife the elements weather cold barren nature wildlife understated suspenseful bed. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="7035" name="Drums of War" code="TSH 024 tk031" libraryid="5" albumid="161" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_024_Conflict/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Everard Lawrence Wells / Robert John Foster" comment="Des percussions militaires menaçantes." styleid="4" lengthseconds="65" time="1:05" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_024_Conflict/TSH024_trk031_DRUMS_OF_WAR_Richard_Everard_Lawrence_Wells_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="31" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, 1900 - 1919, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 40, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), RELIGIEUX, EFFRAYANT, MENAÇANT, DRAMATIQUE, DANGEUREUX, MOUVEMENT, IRRÉGULIER, ÉLANCEMENT, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, GUERRE, MILITAIRE, GUERRE GÉNÉRALE, SCÈNES DE COMBAT, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, GUERRE, MILITAIRE, HISTORIQUE, PREMIERE GUERRE MONDIALE, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, GUERRE, MILITAIRE, HISTORIQUE, SECONDE GUERRE MONDIALE, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, RELIGION &amp; ENVIRONNEMENTS RELIGIEUX, BATTERIE,, PERIODE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), MENACANT, IRREGULIER, PERIODES, 20E SIECLE, ELANCEMENT, ANNEES 40, GUERRE GENERALE, SCENES DE COMBAT Des percussions militaires menaçantes. tsh 024 tk031 richard everard lawrence wells robert john foster drums of war tsh 024 conflict the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer time period modern era 20th century 1900 - 1919 time period modern era 20th century 1940s main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) religious scary menacing dramatic dangerous movement irregular stabbing activities settings war military general war threatening military percussion. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="22357" name="Trepidation" code="WOM 277 tk050" libraryid="6" albumid="479" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_277_Reconstruction_-_Textures/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="La pression monte !" styleid="12" lengthseconds="102" time="1:42" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_277_Reconstruction_-_Textures/WOM277_trk050_TREPIDATION_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="50" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, FORT, ÉNERGIQUE, FORT, IMPLACABLE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, CHEVAUCHER, ÉQUESTRE, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), STYLE VINTAGE, PERIODE, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), ENERGIQUE, PERIODES, EQUESTRE La pression monte ! wom 277 tk050 david ashton trepidation wom 277 reconstruction - textures west one music atmospheres film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral trailer main movies period historical costume drama strong energetic strong relentless movement rhythmic riding equestrian tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) vintage style the pressure is on...! main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="26483" name="Feeling the Pressure (a)" code="WOM 304 tk009" libraryid="6" albumid="568" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_304_Emotive_Minimalism/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Une atmosphère chargée d'anticipation: motifs tendus de cordes et piano réverberant. Tension dramatique à 1:04." styleid="4" lengthseconds="164" time="2:44" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_304_Emotive_Minimalism/WOM304_trk009_FEELING_THE_PRESSURE_(A)_Richard_Allen_Harvey_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, TROUBLANT, TENDU, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, INSISTANT, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, RÉPÉTITIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA,, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), REPETITIF, ACCELERE, ELEMENTS Une atmosphère chargée d'anticipation: motifs tendus de cordes et piano réverberant. Tension dramatique à 1:04. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 304 tk009 richard allen harvey feeling the pressure (a) wom 304 emotive minimalism west one music film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer classical and semi classical symphony orchestra main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic disturbing tense movement rhythmic insistent movement rhythmic repetitive movement rhythmic tense string patterns and reverberant piano build an atmosphere of anticipation. dramatic tension builds at 1:04. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="3112" name="Darker Waters" code="TSH 008 tk003" libraryid="5" albumid="99" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_008_Ambient_Spirit/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Everard Lawrence Wells / Robert John Foster" comment="Un fond sonore anxieux et dérangeant avec des ponctuations graves." styleid="15" lengthseconds="74" time="1:14" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_008_Ambient_Spirit/TSH008_trk003_DARKER_WATERS_Richard_Everard_Lawrence_Wells_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, TROUBLANT, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, NERVEUX, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, DOCUMENTAIRE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MER, SOUS-MARIN, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, ATMOSPHÈRE SCIENTIFIQUE,, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), INQUIETANT, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS, ATMOSPHERE SCIENTIFIQUE Un fond sonore anxieux et dérangeant avec des ponctuations graves. tsh 008 tk003 richard everard lawrence wells robert john foster darker waters tsh 008 ambient spirit the scoring house ambient chill sound elements atmospheres main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) business corporate science technology disturbing dark disturbing disturbing disturbing eerie disturbing mysterious edgy movies crime detective mystery tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama documentary edgy disturbing bed with low punctuations. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="7016" name="State of Alert (a)" code="TSH 024 tk012" libraryid="5" albumid="161" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_024_Conflict/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Everard Lawrence Wells / Robert John Foster" comment="Une progression dark et inquiétante." styleid="4" lengthseconds="104" time="1:44" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_024_Conflict/TSH024_trk012_STATE_OF_ALERT_(A)_Richard_Everard_Lawrence_Wells_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), STYLE VINTAGE, TROUBLANT, SOMBRE, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, EFFRAYANT, HORREUR, EFFRAYANT, MENAÇANT, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, DRAMATIQUE, DANGEUREUX, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, GUERRE, MILITAIRE, HISTORIQUE, GUERRE MODERNE, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER,, PERIODE, MENACANT, 20E SIECLE Une progression dark et inquiétante. tsh 024 tk012 richard everard lawrence wells robert john foster state of alert (a) tsh 024 conflict the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer time period modern era 20th century main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) vintage style disturbing dark disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense scary horror scary menacing scary ominous dramatic dangerous activities settings war military dark threatening build. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="22353" name="Black Waves" code="WOM 277 tk046" libraryid="6" albumid="479" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_277_Reconstruction_-_Textures/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Ashton" comment="Des pulsations sinistres et inquiétantes de cordes graves avec des touches de cuivres menaçantes." styleid="12" lengthseconds="87" time="1:27" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_277_Reconstruction_-_Textures/WOM277_trk046_BLACK_WAVES_David_Ashton_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="46" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), SÉRIEUX, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, EFFRAYANT, MENAÇANT, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE,, PERIODE, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), MENACANT, PERIODES, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS Des pulsations sinistres et inquiétantes de cordes graves avec des touches de cuivres menaçantes. wom 277 tk046 david ashton black waves wom 277 reconstruction - textures west one music atmospheres film score orchestral trailer main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) serious disturbing mysterious disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense scary menacing scary ominous movies action adventure movies crime detective mystery movies human drama movies period historical brooding ominous low string pulses with touches of menacing brass. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="7154" name="Grand Spectacular (e)" code="TSH 029 tk036" libraryid="5" albumid="164" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_029_Symphonic_Fantasia/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Arthur Rhodes" comment="Une progression ponctuée imposante." styleid="4" lengthseconds="39" time="0:39" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_029_Symphonic_Fantasia/TSH029_trk036_GRAND_SPECTACULAR_(E)_Simon_Arthur_Rhodes_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="36" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ALTERNATIF, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, FILMS, SCIENCE FICTION, FILMS, GUERRE, TROUBLANT, TENDU, FORT, CONFIANT, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CUIVRES, CLAIRON, FANFARE, PÉRIODE, ÈRES CULTURELLES, SECONDE GUERRE MONDIALE (1939 - 1945), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, ANNÉES 90, PERIODE, ERES CULTURELLES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), EPIQUE, 20E SIECLE, ANNEES 90 Une progression ponctuée imposante. tsh 029 tk036 simon arthur rhodes grand spectacular (e) tsh 029 symphonic fantasia the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer alternate movies action adventure movies epic movies fantasy adventure movies science fiction movies war disturbing tense strong confident tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) brass bugle fanfare time period cultural eras punctuated imposing build. cut down" waveformpath="" version="Cut Down" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="7153" name="Grand Spectacular (d)" code="TSH 029 tk035" libraryid="5" albumid="164" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_029_Symphonic_Fantasia/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Arthur Rhodes" comment="Des phrases puissantes et ponctuées de percussions." styleid="4" lengthseconds="41" time="0:41" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_029_Symphonic_Fantasia/TSH029_trk035_GRAND_SPECTACULAR_(D)_Simon_Arthur_Rhodes_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="35" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, ÉLÉMENTS MUSICAUX, ALTERNATIF, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, GUERRE, MILITAIRE, HISTORIQUE, FORT, PUISSANT, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, ELEMENTS MUSICAUX, ELEMENTS Des phrases puissantes et ponctuées de percussions. tsh 029 tk035 simon arthur rhodes grand spectacular (d) tsh 029 symphonic fantasia the scoring house film score orchestral sound elements atmospheres music elements alternate activities settings war military historical strong powerful tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) punctuated powerful percussion statements. cut down" waveformpath="" version="Cut Down" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="7481" name="Veil of Shadows (c)" code="TSH 059 tk101" libraryid="5" albumid="168" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_059_Orchestral_Fantasia/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Arthur Rhodes" comment="Atmosphère tendue et empreinte de mal à l'aise, dans la veine de 'The Illusionist'." styleid="4" lengthseconds="65" time="1:05" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_059_Orchestral_Fantasia/TSH_059_trk101_VEIL_OF_SHADOWS_(C)_Simon_Arthur_Rhodes_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="101" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ALTERNATIF, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, CHAUD, DÉSERT, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, TROUBLANT, INQUIÉTANT, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TROUBLANT, SURNATUREL, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, DANGEUREUX, EFFRAYANT, MENAÇANT, EFFRAYANT, DE MAUVAIS AUGURE, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, SERIEUX, INQUIETANT, MENACANT, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS, DESERT Atmosphère tendue et empreinte de mal à l'aise, dans la veine de 'The Illusionist'. tsh 059 tk101 simon arthur rhodes veil of shadows (c) tsh 059 orchestral fantasia the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer alternate movies crime detective mystery movies fantasy adventure nature wildlife the elements land hot desert nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife disturbing eerie disturbing mysterious disturbing supernatural disturbing tense uneasy atmosphere thematic to 'the illusionist'. linking section" waveformpath="" version="Linking section" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="8227" name="Heart of the Machine" code="TSH 051 tk040" libraryid="5" albumid="177" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_051_Nearfield/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Everard Lawrence Wells / Robert John Foster" comment="Battement de coeur pulsatif et tendu." styleid="10" lengthseconds="92" time="1:32" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_051_Nearfield/TSH051_trk040_HEART_OF_THE_MACHINE_Richard_Everard_Lawrence_Wells_Robert_John_Foster_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="40" tracktotal="" search="ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, EFFETS, EFFETS SONORES, HUMAIN, BATTEMENTS DE COEUR, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, PULSATION, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE,, ELEMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS Battement de coeur pulsatif et tendu. tsh 051 tk040 richard everard lawrence wells robert john foster heart of the machine tsh 051 nearfield the scoring house documentary sound elements atmospheres effects sound effects human heartbeat main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense movement rhythmic pulsing movies crime detective mystery tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama pulsating tense heartbeat. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="7315" name="Dawn at Arras" code="TSH 042 tk021" libraryid="5" albumid="167" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_042_A_Soldier's_Story/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Barnaby J Robson" comment="Un morceau tendu d'anticipation pour planter le décor, en progression graduelle." styleid="4" lengthseconds="123" time="2:03" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_042_A_Soldier's_Story/TSH042_trk021_DAWN_AT_ARRAS_Barnaby_J_Robson_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="21" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, GUERRE, MILITAIRE, TROUBLANT, TENDU, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, SÉRIEUX, EVOLUTIF, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), STYLE VINTAGE, SERIEUX, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), DEPRIMANT, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Un morceau tendu d'anticipation pour planter le décor, en progression graduelle. tsh 042 tk021 barnaby j robson dawn at arras tsh 042 a soldier's story the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral documentary main activities settings war military disturbing tense sad depressing sad serious building tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) vintage style tense anticipatory scene-setter gradually building. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="11292" name="Military (b)" code="WOM 039 tk039" libraryid="6" albumid="229" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_039_Drumming_(Percussion)/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Paul Edward Clarvis" comment="Un tambour de parade en solo rejointes progressivement par d'autres." styleid="18" lengthseconds="52" time="0:52" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_039_Drumming_(Percussion)/WOM039_trk039_MILITARY_(B)_Paul_Edward_Clarvis_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="39" tracktotal="" search="MARCHES, ORCHESTRE MILITAIRE, ALTERNATIF, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, GUERRE, MILITAIRE, MARCHES MILITAIRES, ORCHESTRE MILITAIRE, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, FILMS, GUERRE, SÉRIEUX, SOLENNEL, FORT, MARTIAL, FORT, FORT, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), CUIVRES, FANFARE MILITAIRE, PERIODE, SERIEUX, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), PERIODES Un tambour de parade en solo rejointes progressivement par d'autres. wom 039 tk039 paul edward clarvis military (b) wom 039 drumming (percussion) west one music world marches military band alternate activities settings war military military marches military band movies period historical costume drama movies war serious solemn strong martial strong strong tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) brass marching band solo parade drum gradually joined by others. alternative" waveformpath="" version="Alternative" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="24401" name="Lovers’ Requiem (a)" code="WOM 322 tk005" libraryid="6" albumid="526" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_322_Cinematic_Drama/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Martin Tillmann" comment="Des lignes de piano à la beauté troublante entremelées avec des cordes enveloppantes, émouvantes." styleid="14" lengthseconds="151" time="2:31" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_322_Cinematic_Drama/WOM322_trk005_LOVERS_REQUIEM_(A)_Martin_Tillmann_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, MODERNE, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, DRAME FAMILIAL, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, DRAME HOSPITALIER, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, ANXIEUX, TROUBLANT, SUSPENS, TROUBLANT, TENDU, DRAMATIQUE, PASSIONNÉ, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, MÉLANCOLIE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, SÉRIEUX, INQUIET, SÉRIEUX, ÉMOUVANT, SÉRIEUX, SOLENNEL, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, ÉLÉGANT , MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, FORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES, ÉLECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES, SECTION DE CORDES, CLAVIER, PIANO, FORMATIONS GENERALES, SERIEUX, ELECTRO-ACOUSTIQUE, PASSIONNE, DEPRIMANT, EMOUVANT, MELANCOLIE, ELEGANT Des lignes de piano à la beauté troublante entremelées avec des cordes enveloppantes, émouvantes. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 322 tk005 martin tillmann lovers’ requiem (a) wom 322 cinematic drama west one music drama film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral documentary main movies human drama movies modern tv radio tv drama family drama tv radio tv drama medical drama tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing anxious disturbing suspenseful disturbing tense hauntingly beautiful piano lines intertwined with rich emotive strings. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="7134" name="Romanza (a)" code="TSH 029 tk016" libraryid="5" albumid="164" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_029_Symphonic_Fantasia/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Arthur Rhodes" comment="Une ouverture intime vers un thème romantique de grande envergure." styleid="4" lengthseconds="229" time="3:49" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_029_Symphonic_Fantasia/TSH029_trk016_ROMANZA_(A)_Simon_Arthur_Rhodes_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="16" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, MUSIQUE DE CHAMBRE, ENSEMBLE CLASSIQUE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, DROLE, MÉLODRAMATIQUE, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, FORT EN ÉMOTIONS, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, DIVIN, CÉLESTE,, FORT EN EMOTIONS, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), MELODRAMATIQUE, DEPRIMANT, AERIEN, ELEMENTS, CELESTE Une ouverture intime vers un thème romantique de grande envergure. reussite, victoire, annonce, trophee, nommé, nomination, nominé, meilleur, vainqueur, gagnant, montée des marches, scene, montée sur scene, invité, gala, ouverture, cloture, guest, approche, festif, festivite, intermede tsh 029 tk016 simon arthur rhodes romanza (a) tsh 029 symphonic fantasia the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer classical and semi classical chamber music classical ensemble main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) film score orchestral pastoral funny melodramatic peaceful dreamy peaceful peaceful tender intimate tender nostalgic tender romantic tender intimate opening to romantic sweeping theme and poignant end. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="26372" name="Ray of Hope (a)" code="WOM 209 tk008" libraryid="6" albumid="565" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_209_Absolution/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Toby Y. Chu" comment="Des cordes enthousiasmantes et optimistes fusionnées avec des motifs de guitare évocateurs." styleid="4" lengthseconds="128" time="2:08" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_209_Absolution/WOM209_trk008_RAY_OF_HOPE_(A)_Toby_Y._Chu_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="8" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, AÉRIEN, NUAGES, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, CIEL, DIVIN, CÉLESTE, TITRE POUR TRAILER, DROLE, MÉLODRAMATIQUE, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, DÉTENDU, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, COOL, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), MELODRAMATIQUE, DETENDU, AERIEN, ELECTRIQUE, ELEMENTS, CELESTE Des cordes enthousiasmantes et optimistes fusionnées avec des motifs de guitare évocateurs. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz wom 209 tk008 toby y. chu ray of hope (a) wom 209 absolution west one music film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic main movies human drama movies romance nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife the elements sky aerial clouds nature wildlife the elements sky heavenly celestial trailer track stirring optimistic strings fused with evocative guitar patterns. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="6933" name="Destiny (a)" code="TSH 006 tk001" libraryid="5" albumid="159" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_006_Destiny/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Graham Donald Harry Preskett" comment="Un thème ambitieux et distingué évoluant graduellement vers une fin calme." styleid="4" lengthseconds="166" time="2:46" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_006_Destiny/TSH006_trk001_DESTINY_(A)_Graham_Donald_Harry_Preskett_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="CLASSIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, GUERRE, MILITAIRE, GUERRE GÉNÉRALE, SCÈNES DE COMBAT, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, GUERRE, OCCASIONS SPÉCIALES, ÉVÈNEMENTS, CERÉMONIEL, CÉRÉMONIE ROYALE, OCCASIONS SPÉCIALES, ÉVÈNEMENTS, FUNÉRAILLES, PAISIBLE, CALME, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, LUGUBRE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, SÉRIEUX, DIGNE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, PATRIOTIQUE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), SERIEUX, OCCASIONS SPECIALES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, EVENEMENTS, EVENEMENT, CEREMONIEL, FUNERAILLES, GUERRE GENERALE, CEREMONIE ROYALE, SCENES DE COMBAT Un thème ambitieux et distingué évoluant graduellement vers une fin calme. cool, calme, atmosphérique, cocktail, lounge, musique d'ambiance, bar, hotel, jazz tsh 006 tk001 graham donald harry preskett destiny (a) tsh 006 destiny the scoring house film score orchestral classical film score orchestral trailer main activities settings war military general war battle scenes documentary movies war special occasions events ceremonial royal ceremony special occasions events funeral peaceful calm sad depressing funereal sad depressing sad dignified aspirational theme gradually evolving with calm end. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="3439" name="Wishes in the Wind" code="TSH 013 tk012" libraryid="5" albumid="103" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_013_It's_My_Life/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Ian Paul Livingstone" comment="Des espérances silencieuses et secrètes." styleid="10" lengthseconds="111" time="1:51" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_013_It's_My_Life/TSH013_trk012_WISHES_IN_THE_WIND_Ian_Paul_Livingstone_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, TROUBLANT, DROLE, MÉLODRAMATIQUE, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, INTROSPECTIF, PAISIBLE, DOUX, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, SÉRIEUX, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLAVIER, PIANO, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), MELODRAMATIQUE, DEPRIMANT, ELEMENTS Des espérances silencieuses et secrètes. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 013 tk012 ian paul livingstone wishes in the wind tsh 013 it's my life the scoring house documentary film score orchestral pastoral main documentary movies human drama nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife disturbing funny melodramatic peaceful dreamy peaceful introspective peaceful quiet sad depressing lonely sad depressing poignant sad depressing sad quiet introspective hopes. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="6913" name="A Simple Story (a)" code="TSH 001 tk010" libraryid="5" albumid="158" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_001_Cinematic_Adventures/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Un piano et un orchestre pour une pastorale mélancolique et sincère." styleid="4" lengthseconds="275" time="4:35" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_001_Cinematic_Adventures/TSH001_trk010_A_SIMPLE_STORY_(A)_Richard_Allen_Harvey_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="10" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, DROLE, MÉLODRAMATIQUE, PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, FAMILIAL, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, CLAVIER, PIANO,, MELODRAMATIQUE, DEPRIMANT, ELEMENTS Un piano et un orchestre pour une pastorale mélancolique et sincère. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 001 tk010 richard allen harvey a simple story (a) tsh 001 cinematic adventures the scoring house film score orchestral film score orchestral trailer classical and semi classical symphony orchestra main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) film score orchestral pastoral funny melodramatic peaceful contented peaceful dreamy peaceful peaceful tender intimate tender nostalgic tender reflective tender a wistful heartfelt pastorale for piano and orchestra. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="3437" name="Walking Away" code="TSH 013 tk010" libraryid="5" albumid="103" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_013_It's_My_Life/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Ian Paul Livingstone" comment="Un thème profond et émotionnel." styleid="10" lengthseconds="95" time="1:35" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_013_It's_My_Life/TSH013_trk010_WALKING_AWAY_Ian_Paul_Livingstone_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="10" tracktotal="" search="ENFANTS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, TROUBLANT, DROLE, MÉLODRAMATIQUE, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, SÉRIEUX, ÉMOUVANT, SÉRIEUX, ATTENTIONNÉ, TENDRE, INNOCENT, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EVOLUTIF, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, MUSIQUE DE CHAMBRE, ENSEMBLE CLASSIQUE, STYLE VINTAGE, PERIODE, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), MELODRAMATIQUE, DEPRIMANT, EMOUVANT, ATTENTIONNE, PERIODES, ELEMENTS, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Un thème profond et émotionnel. tsh 013 tk010 ian paul livingstone walking away tsh 013 it's my life the scoring house documentary children business corporate luxury film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral pastoral main movies human drama movies period historical costume drama movies romance nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral nature wildlife the elements thoughtful emotional theme. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="4036" name="This Is My Story (a)" code="TSH 022 tk001" libraryid="5" albumid="114" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_022_Human_Stories/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Michael Price / Laurence Love Greed" comment="Un thème expressif de piano solo au déploiement progressif." styleid="10" lengthseconds="184" time="3:04" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_022_Human_Stories/TSH022_trk001_THIS_IS_MY_STORY_(A)_Michael_Price_Laurence_Love_Greed_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, AUTOMNE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, ÉTÉ, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, CLAVIER, PIANO, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), DEPRIMANT, ELEMENTS, ETE Un thème expressif de piano solo au déploiement progressif. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 022 tk001 michael price laurence love greed this is my story (a) tsh 022 human stories the scoring house documentary film score orchestral pastoral main documentary movies human drama nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral nature wildlife the elements seasons time autumn nature wildlife the elements seasons time summer sad depressing poignant sad depressing sad unfolding expressive theme featuring piano and strings. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="7064" name="A Lonely Road" code="TSH 026A tk003" libraryid="5" albumid="162" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_026A_Dimensions/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Troy Banarzi / Alexander Balanescu" comment="Un thème mélancolique et émotif." styleid="4" lengthseconds="140" time="2:20" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_026A_Dimensions/TSH026A_trk003_A_LONELY_ROAD_Troy_Banarzi_Alexander_Balanescu_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), CORDES, VIOLON, DEPRIMANT Un thème mélancolique et émotif. tsh 026a tk003 troy banarzi alexander balanescu a lonely road tsh 026a dimensions the scoring house film score orchestral classical classical styling main documentary sad depressing lonely tender nostalgic tender romantic tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) strings violin wistful emotive theme. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="4618" name="Beauty in Motion" code="TSH 035 tk014" libraryid="5" albumid="125" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_035_A_Winner_is_Born/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Mark Lasker" comment="Des images descriptives et émotionnelles avec un ensemble violoncelle." styleid="22" lengthseconds="118" time="1:58" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_035_A_Winner_is_Born/TSH035_trk014_BEAUTY_IN_MOTION_Mark_Lasker_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="14" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, SÉRIEUX, ÉMOUVANT, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, CORDES, VIOLONCELLE, STYLE VINTAGE, SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, EMOUVANT, ELEMENTS Des images descriptives et émotionnelles avec un ensemble violoncelle. tsh 035 tk014 mark lasker beauty in motion tsh 035 a winner is born the scoring house sport film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral pastoral main documentary movies human drama movies romance nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife the elements land rural countryside pastoral peaceful dreamy peaceful peaceful sad emotional descriptive imagery featuring cello ensemble. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="22759" name="Solitary Thoughts (a)" code="WOM 288 tk005" libraryid="6" albumid="492" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_288_Moments_in_Time/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Patrick Thomas Hawes" comment="Piano et violoncelle beaux et sensibles." styleid="26" lengthseconds="146" time="2:26" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_288_Moments_in_Time/WOM_288_trk005_SOLITARY_THOUGHTS_(A)_Patrick_Thomas_Hawes_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, MUSIQUE DE CHAMBRE, ENSEMBLE CLASSIQUE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, BEAU, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, AUTOMNE, CORDES, VIOLONCELLE,, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), ELEMENTS Piano et violoncelle beaux et sensibles. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 288 tk005 patrick thomas hawes solitary thoughts (a) wom 288 moments in time west one music nature wildlife film score orchestral pastoral classical and semi classical chamber music classical ensemble main tempo 108 - 120 medium fast (moderato) tender nostalgic tender reflective tender romantic beautiful nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife nature wildlife the elements starkly beautiful and emotive for piano and cello. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="18296" name="Arco Noir (a)" code="WOM 192 tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="388" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_192_Strings_of_Sorrow/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Une intéraction lyrique entre des solos de violon et de violoncelle sur un underscore de cordes pulsant et doux." styleid="14" lengthseconds="173" time="2:53" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_192_Strings_of_Sorrow/WOM192_trk001_ARCO_NOIR_(A)_Richard_Allen_Harvey_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, FILM NOIR, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, PAISIBLE, LYRIQUE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRAGIQUE, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, MÉLODIQUE, LYRIQUE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CORDES, VIOLONCELLE, CORDES, VIOLON, MELODIQUE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE Une intéraction lyrique entre des solos de violon et de violoncelle sur un underscore de cordes pulsant et doux. wom 192 tk001 richard allen harvey arco noir (a) wom 192 strings of sorrow west one music drama film score orchestral trailer main documentary movies crime detective mystery movies film noir movies human drama disturbing mysterious peaceful lyrical sad depressing poignant sad depressing sad sad depressing tragic tender reflective tender sentimental melodic lyrical interplay between violin and cello solos over a pulsating gentle string underscore. main delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="4613" name="Each New Day (a)" code="TSH 035 tk009" libraryid="5" albumid="125" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_035_A_Winner_is_Born/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Mark Lasker" comment="Un morceau chaleureux et plein d'attentes évoluant graduellement." styleid="22" lengthseconds="138" time="2:18" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_035_A_Winner_is_Born/TSH035_trk009_EACH_NEW_DAY_(A)_Mark_Lasker_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, IDYLLE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, SENTIMENTAL, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EVOLUTIF, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, RALENTI, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, REVELER, ELEMENTS, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Un morceau chaleureux et plein d'attentes évoluant graduellement. tsh 035 tk009 mark lasker each new day (a) tsh 035 a winner is born the scoring house sport business corporate reveal launch business corporate luxury film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic main business corporate movies human drama movies romance nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama tv radio sports sad depressing warm and expectant gradually evolving. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
    <item id="26516" name="Eternal Motion (c)" code="WOM 304 tk042" libraryid="6" albumid="568" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_304_Emotive_Minimalism/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Richard Allen Harvey" comment="Intro délicate de piano qui évolue en un morceau beau et émouvant." styleid="4" lengthseconds="183" time="3:03" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_304_Emotive_Minimalism/WOM304_trk042_ETERNAL_MOTION_(C)_Richard_Allen_Harvey_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="42" tracktotal="" search="CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE, CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, ALTERNATIF, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MER, PAYSAGE MARIN, PAISIBLE, PAISIBLE, TENDRE, DÉLICAT, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, BEAU, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, COULANT, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, CLAVIER, PIANO, CORDES, VIOLON , EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, ANGLETERRE, 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), DELICAT, AERIEN, ELEMENTS Intro délicate de piano qui évolue en un morceau beau et émouvant. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live wom 304 tk042 richard allen harvey eternal motion (c) wom 304 emotive minimalism west one music film score orchestral classical classical styling classical classical styling film score orchestral panoramic film score orchestral pastoral alternate documentary biographical historical the arts nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife the elements land rural delicate piano introduction evolves into a beautiful emotive cue. without vocal delicate, gentle, soft" waveformpath="" version="Without Vocal" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="21801" name="Respite (a)" code="WOM 264 tk012" libraryid="6" albumid="467" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_264_Emotive_Acoustic/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Alistair Bruce Henry Friend / Ted Brett Barnes" comment="Une guitare acoustique tendre et des cordes intimes et émouvantes." styleid="13" lengthseconds="247" time="4:07" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_264_Emotive_Acoustic/WOM264_trk012_RESPITE_(A)_Alistair_Bruce_Henry_Friend_Ted_Brett_Barnes_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, MUSIQUE DE CHAMBRE, ENSEMBLE CLASSIQUE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), PAISIBLE, SATISFAIT, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, TENDRE, INTIME, TENDRE, NOSTALGIQUE, TENDRE, ROMANTIQUE, TENDRE, TENDRE, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, ACOUSTIQUE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SAISONS, TEMPS, ÉTÉ, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN NYLON, CORDES, GUITARE, ACOUSTIQUE, CORDES EN MÉTAL, CORDES, VIOLON ,, ELEMENTS, CORDES EN METAL, ETE Une guitare acoustique tendre et des cordes intimes et émouvantes. wom 264 tk012 alistair bruce henry friend ted brett barnes respite (a) wom 264 emotive acoustic west one music acoustic film score orchestral pastoral classical and semi classical chamber music classical ensemble main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) peaceful contented peaceful dreamy tender intimate tender nostalgic tender romantic tender tender tender warm acoustic tv radio leisure tender acoustic guitar and intimate emotive strings. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750"/>
    <item id="7390" name="Our Heritage (a)" code="TSH 059 tk010" libraryid="5" albumid="168" albumartpath="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_059_Orchestral_Fantasia/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Simon Arthur Rhodes" comment="Thème plein d'attention et de dignité." styleid="4" lengthseconds="149" time="2:29" samplefile="Music/The Scoring House/TSH_059_Orchestral_Fantasia/TSH_059_trk010_OUR_HERITAGE_(A)_Simon_Arthur_Rhodes_The_Scoring_House.mp3" track="10" tracktotal="" search="CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE, CLASSIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, FILMS, PÉRIODES, HISTORIQUE, DRAME EN COSTUME, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, SÉRIEUX, DIGNE, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, SÉRIEUX, ATTENTIONNÉ, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, PATRIOTIQUE, CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, CLAVIER, PIANO, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, PÉRIODE, PRÉ-20E SIÈCLE, 19E SIÈCLE, AMERIQUE DU NORD, PERIODE, SERIEUX, ETATS-UNIS, PRE-20E SIECLE, ATTENTIONNE, PERIODES, 20E SIECLE, 19E SIECLE, ELEMENTS Thème plein d'attention et de dignité. bruit de fond, piano, chant, piano bar, bar, live tsh 059 tk010 simon arthur rhodes our heritage (a) tsh 059 orchestral fantasia the scoring house film score orchestral classical classical styling classical film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral panoramic film score orchestral pastoral main documentary biographical historical the arts movies period historical costume drama nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama thoughtful dignified theme. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="The Scoring House" cae="00615215382"/>
  </items>
</librarycollection>
