<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<librarycollection>
  <items>
    <item id="21390" name="Street Chase" code="WOM 300A tk030" libraryid="6" albumid="470" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Veigar Margeirsson / Mark David Denis" comment="Poursuite intense et pleine de paranoia. Gros déferlemets de percussion et thèmes épiques de cordes." styleid="2" lengthseconds="109" time="1:49" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/WOM300A_trk030_STREET_CHASE_Veigar_Margeirsson_Mark_David_Denis_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="30" tracktotal="" search="Poursuite intense et pleine de paranoia. Gros déferlemets de percussion et thèmes épiques de cordes. BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, FORT, ÉPIQUE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), EPIQUE Eine intensive Verfolgungsjagd mit schon paranoidem Charakter. Gewaltige Percussion rollt über mächtige Streicher. FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, HAUPTVERSION, FILME, ACTION ABENTEUER, FILME, ACTION DRAMA, FILME, EPISCH, TRAILER, TRAILER TRACK, DRAMATISCH, INTENSIV, KRÄFTIG, EPISCH, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MITTLERES TEMPO (ANDANTE), KRAFTIG wom 300a tk030 veigar margeirsson mark david denis street chase wom 300a wom is 300 west one music trailer film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral trailer main movies action adventure movies action drama movies epic trailers trailer track dramatic intense strong epic tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) paranoid intense pursuit. huge rolling percussion epic string themes. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="21389" name="Enter the Champions" code="WOM 300A tk029" libraryid="6" albumid="470" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Thomas Arthur Swindells / Richard Lewis (Gb 3)" comment="Le décor est planté, que les vainqueurs apparaissent! Cordes exaltantes, breaks dynamiques." styleid="2" lengthseconds="134" time="2:14" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/WOM300A_trk029_ENTER_THE_CHAMPIONS_Thomas_Arthur_Swindells_Richard_Lewis_(Gb_3)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="29" tracktotal="" search="Le décor est planté, que les vainqueurs apparaissent! Cordes exaltantes, breaks dynamiques. BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, CLASSIQUE, FUSION CLASSIQUE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, PUISSANCE, ÉNERGIE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, ACTION, SPORT, TRAILERS, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, TENDU, FORT, PUISSANT, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), ENERGIE Es ist angerichtet, herein mit den Champions! Erhebende Streicher mit treibendem Beat. BUSINESS, CORPORATE, KLASSISCH, KLASSIK FUSION, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, KRAFT, ENERGIE, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, HAUPTVERSION, FILME, ACTION ABENTEUER, FILME, ACTION DRAMA, SPORT, TRAILER, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TRAILER TRACK, VERSTÖREND, ANGESPANNT, KRÄFTIG, KRAFTVOLL, KRÄFTIG, PRESTIGETRÄCHTIG, BEFLÜGELND, BEFLÜGELND, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, TREIBEND, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, ROBUST, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MITTELSCHNELL (MODERATO), BEFLUGELND, KRAFTIG, PRESTIGETRACHTIG, VERSTOREND wom 300a tk029 thomas arthur swindells richard lewis (gb 3) enter the champions wom 300a wom is 300 west one music trailer business corporate classical classical fusion business corporate power energy film score orchestral trailer main movies action adventure movies action drama sports trailers tv radio sports trailer track disturbing tense strong powerful strong prestigious uplifting the scene is set let the victors emerge! uplifting strings driving breaks. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="21388" name="Eyes on the Prize" code="WOM 300A tk028" libraryid="6" albumid="470" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Veigar Margeirsson" comment="Action thriller intense. Batterie martelée, cordes massives et cuivres grinçants." styleid="2" lengthseconds="150" time="2:30" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/WOM300A_trk028_EYES_ON_THE_PRIZE_Veigar_Margeirsson_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="28" tracktotal="" search="Action thriller intense. Batterie martelée, cordes massives et cuivres grinçants. BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, TRAILERS, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TITRE POUR TRAILER, DRAMATIQUE, INTENSE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), EPIQUE Stampfende Drums, gewichtige Streicher und ein kratziger Bass sorgen für einen intensiven Action-Thriller-Soundtrack. FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, HAUPTVERSION, FILME, ACTION DRAMA, FILME, EPISCH, FILME, FANTASY ABENTEUER, TRAILER, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TRAILER TRACK, DRAMATISCH, INTENSIV, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, TREIBEND, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, ROBUST, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MITTLERES TEMPO (ANDANTE) wom 300a tk028 veigar margeirsson eyes on the prize wom 300a wom is 300 west one music trailer film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral trailer main movies action drama movies epic movies fantasy adventure trailers tv radio sports trailer track dramatic intense movement rhythmic driving movement rhythmic rugged tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) intense action thriller. pounding drums massed strings rasping brass. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="21387" name="Power Trip" code="WOM 300A tk027" libraryid="6" albumid="470" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Veigar Margeirsson" comment="Entrainant, spectaculaire. Des pulsations basses de cordes soutiennent des mélodies poids lourd de cordes, bois et cuivres." styleid="2" lengthseconds="113" time="1:53" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/WOM300A_trk027_POWER_TRIP_Veigar_Margeirsson_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="27" tracktotal="" search="Entrainant, spectaculaire. Des pulsations basses de cordes soutiennent des mélodies poids lourd de cordes, bois et cuivres. CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE, CLASSIQUE, STYLE CLASSIQUE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SPORT, ÉQUITATION, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, SÉRIEUX, DIGNE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), EUROPE, EUROPE DU NORD, ANGLETERRE, SERIEUX, EQUITATION Treibendes und dramatisches Theme mit tiefen, pulsierenden Streichern und Holz- sowie Blechbläsern. KLASSISCH, KLASSISCHER STIL, KLASSISCH, KLASSISCHER STIL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, HAUPTVERSION, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, SPORT, REITSPORT, TV, RADIO, KINDER, JUGENDPROGRAMM, TV, RADIO, SPORT, ERNST, WÜRDEVOLL, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, TREIBEND, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MITTLERES TEMPO (ANDANTE), EUROPA, NORDEUROPA, ENGLAND, WURDEVOLL wom 300a tk027 veigar margeirsson power trip wom 300a wom is 300 west one music trailer classical classical styling classical classical styling business corporate film score orchestral trailer main business corporate sports equestrian events tv radio children youth tv tv radio sports serious dignified movement rhythmic driving tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) driving dramatic. low string pulses underpin heavyweight string woodwind brass melodies. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="21386" name="Concentric Circles" code="WOM 300A tk026" libraryid="6" albumid="470" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Veigar Margeirsson / James Brian Brasher" comment="Piano simple, répétitif. Motif de cordes évoluant jusqu'à un climax émouvant." styleid="2" lengthseconds="134" time="2:14" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/WOM300A_trk026_CONCENTRIC_CIRCLES_Veigar_Margeirsson_James_Brian_Brasher_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="26" tracktotal="" search="Piano simple, répétitif. Motif de cordes évoluant jusqu'à un climax émouvant. CLASSIQUE, STYLE MINIMALISTE, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, CRIME, DÉTECTIVE, MYSTÈRE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ABSTRAIT, SIMPLE, TROUBLANT, MYSTERIEUX, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, SOLITAIRE, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, SÉRIEUX, TENDRE, SONGEUR, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), SERIEUX, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DEPRIMANT, DETECTIVE, MYSTERE, ELEMENTS Ein schlichtes, sich wiederholendes Motiv mit Piano und Streichern, das sich zu einem bewegenden Höhepunkt emporschraubt. KLASSISCH, MINIMALISTISCHER STIL, HAUPTVERSION, DOKUMENTATION, FILME, CRIME, DETEKTIV, MYSTERY, FILME, MENSCHLICHE DRAMEN, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, NATURKUNDE, WILDNIS, ABSTRAKT, SCHLICHT, VERSTÖREND, MYSTERIÖS, TRAURIG, BEDRÜCKEND, EINSAM, TRAURIG, BEDRÜCKEND, SCHMERZLICH, TRAURIG, BEDRÜCKEND, TRAURIG, ERNST, ZÄRTLICH, NACHDENKLICH, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), BEDRUCKEND, MYSTERIOS, VERSTOREND, ZARTLICH wom 300a tk026 veigar margeirsson james brian brasher concentric circles wom 300a wom is 300 west one music trailer classical minimalist style main documentary movies crime detective mystery movies human drama nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife abstract simple disturbing mysterious sad depressing lonely sad depressing poignant sad depressing sad serious tender simple repeating piano string motif gradually builds to an emotive climax. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="21385" name="Straight to Hell" code="WOM 300A tk025" libraryid="6" albumid="470" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Gresby Race Nash" comment="Une ouverture sombre, gothique, se construit avec des motifs répétés de piano et des cordes." styleid="2" lengthseconds="130" time="2:10" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/WOM300A_trk025_STRAIGHT_TO_HELL_Gresby_Race_Nash_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="25" tracktotal="" search="Une ouverture sombre, gothique, se construit avec des motifs répétés de piano et des cordes. BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, PRESTIGE , BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, FILMS, SCIENCE FICTION, SPORT, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, TENDU, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, EVOLUTIF, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), EPIQUE, REVELER, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Ein bedrohlich brodelndes Gothic-Intro, das sich mit Streichern und einem repetetiven Piano nach oben schraubt. BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTHÜLLUNG, LAUNCH, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, PRESTIGE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTHÜLLUNG, LAUNCH, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, HAUPTVERSION, FILME, EPISCH, FILME, FANTASY ABENTEUER, FILME, SCIENCE FICTION, SPORT, TRAILER, TRAILER TRACK, VERSTÖREND, ANGESPANNT, KRÄFTIG, PRESTIGETRÄCHTIG, AUFBAUEND, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MITTLERES TEMPO (ANDANTE), ENTHULLUNG, KRAFTIG, PRESTIGETRACHTIG, VERSTOREND wom 300a tk025 gresby race nash straight to hell wom 300a wom is 300 west one music trailer business corporate reveal launch business corporate prestige business corporate reveal launch film score orchestral trailer main movies epic movies fantasy adventure movies science fiction sports trailers trailer track disturbing tense strong prestigious building tempo brooding gothic opening builds with repeating piano patterns strings. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="21384" name="Beyond the Stratosphere" code="WOM 300A tk024" libraryid="6" albumid="470" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Daniel Law Heath / James Brian Brasher" comment="Une envolée de cordes somptueuses, des flutes ethniques reveuses et de magnifiques et évocateurs motifs de piano." styleid="2" lengthseconds="168" time="2:48" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/WOM300A_trk024_BEYOND_THE_STRATOSPHERE_Daniel_Law_Heath_James_Brian_Brasher_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="24" tracktotal="" search="Une envolée de cordes somptueuses, des flutes ethniques reveuses et de magnifiques et évocateurs motifs de piano. BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMIQUE, PRINCIPAL, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, PAYSAGES, PANORAMA, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, SCIENCES NATURELLES, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, POIGNANT, TRISTE, DÉPRIMANT, TRISTE, SÉRIEUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, JAILLIR, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UNE HORLOGE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ACCÉLÉRÉ, IMAGE PAR IMAGE, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), SERIEUX, DEPRIMANT, ACCELERE, AERIEN, ELEMENTS Schwelgerische und langsam emporsteigende Streicher mit verträumten ethnischen Flöten und herrlichen Pianofiguren. FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, PANORAMA, HAUPTVERSION, DOKUMENTATION, FILME, MENSCHLICHE DRAMEN, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LANDSCHAFTEN, PANORAMA, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, NATURKUNDE, WILDNIS, FRIEDLICH, VERTRÄUMT, TRAURIG, BEDRÜCKEND, SCHMERZLICH, TRAURIG, BEDRÜCKEND, TRAURIG, ERNST, BEFLÜGELND, EMPORSTEIGEND, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, UHRENARTIG, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, BESCHLEUNIGT, ZEITRAFFER, BEWEGUNG, SMOOTH, HIMMEL / LUFT, DAHINTREIBEN, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MITTLERES TEMPO (ANDANTE), BEDRUCKEND, BEFLUGELND, VERTRAUMT wom 300a tk024 daniel law heath james brian brasher beyond the stratosphere wom 300a wom is 300 west one music trailer film score orchestral panoramic main documentary movies human drama nature wildlife the elements land landscapes panorama nature wildlife the elements nature study wildlife peaceful dreamy sad depressing poignant sad depressing sad serious uplifting soaring movement soaring sumptuous strings dreamy ethnic flutes gorgeous evocative piano patterns. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="21383" name="Propelling Force" code="WOM 300A tk023" libraryid="6" albumid="470" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Christian Telford / Nigel William Graham" comment="Orchestre majestueux avec cordes tourbillonantes et pulsantes. Se développe jusqu'à un final énorme." styleid="2" lengthseconds="111" time="1:51" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/WOM300A_trk023_PROPELLING_FORCE_Christian_Telford_Nigel_William_Graham_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="23" tracktotal="" search="Orchestre majestueux avec cordes tourbillonantes et pulsantes. Se développe jusqu'à un final énorme. BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, AVENTURE FANTASTIQUE, TRAILERS, TV, RADIO, TÉLÉ RÉALITÉ, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, TENDU, FORT, MAJESTUEUX, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), TELE REALITE Majestätisches Orchester mit pulsierenden, wirbelnden Streichern und einem fantastischen Höhepunkt. FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, HAUPTVERSION, FILME, ACTION ABENTEUER, FILME, FANTASY ABENTEUER, TRAILER, TV, RADIO, REALITY TV, TRAILER TRACK, VERSTÖREND, ANGESPANNT, KRÄFTIG, MAJESTÄTISCH, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), KRAFTIG, MAJESTATISCH, VERSTOREND wom 300a tk023 christian telford nigel william graham propelling force wom 300a wom is 300 west one music trailer film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral trailer main movies action adventure movies fantasy adventure trailers tv radio reality tv trailer track disturbing tense strong majestic tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) majestic orchestra with pulsating swirling strings builds to a huge climax. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="21382" name="Agent X" code="WOM 300A tk022" libraryid="6" albumid="470" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Danny Mccarthy / Robert Leslie Bennett" comment="Tension dramatique en développement. Synthétiseurs répétitifs pleins de tension, cordes dessinant une mélodie obsédante." styleid="2" lengthseconds="123" time="2:03" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/WOM300A_trk022_AGENT_X_Danny_Mccarthy_Robert_Leslie_Bennett_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="22" tracktotal="" search="Tension dramatique en développement. Synthétiseurs répétitifs pleins de tension, cordes dessinant une mélodie obsédante. BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ACTION, FILMS, ESPIONNAGE, ESPION, FILMS, HORREUR, THRILLER, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MER, PAYSAGE MARIN, TRAILERS, TITRE POUR TRAILER, TROUBLANT, TENDU, EVOLUTIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, POURSUITE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), ELEMENTS, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Anwachsende Anspannung und Dramatik. Getriebene, sich wiederholende Synthies und Streicher mit einer eindringlichen Melodie. FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, HAUPTVERSION, FILME, ACTION DRAMA, FILME, SPIONAGE, SPION, FILME, HORROR, THRILLER, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, MEER, MEERESPANORAMA, TRAILER, TRAILER TRACK, VERSTÖREND, ANGESPANNT, AUFBAUEND, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, VERFOLGUNGSJAGD, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MITTLERES TEMPO (ANDANTE), VERSTOREND wom 300a tk022 danny mccarthy robert leslie bennett agent x wom 300a wom is 300 west one music trailer film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral trailer main movies action drama movies espionage spy movies horror thriller nature wildlife the elements sea seascape trailers trailer track disturbing tense building movement rhythmic chase tempo building dramatic tension. tense repeating synths strings with a haunting melody. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="21381" name="Ultimate Discovery" code="WOM 300A tk021" libraryid="6" albumid="470" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Matt Norman" comment="Piano solo qui amène progressivement à un climax orchestral épique." styleid="2" lengthseconds="117" time="1:57" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/WOM300A_trk021_ULTIMATE_DISCOVERY_Matt_Norman_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="21" tracktotal="" search="Piano solo qui amène progressivement à un climax orchestral épique. CLASSIQUE, STYLE MINIMALISTE, CLASSIQUE, STYLE MINIMALISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FILMS, ACTION AVENTURE, FILMS, SCIENCE FICTION, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, MER, PAYSAGE MARIN, SPORT, JEUX OLYMPIQUES, FORT, ÉPIQUE, EVOLUTIF, TEMPO, 66 - 76 À L'AISE (ADAGIO), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, 20E SIÈCLE, PERIODE, 66 - 76 A L'AISE (ADAGIO), EPIQUE, 20E SIECLE, REVELER, ELEMENTS, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Das Piano schraubt sich allmählich zu einem orchestralen Höhepunkt empor. KLASSISCH, MINIMALISTISCHER STIL, KLASSISCH, MINIMALISTISCHER STIL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTHÜLLUNG, LAUNCH, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, HAUPTVERSION, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, FILME, ACTION ABENTEUER, FILME, SCIENCE FICTION, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, MEER, MEERESPANORAMA, SPORT, OLYMPISCHE SPIELE, KRÄFTIG, EPISCH, AUFBAUEND, TEMPO, 66 - 76 GETRAGEN (ADAGIO), ZEITALTER, MODERNE ZEIT, VOR 20. JHD., ENTHULLUNG, KRAFTIG wom 300a tk021 matt norman ultimate discovery wom 300a wom is 300 west one music trailer classical minimalist style classical minimalist style business corporate reveal launch film score orchestral trailer main business corporate movies action adventure movies science fiction nature wildlife the elements sea seascape sports olympics strong epic building tempo solo piano gradually builds into an epic orchestral climax. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="21380" name="Morning Star" code="WOM 300A tk020" libraryid="6" albumid="470" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Charlie Taylor / Jake Jarvis" comment="Amène lentement à des chorus euphoriques." styleid="2" lengthseconds="200" time="3:20" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/WOM300A_trk020_MORNING_STAR_Charlie_Taylor_Jake_Jarvis_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="20" tracktotal="" search="Amène lentement à des chorus euphoriques. BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, FOLK CONTEMPORAINE, FOLK ROCK, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, ROCK, INDIE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ROAD MOVIE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, NOURRITURE, LOISIR, MAISON, JARDIN, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EVOLUTIF, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CORDES, BANJO, AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, AMERIQUE DU NORD, ETATS-UNIS, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ELEMENTS, JOURNEE, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Lebe deinen Traum. Dynamischer Rock, der gute Laune verbreitet. BUSINESS, CORPORATE, MOTIVIEREND, ZEITGENÖSSISCHER FOLK, FOLK ROCK, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, MOTIVIEREND, ROCK, INDIE, HAUPTVERSION, FILME, ROAD MOVIE, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, SONNE, TROPISCH, KÜSTENLANDSCHAFT, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, ESSEN, FREIZEIT, HEIM, GARTEN, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, REISEN, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, UNTERHALTUNG, DAYTIME - TV, FRÖHLICH, GUT GELAUNT, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, BEFLÜGELND, EUPHORISCH, BEFLÜGELND, MOTIVIEREND, AUFBAUEND, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), SAITENINSTRUMENTE, BANJO, NORDAMERIKA, USA, BEFLUGELND, FROHLICH, KUSTENLANDSCHAFT, ZEITGENOSSISCH, ZEITGENOSSISCHER FOLK wom 300a tk020 charlie taylor jake jarvis morning star wom 300a wom is 300 west one music trailer business corporate motivational contemporary folk folk rock business corporate motivational rock indie main movies road movie nature wildlife the elements land sun tropical seaside tv radio leisure lifestyle food leisure home garden tv radio leisure lifestyle travel slowly building to euphoric choruses. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="21379" name="Shape the Future" code="WOM 300A tk019" libraryid="6" albumid="470" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Dan Cassady" comment="Stimulant, entrainant. Se développe, d'un humble début à une apogée passionée." styleid="2" lengthseconds="175" time="2:55" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/WOM300A_trk019_SHAPE_THE_FUTURE_Dan_Cassady_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="19" tracktotal="" search="Stimulant, entrainant. Se développe, d'un humble début à une apogée passionée. BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, UNDERSCORE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, PRESTIGE , BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FORMATION, INFORMATION, ROCK, INDIE, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, COMME UN TRAIN, EVOLUTIF, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, SPORT,, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), REVELER, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Treibender, breiter Tween-Rock. BUSINESS, CORPORATE, BETTEN, UNDERSCORE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), BUSINESS, CORPORATE, BETTEN, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, PRESTIGE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTHÜLLUNG, LAUNCH, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, TRAINING, INFORMATION, ROCK, INDIE, KRÄFTIG, PRESTIGETRÄCHTIG, BEFLÜGELND, BEFLÜGELND, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, EISENBAHNARTIG, AUFBAUEND, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, SPORT, BEFLUGELND, ENTHULLUNG, KRAFTIG, PRESTIGETRACHTIG wom 300a tk019 dan cassady shape the future wom 300a wom is 300 west one music trailer business corporate beds underscore tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) business corporate beds business corporate prestige business corporate reveal launch business corporate training information rock indie strong prestigious uplifting uplifting movement rhythmic train like inspiring uplifting. building from small beginnings to a rousing climax. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="21378" name="Clear Way" code="WOM 300A tk018" libraryid="6" albumid="470" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Paul Reeves (Gb 2)" comment="Réchauffe le coeur, inspire, motive." styleid="2" lengthseconds="142" time="2:22" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/WOM300A_trk018_CLEAR_WAY_Paul_Reeves_(Gb_2)_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="18" tracktotal="" search="Réchauffe le coeur, inspire, motive. BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, COMMUNICATION, ACTUALITÉS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, PASTORAL, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, DOCUMENTAIRE, FILMS, FAMILIAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, RURAL, CAMPAGNE, PASTORAL, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, TENDRE, PLEIN D'ESPOIR, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE ET SEMI-CLASSIQUE, ORCHESTRE SYMPHONIQUE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), AERIEN, ACTUALITES, ELEMENTS Vintage goes Pop. Eleganter und schwungvoller moderner Pop mit einem dicken Vintage-Anstrich. BUSINESS, CORPORATE, BETTEN, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, BETTEN, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, KOMMUNIKATION, NACHRICHTEN, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, LUXUS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, MOTIVIEREND, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, IDYLLISCH, HAUPTVERSION, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, DOKUMENTATION, FILME, FAMILIE, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, LÄNDLICH, LANDSCHAFT, IDYLLISCH, FRIEDLICH, VERTRÄUMT, ZÄRTLICH, HOFFNUNGSVOLL, ZÄRTLICH, WARM, BEFLÜGELND, MOTIVIEREND, BEFLÜGELND, BEFLÜGELND, GLAMOURÖS, LUXURIÖS, BEWEGUNG, SMOOTH, HIMMEL / LUFT, FLIEGEN, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), KLASSISCH &amp; SEMIKLASSISCH, SINFONIEORCHESTER, BEFLUGELND, GLAMOUROS, LANDLICH, LUXURIOS, VERTRAUMT, ZARTLICH wom 300a tk018 paul reeves (gb 2) clear way wom 300a wom is 300 west one music trailer business corporate beds business corporate beds business corporate communication news business corporate luxury business corporate motivational film score orchestral pastoral main business corporate documentary movies family nature wildlife the elements land rural heartwarming uplifting inspiring. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="21377" name="The Winner" code="WOM 300A tk017" libraryid="6" albumid="470" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Matthew James Robertson / Mike Reed / Tom Howe" comment="Le gagnant remporte la mise. Célébration indie et entrainante." styleid="2" lengthseconds="160" time="2:40" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/WOM300A_trk017_THE_WINNER_Matthew_James_Robertson_Mike_Reed_Tom_Howe_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="17" tracktotal="" search="Le gagnant remporte la mise. Célébration indie et entrainante. BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CLASSIQUE, FUSION CLASSIQUE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, PRESTIGE , BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FORMATION, INFORMATION, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, SPORT,, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), AERIEN, JOURNEE Kraftvoll, edel und funky. Eingängiger und cooler Song mit weiblichem Gesang und einer Extraportion Attitude. BUSINESS, CORPORATE, HEITER, OPTIMISTISCH, HAUPTVERSION, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), KLASSISCH, KLASSIK FUSION, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, HEITER, OPTIMISTISCH, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, MOTIVIEREND, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, PRESTIGE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, TRAINING, INFORMATION, KRÄFTIG, PRESTIGETRÄCHTIG, BEFLÜGELND, MOTIVIEREND, BEFLÜGELND, BEFLÜGELND, FRÖHLICH, GUT GELAUNT, BEWEGUNG, SMOOTH, HIMMEL / LUFT, FLIEGEN, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, REISEN, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, UNTERHALTUNG, DAYTIME - TV, SPORT, BEFLUGELND, FROHLICH, KRAFTIG, PRESTIGETRACHTIG wom 300a tk017 matthew james robertson mike reed tom howe the winner wom 300a wom is 300 west one music trailer business corporate bright optimistic main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) classical classical fusion business corporate bright optimistic business corporate motivational business corporate prestige business corporate training information strong prestigious uplifting the winner takes it all. an uplifting indie-infused celebration. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="21376" name="Finally Free" code="WOM 300A tk016" libraryid="6" albumid="470" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Christian Telford / Nigel William Graham" comment="Cordes enveloppants, émouvantes et sound design reveur." styleid="2" lengthseconds="103" time="1:43" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/WOM300A_trk016_FINALLY_FREE_Christian_Telford_Nigel_William_Graham_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="16" tracktotal="" search="Cordes enveloppants, émouvantes et sound design reveur. BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, BEDS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, ÉLÉMENTS SONORES, ATMOSPHÈRES, SOUND DESIGN, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, DOCUMENTAIRE, BIOGRAPHIQUE, HISTORIQUE, ARTS, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, AMBIANCES ET FONDS SONORES POUR PROJETS, SPORT, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, PAISIBLE, REVEUR, PAISIBLE, DÉTENDU, TENDRE, CHALEUREUX, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, FLOTTANT, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, AÉRIEN, EN VOL, MOUVEMENT, EN DOUCEUR, RALENTI, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), PÉRIODE, TEMPS MODERNES, FUTURISTE, ELEMENTS SONORES, PERIODE, ATMOSPHERES, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), DETENDU, AERIEN, ELEMENTS Selbstbewusster und stampfender Hip Hop mit Gesang im Girl-Band-Stil. BUSINESS, CORPORATE, BETTEN, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, BETTEN, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, LUXUS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, WISSENSCHAFT, TECHNOLOGIE, SOUNDELEMENTE, ATMOSPHÄREN, SOUNDDESIGN, HAUPTVERSION, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, DOKUMENTATION, BIOGRAFISCH, HISTORISCH, KÜNSTE, WISSENSCHAFT, TECHNOLOGIE, INDUSTRIE, BETTEN FÜR DESIGN, SPORT, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, REISEN, FRIEDLICH, VERTRÄUMT, FRIEDLICH, ENTSPANNT, ZÄRTLICH, WARM, GLAMOURÖS, LUXURIÖS, BEWEGUNG, SMOOTH, HIMMEL / LUFT, DAHINTREIBEN, BEWEGUNG, SMOOTH, HIMMEL / LUFT, FLIEGEN, BEWEGUNG, SMOOTH, ZEITLUPE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), ZEITALTER, MODERNE ZEIT, FUTURISTISCH, ATMOSPHAREN, BETTEN FUR DESIGN, GLAMOUROS, KUNSTE, LUXURIOS, VERTRAUMT, ZARTLICH wom 300a tk016 christian telford nigel william graham finally free wom 300a wom is 300 west one music trailer business corporate beds business corporate beds business corporate luxury business corporate science technology sound elements atmospheres sound design main business corporate documentary biographical historical the arts science technology industry design beds sports tv lush evocative strings dream-like sound design. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="21375" name="Against the Odds" code="WOM 300A tk015" libraryid="6" albumid="470" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jay Price" comment="Des lames de piano et de guitare électrique se brisent en une indie motivante et dynamique." styleid="2" lengthseconds="174" time="2:54" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/WOM300A_trk015_AGAINST_THE_ODDS_Jay_Price_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="15" tracktotal="" search="Des lames de piano et de guitare électrique se brisent en une indie motivante et dynamique. BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, PRESTIGE , BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SPORT, TV, RADIO, SPORT, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EVOLUTIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), REVELER, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Umwerfender Folk-Rock von der Westküste, inklusive Banjo, Pedal Steel und süßem weiblichem Gesang. BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTHÜLLUNG, LAUNCH, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, MOTIVIEREND, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, PRESTIGE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTHÜLLUNG, LAUNCH, HAUPTVERSION, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, SPORT, TV, RADIO, SPORT, KRÄFTIG, PRESTIGETRÄCHTIG, BEFLÜGELND, MOTIVIEREND, AUFBAUEND, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, TREIBEND, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), BEFLUGELND, ENTHULLUNG, KRAFTIG, PRESTIGETRACHTIG wom 300a tk015 jay price against the odds wom 300a wom is 300 west one music trailer business corporate reveal launch business corporate motivational business corporate prestige business corporate reveal launch main business corporate sports tv radio sports strong prestigious uplifting motivational building movement rhythmic driving tempo swells of piano electric guitar break to motivating driving indie. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="21374" name="The Afterlife" code="WOM 300A tk014" libraryid="6" albumid="470" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Timothy Stephen Pierce / Brett Carr Boyett" comment="Une introduction optimiste commence un développement vers l'épique à 2:18. Exaltant, cinématique." styleid="2" lengthseconds="241" time="4:01" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/WOM300A_trk014_THE_AFTERLIFE_Timothy_Stephen_Pierce_Brett_Carr_Boyett_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="14" tracktotal="" search="Une introduction optimiste commence un développement vers l'épique à 2:18. Exaltant, cinématique. ENFANTS, ENFANTS, ROCK, ROCK ALTERNATIF, ROCK, INDIE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, FORT, ÉPIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, OPTIMISTE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), EPIQUE Crossover von Hip Hop und R&amp;B mit 80er-Feeling. Mit männlichem Rap-Gesang. KINDER, KINDER, ROCK, ALTERNATIVE ROCK, ROCK, INDIE, HAUPTVERSION, FILME, EPISCH, TV, RADIO, KINDER, JUGENDPROGRAMM, KRÄFTIG, EPISCH, BEFLÜGELND, OPTIMISTISCH, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, TREIBEND, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MITTLERES TEMPO (ANDANTE), BEFLUGELND, KRAFTIG wom 300a tk014 timothy stephen pierce brett carr boyett the afterlife wom 300a wom is 300 west one music trailer children children rock alternative rock rock indie main movies epic tv radio children youth tv strong epic uplifting optimistic movement rhythmic driving tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) optimistic introduction starts epic build at 2:18. inspiring cinematic. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="21373" name="Silver and Gold" code="WOM 300A tk013" libraryid="6" albumid="470" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Matthew James Robertson / Mike Reed / Tom Howe" comment="De sublimes chorus évocateurs se construisent progressivement." styleid="2" lengthseconds="175" time="2:55" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/WOM300A_trk013_SILVER_AND_GOLD_Matthew_James_Robertson_Mike_Reed_Tom_Howe_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="13" tracktotal="" search="De sublimes chorus évocateurs se construisent progressivement. ROCK, INDIE, ROCK, INDIE, PRINCIPAL, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, SPORT, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, BEAU, EVOLUTIF, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ELEMENTS, JOURNEE, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Warmer, optimistischer und sonniger Akustik-Pop-Rock. Mit männlichem Gesang. ROCK, INDIE, ROCK, INDIE, HAUPTVERSION, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, SONNE, TROPISCH, KÜSTENLANDSCHAFT, SPORT, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, REISEN, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, UNTERHALTUNG, DAYTIME - TV, KRÄFTIG, PRESTIGETRÄCHTIG, SCHÖN, AUFBAUEND, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), KRAFTIG, KUSTENLANDSCHAFT, PRESTIGETRACHTIG, SCHON wom 300a tk013 matthew james robertson mike reed tom howe silver and gold wom 300a wom is 300 west one music trailer rock indie rock indie main nature wildlife the elements land sun tropical seaside sports tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio sports tv radio talkshow entertainment daytime strong prestigious beautiful building tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) gradually building to beautiful atmospheric choruses. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="21372" name="Sunshine Skyway" code="WOM 300A tk012" libraryid="6" albumid="470" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Tyler Van Den Berg" comment="Indie de stade. Euphorique." styleid="2" lengthseconds="119" time="1:59" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/WOM300A_trk012_SUNSHINE_SKYWAY_Tyler_Van_Den_Berg_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="12" tracktotal="" search="Indie de stade. Euphorique. ROCK, INDIE, ROCK, INDIE, PRINCIPAL, SPORT, SPORTS EXTREMES, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), CORDES, GUITARE, ÉLECTRIQUE, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), ELECTRIQUE Rauer Crossover von Hip Hop und R&amp;B. Inklusive omnipräsentem Bass und keckem weiblichem Gesang. ROCK, INDIE, ROCK, INDIE, HAUPTVERSION, SPORT, EXTREMSPORT, TV, RADIO, KINDER, JUGENDPROGRAMM, TV, RADIO, SPORT, BEFLÜGELND, EUPHORISCH, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, TREIBEND, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, ROBUST, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), SAITENINSTRUMENTE, GITARRE - ELEKTRISCH, BEFLUGELND wom 300a tk012 tyler van den berg sunshine skyway wom 300a wom is 300 west one music trailer rock indie rock indie main sports extreme sports tv radio children youth tv tv radio sports uplifting euphoric movement rhythmic driving movement rhythmic rugged tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) strings guitar electric euphoric stadium indie. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="21371" name="Home Free" code="WOM 300A tk011" libraryid="6" albumid="470" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jay Price" comment="Motifs inspirants de piano sur une indie pop en progression." styleid="2" lengthseconds="166" time="2:46" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/WOM300A_trk011_HOME_FREE_Jay_Price_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="11" tracktotal="" search="Motifs inspirants de piano sur une indie pop en progression. BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, LUXE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, ROCK, INDIE, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, SPORT, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EVOLUTIF, GLAMOUR, LUXUEUX, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO), JOURNEE, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Mächtige Synthie-Riffs und ein epischer Chorus wechseln sich mit einer knackigen und funky Strophe ab. Mit weiblichem Gesang. BUSINESS, CORPORATE, HEITER, OPTIMISTISCH, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, HEITER, OPTIMISTISCH, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, LUXUS, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, MOTIVIEREND, ROCK, INDIE, HAUPTVERSION, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, SPORT, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, REISEN, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, UNTERHALTUNG, DAYTIME - TV, FRÖHLICH, GUT GELAUNT, BEFLÜGELND, MOTIVIEREND, BEFLÜGELND, BEFLÜGELND, AUFBAUEND, GLAMOURÖS, LUXURIÖS, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MITTELSCHNELL (MODERATO), BEFLUGELND, FROHLICH, GLAMOUROS, LUXURIOS wom 300a tk011 jay price home free wom 300a wom is 300 west one music trailer business corporate bright optimistic business corporate bright optimistic business corporate luxury business corporate motivational rock indie main business corporate sports tv radio leisure lifestyle travel tv radio sports tv radio talkshow entertainment daytime inspiring piano patterns over building indie pop. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="21370" name="Lassoed in Blue" code="WOM 300A tk010" libraryid="6" albumid="470" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Ian Mccutcheon" comment="Pop acoustique enjouée qui met de bonne humeur." styleid="2" lengthseconds="117" time="1:57" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/WOM300A_trk010_LASSOED_IN_BLUE_Ian_Mccutcheon_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="10" tracktotal="" search="Pop acoustique enjouée qui met de bonne humeur. POP, POP POUR ENFANTS, ENFANTS, POP, POP POUR ENFANTS, ROCK, INDIE, PRINCIPAL, SPORT, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, ENTRAINANT, ACOUSTIQUE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE) Eingängige Gute-Laune-Nummer. POP, KINDERPOP, KINDER, POP, KINDERPOP, ROCK, INDIE, HAUPTVERSION, SPORT, TV, RADIO, KINDER, JUGENDPROGRAMM, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, FRÖHLICH, GUT GELAUNT, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, AKUSTISCH, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MITTLERES TEMPO (ANDANTE), FROHLICH wom 300a tk010 ian mccutcheon lassoed in blue wom 300a wom is 300 west one music trailer pop kiddie pop children pop kiddie pop rock indie main sports tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle tv radio sports happy feel good happy happy happy upbeat acoustic tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) feelgood upbeat acoustic pop. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="21369" name="Wanderlust" code="WOM 300A tk009" libraryid="6" albumid="470" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Mark Peter Revell" comment="Splendide fusion eletro-indie." styleid="2" lengthseconds="134" time="2:14" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/WOM300A_trk009_WANDERLUST_Mark_Peter_Revell_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="9" tracktotal="" search="Splendide fusion eletro-indie. ROCK, INDIE, ROCK, INDIE, PRINCIPAL, SPORT, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO) Herrliche Fusionnummer aus Electro und Indie. ROCK, INDIE, ROCK, INDIE, HAUPTVERSION, SPORT, TV, RADIO, KINDER, JUGENDPROGRAMM, TV, RADIO, SPORT, BEFLÜGELND, BEFLÜGELND, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, TREIBEND, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, ROBUST, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), BEFLUGELND wom 300a tk009 mark peter revell wanderlust wom 300a wom is 300 west one music trailer rock indie rock indie main sports tv radio children youth tv tv radio sports uplifting uplifting movement rhythmic driving movement rhythmic rugged tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) glorious electro-indie fusion. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="21368" name="Midnight Drive" code="WOM 300A tk008" libraryid="6" albumid="470" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Caspar John Valentine Kedros / Scott Doran" comment="Entrainant et déterminé. Batterie electro pechue, guitares tendues et nerveuses." styleid="2" lengthseconds="170" time="2:50" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/WOM300A_trk008_MIDNIGHT_DRIVE_Caspar_John_Valentine_Kedros_Scott_Doran_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="8" tracktotal="" search="Entrainant et déterminé. Batterie electro pechue, guitares tendues et nerveuses. BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ROCK, INDIE, UNDERSCORE, FILMS, DRAME HUMAIN, FILMS, DRAME URBAIN, SPORT, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TV, RADIO, DRAME TV, POLICE, JURIDIQUE, DRAME JUDICIAIRE, TROUBLANT, TENDU, NERVEUX, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MODÉRÉ (MODERATO), 108 - 120 MODERE (MODERATO) Antreibender und entschlossener Song mit knackigen Electro-Drums und angespannten Gitarren-Lines. FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ROCK, INDIE, UNDERSCORE, FILME, MENSCHLICHE DRAMEN, FILME, URBAN DRAMA, SPORT, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TV, RADIO, TV-DRAMA, POLIZEI, RECHTLICH, JUSTIZDRAMA, VERSTÖREND, ANGESPANNT, EDGY, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, TREIBEND, TEMPO, 108 - 120 MITTELSCHNELL (MODERATO), VERSTOREND wom 300a tk008 caspar john valentine kedros scott doran midnight drive wom 300a wom is 300 west one music trailer film score orchestral trailer film score orchestral trailer rock indie underscore movies human drama movies urban drama sports tv radio sports tv radio tv drama police legal courtroom drama disturbing tense edgy movement rhythmic driving tempo driving purposeful. punchy electro drums tense edgy guitars. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="21367" name="The Breakthrough" code="WOM 300A tk007" libraryid="6" albumid="470" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Tyler Van Den Berg" comment="Guitare métalliques, chorus épiques, réjouissants." styleid="2" lengthseconds="124" time="2:04" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/WOM300A_trk007_THE_BREAKTHROUGH_Tyler_Van_Den_Berg_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="7" tracktotal="" search="Guitare métalliques, chorus épiques, réjouissants. BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, ROCK, INDIE, PRINCIPAL, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, FILMS, ÉPIQUE, SPORT, TV, RADIO, SPORT, FORT, ÉPIQUE, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EVOLUTIF, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), EPIQUE, REVELER, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Die in den Strophen noch zurückhaltenden Gitarren wachsen im lebensbejahenden Chorus über sich hinaus. BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTHÜLLUNG, LAUNCH, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, MOTIVIEREND, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTHÜLLUNG, LAUNCH, ROCK, INDIE, HAUPTVERSION, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, FILME, EPISCH, SPORT, TV, RADIO, SPORT, KRÄFTIG, EPISCH, KRÄFTIG, PRESTIGETRÄCHTIG, BEFLÜGELND, MOTIVIEREND, AUFBAUEND, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, TREIBEND, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, ROBUST, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), BEFLUGELND, ENTHULLUNG, KRAFTIG, PRESTIGETRACHTIG wom 300a tk007 tyler van den berg the breakthrough wom 300a wom is 300 west one music trailer business corporate reveal launch business corporate motivational business corporate reveal launch rock indie main business corporate movies epic sports tv radio sports strong epic strong prestigious uplifting motivational building movement rhythmic driving movement jangling guitars epic life affirming choruses. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="21366" name="Future Perfect" code="WOM 300A tk006" libraryid="6" albumid="470" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Matthew James Robertson / Mike Reed / Tom Howe" comment="Tourbillons de piano et celeste sur un fond de guitares et batterie planantes." styleid="2" lengthseconds="141" time="2:21" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/WOM300A_trk006_FUTURE_PERFECT_Matthew_James_Robertson_Mike_Reed_Tom_Howe_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="6" tracktotal="" search="Tourbillons de piano et celeste sur un fond de guitares et batterie planantes. BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, MOTIVANT, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, ROCK, INDIE, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, MOTIVANT, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, JAILLIR, EVOLUTIF, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, SPORT, CLAVIER, CELESTE,, REVELER, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Wirbelndes Piano und Celesta werden von einer hellen, schneidenden Gitarre und Drums begleitet. BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTHÜLLUNG, LAUNCH, HAUPTVERSION, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MITTLERES TEMPO (ANDANTE), BUSINESS, CORPORATE, MOTIVIEREND, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTHÜLLUNG, LAUNCH, ROCK, INDIE, KRÄFTIG, PRESTIGETRÄCHTIG, BEFLÜGELND, MOTIVIEREND, BEFLÜGELND, EMPORSTEIGEND, AUFBAUEND, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, SPORT, KEYBOARD, CELESTA, BEFLUGELND, ENTHULLUNG, KRAFTIG, PRESTIGETRACHTIG wom 300a tk006 matthew james robertson mike reed tom howe future perfect wom 300a wom is 300 west one music trailer business corporate reveal launch main tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) business corporate motivational business corporate reveal launch rock indie strong prestigious uplifting motivational uplifting soaring building business corporate tv radio sports sports keyboard swirls of piano and celeste over soaring guitars and drums. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="21365" name="Cheap Thrills" code="WOM 300A tk005" libraryid="6" albumid="470" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Jack Saturday / Jeff Coates / Vezio Bacci" comment="Mur du son chaotique avec une mélodie sifflée accrocheuse à souhait." styleid="2" lengthseconds="139" time="2:19" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/WOM300A_trk005_CHEAP_THRILLS_Jack_Saturday_Jeff_Coates_Vezio_Bacci_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="5" tracktotal="" search="Mur du son chaotique avec une mélodie sifflée accrocheuse à souhait. POP, POP POUR ENFANTS, ENFANTS, POP, POP POUR ENFANTS, ROCK, GARAGE ROCK, PRINCIPAL, SPORT, SPORTS EXTREMES, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), VOCAL, SIFFLEMENT, EFFETS SONORES, HUMAIN, SIFFLEMENT, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), JOURNEE Eine chaotische Wall of Sound. POP, KINDERPOP, KINDER, POP, KINDERPOP, ROCK, GARAGE ROCK, HAUPTVERSION, SPORT, EXTREMSPORT, TV, RADIO, KINDER, JUGENDPROGRAMM, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, UNTERHALTUNG, DAYTIME - TV, BEFLÜGELND, EUPHORISCH, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), VOCALS, PFEIFEN, SOUNDEFFEKTE, MENSCHLICH, MENSCHLICHES PFEIFEN, BEFLUGELND wom 300a tk005 jack saturday jeff coates vezio bacci cheap thrills wom 300a wom is 300 west one music trailer pop kiddie pop children pop kiddie pop rock garage rock main sports extreme sports tv radio children youth tv tv radio sports tv radio talkshow entertainment daytime uplifting euphoric tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) vocals whistling sound effects human human whistle shambolic wall of sound featuring catchy whistling melody. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="21364" name="Young Guns" code="WOM 300A tk004" libraryid="6" albumid="470" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Wesley Ayers" comment="Indie euphorique et réjouissante." styleid="2" lengthseconds="173" time="2:53" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/WOM300A_trk004_YOUNG_GUNS_David_Wesley_Ayers_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="4" tracktotal="" search="Indie euphorique et réjouissante. POP, POP POUR ENFANTS, ENFANTS, POP, POP POUR ENFANTS, POP, SYNTH POP, ROCK, INDIE, PRINCIPAL, SPORT, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EUPHORIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ROBUSTE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), JOURNEE Euphorischer und lebensbejahender Indie. POP, KINDERPOP, KINDER, POP, KINDERPOP, POP, SYNTHIE POP, ROCK, INDIE, HAUPTVERSION, SPORT, TV, RADIO, KINDER, JUGENDPROGRAMM, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, FASHION, STIL, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, UNTERHALTUNG, DAYTIME - TV, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, BEFLÜGELND, EUPHORISCH, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, TREIBEND, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, ROBUST, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MITTLERES TEMPO (ANDANTE), BEFLUGELND, FROHLICH wom 300a tk004 david wesley ayers young guns wom 300a wom is 300 west one music trailer pop kiddie pop children pop kiddie pop pop synth pop rock indie main sports tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio sports tv radio talkshow entertainment daytime happy happy uplifting euphoric movement rhythmic driving euphoric life-affirming indie. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="21363" name="Big Skies" code="WOM 300A tk003" libraryid="6" albumid="470" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Timothy Stephen Pierce / Brett Carr Boyett" comment="Musique pour Dame Nature. Paysages sonores enveloppants et chorus teintés d'Americana." styleid="2" lengthseconds="215" time="3:35" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/WOM300A_trk003_BIG_SKIES_Timothy_Stephen_Pierce_Brett_Carr_Boyett_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="3" tracktotal="" search="Musique pour Dame Nature. Paysages sonores enveloppants et chorus teintés d'Americana. ENFANTS, ENFANTS, BANDE ORIGINALE, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ROCK, ROCK ALTERNATIF, ROCK, INDIE, PRINCIPAL, FILMS, ROAD MOVIE, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, VOYAGE, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), AMÉRIQUE DU NORD, ÉTATS-UNIS, AMERIQUE DU NORD, ETATS-UNIS Musik für eine Reise durch die Wildnis. Eine ausladende Soundkulisse mit einem kräftigen, von Americana beeinflussten Chorus. KINDER, KINDER, FILMMUSIK, ORCHESTRAL, TRAILER, ROCK, ALTERNATIVE ROCK, ROCK, INDIE, HAUPTVERSION, FILME, ROAD MOVIE, TV, RADIO, KINDER, JUGENDPROGRAMM, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, REISEN, FRÖHLICH, GUT GELAUNT, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MITTLERES TEMPO (ANDANTE), NORDAMERIKA, USA, FROHLICH wom 300a tk003 timothy stephen pierce brett carr boyett big skies wom 300a wom is 300 west one music trailer children children film score orchestral trailer rock alternative rock rock indie main movies road movie tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle travel happy feel good tempo 76 - 108 medium (andante) north america usa music for the wilderness. lush soundscapes big americana-tinged choruses. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="21362" name="Making Waves" code="WOM 300A tk002" libraryid="6" albumid="470" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="Matthew James Robertson / Mike Reed / Tom Howe" comment="Batterie martelée et piano qui met de bonne humeur mènent à un final indie inoubliable." styleid="2" lengthseconds="168" time="2:48" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/WOM300A_trk002_MAKING_WAVES_Matthew_James_Robertson_Mike_Reed_Tom_Howe_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="2" tracktotal="" search="Batterie martelée et piano qui met de bonne humeur mènent à un final indie inoubliable. BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, PRINCIPAL, TEMPO, 120 - 168 ALLÈGRE (ALLEGRO), BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, VIF, OPTIMISTE, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, RÉVÉLER, LANCEMENT, ROCK, INDIE, FORT, PRESTIGIEUX, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EMBLÉMATIQUE, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, EXALTANT, ASPIRATIONNEL, HEUREUX, DE BONNE HUMEUR, MOUVEMENT, RYTHMIQUE, ENERGIQUE, EVOLUTIF, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTREPRISE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, SPORT,, 120 - 168 ALLEGRE (ALLEGRO), EMBLEMATIQUE, REVELER, JOURNEE, MONTEE, MONTÉE, EVOLUTION Stampfende und motivierende Drums bewegen sich gemeinsam mit Piano dem hymnischen Finale entgegen. BUSINESS, CORPORATE, HEITER, OPTIMISTISCH, HAUPTVERSION, TEMPO, 120 - 168 SCHNELL (ALLEGRO), BUSINESS, CORPORATE, HEITER, OPTIMISTISCH, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, ENTHÜLLUNG, LAUNCH, ROCK, INDIE, KRÄFTIG, PRESTIGETRÄCHTIG, BEFLÜGELND, HYMNISCH, BEFLÜGELND, BEFLÜGELND, FRÖHLICH, GUT GELAUNT, BEWEGUNG, RHYTHMISCH, TREIBEND, AUFBAUEND, BUSINESS, CORPORATE, TV, RADIO, SPORT, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, UNTERHALTUNG, DAYTIME - TV, SPORT, BEFLUGELND, ENTHULLUNG, FROHLICH, KRAFTIG, PRESTIGETRACHTIG wom 300a tk002 matthew james robertson mike reed tom howe making waves wom 300a wom is 300 west one music trailer business corporate bright optimistic main tempo 120 - 168 fast (allegro) business corporate bright optimistic business corporate reveal launch rock indie strong prestigious uplifting anthemic uplifting uplifting happy feel good movement rhythmic driving building business pounding uplifting drums piano building to anthemic finale. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
    <item id="21361" name="Never too Late" code="WOM 300A tk001" libraryid="6" albumid="470" albumartpath="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/albumart_hd.jpg" composer="David Wesley Ayers" comment="Indie épique pour stade, avec des chorus à donner le frisson." styleid="2" lengthseconds="184" time="3:04" samplefile="Music/West One Music/WOM_300A_WOM_is_300/WOM300A_trk001_NEVER_TOO_LATE_David_Wesley_Ayers_West_One_Music_Limited.mp3" track="1" tracktotal="" search="Indie épique pour stade, avec des chorus à donner le frisson. POP, POP POUR ENFANTS, ENFANTS, POP, POP POUR ENFANTS, POP, SYNTH POP, ROCK, INDIE, PRINCIPAL, SITUATIONS, ENVIRONNEMENTS, DÉFILÉ DE MODE, NATURE, NATURE, FAUNE ET FLORE, ÉLÉMENTS, TERRE, SOLEIL, TROPICAL, BORD DE MER, TV, RADIO, ENFANTS, PROGRAMMES JEUNESSE, TV, RADIO, LOISIR, LIFESTYLE, MODE, STYLE, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, DIVERTISSEMENT, JOURNÉE, HEUREUX, HEUREUX, FORT, ÉPIQUE, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MOYEN (ANDANTE), EPIQUE, DEFILE DE MODE, DEFILE, ELEMENTS, JOURNEE Mitreißender Stadion-Indie mit Ohrwurm-Qualitäten. POP, KINDERPOP, KINDER, POP, KINDERPOP, POP, SYNTHIE POP, ROCK, INDIE, HAUPTVERSION, AKTIVITÄTEN, SETTINGS, MODENSCHAU, NATUR, WILDNIS, DIE ELEMENTE, LAND, SONNE, TROPISCH, KÜSTENLANDSCHAFT, TV, RADIO, KINDER, JUGENDPROGRAMM, TV, RADIO, FREIZEIT, LIFESTYLE, FASHION, STIL, TV, RADIO, TALKSHOW, UNTERHALTUNG, DAYTIME - TV, FRÖHLICH, FRÖHLICH, KRÄFTIG, EPISCH, TEMPO, 76 - 108 MITTLERES TEMPO (ANDANTE), AKTIVITATEN, FROHLICH, KRAFTIG, KUSTENLANDSCHAFT wom 300a tk001 david wesley ayers never too late wom 300a wom is 300 west one music trailer pop kiddie pop children pop kiddie pop pop synth pop rock indie main activities settings fashion show nature wildlife the elements land sun tropical seaside tv radio children youth tv tv radio leisure lifestyle fashion style tv radio talkshow entertainment daytime epic stadium indie with spine-tingling choruses. main" waveformpath="" version="Main" publisher="West One Music Limited" cae="00428434750" lc="12846"/>
  </items>
</librarycollection>
